<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Simulation on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulation/</link><description>Recent content in Simulation on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Undusted: Letters from the Past</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undusted-letters-from-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undusted-letters-from-the-past/</guid><description>Game Description Undusted Letters from the Past is a touching story about a girl named Jane who, after moving into her late grandmother&amp;rsquo;s house, discovers an abandoned workshop full of dusty and broken objects. Every item, be it an old camera or a music box, requires careful restoration. The process of dusting and repairing the mechanisms reveals hidden letters and memories, gradually revealing a secret love story from her family&amp;rsquo;s past.</description></item><item><title>Pocket Boss</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-boss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-boss/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket Boss puts the player in the role of a remote employee whose main task is to manipulate business schedules. The central goal is to achieve a promotion in one week by adjusting data to meet the demands of superiors. These activities include inflating performance metrics, increasing shareholder value, and hiding financial losses in reports. Each task requires you to find a convincing solution to an information puzzle while taking into account the whims of your boss.</description></item><item><title>The Legacy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-legacy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-legacy/</guid><description>Game Description The Legacy is a co-op survival horror game set in a dark tale of a family curse in a deserted town. Events unfold years after in 1990, Grandfather Molfar, a local sorcerer, refused to sacrifice one of his descendants to the dark forces of the forest. To save his grandchildren, he sent them from their hometown of Svetlograd to Kyiv, but this act doomed the entire area to death and desolation.</description></item><item><title>Mars First Logistics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-first-logistics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-first-logistics/</guid><description>Game Description Mars First Logistics physics and transportation simulator with an open world to explore. The game was invented so that the player could feel like a delivery driver of various cargo items with a capricious shape. To deliver the cargo that the game provides, you need to take a vehicle. You can make a car or a vehicle on wheels yourself from various mechanisms offered by the game. To promote and develop your mechanical creation, you need to receive virtual currency called credits.</description></item><item><title>eXoSpace Combat Engineer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exospace-combat-engineer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exospace-combat-engineer/</guid><description>Game Description eXoSpace Combat Engineer is a journey into the depths of a procedurally generated galaxy, where survival depends solely on engineering savvy and piloting skill. In the role of a bounty hunter, you will have to chart a course through unexplored sectors of space, each hyperjump in which promises unpredictable events. Fate can lead you to a research station in distress, throw you into the thick of a battle with pirates, or force you to face a moral choice - to provide assistance or engage in robbery.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Farming ~ Minoriko's Homestead Harvest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-farming-minorikos-homestead-harvest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-farming-minorikos-homestead-harvest/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Farming ~ Minoriko&amp;rsquo;s Homestead Harvest challenges the harvest goddess Minoriko Aki to increase the number of her followers. In the world of Gensokyo, there is high competition among deities, so the heroine strives to provide food for the growing Human Settlement. Her main goal is to accumulate faith, which serves as a measure of popularity, by growing various crops, including a special sweet potato. All of these activities are carried out in conjunction with the Moriya Shrine to take advantage of the changes in the region.</description></item><item><title>Waterpark Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/waterpark-simulator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/waterpark-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Waterpark Simulator invites the player to build unique attractions and manage the water complex from the first person. At first, all duties are performed manually: from selling tickets and preparing food to rescuing drowning visitors. Operational chaos also affects the maintenance of infrastructure, including repairing broken slides, cleaning the area and removing debris from swimming pools.
Every aspect of the establishment&amp;rsquo;s layout and design is subject to direct instructions.</description></item><item><title>Ways of Alchemy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</guid><description>Game Description In Ways of Alchemy, the player begins his journey in a secluded hut, where he uses card mechanics to create powerful elixirs from many ingredients. The final goal is to build an entire alchemical empire on the basis of a modest shack, using intelligence and tactical thinking. To do this, you will have to look for ancient recipes and recruit adventurers, constantly avoiding the close attention of the Inquisition.</description></item><item><title>Grand Empire 2: Portals Apart</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-emprise-2-portals-apart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-emprise-2-portals-apart/</guid><description>Game Description Grand Emprise 2: Portals Apart is a survival and crafting experience built around traversing magical portals. As a sequel to Grand Emprise: Time Travel, this project develops the concept of a directed adventure. The journey takes the player through a series of fantasy worlds, where each portal opens up access to new resources. Development follows a linear technology path, forming a structured single-player campaign instead of an open-world sandbox where the gamer determines his own goals.</description></item><item><title>Who's at the door?</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whos-at-the-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whos-at-the-door/</guid><description>Game Description Who&amp;rsquo;s at the door? puts the player in the shoes of a man locked in a house and suffering from psychosis with amnesia. The protagonist, being a psychiatric patient, has no memories of the beginning of his condition, but experiences headaches and hallucinations. The main task is to survive for 8 days, for which you need to receive medicine from visitors. This requires carefully examining your surroundings, because the boundary between perception and reality has begun to disappear.</description></item><item><title>Crime Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Crime Simulator allows you to quit your nine-to-five job and dive into a virtual life of crime. In this open-world sandbox, you&amp;rsquo;ll dive headfirst into the dirty underbelly of illegal activities. From petty thefts to sophisticated heists, Crime Simulator offers a buffet of criminal adventures. Start your journey from the very bottom of the food chain, completing small assignments to climb the criminal ladder.
As your reputation grows, new opportunities open up.</description></item><item><title>JDM: Japanese Drift Master</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</guid><description>Game Description JDM: Japanese Drift Master is a colorful car simulator that will take you into the exciting world of drifting on the streets of Japan. A huge open world with varied landscapes, from serene lakes to bustling city areas, offers endless opportunities for exploration, racing and, of course, the art of drifting itself. What sets the game apart is the freedom it gives players to customize their cars, allowing them to truly make it their own.</description></item><item><title>gogh: Focus with Your Avatar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gogh-focus-with-your-avatar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gogh-focus-with-your-avatar/</guid><description>Game Description Gogh: Focus with Your Avatar combines focus tools and simulation gameplay mechanics, allowing you to create a character and design a location. Gamers interact with a virtual hero and a companion creature in a variable room. This project includes time management tools in addition to customization capabilities. The main task is to help with work sessions through a combination of these elements of the simulation game.
In gogh: Focus with Your Avatar, a person arranges his own room by arranging furniture, choosing decor and choosing a palette.</description></item><item><title>Device Doctor Simulator 2024</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/device-doctor-simulator-2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/device-doctor-simulator-2024/</guid><description>Game Description Device Doctor Simulator 2024 puts the gamer in the role of a repair expert. The meaning of the title is to diagnose and repair various digital gadgets. As a user, you find yourself in a workshop filled with broken devices that require attention. In the gameplay you will have to understand how the devices function and apply solutions to restore their functionality.
Each scenario represents a different task, ranging from simple tasks such as replacing a screen to more complex problems involving hardware or software failures.</description></item><item><title>Do No Harm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/do-no-harm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/do-no-harm/</guid><description>Game Description Do No Harm is a doctor simulator that is an unusual mixture of medical practice and Lovecraftian horror. In a small, isolated village, gamers take on the role of a doctor who must diagnose and treat patients using an unusual Book of Medicine. In the title you have to navigate not only the medical mysteries of that time, but also the terrible forces influencing reality. Here you have to make difficult decisions that will not only affect the lives of your patients, but will also determine the outcome of the plot.</description></item><item><title>Midori no Kaori</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</guid><description>Game Description Midori no Kaori is an adventure game based on the art of peaceful store management. In this relaxed environment, gamers will create and manage their own establishment, drawing on elements of Japanese culture to shape their vision. The title doesn&amp;rsquo;t focus on fast-paced action or intense competition, but rather encourages players to create a space that reflects their personal taste. There are no strict goals or deadlines, making it a refreshing alternative to many other games that prioritize speed or performance.</description></item><item><title>Lost But Found</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-but-found/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-but-found/</guid><description>Game Description InLost But Found, gamers will take on the role of an airport employee dealing with lost and found items. The idea is simple: sort, organize and return lost items to their rightful owners. The setting is an airport, where the task of returning passengers to their belongings takes place on a cluttered table with an overhead view. The title revolves around decisions, management and moral issues. This mixture of job simulator and hidden object mechanics defines the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Scourge of the village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scourge-of-the-village/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scourge-of-the-village/</guid><description>Game Description Scourge of the Village takes gamers on an eerie journey through a mountain village shrouded in mystery and supernatural elements. Set against the backdrop of Chinese folk horror, the plot revolves around an investigation that goes wrong. Chen Xi, a trainee reporter, begins investigating a wastewater discharge incident at a factory, but soon finds himself in a much more alarming situation. As she navigates the twisted paths of reality and dreams, the boundaries between the two worlds blur, and what was once an investigation into environmental crimes turns into a struggle to understand the tragic history of the village.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microsoft-flight-simulator-2024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microsoft-flight-simulator-2024/</guid><description>Game Description Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024 . Fasten your seatbelts and get ready to take the controls of a meticulously detailed fleet of aircraft, from light jets to colossal wide-body jets. Remember your childhood dream - to fly into the clouds? Here it will become reality. Explore a stunningly realistic world, recreated down to the smallest detail. Forget jet lag - this is a journey where time melts away as you lose yourself in the endless expanses of the virtual sky.</description></item><item><title>Node Farm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/node-farm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/node-farm/</guid><description>Game Description Node Farm is an adventure game, the essence of which is to create an automated farm using nodes. The concept is simple: connect nodes to grow crops, harvest them and sell them for profit. Gamers can then reinvest this money to expand their farms and discover new islands. Over time, the farm becomes more efficient as users develop strategies to automate every step of the farming process. This constant development is at the heart of the game, offering a satisfying combination of resource management and strategic planning.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Command is a strategy with elements of a bagel and a card game. You need to collect resources, form a unique deck of cards and fight against robots. When gathering an army, you need to study the enemy&amp;rsquo;s tactics in order to deal a crushing blow to him. While exploring locations, you need to obtain resources to build buildings and hire units. There are factories, auxiliary buildings, turrets and special weapons of mass destruction.</description></item><item><title>Finnish Cottage Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finnish-cottage-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finnish-cottage-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Finnish Cottage Simulator is an adventure game that invites gamers into the tranquil world of Finnish summer traditions. From the first minutes you find yourself in a quiet corner of the Finnish countryside, where the pace of life is leisurely and nature takes center stage. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s grilling sausages by the lake, going to the sauna with friends or just walking through the woods, the game gives you an insight into what Finnish country life is like at its truest.</description></item><item><title>My Hotel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</guid><description>Game Description Users inMy Hotel have to try their hand at being a novice businessman who is going to set up a small hotel and gradually develop it. You will have to buy a dirty and in terrible condition of a house in which you can arrange rooms for living and set up a reception. It is necessary to wash all the floors, clean the furniture from dust and do everything possible to make an attractive and prestigious appearance for the building.</description></item><item><title>Space Trash Scavenger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</guid><description>Game Description Space Trash Scavenger takes place in a future where humanity has reached for the stars and survival means using what others have left behind. Here, gamers take on the role of scavengers operating in a galaxy littered with the rubble of an ancient conflict. The journey begins with a space drill - a multi-purpose node floating among the remains of abandoned ships, forgotten outposts and asteroid fields. This is not just a shelter, but a factory, equipped with critical systems for agriculture, defense and waste processing - all necessary to turn interstellar waste into something valuable.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Shave and Stuff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</guid><description>Game Description InShave and Stuff, gamers find themselves in a lively and practical simulator, where two roles come to the fore - a hairdresser and a tattoo artist. The title combines hairdressing and paint work, which promotes creativity and experimentation. Whether performing precision cutting tasks or plunging into the complex world of body art, users are immersed in a world of tools, techniques and client preferences. A constant flow of tasks and light humor provide the basis for an original approach to customization and self-expression.</description></item><item><title>XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</guid><description>Game Description XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION transports gamers to a high-octane world where the classic game of pinball meets hostile forces for an intense blend of arcade action. The adventure follows the path of its predecessor, Demon&amp;rsquo;s Tilt, and brings familiar gameplay mechanics while adding many new challenges. Each new table offers a new set of obstacles, targets and bonuses that force users to be on their guard. Pinball here is not just about throwing a ball, it is a battle against time, enemies and your own reflexes.</description></item><item><title>Farming Simulator 25</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farming-simulator-25/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farming-simulator-25/</guid><description>Game Description Farming Simulator 25 takes gamers on a new journey through the world of farming with new settings and expanded features. This installment features new environments spanning the regions of East Asia, North America, and Central Europe, each offering their own unique challenges and rewards. These diverse landscapes offer a wide variety of agricultural opportunities, from rice paddies in Asia to large grain fields in the Americas.
Users can fully immerse themselves in a variety of landscapes, each of which has its own farming requirements, making each farm special.</description></item><item><title>Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</guid><description>Game Description Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is a naval combat game in which you control two warring factions: NATO forces and representatives of the Warsaw Pact. Take part in the naval conflicts of the 80s. Control a huge number of different ships, use all modern types of weapons and technologies. Your main task in Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is to defeat the enemy army.</description></item><item><title>Take Me</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/take-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/take-me/</guid><description>Game Description Take Me is a title that is a distinct fusion of stealth, horror and dark humor. The story centers on Maria, a young woman who finds herself in an unexpected and somewhat strange situation. After attending a masquerade, Maria loses consciousness and wakes up in a strange situation - in the house of a mysterious man named Vitaly. From the very beginning, the gamer finds himself in the role of Maria, trying to get out of a place that seems both mysterious and dangerous.</description></item><item><title>Mirthwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</guid><description>Game Description Mirthwood is a fun medieval fantasy sandbox game that combines the charm of a life simulation with the thrill of an RPG. It offers gamers the opportunity to create their own adventure in a new country, escaping their war-torn homeland. The game offers two main paths: settle down and build a farm, trade with other cities and start a family; or explore a huge open world and fight bandits, monsters and other dangers.</description></item><item><title>Terror of the Seven Seas</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</guid><description>Game Description Terror of the Seven Seas is a game that immerses gamers in the complex maritime life of an era of exploration and piracy. The game takes place in a vast open world and offers a wide range of entertainment - from participating in large-scale naval battles to treasure hunting. Users take on the roles of various characters, each with their own unique responsibilities and abilities. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a captain leading a ship through stormy seas, an officer commanding a crew, a merchant transporting goods across vast oceans, or an explorer reaching into the unknown, there is something for every type of adventurer.</description></item><item><title>Warlords Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Warlords Battle Simulator is a game that places gamers in the role of generals who must lead armies in strategic and often unpredictable battles. In this tactical roguelike auto-action game, success largely depends on how well users manage resources, select units and place them on the battlefield. Each faction - be it the Kingdom, Greenskins, Undead or Barbarians - offers a unique set of units and commanders, each with special abilities that can change the tide of battle.</description></item><item><title>Quadrober Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Quadrober Simulator invites users to test themselves as a four-legged creature in a diverse environment. There is a lot of choice in this game. Users can choose from a variety of animals, each with specific traits and skills. These choices set the stage for a unique journey through different ecosystems. As gamers navigate these landscapes, they are faced with opportunities to explore, survive, and interact with the environment. Gameplay revolves around several key activities, including hunting, foraging, and building shelters.</description></item><item><title>Fruitbus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fruitbus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fruitbus/</guid><description>Game Description Fruitbus is an open world culinary adventure game that invites gamers into a vibrant world full of culinary possibilities. Here, players control a customizable van as they explore the Gustum Archipelago. Each island presents a new selection of fruits and vegetables. During the journey, users collect ingredients that can be combined to create unique menus. These dishes serve not only to feed, but also to bring happiness to the inhabitants of the island.</description></item><item><title>Dollmare</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dollmare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dollmare/</guid><description>Game Description Dollmare is a psychological horror adventure in which gamers have to work in a mysterious doll factory. The factory is not just a background, it is a character in its own right, filled with secrets waiting in the wings. Entering the role of a factory worker, users quickly realize that there is more to this place than meets the eye. Strange occurrences become the norm, and the unsettling nature of the dolls hints at deeper secrets lurking in the shadows.</description></item><item><title>You Are Grounded</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/you-are-grounded/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/you-are-grounded/</guid><description>Game Description You Are Grounded places gamers in a tense environment where a teenager is locked in his room on Halloween night. The story is set against the backdrop of a community celebrating a holiday while the protagonist contemplates the consequences of his actions. The night takes a dark turn when the news reports of an escaped maniac dressed as a clown, adding extra urgency to the situation. With parents punishing the teenager, his predicament becomes a major theme as he moves around the house looking for items that might help him survive.</description></item><item><title>Tech Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Tech Store Simulator immerses gamers in the fast-paced world of tech retail, giving them hands-on experience in running their own electronics store. The title&amp;rsquo;s focus is on strategic decision-making, requiring users to balance inventory management with customer satisfaction. Gamers will have to navigate the ins and outs of running a successful tech business, from stocking shelves with the latest gadgets to setting competitive prices.
Hiring and managing staff is another key aspect of the game to keep the store running smoothly and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Whimel Academy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whimel-academy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whimel-academy/</guid><description>Game Description Whimel Academy immerses gamers in the everyday life of a magic school student. This time management simulation game offers a fun environment where users juggle classes, extracurricular activities, and social interactions. Every day is a combination of learning and personal growth as gamers navigate the complexities of school and relationships. By taking on the role of a student, users will experience the ups and downs of managing schedules and developing skills in various magical disciplines.</description></item><item><title>Undisputed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undisputed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undisputed/</guid><description>Game Description Undisputed is a sports simulator about boxing, where a special emphasis is placed on realism. Having created his own fighter, the player will have to go from amateur matches to the professional stage. The main goal will be to obtain the eWBC world title. Achieving this title will require constant honing of your skills, learning new techniques and choosing the right strategy. You can carefully choose your approach to each enemy and not take too many risks, or you can go for the trouble and show your full potential in every battle.</description></item><item><title>Diplomacy is Not an Option</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</guid><description>Game Description InDiplomacy is Not an Option the player becomes a feudal lord in the Middle Ages. The main character is going through a midlife crisis. Every day the protagonist comes up with hundreds of ways to improve his own economy, how to properly lead his subjects and competently develop the city. He lived like this for a long time. He was tired of monotonous and meaningless intellectual stress.
New adventures in the life of the central character begin when hordes of monsters began to attack settlements, and the townspeople rebelled together.</description></item><item><title>Aim Camp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</guid><description>Game Description Aim Camp is an adventure game that combines military simulator and interactive gameplay. It immerses gamers in a variety of training exercises aimed at honing their aiming and accuracy skills. Each exercise presents users with unique challenges, including scenarios such as close combat, sniping and drone operations. Gamers immerse themselves in these drills, where the goal is not only competition, but also a deeper understanding of accuracy.
The design of each scenario encourages a focused approach, requiring players to constantly adapt and improve their techniques.</description></item><item><title>Recycling Center Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recycling-center-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recycling-center-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Recycling Center Simulator puts gamers in the role of a recycling center manager. The adventure game focuses on collecting raw materials from various locations. Users sort these materials using specialized machines. The goal is efficient processing and production of new products. Users start with basic hardware. They must upgrade their equipment to handle more complex materials. There is a special focus on time management and strategic planning. Gamers must decide which materials to choose.</description></item><item><title>Moving Houses</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moving-houses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moving-houses/</guid><description>Game Description Moving Houses is a physics-based game that revolves around the seemingly simple task of packing things in a house. Gamers are given the freedom to approach a task however they see fit, whether that means carefully organizing items in boxes or throwing items into chaos. The title presents a deceptively simple goal that soon turns out to be anything but simple. As gamers delve into the title, they are faced with various household items that need to be packed.</description></item><item><title>exclusive memory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</guid><description>Game Description Exclusive Memory draws gamers into a narrative where every choice and interaction can change the storyline. The protagonist finds himself in a maze of memories, each of which serves as a puzzle box that needs to be opened. As users delve deeper, they uncover layers of the character&amp;rsquo;s past, encountering various figures that are pieces of a larger puzzle. These interactions not only move the narrative forward, but also provide insight into the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s psyche, shaping his journey.</description></item><item><title>Prison Alone</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prison-alone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prison-alone/</guid><description>Game Description Prison Alone is a psychological horror game that immerses gamers in the chilling setting of an abandoned prison. Against a backdrop of decay and desolation, users take on the role of a prisoner who makes the questionable decision to remain in prison during a mass transfer of prisoners. This choice sets off a chain of eerie events that drive the narrative forward. While exploring dark corridors and confined spaces, users encounter a number of unsettling moments.</description></item><item><title>Start Over</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</guid><description>Game Description Start Over is a multiplayer survival simulator set on a desert island, providing an immersive experience. You have to build a base, make the necessary equipment and defend against waves of enemies. The game features a realistic and dynamic environment where you need to adapt to constantly changing weather conditions, hunt animals, collect resources for survival and engage in trading items to earn money. As you explore the island, you can discover hidden secrets such as secret caves, ancient ruins, and even military camps.</description></item><item><title>Mechabellum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</guid><description>Game Description Mechabellum is an epic auto battler set in a sci-fi setting that puts you in the shoes of a commander leading an army of mechs on the newly colonized planet Far-Away. Your opponents will tremble in fear as you customize and level up your units, strategically place them on the battlefield and watch them ruthlessly destroy your enemies. You&amp;rsquo;ll have an arsenal of unique &amp;lsquo;Mechs at your disposal, from the nimble light craft of Wasps to the massive Vulcans.</description></item><item><title>Alchemist: The Potion Monger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemist-the-potion-monger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemist-the-potion-monger/</guid><description>Game Description Alchemist: The Potion Monger invites users into a world where alchemy reigns. This first-person simulation game combines RPG elements, immersing gamers in a realm rich with ingredients and potions waiting in the wings. From the moment you step out of the cozy alchemy hut, you will be overcome with a sense of adventure. The environment is rife with opportunities to collect rare materials and brew unique drinks. Each exploration leads to discoveries that expand your alchemical repertoire and keep gameplay fresh and exciting.</description></item><item><title>City 20</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-20/</guid><description>Game Description City 20 is not an ordinary survival game where you need to search for resources. Of course, there is the usual wasteland after a disaster, the constant struggle for survival, the excitement associated with finding decent scrap metal. But the title adds a twist to the story - your choices rewrite the rules. Every decision you make sends ripples through this broken society, pushing NPCs in new directions and changing the course of events.</description></item><item><title>Rally Arcade Classics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Rally Arcade Classics takes gamers into the heart of rally racing history, bringing classic arcade gaming to the world of motorsports. With 44 cars from four different decades - the 70s, 80s, 90s and 00s - you&amp;rsquo;ll get a look at the cars that helped shape the rally scene. There&amp;rsquo;s a wide variety of iconic cars here, each offering its own set of challenges and driving features. In addition to the impressive list of cars, there are 48 tracks, each designed for a different type of racing.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Glade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-glade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-glade/</guid><description>Game Description Tiny Glade is a fun game that lets you unleash your creativity and build adorable scenes using simple, easy-to-use tools. Here the possibilities are endless, because the user can build whatever his heart desires - from magnificent castles to serene gardens. What sets the project apart is its ability to transform ideas into cozy and captivating dioramas, capturing the imagination and senses.
One of the great aspects of Tiny Glade is that there are no fixed rules or goals.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk 2 is a continuation of the survival game, which is based on management and construction. The events of the game take place 30 years after the catastrophe that covered the Earth. Now the planet has experienced severe cooling and people are suffering from constant frosts. In the urban planning simulator, you are asked to try on the role of a hero who, in the process, must lead an entire metropolis and take care of the well-being of local residents.</description></item><item><title>Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</guid><description>Game Description Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell is a first-person psychological horror game that explores themes of grief, guilt, and the paranormal. Players take on the role of Mark, a man coping with the recent loss of his wife Jane. The game begins with Mark returning to his and Jane&amp;rsquo;s old country house to prepare for her funeral. However, what is meant to be a grim homecoming quickly turns into a terrifying ordeal.</description></item><item><title>Psycho Fear</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psycho-fear/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psycho-fear/</guid><description>Game Description Psycho Fear is a puzzle game that immerses users in a world filled with challenging tasks and life-threatening obstacles. Finding themselves in this tense environment, gamers quickly realize that survival depends on their ability to solve problems. The title offers a buffet of puzzles, each designed to engage the users' minds, testing their intelligence and creativity while requiring quick thinking and adaptation. From the moment they enter, gamers are overcome with a sense of urgency, prompting them to explore their surroundings for clues and solutions.</description></item><item><title>Toy Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Toy Tactics is a colorful action strategy game that will take you into the world of exciting strategies and physics experiments. Here you will become the main general, tasked with controlling little toy soldiers and defeating the enemy. You will have to place units on the battlefield and create various formations to guide your toy army towards victory. But don’t forget that physics plays an important role here! When the toy soldiers collide with each other, their helmets will fly in all directions, just like in a cartoon.</description></item><item><title>Train Sim World 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-sim-world-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-sim-world-5/</guid><description>Game Description Train Sim World 5 introduces a range of new features and routes to enhance the experience for train enthusiasts. The game includes three new routes: the West Coast Main Line from London Euston to Milton Keynes, the Frankfurt - Fulda route in Germany and the San Bernardino Line in the US. Each route offers gamers unique challenges and opportunities to explore different types of train controls. One of the features of Train Sim World 5 is Conductor Mode, which allows users to take on the role of a train conductor, managing the boarding of passengers and ensuring timely departures.</description></item><item><title>Fera: The Sundered Tribes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</guid><description>Game Description Fera: The Sundered Tribes throws its hat into the action-RPG ring, but with a twist. You will not only have to smash the skulls of monsters, but also lead your tribe to restoration in a world devastated by magic. Imagine: A monster hunter by day, a mayor by night. The world of Fera is a post-apocalyptic mess, twisted by magic and infested with giant monsters that are eager to add your tribe to their menu of creatures.</description></item><item><title>Train Yard Builder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-yard-builder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-yard-builder/</guid><description>Game Description Train Yard Builder invites gamers into a miniature world where they can build and manage their own train yards. With a diverse selection of trains and carriages, users can create unique and personalized collections. The title provides customization tools, allowing users to paint and decorate their trains, adding a personal touch to their creations.
In addition to trains, users can design and decorate their yards. Using landscaping tools, they can build intricate paths and create beautiful surroundings.</description></item><item><title>TCG Card Shop Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tcg-card-shop-simulator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tcg-card-shop-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description TCG Card Shop Simulator puts players in the role of a trading card store (TCG) owner who is responsible for the day-to-day operations and long-term growth of their business. From the very beginning, users are immersed in the mechanics of arranging shelves, pricing goods, and interacting with customers. You&amp;rsquo;re not just haphazardly putting products on display; careful planning is required to ensure that the right products are available at the right time.</description></item><item><title>City Bus Simulator 2024</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-bus-simulator-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-bus-simulator-2024/</guid><description>Game Description City Bus Simulator 2024 puts gamers in the role of a bus driver navigating a busy urban environment. The game offers a detailed simulation of city life, where users must manage schedules and routes while interacting with a variety of passengers. Each ride presents unique challenges, from navigating tight turns to unpredictable road conditions. Users can explore different areas, each with their own character and attractions.
The project emphasizes the importance of time management and efficiency, requiring players to adhere to strict schedules while ensuring passenger satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>Head To Hell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/head-to-hell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/head-to-hell/</guid><description>Game Description Head To Hell begins with the main character waking up on a moving train with no memory of how he got there or what lies ahead. The only thing that gives any semblance of direction is a text message. Not the most pleasant thing when you&amp;rsquo;re on a train that never seems to stop. The message gives clues, but they are vague and mysterious, leaving the user guessing about what it really is.</description></item><item><title>Surreal Farm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</guid><description>Game Description Surreal Farm is an adventure game that invites gamers into a vibrant world where imagination and strategy intertwine. Starting with a modest plot of land, gamers grow crops, care for unique animals and turn their farm into a thriving enterprise. As they progress, they discover many fantastical elements, from magical tools to surreal cultures and mythical creatures. The charm lies in the combination of casual gameplay and strategic depth.</description></item><item><title>Stardiver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</guid><description>Game Description The underwater world ofStardiver amazes with its diversity. Under the water column lies an entire civilization that has adapted to this way of existence so that other forms of life do not bother them and do not start wars. Nevertheless, for humanity, a planet completely covered with water turned out to be more than a curious subject of research.
The main character is the head of a scientific group for the study of extraterrestrial forms of civilization.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>Demolish and Build 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</guid><description>Game Description Demolish and Build 3 is a first-person simulator that puts you in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat of a demolition company. You will complete orders and lead your team to victory using a variety of tools and heavy equipment. This game will test your skills as you manage your business and complete every project with precision and efficiency. A completely new realistic model of destruction will make you marvel at what you see more than once, since each fragment is physically simulated.</description></item><item><title>Satisfactory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</guid><description>Game Description Satisfactory is an open-world first-person adventure where you build industrial buildings, explore, and fight. Explore a new planet alone or with other users. Build huge structures and do whatever you want in assembly line paradise. You are an employee of FICSIT Corporation.
Players can build wherever they want. Expand production in all directions, install factories in the mountains, forests or plains. Mine natural resources found all around you. Build complex networks and transport routes, automate all mechanics, without forgetting about safety.</description></item><item><title>Zero Hour</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Hour is a multiplayer tactical first-person shooter with realistic game mechanics that replicate the behavior of real special forces units in anti-terrorist operations. The setting for the action is criminal Bangladesh, where banditry is at a high level and is not going to give up ground to law enforcement officers. The locations where clashes between groups of terrorists and special forces occur are made using real scale, which greatly helps the atmosphere and involves gamers in the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Ale and Tale Tavern</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-and-tale-tavern/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-and-tale-tavern/</guid><description>Game Description Ale and Tale Tavern is a first-person, open-world co-op fantasy tavern simulator. Gamers step into the role of a tavern owner tasked with restoring an abandoned establishment to its former glory. The title offers a variety of activities including cooking, fishing, hunting and exploration. Users can complete a variety of quests, interact with unique characters, and manage various aspects of the tavern, such as decoration and crafting.
The gameplay of Ale and Tale Tavern allows you to play both alone and in co-op - up to four users can work together.</description></item><item><title>Skoof Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Skoof Simulator will introduce gamers to the life of Skoof, an ordinary worker whose everyday life is not like a routine. The title combines simulation and adventure elements, offering a unique and sarcastic look at everyday activities. Players guide Skuf through a variety of missions, ranging from factory shifts to humorous and unexpected situations. Users will have to manage Skuf&amp;rsquo;s life, making decisions that affect the outcome of his adventures.</description></item><item><title>Fantasy Map Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fantasy-map-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fantasy-map-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Fantasy Map Simulator will be an exciting experience, because this simulator invites history and fantasy lovers to create and watch the development of fictional worlds. Imagine a canvas stretched across centuries, where empires rise and fall, nations emerge, and destinies intertwine. The title allows users to create complex maps, each of which is a testament to their creativity. These cards, like living organisms, develop autonomously, guided by logic.</description></item><item><title>The Moon 2044</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</guid><description>Game Description The Moon 2044 takes place in a secret research facility on the Moon, where gamers take on the role of a genetically modified commando codenamed XV-11. The mission is to retrieve priceless samples from the depths of a lunar base that has fallen into darkness and is now overrun by hostile creatures. The facility, originally intended for experimental cancer research, hides many dark secrets that users will have to uncover.</description></item><item><title>Star Trucker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-trucker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-trucker/</guid><description>Game Description InStar Trucker imagine yourself speeding through space, a lone trucker in a galaxy of endless possibilities. Welcome to a game that combines the spirit of the open road of American trucking with the vastness of space. You are not just a driver, you are the captain of your destiny in a space suit. What is your mission? Transport cargo, search for salvaged items and communicate with other truckers across the galaxy.</description></item><item><title>We Heist Too</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</guid><description>Game Description We Heist Too takes place in Rivadorium, a city where nothing ever stays the same. Users get used to the role of a thief, move silently through the streets, plan and carry out high-stakes robberies. This world doesn&amp;rsquo;t require much care, and from the very beginning you will notice that every corner of the city is fraught with opportunity. But the tricky part is knowing which opportunities are worth pursuing.</description></item><item><title>Why don't they laugh?</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/why-dont-they-laugh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/why-dont-they-laugh/</guid><description>Game Description Why don&amp;rsquo;t they laugh? is a first-person horror game that invites gamers into the mysterious world of the Kensington circus dynasty. Users take on the role of April, a young woman who finds herself at an ancient estate in Maine, drawn there by a request to help the last heir of the Kensington family. The estate that was once a symbol of the Kensingtons' glory now hides more than just memories within its walls.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>MEMORIAPOLIS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/memoriapolis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/memoriapolis/</guid><description>Game Description MEMORIAPOLIS is an urban construction set unlike any other. This is a time machine, a sandbox for history buffs. Studio 5PM created this brainchild, offering users a playground for 2500 years. From the dawn of civilization to the Age of Enlightenment, gamers create a city. It&amp;rsquo;s not just bricks and mortar, it&amp;rsquo;s a living, breathing organism that reacts to your every move. Time is the currency here. Users go through Antiquity, the Middle Ages, the Renaissance and the Enlightenment.</description></item><item><title>Squirrel with a Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Squirrel with a Gun offers a unique experience. Users control a squirrel armed with a gun. Target? Collect golden acorns in a secret underground vault. The squirrel that haunts the neighbors becomes a hero. Gamers move through a sandbox filled with puzzles and enemies. The facility serves as a playground for chaos. To survive, the squirrel uses weapons, claws and teeth. The gameplay combines shooting and platforming. Users collect golden acorns - a squirrel&amp;rsquo;s obsession.</description></item><item><title>Star Command Galaxies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</guid><description>Game Description Star Command Galaxies is a space simulator in which you play as a ship captain. You need to build your own shuttle, recruit staff and go explore the randomly generated expanses of outer space. Manage your staff, collect resources, fight the alien threat and upgrade your ship. Clear the galaxy from enemies and various parasites. Fight pirates, zombies and many other opponents.
You need to monitor the status of your team.</description></item><item><title>Core Keeper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</guid><description>Game Description Going on an adventure inCore Keeper, you are immersed in an atmosphere of the unknown, requiring exploration on behalf of an archaeologist who wants to discover as many new relics and ancient artifacts as possible. Waking up in an unfamiliar area that resembles a cave, the protagonist will have to fight through a variety of monsters and obstacles that impede progress in order to achieve his goals.
Taking control of the main character, who finds himself in a pixel world filled with the spirit of adventure and precious treasures, you have to survive and explore the dangerous environment.</description></item><item><title>Motel Manager Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motel-manager-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motel-manager-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Motel Manager Simulator puts players in the shoes of a motel owner. But this is not just a motel - it is a place where travelers rest from fatigue, where they refuel with gasoline and where a small store sells essential goods. Your first task is to revive the motel. Clear it of cobwebs, fix broken lamps and breathe life into the rooms. Every room is a canvas waiting for your creativity.</description></item><item><title>9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</guid><description>Game Description 9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far is a real-time strategy game developed by Petroglyph Games, a continuation of the 8-Bit Armies series. Gamers lead modern military forces across various battlefields, participating in land, sea and air battles. The project offers more than two dozen missions, online skirmishes and cooperative play. A base construction system has been implemented in which players build structures, unlock units and launch attacks. The game is designed for both new and experienced RTS players with an easy to learn interface but a challenging skill ceiling.</description></item><item><title>Before They Wake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/before-they-wake/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/before-they-wake/</guid><description>Game Description Before They Wake takes place in the summer of 1984 and tells the story of Alfred, who is confined to a wheelchair. Trapped in an orphanage overrun by sound-sensitive mutants, Alfred navigates a path of survival and escape. His wheelchair squeaks with every movement, adding to the stress as he navigates the dangerous environment. The mechanics boil down to controlling the noise level so as not to attract the attention of mutants.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Dynasty takes place in 1800s America. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to build his own ranch, providing himself with wealth and food. Over time, other settlers, workers and friends will join the main character. Each minor character has their own qualities, characteristics and mannerisms. Many of them will turn out to be bandits, and only the gamer can decide who is sent to the gallows.
Having become determined, the central character set out to build a Wild West dynasty, moving further across the Pacific region of America.</description></item><item><title>Who is Abby</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</guid><description>Game Description Who is Abby begins with Tom, a man determined to find his missing sister. The title immerses users in an intense psychological thriller where mystery and exploration go hand in hand. With every step, Tom plunges deeper into the mystery of Abby&amp;rsquo;s disappearance, revealing a story shrouded in mystery and darkness. As you take on the role of Tom, the journey becomes personal, with each discovery adding another piece to the puzzle of Abby&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>shapez 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapez-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapez-2/</guid><description>Game Description Shapez 2 is a simulator about the construction of factories with a top view, in which you need to automate the process of processing geometric shapes. Players must build and optimize massive production facilities to solve increasingly complex logistics problems. Gameplay involves cutting, rotating, stacking, painting and delivering shapes to unlock advanced technologies and expand enterprise capabilities.
What&amp;rsquo;s unique is that each object is a separate set of building blocks that can be disassembled, folded, painted and put back together in special ways.</description></item><item><title>Crime Scene Cleaner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-scene-cleaner/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-scene-cleaner/</guid><description>Game Description Crime Scene Cleaner is an unusual simulator in which you clean up traces of a crime. As soon as the customer calls you, and usually this is the mafia boss, you need to rush to the crime scene and wield a brush, a mop and many other tools. If you find yourself in a room full of corpses and blood, pull yourself together and do the job professionally. Don&amp;rsquo;t give investigators a chance to find the killer.</description></item><item><title>Fields of Mistria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</guid><description>Game Description Fields of Mistria invites users to exchange the hustle and bustle for a charming life in the village of Mistria. Here the fields lie between a whispering forest and a sparkling sea. But in Mystria, not everything is so rosy and sunny. The recent earthquake has left its mark, and now there is a strange magic in the air. This is where you come to the rescue. In Mystria you inherit an overgrown estate - a diamond in the bowels of the earth.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>7 Days to Die</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</guid><description>Game Description In7 Days to Die you will need the ability to loot, kill other players, take loot, build buildings, craft items, shoot accurately and keep track of time, because in the open world there is a night in which zombies and other undead sharpen their attention . A horror first-person shooter that combines city building, multiplayer, survival, tower defense and character leveling in an RPG style. Despite the fact that a severe epidemic has struck the world, you will be able to kill animals to take their meat and skin.</description></item><item><title>Workers and Resources: Soviet Republic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</guid><description>Game Description InWorkers and Resources: Soviet Republic you have to lead a fallen country and turn it into the strongest republic, making it a superpower with the happiest inhabitants who have built world progress. The urban planning strategy will show you a country that is very similar to the Soviet Union. You accept it broken, plundered, ruined. There is absolutely no money in the treasury, and people have no opportunity to raise territories, plant crops, go to work, simply because there is no money even for food, but you understand that all this can be corrected.</description></item><item><title>Chained Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chained-together/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chained-together/</guid><description>Game Description Chained Together throws you into the depths of hell so you can escape. But there is one peculiarity: you are chained to your comrades. That&amp;rsquo;s right, teamwork (or at least some serious coordination) is essential if you want to survive the scorching heat and treacherous platforms.
Play through the game alone or take up to three friends for a chaotic co-op adventure. Each world presents new challenges, testing your ability to navigate the chain.</description></item><item><title>Blade and Sorcery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</guid><description>Game Description Blade and Sorcery is a first-person fantasy action game focused on realistic hand-to-hand combat physics. You play as a hero who knows how to fight with melee and long-range weapons, as well as magical abilities. There are three classes to choose from: Warrior, Ranger and Wizard. The gameplay is adapted for virtual reality helmets Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift and Windows Mixed Reality.
The gameplay is based on body physics and fair hitboxes.</description></item><item><title>Grocery Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grocery-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grocery-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Grocery Store Simulator puts you in the shoes of a grocery store manager. Give up fashionable suits and briefcases, smart shoes - this is the new move of power. This first-person simulator from FEKK Games lets you run your own store. You control everything from stocking the shelves to setting prices. Do you want to play alone or team up with friends in four-player co-op? Grocery Store Simulator will satisfy both the lone wolf and those who like to work together.</description></item><item><title>Bodycam</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</guid><description>Game Description Bodycam throws you headlong into a hyper-realistic multiplayer battlefield. Powered by Unreal Engine 5, this all-new shooter promises a next-gen experience that will redefine your expectations. Teamwork is key here. Every bullet counts, and the victory or defeat of your squad depends on your every decision.
Forget playing Rambo. Bodycam requires strategic thinking and coordinated attacks. Team up with your teammates, map out a plan of action, and use your arsenal to outmaneuver your opponents.</description></item><item><title>Empires of the Undergrowth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</guid><description>Game Description Empires of the Undergrowth is a simulation and real-time strategy game with unique mechanics. In the game you will have to manage a colony of ants. Starting to play as one ant, you will hunt, manage builders, and create a unique hive. The design of your hive will determine whether your colony can survive in this harsh world. Why harsh?
Throughout the game you will face various obstacles. First of all, these are your enemies!</description></item><item><title>WARNO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</guid><description>Game Description Tactical battles inWARNO take place in real time, where users will be able to take control of modern combat vehicles and go to the front, plunging into the Third World War. The game is made in the genre of strategy and army command simulator, where you need to think through the movement of units and observe the events taking place. The storyline is about a coup that occurs after Gorbachev leaves, creating a tense conflict between states in 1989.</description></item><item><title>Homeworld 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/homeworld-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/homeworld-3/</guid><description>Game Description Homeworld 3 is a new part of the famous space battle franchise, which is a sequel and continues the storyline. Nevertheless, the game is also suitable for those who are not familiar with the universe, if you only dive into the mode of multiplayer confrontations on ships. Now abandoned galactic stations are scattered across the universe, which have turned into arenas where you can feel the battle with a random user.</description></item><item><title>Little Kitty, Big City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-kitty-big-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-kitty-big-city/</guid><description>Game Description Little Kitty, Big City will help you learn about all the difficulties that street cats face. Despite the fact that animals seem to people to be foolish and unable to live without humans, they have their own hierarchy, connections, and they support communication between species. Often, even dogs and cats team up for common survival or give advice to new recruits.
The main character is a teenage black kitten who got lost in a big city and now has to urgently find his way home.</description></item><item><title>Manor Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Manor Lords is a strategy game set in the Middle Ages. The game mechanics center on the realistic process of constructing buildings and intense fights with the enemy army. The building element is based on historical data about cities and villages. All buildings presented in Manor Lords are as authentic as possible. Landscapes and types of terrain influence the process of settlement formation.
Create trade routes, establish market relations with neighboring cities and promote the economic prosperity of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Rusty's Retirement</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-retirement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-retirement/</guid><description>Game Description Rusty&amp;rsquo;s Retirement allows players to experience farming on the go. Designed as a project for idlers, it allows you to manage a virtual farm while doing other things. Gamers take on the role of Rusty, a retired robot who tends to his crops. The game develops automatically: Rusty plants, waters and harvests crops without constant player interaction. As you progress, you can discover new cultures, adding variety to your virtual fields.</description></item><item><title>Bellwright</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</guid><description>Game Description Bellwright throws you into a world of rebellion and intrigue. Finding yourself in prison for a heinous crime, you must not only clear your name, but also organize a revolution against a tyrannical ruler. Build and manage settlements, collect resources and recruit villagers into your ranks. Each new adept brings valuable skills, strengthening your rebellion and unlocking new technologies for your cities.
Combat is based on skill and focus.</description></item><item><title>Spirit City: Lofi Sessions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spirit-city-lofi-sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spirit-city-lofi-sessions/</guid><description>Game Description Spirit City: Lofi Sessions is not an ordinary adventure game. It combines game elements and practical tools to improve focus and reduce stress. You will find yourself in a virtual world filled with a variety of activities, the essence of which comes down to collecting and interacting with spirits. These aren&amp;rsquo;t just pretty additions to your virtual homes - they play an important role in achieving the goal of making you more productive.</description></item><item><title>The Lost Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</guid><description>Game Description InThe Lost Village you have to restore a once great sect. You take on the role of the heir to a leader who has returned to an abandoned mountain and is tasked with restoring it to its former glory. The game combines a management simulator with roguelike elements. Gamers will guide students by collecting resources, building structures and cultivating the land. Students have unique personalities and talents, allowing assignments to be specialized.</description></item><item><title>Buckshot Roulette</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</guid><description>Game Description Two enter, one leaves. That&amp;rsquo;s the motto ofBuckshot Roulette, a horror game that takes the classic game of Russian Roulette and turns it into a high-stakes shotgun game. Immerse yourself in the dark atmosphere of an underground nightclub, where metal railings beat to the beat of forgotten drum kits and the stakes couldn&amp;rsquo;t be higher. This is not Russian roulette. This is where you swap the revolver for a 12 gauge shotgun, because shotguns are just better, right?</description></item><item><title>Knowledge, or know Lady</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</guid><description>Game Description Knowledge, or know Lady throws you into the heart of a unique dating simulator. As the only guy at an all-girl university, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself caught up in a whirlwind of romance and college life. Will you succumb to the charms of the beauties around you or forge your own path to become a campus legend? Ladies School Prince unfolds through your eyes, offering a first-person perspective. Your</description></item><item><title>Between the Stars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/between-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/between-the-stars/</guid><description>Game Description In Between the Stars, a space simulator, the gamer discovers new territories, fights with numerous opponents and upgrades his own ship. The hero&amp;rsquo;s goal is to save the Interstellar Republic. The game has procedural generation of the environment, enemies and stations.
The protagonist&amp;rsquo;s universe is suffering from attacks from the Children of the Sun clan. Enemy representatives have appeared from other worlds and are trying to capture these spaces.</description></item><item><title>Sons of the Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Sons of The Forest is a first-person multiplayer horror game with survival elements. The game is a sequel to the acclaimed hit The Forest. As in the previous part, you need to explore a mysterious forest inhabited by bloodthirsty monsters. Survive by hiding from enemies and carefully study the surrounding areas. Arm yourself with powerful weapons to face numerous opponents.
The story centers on a special forces soldier with a Fight Demons tattoo.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>Supermarket Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermarket-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermarket-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Supermarket Simulator puts you in the shoes of a retailer tasked with reviving abandoned grocery stores. Roll up your sleeves and get ready to breathe new life into forgotten stalls. First of all, assess the damage. Broken freezers? Leaky windows? Collapsing shelves? Throw away what&amp;rsquo;s irreparable and develop a repair strategy for the rest. Imagine a bright future filled with colorful products - this will become the basis of your renovation plan.</description></item><item><title>Balatro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</guid><description>Game Description Balatro - the word &amp;ldquo;poker&amp;rdquo; crackles with energy, whispering promises of high stakes and cunning deals. This poker roguelike beckons players into a deck-building odyssey where bluffing becomes the spell and chips become your lifeblood. Forget about limping into pots with low pairs. Here you create powerful synergies by weaving intricate combinations that unleash explosive power. Valid poker hands dance with unique wild cards, their abilities changing the course of the game like a magician.</description></item><item><title>Stargate: Timekeepers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stargate-timekeepers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stargate-timekeepers/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the Stargate: Timekeepers project take place within a separate universe called SG-1. It all begins with the Battle of Antarctica, where Commander Eve McKine leads the battle against Anubis' fleet. After this, the user will be able to take control of a squad subordinate to this very Eve in order to penetrate behind enemy lines and complete a number of dangerous tasks. The outcome of the war depends on this, so no one has the right to make a mistake.</description></item><item><title>The Universim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city construction, the development of an entire planet and a ward civilization -The Universim is a short sand strategy in which you have to try on the role of God. The game begins with the fact that you settle several people on one of the planets, give them food, indicate what needs to be done - set priorities. And then watch how people develop on their own, without your help.</description></item><item><title>KinitoPET</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</guid><description>Game Description KinitoPET promises a world of endless fun and communication with your virtual assistant Kinito. This early 2000s wonder can walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games, making him a friend like no other. But beneath the surface of this seemingly perfect companion lies a disturbing truth. Step into &amp;ldquo;Eternal Fun!&amp;rdquo;, and Kinito will become your personal assistant, ready to fulfill your every request. Its cutting-edge technology promises a &amp;ldquo;truly unique experience&amp;rdquo; designed just for you.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>The Kindeman Remedy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-kindeman-remedy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-kindeman-remedy/</guid><description>Game Description A management game unlike any other, The Kindeman Remedy plunges you into the realm of sacrilege and madness. In this diabolical creation, you step into the shoes of Dr. Carl Kindeman, a man who has lost everything - his reputation tarnished by the medical community&amp;rsquo;s disdain for his unorthodox methods. To regain his honor, he takes a grim position in a nightmarish prison, where he hopes to restore his lost authority through unspeakable deeds.</description></item><item><title>Cuisineer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cuisineer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cuisineer/</guid><description>Game Description Cuisineer is a delightful mix of dungeon crawling, cooking, and restaurant management that takes you into the captivating story of Pom, an energetic adventurer who must save her family&amp;rsquo;s diner in Paella. Armed with her culinary skills, she travels beyond her hometown, engaging in culinary battles with monsters and collecting ingredients to prepare delicious dishes for her visitors. Offering a variety of culinary adventures with an extensive repertoire of over 100 recipes spanning the globe, from savory Popiah rolls to sweet Kaya jam and crispy chicken delicacies.</description></item><item><title>Living Cell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/living-cell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/living-cell/</guid><description>Game Description Living Cell is a dark adventure game with survival elements that immerses you in the atmosphere of Samosbor - a dystopian world where residents live in endless apartment buildings called &amp;ldquo;Gigahrushchevkas&amp;rdquo;. In this exciting story, you will take the place of the liquidator, who is entrusted with the responsibility of maintaining order and security in the quarter. At the beginning of the story, players find themselves the only survivors in block G-326 after a mysterious incident.</description></item><item><title>DON'T SCREAM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-scream/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-scream/</guid><description>Game Description DON&amp;rsquo;T SCREAM is a thrilling indie horror game that plunges you into the heart of an eerie forest with a nerve-wracking twist: silence is the key to survival. The basic concept is simple, but fiendishly difficult: survive in a creepy forest for 18 minutes without letting out a single scream. An integral component of the game is a functional microphone, and any flash, scream or loud noise will result in the character&amp;rsquo;s untimely demise, causing an unfortunate restart.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Slay the Princess is a dark and daring adventure that will put your skills to the ultimate test, combining the genres of psychological horror and dating simulator. Your mission is simple: kill the princess and save the world from destruction. But don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by her charms and promises. She will stop at nothing to stop you from completing your task. Make your way through the dense forest and find the hut at the end of the path.</description></item><item><title>Sumerians</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerians/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerians/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of Sumerians is based on the story of 3000 BC in Mesopotamia, a time of rapid settlement growth and the development of Sumerian cities. The player will play the role of a ruler and will build his own city, manage resources, plan future infrastructure and try to cope with the economy.
In the process you only have to improve the city, build and manage the economy, there are no wars or attacks, but there will be numerous obstacles created by the population or nature.</description></item><item><title>EA SPORTS FC 24</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ea-sports-fc-24/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ea-sports-fc-24/</guid><description>Game Description EA SPORTS FC 24 is designed to revolutionize virtual football. With an impressive roster of over 19,000 licensed athletes, over 30 leagues, and recreations of over 100 iconic stadiums, it&amp;rsquo;s a fan&amp;rsquo;s dream. At the heart of FIFA 24 is HyperMotion V, a revolutionary technology that uses volumetric data collected from cameras strategically placed around stadiums during more than 180 top-tier matches. Thanks to this technology, an unreal level of realism is achieved.</description></item><item><title>Moonstone Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moonstone-island/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moonstone-island/</guid><description>Game Description Moonstone Island is a life-sim with collecting creatures, immersing you in a huge open world full of adventures. The game has 100 islands to explore, promising an exciting journey like no other. As someone who has visited this enchanting world, I can say that Moonstone Island offers a truly unique and exciting experience. You step into the shoes of a novice alchemist, following village traditions. Your task is to undergo alchemy training on a floating island in the sky.</description></item><item><title>ABRISS - build to destroy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abriss-build-to-destroy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abriss-build-to-destroy/</guid><description>Game Description ABRISS - build to destroy is a simulator based on physical laws. The gameplay is focused on building an atmospheric layer that destroys physics. The user has access to many designs that can crash into specified targets and destroy them. The story campaign gradually opens up access to new details, which will allow you to destroy large creations and observe entropy in digital and futuristic landscapes.
Opportunities in construction and destruction:</description></item><item><title>Sengoku Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Sengoku Dynasty tells the story of difficult life in feudal Japan. To convey everything with maximum accuracy, the developers consulted with a historical group, which provided valuable advice and confirmed records with information about the life of that period. The player will have to become the leader of one of the villages and lead it to prosperity and expansion in one of the ways.
The player will have one, almost abandoned settlement at his disposal, which he will have to restore and provide the inhabitants with everything they need.</description></item><item><title>Techtonica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/techtonica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/techtonica/</guid><description>Game Description Techtonica is a factory construction and management simulator. Compared to many other similar games, this title stands out in that all actions here must be carried out from a first-person view. The second feature is that the plant itself is underground. Unlike most sandboxes, there is an end goal. There is also end-game content. Here you need to extract resources, build and move objects, stretch conveyor belts, automate production, craft improved tools to be able to go even deeper.</description></item><item><title>Sticky Business</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sticky-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sticky-business/</guid><description>Game Description Sticky Business immerses users in the art of running a sticker store, where creativity and organization intertwine. Gamers are immersed in the daily work of creating original sticker designs and fulfilling customer orders. The title presents many options for combining elements, which allows users to focus on different tastes and preferences. From whimsical illustrations to fashionable motifs, the potential for creativity is at the forefront.
Players quickly realize that creating something attractive is just the beginning; running a store requires careful planning and resource management.</description></item><item><title>Brick Rigs</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</guid><description>Game Description Brick Rigs is a sandbox that allows you to create a variety of vehicles, and then enjoy realistic driving and destruction physics. You need to build cars using various blocks. The Brick Rings toolkit allows you to create a dragster, a fire truck, a forklift, a helicopter, an airplane or even a tank - it all depends on your imagination and skill.
Gameplay Brick Rigs is a full-fledged construction set with which you can create any type of transport.</description></item><item><title>Dave The Diver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</guid><description>Game Description Dave The Diver - a sea adventure about a diver named Dave. Events take place in a mysterious place called the Blue Hole. During the day, the protagonist explores the ocean, diving to the very bottom in search of treasures, and at night he manages a sushi restaurant. Dave is partnered with 3 charismatic friends to help him on his adventures. Each character has an individual character, introducing dynamics into the relationships between the characters.</description></item><item><title>It's Only Money</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</guid><description>Game Description It&amp;rsquo;s Only Money will immerse gamers in the realistic story of a resident of the underworld, who, by order of the mayor of Rockhaven, was thrown into a huge pit. But don&amp;rsquo;t despair! Together with other inhabitants of the underground, you can return to the surface and begin your path to wealth and power. You must steal from the rich, fight tycoons, and regain control of the city block by block.</description></item><item><title>Space Reign</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-reign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-reign/</guid><description>Game Description Space Reign is an exciting project that combines several colorful formats. In addition to the main storyline, there is a sandbox mode in which you can freely explore the universe and engage in open-ended gameplay. Here you need to try different strategies, experiment with the configuration of ships, discover hidden secrets and rare resources. One of the product&amp;rsquo;s strengths is its attention to detail and immersion. The universe feels alive - bustling space stations, bustling trade routes, clashes with friendly and hostile factions.</description></item><item><title>Tale of Immortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</guid><description>Game Description Tale of Immortal, an open-world sandbox deeply rooted in Chinese mythology and cultivation, invites players into an immersive experience where the path to immortality is paved through strategic choices and the conquest of mythical monsters from the Classic of Mountains and Seasons. Your journey as a novice Qi Refinement Stage cultivator begins in Yukong Village. A world filled with unpredictable monsters, mystical kingdoms and treasures waiting in the wings will open before you.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>Spectator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spectator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spectator/</guid><description>Game Description Spectator can please fans of Internet folklore. This game is inspired by popular urban legends. Here you can go Backstage, visit Slenderman’s habitat and visit other locations. It&amp;rsquo;s full of all kinds of references. The video game is a representative of the point-and-click survival horror genre. The indie title uses a first-person perspective. Before you start, you can choose one of 3 difficulty types: normal, hard and nightmare. There are 6 levels (days) in total.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging intoZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>Silver Nornir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silver-nornir/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silver-nornir/</guid><description>Game Description Silver Nornir invites gamers to plunge into an exciting world where the fate of the entire world is at stake. This is an exciting old school RPG in a fantasy setting. Survivors of two disasters are ready to fight to the end to stop the end of the world. But they need your help! Exciting adventures and exciting battles using magical gems and combo techniques with friends and allies await you.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</guid><description>Game Description Mount and Blade 2 Bannerlord is a role-playing game with elements of medieval wars, the action of which takes place 200 years before the start of Part 1. In this sequel you will find an improved combat system and an enlarged game world - Calradia. Fight with hundreds of troops under your command and take direct part in the battles as one of the soldiers. You can storm enemy fortresses and destroy fortifications with siege weapons in Mount &amp;amp; Blade II: Bannerlord.</description></item><item><title>CHEMISTS: Area of ​​infection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chemists-area-of-infection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chemists-area-of-infection/</guid><description>Game Description CHEMISTS: Area of ​​Infection is a 3rd person shooter that will take you to an alternate reality full of dangers and mysteries. Years have passed since a global catastrophe, and you wake up in a hospital, remembering nothing from the past. Now your task is to survive in this harsh world and find out what happened. Players will have to rely on their experience and navigate the environment, remembering every corner so as not to get lost.</description></item><item><title>PowerWash Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/powerwash-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/powerwash-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description In thePowerWash Simulator you need to clean surfaces from dirt, plaque, rust and much more. The calming and peaceful gameplay of PowerWash Simulator is designed for those who love the noise of dishwashers and love cleanliness. You will have a water pump in your hands that can clean absolutely any surface.
Wash away all the dirt from the city and show society who the real professional is here! Do your job carefully and earn reputation points.</description></item><item><title>Placid Plastic Duck Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/placid-plastic-duck-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/placid-plastic-duck-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Placid Plastic Duck Simulator is an opportunity to immerse yourself in the funny adventures of a little rubber duck, who must move through a variety of colorful locations. Users will be able to enjoy elaborate graphics and visual effects, as well as selected meditative music. The project aims to physically interact with an interactive environment in a three-dimensional space, where you need to try yourself in the role of one of the toy ducks that swim in the pool.</description></item><item><title>Raft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</guid><description>Game Description Raft is a first-person survival sandbox in which the player will have to survive on a small raft and explore new lands. The main character will begin his journey by waking up hungry and dehydrated on a small wreck of a ship. Get food and drink by catching garbage floating past the hero on the waves. To catch the item, you can use the hook. Find useful items and materials to craft a mug, light a fire, and filter sea water.</description></item><item><title>Dorfromantik</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dorfromantik/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dorfromantik/</guid><description>Game Description Dorfromantik - strategy in low-poly style. The game encourages you not to think about military strategies and operations. enjoy peaceful buildings and development of your lands. Game mechanics of Dorfromantic combine classic RTS and puzzle. Create a village, developing and expanding, building new buildings on hexagonal tiles.
Explore a procedurally generated world filled with diverse and colorful biomes. Complete tasks to fill locations with new life and create truly unique worlds.</description></item><item><title>Teardown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</guid><description>Game Description Teardown is a robbery simulator in a variety of conditions prepared by indie developers from Tuxedo Labs. Stylistically, the project was made using a voxel graphic component. This solution made it possible to implement complete destructibility of all available objects in the location. This freedom opens up the possibility of performing operations in a variety of ways, improvising on the fly. The gamer will have at his disposal explosives and a sledgehammer for destroying all kinds of surfaces to penetrate the territory, as well as several types of vehicles of different sizes for loading valuables and other things that need to be stolen according to the terms of a particular task.</description></item><item><title>Stacklands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</guid><description>Game Description InStacklands you have to build a village, completing various levels in the style of a deck-building battler. Users will collect food, build buildings and fight monsters on a special field using ability cards. It will be possible to use combinations of cards. For example, when you move a “village dweller” to a “berry bush”, “berries” will appear, which the city dweller will consume as food and get a chance to survive.</description></item><item><title>Wobbledogs</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbledogs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbledogs/</guid><description>Game Description Wobbledogs is a bright sandbox with simulation elements, based on funny physics and funny ragdoll. The gameplay is a pet simulator. Take care and raise fancy dogs. They can change shape and mutate. Acid colors, funny style and cute animals are the basis of such an unusual project. Wobbledogs helps you learn how to take care of your pets.
At the beginning of their life, dogs behave relatively calmly and normally.</description></item><item><title>Mon Bazou</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</guid><description>Game Description While repairing a car inMon Bazou, players have to deal with a variety of everyday problems that affect the life of the main character. The protagonist is a guy who dreams of turning his old car into a racing car that can compete with professional drivers and reach great speed. The game is made in the form of a simulator, where users have to take on the role of a novice racer who will live the everyday routine and do simple things, trying to earn a living.</description></item><item><title>Noble Fates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</guid><description>Game Description The fantasy world of Noble Fates immerses you in adventures taking place in a fairy-tale kingdom. A group of gods oversee the plane of human material existence while mortals vie for control over territories and new lands. The main character is Contra, who is a demigod and capable of influencing people and other inhabitants of the planet. It will be possible to manage entire colonies of settlers in order to achieve prosperity for the future great civilization.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Mystia's Izakaya</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Mystia&amp;rsquo;s Izakaya takes gamers to a fictional Japanese town called Gensoke, where the young and very charming owner of the local night izakaya lives. This term usually refers to a night drinking establishment where people gather, usually after a night shift, and drink alcoholic beverages. The protagonist is the beautiful Mistia Lorelei, who has a dream to make the entire establishment the most popular in the city.</description></item><item><title>Cookie Clicker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cookie-clicker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cookie-clicker/</guid><description>Game Description Cookie Clicker lives up to its name. This is a clicker about earning cookies. The title is considered one of the first such games. The project developed and popularized an entire genre.
Initially it was a browser. Here is an improved version of Cookie Clicker. The re-release boasts an achievement system with 500 achievements, 600 improvements, the ability to exchange some goodies for others, and receiving constant upgrades. There are also mini-games here.</description></item><item><title>Cruelty Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Cruelty Squad is an immersive simulator that includes elements of stealth and first-person shooter. You will need to penetrate the depths of a high-tech corporation to stop its atrocities. A huge arsenal of weapons is available, including shotguns, darts, pistols, launchers and much more. The difficulty increases with each new stage. It is necessary to take part in intense firefights with a huge number of different enemies.
It is possible to emerge victorious from a fight without death.</description></item><item><title>Rise Eterna</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna/</guid><description>Game Description The story of Rise Eterna follows Lua as she attempts to uncover the secrets of her own origins. The gameplay combines tactical elements and RPG in a Japanese animated style. The user will assemble a squad of characters with special skills and characteristics. A squad can have up to 14 wards. The heroes will go through brutal battles, dungeons and boss encounters.
As the player progresses, he discovers a dark and mature story centered around the relationship between two lost souls.</description></item><item><title>Totally Accurate Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Totally Accurate Battle Simulator is a crazy tactical war game, heavily tied to physics. The battles take place in real time using weapons from different eras. The game is built on the laws of physics, so you can witness the most incredible combat in the history of video games!
One of the main features of the game is its caricature and the creation of the most insane atmosphere of battles.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Dyson Sphere Program</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dyson-sphere-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dyson-sphere-program/</guid><description>Game Description Dyson Sphere Program is a space simulator that allows you to develop your base and explore the galaxy. Go into the vastness of outer space to colonize distant planets. Build an intergalactic factory using the power of the stars. Design and plan production chains. Collect resources and develop your base. Start your journey as a small workshop and progress to the Dyson Sphere - a megastructure that orbits the stars.</description></item><item><title>Founders' Fortune</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/founders-fortune/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/founders-fortune/</guid><description>Game Description Founders' Fortune is a fantasy sim where, in addition to building and defending a base, you need to monitor the psychological state of the heroes. The colonists reach the island empty-handed to settle in a new place. By collecting resources, they build houses and various objects. Construction begins with walls and floors, after which furniture is placed and the façade is put in order.
Colonists are the main element of Founders' Fortune.</description></item><item><title>Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</guid><description>Game Description Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game is an adventure game in which the player is invited to travel around the world by car. The universe around the main character experienced a terrible apocalypse, turning into a desert. Graphically, the project is made using low-detail textures to create its own style. The locations where the gamer is present are created randomly thanks to the use of artificial intelligence in the process of generating territories, which is responsible for randomizing the environment.</description></item><item><title>Crusader Kings 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</guid><description>Game Description Crusader Kings 3 is a global strategy that significantly expands the capabilities of the previous part. Crusader Kings 3 covers the time period from 1066 to 1453. Unlike the second part, you won’t be able to start the game at any time. The new map stretches from Spain to Burma and Mongolia, and from Scandinavia to Central Africa. The scale of the game is quadrupled. The points on the map represent not only counties, but also baronial possessions.</description></item><item><title>Factorio</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</guid><description>Game Description The new planet should have everything to provide people with a comfortable, peaceful existence. Factorio is a sandbox in 2D graphics, where a new planet should be fully equipped for the future life of people. As soon as we arrive in a new place, we need to extract resources, assemble elements from them, and build structures so that people in the future can settle in and exist peacefully. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that the planet reacts aggressively to colonizers.</description></item><item><title>There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</guid><description>Game Description There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is a humorous adventure game where you have to click on every element available in the locations. You are taken on an amazing adventure through different video game universes. The visual style of the game is made in a 2D pixel style.
Each of the numerous characters in There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is voiced and played by professional actors. On your way there are many puzzles that need to be solved in an unconventional way.</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Polytopia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-battle-of-polytopia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-battle-of-polytopia/</guid><description>Game Description The Battle of Polytopia is a turn-based strategy game with city builder elements. The events of the game develop in the fictional world of Square. There are 12 factions to choose from, one of which you can start a campaign for. Lead your people to world domination by expanding your sphere of influence and exploring new technologies.
You will explore the surrounding lands, develop various technologies and collect useful materials, on the basis of which your base will develop.</description></item><item><title>Wobbly Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbly-life/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbly-life/</guid><description>Game Description Wobbly Life is a bright and dynamic sandbox that relies on an open world and body physics. The gameplay is tailored for local and online co-op. Team up with friends to compete in various mini-games and competitions. There is a single-player game aimed at developing your hero. Earn money and spend it on new skins, clothes, equipment and much more.
You will explore the vastness of Wobbly Island, controlling cute characters that resemble children&amp;rsquo;s toys.</description></item><item><title>Outer Wilds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outer-wilds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outer-wilds/</guid><description>Game Description Outer Wilds is a first-person action-adventure game based on the popular Groundhog Day theme. Events take place on the fictional planet Kamelok, which is destroyed by a star explosion 22 minutes after the start of the game. But the story is just beginning. The user finds himself in a “time loop”, which allows you to gradually develop the plot, travel through the planetary system and meet new characters. After a “reboot” of life, all accumulated information remains available.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Battles 4 Guadalcanal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carrier-battles-4-guadalcanal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carrier-battles-4-guadalcanal/</guid><description>Game Description Carrier Battles 4 Guadalcanal - Pacific War Naval Warfare dives into the air conflicts that unfolded in the Pacific during World War II. This strategy game puts you in the middle of the historical battles between the US and Japan in 1942-1943. Using a system of hexes and counters, the title tasks you with outflanking your opponent while defending critical areas or attacking key enemy positions. It&amp;rsquo;s all about decision making: when to strike, when to retreat, how to preserve your carriers and prevent the enemy from gaining a foothold.</description></item><item><title>The Test</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</guid><description>Game Description The Test is a psychological horror with elements of a visual novel, role-playing adventure, and immersive sim with a lot of text monologues inside the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s head. The player gets the opportunity to directly influence what is happening using a decision-making system of varying degrees of importance. The isometric camera allows you to get the best view of the two-dimensional space where all the action of the single-player campaign takes place with a well-developed plot about mental suffering.</description></item><item><title>Railroad Corporation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railroad-corporation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railroad-corporation/</guid><description>Game Description Railroad Corporation is a railway construction simulator. You have to build your own empire from numerous freight and passenger routes. The game takes place in North America in the 19th century. The gamer will have to master the road to new lands. The player needs to establish friendly relations with various foreign enterprises. Build your own factories and populate residential buildings.
From the very beginning you will only have a small amount of money.</description></item><item><title>Little Big Workshop</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-workshop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-workshop/</guid><description>Game Description Little Big Workshop is a meditation game with calm, measured gameplay. The passage begins very strangely, someone left a game with figures of little human workers on his desktop. And this someone begins to fantasize that these little men come to life, and work is in full swing in their toy workshop. It is the fantasies of the mysterious protagonist that gamers will have to watch.
The strategy will not give the player time to rest, because orders will immediately begin to arrive, and the virtual phone will be ringing off the hook with constant calls to it.</description></item><item><title>Oxygen Not Included</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</guid><description>Game Description The player&amp;rsquo;s task inOxygen Not Included is to obtain food, water, oxygen, valuable resources and happiness for the duplicates - the inhabitants of his colony. The world settled into different parts, because of this, half of the people went to other planets, and the second part called themselves duplicates and decided to travel through space, flying between asteroids.
The idea of ​​the most hardcore survival simulator in a strategic shell - Oxygen Not Included - shows that maintaining your own base and several people on it is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>People Playground</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/people-playground/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/people-playground/</guid><description>Game Description People Playground is an indie game, a kind of murder simulator in different ways. Here you can simply drag mannequins of creatures across the screen and throw them from a height, or create dangerous situations with your own hands - accidents, torture chambers, obstacle courses. There are 5 types of creatures available for destruction: a fragile person, a heavier and stronger robot, a gorse (spider), a regular and improved turret.</description></item><item><title>Total War: THREE KINGDOMS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Total War: THREE KINGDOMS is the first game in the series that recreates epic conflicts in Ancient China. The game combines a turn-based campaign of empire building and conquest with epic real-time battles. 190 AD. A beautiful but fragmented country awaits a new emperor and a new life. The player will have to unify China, create the next great dynasty and leave a legacy that will endure for millennia.</description></item><item><title>Construction Simulator 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/construction-simulator-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/construction-simulator-3/</guid><description>Game Description Construction Simulator 3 invites gamers into a detailed construction environment filled with tasks and responsibilities. An adventure game set in a quaint European town, you can participate in various construction projects. Gamers can choose from contracts to build roads, bridges, and even landscaping. The variety of contracts keeps the gameplay fresh and encourages you to explore different aspects of the construction industry.
Construction Simulator 3 features over 50 vehicles and machines from 14 different brands, giving users plenty to choose from as they expand their operations.</description></item><item><title>Wushu Chronicles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wushu-chronicles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wushu-chronicles/</guid><description>Game Description Wushu Chronicles is an adventure role-playing game that invites you to explore the vast expanses of an open eastern world. Events take place during the early Ming Dynasty. The story begins in the 25th year of Hongwu&amp;rsquo;s reign and continues until the Battle of Jingnan. You have to explore the world of Ming Wushu, which is filled with numerous activities and interesting quests.
There are two dozen factions that you are free to join.</description></item><item><title>Unheard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unheard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unheard/</guid><description>Game Description Unheard is a well-developed detective simulator with many implemented mechanics aimed at allowing the player to understand the crimes committed in various ways. A team of indie developers worked on the project, with a rather unusual idea and implementation, who decided to use the setting of detective fiction, because the protagonist uses devices that are not available in the real world. The devices make it possible to establish some kind of invisible connection between criminals and lawmen.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay ofSpace Engineers is that you will build space stations, ships, and begin to study neighboring planets and passing asteroids, where you will find many useful resources. Control is carried out from the perspective of a person, a ship, a base, a flying station, and you can change the camera view from both the third and first person.
When you create a world, the game automatically generates a random sequence of planets on which you can find valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency: Sandstorm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency: Sandstorm is a sequel to a multiplayer shooter built on deathmatches in confined spaces, with the ability to use light vehicles. The game has been significantly improved and expanded. The key to victory lies only through well-coordinated teamwork.
The action takes place in the Middle East, on the ruins of settlements and military bases. You need to carefully choose your weapon and explore the territory, because without caution and tactics you can quickly catch a bullet in the forehead.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Two Crows</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Two Crowns is a cooperative microstrategy that tells about the brave, who has become a king and now he needs to gather his army. Having saddled the right horse, he goes on a long journey to expand the kingdom. He will be opposed by the army of greed, trying to take everything from him that he has set up with his own labor. The game offers to rush not only in European medieval landscapes, but also to see many radically new ones.</description></item><item><title>Kenshi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</guid><description>Game Description Kenshi forces you to survive from the very first minutes of the game. An impressive RPG with an open world and the ability to create your own squad, the remaining player privileges are gradually revealed to us. For example, you can build your own buildings in any location, conquer them from other factions, create your own business, sell goods in peaceful settlements, craft whatever you want, explore the environment and do whatever you want.</description></item><item><title>RimWorld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city planning and strategic base development on a planet unknown to the player. The player inRimWorld must build a base where the last forces of people are concentrated. To survive, get food, study the technology tree and understand what the planet wants from you is the main task of the player. The project itself is characterized by the enormous depth of built mechanics that you can apply to your buildings and the base as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Construction Simulator 2 US - Pocket Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/construction-simulator-2-us-pocket-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/construction-simulator-2-us-pocket-edition/</guid><description>Game Description An urban planning simulator, the basis of which is the construction of roads under contracts, introduces us to the business of a small construction company that purchases equipment, vehicles and materials for successful career advancement among other companies. What is required from the player? Following plot contracts, the completion of which leads to enrichment and the purchase of new equipment. Construction Simulator 2 US - Pocket Edition offers us more than 40 units of construction vehicles from the following companies: Kenworth, Caterpillar, Kipper, Liebherr, MEILLER, Palfinger, Mack Trucks, Bell and others.</description></item><item><title>Liftoff: FPV Drone Racing</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff FPV Drone Racing is a training ground for quadcopter pilots. The game is a training ground for both beginners and an obstacle course for experienced gamers. Professionals can test their strength in a new environment, and people who have recently become interested in this sport can hone their skills before taking on real prototypes.
In Liftoff FPV Drone Racing, users can take their first steps towards the sport of quadcopter racing.</description></item><item><title>Football, Tactics &amp; Glory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/football-tactics-amp-glory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/football-tactics-amp-glory/</guid><description>Game Description Football, Tactics &amp;amp; Glory is a football team management simulator with strategy elements. As a coach, the player will need to identify the weaknesses and strengths of his opponent in order to identify unique tactics. With the help of a well-chosen strategy, you can defeat even a stronger opponent. Each match is like a puzzle where you need to find the key that helps you win. Each athlete on the field is a unique character, and you can even develop a relationship with each of them.</description></item><item><title>House Flipper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/house-flipper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/house-flipper/</guid><description>Game Description A renovation crew simulator in which you take on the role of the boss and the only employee -House Flipper - allows you to destroy beautiful houses, but build beautiful apartments with amazing renovations in their place. In this game you can make rooms the way you see them in your life. The game also encourages you to use the latest repair tools, but one thing remains unchanged: you&amp;rsquo;ll have to take down walls with a sledgehammer!</description></item><item><title>Conan Exiles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</guid><description>Game Description Conan Exiles is an amazing multiplayer survival game with RPG and action elements. Employees of the Norwegian company Funcom worked on the project. The project was released at the end of spring 2018. Stunning graphics are a rare quality that developers of various MMORPG games pay attention to. But this time everything happened exactly the opposite. Funcom, 10 years before Conan Exiles, had already released a similar game called Age Of Conan.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk is an economic strategy game, a simulator of city construction in extremely harsh climatic conditions, where there are no wars, but there is a main enemy in the form of global cooling. The employees of the main office of 11 bit studios worked on the creation of this project. The official release of the game took place in April 2018.
In technical terms, we have a three-dimensional strategy game, with a top-down view, a simulator of the leader of a surviving human population in the Arctic cold.</description></item><item><title>Pure Rock Crawling</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pure-rock-crawling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pure-rock-crawling/</guid><description>Game Description Pure Rock Crawling is an SUV simulator, the main concept of which is built around a realistic simulation of tires and suspension. The developers set a goal to create the most realistic ride on rocky paths, deserts, hills, etc. A meditative ride through the stones is one of the best ways to experience the adventure of the wild lands of the entire planet.
At first glance, the task in Pure Rock Crawling is extremely simple: drive through 10 gates consisting of cones to get along a designated route from one point on the map to another.</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>VTOL VR</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vtol-vr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vtol-vr/</guid><description>Game Description VTOL VR is a military flight simulator with a first-person view and in the surroundings of the near future. The game requires a VR headset and a motion controller. The title allows you to freely rotate your head while sitting in the virtual cockpit. Modes include training, campaign and free flight. There are a lot of tasks here. In addition to other aircraft, ships, tanks, anti-aircraft and artillery installations act as opponents and allies.</description></item><item><title>Slime Rancher</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slime-rancher/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slime-rancher/</guid><description>Game Description A funny open-world first-person shooter -Slime Rancher is a mixture of genres in one complex picture, which the developers called - Boundless Outland. We plunge into a special experimental environment. Our hero&amp;rsquo;s name is Beatrix LeBeau, and he is a farmer. Armed with courage, madness and a funny vacuum cleaner, he decides to stay on the planet of the Boundless Outlands, because a certain Hobson Twillgers left us his farm.</description></item><item><title>The Long Dark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</guid><description>Game Description A game about survival in a world without electricity. The Long Dark is eternal darkness in locations, gorgeous graphics from developers who love the sky and stars as their second home. Players were pleased that the entire gameplay is divided into two modes. The first is a story-based passage of 5 episodes, the total duration of which is 60-70 hours, depending on how the plot is followed. The second mode is survival in an excellent open world, where you will have to keep an eye on the contents of your backpack, check for items, collect skins, fry meat, take refuge in shelters, furnish your own house or a small corner in a house for survivors, where the owner of this establishment will shelter you.</description></item><item><title>Ravenfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</guid><description>Game Description The team-tactical shooterRavenfield will allow you to plunge into furious battles, where you have everything - from tanks to fleets. There is a complete lack of storyline and even multiplayer. The latter fact is extremely unusual for projects of this genre. It would seem that it is interesting to play against bots and when there are no real users on the map. This omission at first glance is more than compensated for by a fairly developed artificial intelligence - opponents and allies behave extremely intelligently and together with them you can perform a variety of tactics using numerous commands and options.</description></item><item><title>theHunter: Call of the Wild</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</guid><description>Game Description The Hunter&amp;rsquo;s Open World is now available intheHunter: Call of the Wild. This is not a simple hunter simulator, where we will have to climb trees and hide in the grass to kill the next deer, but a full-fledged world with smells, changing wind and weather; with the individual behavior of each animal that must be killed to complete the task. This is not a simple hunt, but a real one!</description></item><item><title>ASTRONER</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astroneer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astroneer/</guid><description>Game Description New resources inASTRONEER are presented in the form of any discovery on other planets, and everything that a person could bring with him after a galactic expedition was bought up at a clean price. There was an explosion in the world. Humanity is again hunting for “gold”, sending its compatriots into space. However, in the 25th century, when humanity has fully explored space, they send people to distant planets, where all that is known is that the planets are just as round.</description></item><item><title>Sid Meiers Civilization 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-6/</guid><description>Game Description A turn-based strategy from famous developers -Sid Meier&amp;rsquo;s Civilization VI, where the player&amp;rsquo;s main goal is to develop his own settlement from a small group of people. They build cities, become diplomats, politicians, officials, and make scientific achievements. The population of your city, and then the state, is gradually increasing, and you are moving towards capturing the land around you. Together with allies or alone, you fight against opponents controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>No Man's Sky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</guid><description>Game Description Travel on an intergalactic level has become too simple and ordinary. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly difficult to create a game that captivates with its graphics, but the developers ofNo Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky, an indie adventure game with an open world and a wonderful RPG base, were able to recreate the image of space. Distant, limitless, completely open and so human.
We play as a character, but then our gameplay switches to an entire space station or ship.</description></item><item><title>Human: Fall Flat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/human-fall-flat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/human-fall-flat/</guid><description>Game Description Human: Fall Flat is an adventure puzzle game with amazing physics and engine. Take control of Bob, who every time has a dream from which he must find a way out. Usually such dreams are accompanied by colorful locations in which he needs to get to a certain point and solve many difficult problems.
Explore the open world in your own way. Climb any building, rock, tree or other object, going through the same place differently each time.</description></item><item><title>VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</guid><description>Game Description VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action is an adventure simulator of a bartender in the setting of a dystopian future, where humanity finds itself under the control of huge corporations dictating the rules of life, and nanorobots controlling every area of ​​human activity and the implementation of laws and regulations adopted new world government. Stylistically, this project refers to Japanese games of the last century. The gameplay consists of communicating with bar visitors and providing them with high-quality service in order to build warm, friendly relationships with them.</description></item><item><title>Hearts of Iron 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the fact thatHearts of Iron 4 is famous for its realism, the new part has completely redesigned the focus tree for individual countries and nationalities. The strategy, dedicated to the Second World War, invites you to play in countries such as Italy, Ethiopia, Spain, Japan and China. Two scenarios that differ in their dates: 1936 and 1939. In one of them you will take part in the Second Italo-Ethiopian War and the Spanish Civil War, and in the second you will see how Japan invaded China, and the Second World War was fought.</description></item><item><title>Stellaris</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellaris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellaris/</guid><description>Game Description Real-time strategy -Stellaris - immerses us in outer space, where we become kings of the galaxy from the very first minutes. The gameplay surrounds you with a huge number of ships and their types. For example, merchant spaceships will travel between different planets and sell/buy resources, reconnaissance ships will be able to explore new distances, and construction ships will help occupy - for friendly purposes - a new planet and recreate an entire empire on it.</description></item><item><title>Street Legal Racing: Redline</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</guid><description>Game Description Street Legal Racing: Redline is a car mechanic simulator that allows you to assemble a car completely from scratch. At the same time, street racing with assembled vehicles is available. New parts can affect the characteristics of the car, which are responsible for acceleration, handling and maximum speed. Street Legal Racing does not provide package upgrades. The rider must install each individual part himself.
The game has many features:</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve Together is a survival simulator in an unknown world, where our character, pre-selected in the editor, wakes up and immediately goes to look for firewood, because Maxwell said so. The game is cooperative, since the story passage is divided into 2 parts. The first is survival. It is built on three phases of the day: day, evening and night.
During the day, your character calmly survives, collects items, crafts new ones, eats and carries out orders for Maxwell.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</guid><description>Game Description The gameHot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades can be called a full-fledged weapons simulator. You need to go to the training ground, which contains a huge selection of different firearms: pistols, machine guns, shotguns, rocket launchers, grenades, etc. You can use any available ammunition, training on targets and taking the highest positions on the leaderboard. Afterwards you can go and set off fireworks.
Targets can be not only static within the walls of a gray pavilion, but also moving in open space.</description></item><item><title>Stardew Valley</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardew-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardew-valley/</guid><description>Game Description Stardew Valley is a sandbox simulator with pixel graphics and multi-platform support, but with a well-thought-out system for earning money and maintaining game balance for the player. The beginning of the game shows how our hero first comes to an abandoned farm, which he received from a deceased relative. Since the protagonist does not mind making money by planting and selling vegetables and fruits, he decides not to sell the farm, but to start equipping it.</description></item><item><title>American Truck Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/american-truck-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/american-truck-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description American Truck Simulator doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the typical pick-up-and-drop-off. This is a strategic and economic simulator rolled into one: we will upgrade our trucks, buy new ones, decide which contracts to take on and what to leave aside. An important component in the process is the driving itself, because it is done in the first person, from the driver’s cabin. Compliance with all traffic rules is the basis and responsibility of every driver.</description></item><item><title>Scrap Mechanic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</guid><description>Game Description Scrap Mechanic is a multiplayer engineering sandbox that offers you to design various mechanisms and compete with friends. The game world revolves around a mechanic who maintains robots on an agricultural planet. He makes sure that they are working properly: that they are cultivating the land on time, sowing, collecting raw materials, which the hero then sends to the central planets, where people live ordinary lives. But one day the spaceship crashed, and the robots around went crazy.</description></item><item><title>The Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</guid><description>Game Description The island on whichThe Isle takes place has a rich and varied environment that is randomly generated. All artifacts, items and events will be located in different places with each new launch. Players must team up to effectively explore the area, which contains many secrets, including various quest items that further advance the plot. The map contains an area of ​​16x16 square kilometers. Multiplayer survival game The Isle allows you to play with three different factions in three different modes:</description></item><item><title>Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes/</guid><description>Game Description Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes is a cooperative sapper simulator. You are locked up with your friends. No one knows where the explosives are, but instructions are issued on how to disarm them. They must verbally explain what elements the bomb consists of and ensure that the player, acting as a sapper, can defuse it.
Each round will be quite intense. Everything depends only on the correct and competent relationship between the participants.</description></item><item><title>BeamNG drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</guid><description>Game Description BeamNG.drive is a car simulator that simulates the behavior of cars during collisions. Excellent physics, realistic controls and spectacular accidents are the main features of the game. The simulator allows you to find out what the consequences will be if, for example, the steering wheel of a Ferrari jams and the car flies into the oncoming lane, where it collides with a 40-ton truck. Or assess the damage to an army jeep whose brakes jammed when it was going down a hill at a speed of 90 km/h, flew off the road and crashed into a tree.</description></item><item><title>Kerbal Space Program</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kerbal-space-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kerbal-space-program/</guid><description>Game Description In the space simulatorKerbal Space Program the player will lead the Kerbal race exploring the vastness of space. Be the one who guides them towards a brighter future, inventing new technologies, constructing many new mechanisms and helping in the exploration of the galaxy.
Start your journey in one of three modes. In “Career” you will need to monitor the education and training of your charges, as well as help in modernizing their devices.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</guid><description>Game Description Elite Dangerous is an online multiplayer game, the third part of the &amp;ldquo;Elite&amp;rdquo; franchise, which began in 1984. The player is given complete freedom to explore and travel, and has the opportunity to influence the storyline. The action takes place thousands of years later in the distant future on the territory of several million star galaxies. Most of the stars, planets, asteroids and other cosmic bodies that exist in the real world.</description></item><item><title>Cities: Skylines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</guid><description>Game Description The city-planning simulator -Cities: Skylines - is in the best traditions of the real game, in which its own physical laws were created to transfer them into gaming reality. On the territory of your new city, it will be taken into account that the profile road is built in one way, and the road at the airport - in another. It will count if you correctly lay the pipeline for the heating system, and also if you can show people that they live in a real paradise, and not just a metropolis where they want to buy them at the expense of shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa is a car simulator developed based on test drives of cars using a model of real behavior. Includes both single player and multiplayer modes.
The developers presented a variety of licensed cars and tracks, which were specially digitized specifically for the race to convey maximum authenticity to their prototypes. The machines can be customized to your individual taste, because&amp;hellip; the creators have added an extensive set of settings and support for modifications.</description></item><item><title>This War of Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</guid><description>Game Description This War of Mine is a cross-platform platformer game with elements of survival for an entire group of people. At the beginning of the game, you are given several characters to control the group, and you develop them depending on the time of day. During the day, the characters live in a house located in a city besieged by rebels. They arrange their everyday life, help each other, perform joint tasks and craft the necessary items.</description></item><item><title>Project Zomboid</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</guid><description>Game Description Project Zomboid is a cross-platform game in which we will have to find a house, equip it, and start surviving in a world where a zombie apocalypse has recently occurred. We are located in Knox County. The latest epidemic infected more than 90% of the district&amp;rsquo;s residents, and they all became zombies. Difficult conditions will force us to survive, stock up on food, water, weapons and all available supplies in order to simply survive.</description></item><item><title>Arma 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</guid><description>Game Description InArma 3 we regain our independence by playing as a neutral side of this war. Inside the universe of the third Arma - 2030. Key opponents are still fighting for independence in economic and commodity terms. Among the enemies, a new structural organization CSAT appears, acting as a military-political alliance. While the crisis rages in Europe, the United States is at odds with China in the Pacific.
More than 400 square kilometers of gaming space, where the player, playing the role of a NATO peacekeeper, will save his group from real traitors who show themselves at the beginning of the story campaign.</description></item><item><title>Total War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</guid><description>Game Description InTotal War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition we are allowed to play as one of Caesar&amp;rsquo;s three followers. This is Octavian, the adopted son of a former ruler who is obliged to become the ruler of Rome; Mark Antony is Caesar&amp;rsquo;s loyal friend and best military leader; and Lepidus, the man through whom Caesar achieved universal recognition. After Caesar was killed, chaos erupted within the Roman Empire. The foreign policy of the empire maintained proper balance, while civil war was taking place inside, and the territory was divided into three parts.</description></item><item><title>Europa Universalis 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/europa-universalis-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/europa-universalis-4/</guid><description>Game Description A new part of the real-time strategyEuropa Universalis 4, the multiplayer mode of which allows up to 32 people to play on one server. Based on the previous parts, we can say that there are no more spies in the game, since they upset the overall balance of the game. The magistrate system has also changed greatly as the city&amp;rsquo;s development has undergone significant changes. The trading system has improved the most.</description></item><item><title>Papers, Please</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/papers-please/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/papers-please/</guid><description>Game Description The fictional country of Arstotzka is a small world of the game’s protagonist, where he will check documents at customs every day. The plot ofPapers, Please - a puzzle game with an unusual approach and graphics, as well as the beginning of the simulator - shows the events with the main character winning the profession of a customs officer at a checkpoint in the lottery. His task will be to check documents and apply stamps.</description></item><item><title>Company of Heroes 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</guid><description>Game Description The events ofCompany of Heroes 2 unfold before us in snowy Norilsk, where one of the largest Stalinist Gulags is located. NKVD officer Churkin comes here, who understands that he will not survive the next Stalinist purge of officers. In the Gulag he finds his comrade from the front, who is serving his sentence and preparing to be shot. Isakovich is the name of the character, he wrote a tome with the real actions of the commanders of the Red Army, for which he was sentenced to death.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve is an adventure arcade game in the action strategy genre with crafting elements. This game is an interesting survival simulator with a complete open game world. The plot tells us about the main character who was sailing on a ship and was shipwrecked. He woke up on an abandoned island. You will travel a lot through beautiful locations that were drawn by hand. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin to explore previously unknown living creatures and the remains of bygone times.</description></item><item><title>Euro Truck Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/euro-truck-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/euro-truck-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description The basis ofEuro Truck Simulator 2 is permanent contracts that will be stolen from under your nose by more experienced players controlled by artificial intelligence. Long routes to the capital of Germany, the Netherlands, England, France and Belgium are your main route when traveling with dangerous or simply expensive cargo. The main task of the driver is to deliver on time, deliver in good condition and not get caught with a fine.</description></item><item><title>FTL: Faster Than Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</guid><description>Game Description FTL: Faster Than Light - this project is a two-dimensional simulator of a space combat ship. The creation and publication of this media product was carried out by the Subset Games studio. The official release took place in the first half of autumn 2012. The gameplay is based on the interaction between the player and the crew of the combat starship.
The success of this space tactical strategy will depend on how successful this cooperation is.</description></item><item><title>Sid Meier's Civilization 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-5/</guid><description>Game Description Sid Meier&amp;rsquo;s Civilization V is a strategy game with an RTS style, where we still build a civilization from primitive times to the present. You can choose from 18 strong powers of this world, within which you can add 7 wonders of the world, put in control a leader who has individual characteristics, and also does everything in his own way. The legendary turn-based strategy series introduces us to the sequel, in which a huge number of additional areas have been added.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade: Warband</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</guid><description>Game Description Mount &amp;amp; Blade: Warband is a standalone add-on that brings many improvements and innovations to the game. New textures, object and character models, as well as sophisticated visualization settings. Change FSAA anti-aliasing, tone mapping and other effects in the settings. Modernized animations, improved combat system and the spirit of the heroes. People will flee if they are in imminent danger or, conversely, fight to the last if their morality is high.</description></item><item><title>Garry's Mod</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</guid><description>Game Description Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod is a game and physics sandbox. The main game mode is aimless and provides the player with a freely customizable world powered by the Source engine. The player creates non-player characters with various interaction objects. Special tools and tools allow you to construct new objects in reality, fix beams, iron, objects. Changing facial expressions is also available.
Thanks to the flexible engine, users create their own modifications: Spacebuild, Wiremod, Elevator: Source, DarkRP, Prop Hunt and others.</description></item><item><title>STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</guid><description>Game Description STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack is a collection of real-time strategies based on the Star Wars plot. You will play the role of an army manager on one of the sides in an intergalactic civil war. Command units of the Empire, Rebels, Republic or other civilizations.
In Star Wars Empire at War, you will command your team, completing tasks and freeing planets from enemies. Visit Tatooine, Kashyyyk, Dagobah or other hot spots in the galaxy.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment,Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Stronghold Crusader HD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-hd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-hd/</guid><description>Game Description A real-time strategy with an in-depth system for leveling up your settlement -Stronghold Crusader HD - was released with an addition that allows you to display the picture on a large screen with good quality. The basis of the game remains the same: we develop, build a large army, attack the enemy, whoever he is, win and move on. **The game has 4 historical campaigns, which are divided into stages in history.</description></item><item><title>AGRONOM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/agronom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/agronom/</guid><description>Game Description AGRONOM sends players to 22nd century Mars to build a working estate. You arrive on a specific piece of Martian land with a specific task. This mission involves creating a living space designed to fulfill the wishes of Grandfather Makar and dedicated to the memory of his late wife Sofia. The idea extends beyond the simple construction of buildings, seeking to recreate the atmosphere symbolized by pancakes with plum jam, pickled cucumbers and home-made moonshine.</description></item><item><title>Cultist Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultist-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultist-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Cultist Simulator is a role-playing card game that allows you to create your own unique card deck. The plot tells us about a magical world, in which they give the opportunity to find out all the mysterious and mysterious events that happened in the real world. You can go fight witches, find Masons and go in search of other adventures.
At the very beginning, gamers have the opportunity to choose starting cards, and then start completing missions and exploring a huge text world.</description></item><item><title>Soulmask</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</guid><description>Game Description Soulmask is a mystical twist on the survival genre. Gamers eschew the usual &amp;ldquo;rags&amp;rdquo; and instead awaken clutching an ancient mask after a near-death experience. This relic is more than just a creepy wall decoration, it&amp;rsquo;s a game changer. Angry weather and wild animals won&amp;rsquo;t be your only problem. Soulmask features a vast open world that you must navigate in order to survive. Gathering resources is a must, but you can&amp;rsquo;t do it alone.</description></item></channel></rss>