<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Action on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/action/</link><description>Recent content in Action on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enigma of Fear</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enigma-of-fear/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enigma-of-fear/</guid><description>Game Description Enigma of Fear is a title that puts gamers in the shoes of Mia, a paranormal investigator on a personal mission: to find her missing father. Finding themselves in the Perimeter, a place that exists outside of reality, Mia and her dog Loopy are plunged into the unknown, where nothing is as it seems. The Perimeter is shrouded in mystery, filled with strange happenings, sinister creatures and a web of secrets that Mia must unravel.</description></item><item><title>One Boss One Fight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-boss-one-fight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-boss-one-fight/</guid><description>Game Description In One Boss One Fight players face one unforgiving enemy - Death. From the moment you enter the arena, every decision, every dodge and every blow becomes a matter of survival. This roguelike is built around one intense fight where the stakes couldn&amp;rsquo;t be higher. Death is not just an adversary, it is a force of nature, adapting and evolving with each stage. Combat unfolds in multiple layers, each more complex than the last, requiring precision and adaptation from even the most experienced players.</description></item><item><title>Snow Bros. Wonderland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-bros-wonderland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-bros-wonderland/</guid><description>Game Description Snow Bros. Wonderland is a new adventure of the beloved snowman duo Nick and Tom. This time around, the classic gameplay has been updated with a 3D isometric perspective, offering players new ways to interact with the icy world. The core mechanics remain the same: shoot ice pellets, turn enemies into snowballs, and send them flying to destroy everything in their path. Large bosses have appeared in the game, and to clear their path you will need a strategic chain of snowballs.</description></item><item><title>Renaissance Kingdom Wars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/renaissance-kingdom-wars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/renaissance-kingdom-wars/</guid><description>Game Description Renaissance Kingdom Wars is a rich blend of grand strategy and real-time strategy set against the backdrop of 1510. At the beginning of the game, you have nothing but a name - you are just a mercenary captain with dreams of greatness. Rise through the ranks, from lord to king, and make your mark on a vast world spanning Europe, Africa and the Middle East.
The main thing in Renaissance Kingdom Wars is making strategic decisions.</description></item><item><title>Void Crew</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-crew/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-crew/</guid><description>Game Description Void Crew invites you to go on an exciting journey through space with your crew members. In this high-stakes interstellar odyssey, teamwork is paramount as you and your friends face the challenges of deep space together. You will find yourself at the helm of a modern spaceship, which will rush through outer space, performing the most ordinary tasks. Asteroid storms, solar flares and random mistakes by crew members - there is never a dull moment in the game.</description></item><item><title>ATLYSS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atlyss/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atlyss/</guid><description>Game Description ATLYSS is an open world RPG adventure game that introduces gamers to a vast and surreal universe. It is filled with a variety of creatures and mysterious locations, inviting users to explore every corner of it. Users can choose how they interact with the world: collaborate with others or cope with difficulties alone. The dynamic nature allows them to adapt their style, fostering a sense of responsibility for their experiences.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Clawler</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Clawler brings a fresh twist to the roguelike formula. It combines the familiar thrills of dungeon crawling with claw machine mechanics that put a twist on traditional gameplay. You navigate treacherous environments, but instead of directly grabbing weapons and armor, you rely on the claw to get you the loot you need. This adds strategic thinking, because every item you take out of the car can play a decisive role in the next battle or encounter.</description></item><item><title>Dark Honor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-honor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-honor/</guid><description>Game Description Dark Honor puts gamers in the shoes of a lone warrior on a path of revenge, navigating a dark world defined by a ruthless samurai tribe. The plot sets the stage for a personal quest imbued with the promise of retribution as the protagonist hunts down those responsible for deep personal loss. During this journey, combat comes to the fore, forcing users to learn the intricacies of its advanced system.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl is a first-person shooter in a post-apocalyptic world. The events of the game will develop in the exclusion zone formed as a result of the disaster at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. In 2006, a new catastrophe occurred, which led to various physical, chemical and biological processes, creating many anomalies, artifacts and generating a large number of mutants.
The gameplay is a classic FPS with elements of a role-playing game, immersive sim and horror.</description></item><item><title>RAM: Random Access Mayhem</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ram-random-access-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ram-random-access-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description RAM: Random Access Mayhem is a roguelike shooter that takes a familiar concept and turns it into something chaotic and strategic. In a world filled with bizarre robots, gamers take on the role of a disembodied AI programmed to wreak havoc. Unlike typical shooters, the adventure game features new mechanics: you control and switch between eight different types of enemies, each with their own unique abilities. This twist not only keeps the action fresh, but also requires quick thinking and strategy as you progress through increasingly difficult levels.</description></item><item><title>Incantation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incantation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incantation/</guid><description>Game Description Incantation is a first-person horror game that immerses gamers in the eerie world of Chen Village, where danger and mystery are never left behind. As the main character, a mother desperately searching for her missing daughter, users will have to navigate the web of secrets, rituals and cults that seem to seep from every crack in the village walls. The plot unfolds gradually, and with each step more and more information is revealed about the strange forces operating in the village.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Command is a strategy with elements of a bagel and a card game. You need to collect resources, form a unique deck of cards and fight against robots. When gathering an army, you need to study the enemy&amp;rsquo;s tactics in order to deal a crushing blow to him. While exploring locations, you need to obtain resources to build buildings and hire units. There are factories, auxiliary buildings, turrets and special weapons of mass destruction.</description></item><item><title>420BLAZEIT 2: GAME OF THE YEAR - Dank Dreams and Goated Memes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/420blazeit-2-game-of-the-year-dank-dreams-and-goated-memes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/420blazeit-2-game-of-the-year-dank-dreams-and-goated-memes/</guid><description>Game Description 420BLAZEIT 2: GAME OF THE YEAR - Dank Dreams and Goated Memes is a first-person shooter that stands out for its wild premise and unpredictable gameplay. The story follows a former Secret Service agent who leaves behind a life of danger and intrigue to pursue a quieter existence as an artist. However, peace does not last long. The agent is soon forced back into action to save memes from the clutches of the Illuminati, a shadowy organization that seems intent on controlling the internet&amp;rsquo;s most valuable content.</description></item><item><title>Space Trash Scavenger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</guid><description>Game Description Space Trash Scavenger takes place in a future where humanity has reached for the stars and survival means using what others have left behind. Here, gamers take on the role of scavengers operating in a galaxy littered with the rubble of an ancient conflict. The journey begins with a space drill - a multi-purpose node floating among the remains of abandoned ships, forgotten outposts and asteroid fields. This is not just a shelter, but a factory, equipped with critical systems for agriculture, defense and waste processing - all necessary to turn interstellar waste into something valuable.</description></item><item><title>TIME SOUL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/time-soul/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/time-soul/</guid><description>Game Description TIME SOUL is an action-platformer with a unique approach to the usual souls-like genre. In a universe where time is both weapon and enemy, gamers will battle through procedurally generated worlds filled with treacherous platforms, unexpected obstacles and formidable enemies. Moving forward, users will fight with the guardians of time, collect fragments and clocks, trying to prevent the complete collapse of time. It&amp;rsquo;s a race against time, literally, as the ultimate goal is to defeat the Time Lord within a limited time of 60 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Beyond The Darkness</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-darkness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-darkness/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond The Darkness is an adventure game that immerses gamers in a world of ghostly memories and disturbing experiences. The game follows the story of Millie, a young girl whose family mysteriously disappeared. Her journey takes her through several eerie, memory-based worlds, each more complex and disturbing than the last. The narrative revolves around Millie&amp;rsquo;s quest to discover the truth about her family&amp;rsquo;s fate while at the same time confronting the nightmares that seem to manifest themselves in the very fabric of her memories.</description></item><item><title>Bullet Runner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</guid><description>Game Description The dynamic shootouts in Bullet Runner show the adventures of a pixelated man who is forced to resist against a crowd of evil opponents. The game is a top-down action shooter where you have to fight with various opponents. The project is filled with fast and active gameplay, where users can test the speed of their reaction to current events. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to move around the map and shoot enemies using a wide arsenal of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Codex Lost</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/codex-lost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/codex-lost/</guid><description>Game Description Codex Lost is an open-world role-playing adventure game that immerses gamers in a realm where magic, mystery and danger intertwine. Against the backdrop of a fractured world, users take on the role of the Guardian, a figure tasked with finding stolen grimoires and saving a reality on the brink of collapse. The stakes are high and the journey is filled with challenges, but what really sets the title apart is its focus on freedom, discovery and strategic combat.</description></item><item><title>LEGO Horizon Adventures</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lego-horizon-adventures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lego-horizon-adventures/</guid><description>Game Description LEGO Horizon Adventures takes gamers on a whimsical journey through a future made entirely of LEGO bricks. Forget lush greenery and jagged rocks - even the colossal dinosaur-like machines that roam the earth are carefully sculpted from colorful bricks. Developed by Guerrilla Games and Studio Gobo, this action-adventure game takes inspiration from the critically acclaimed Horizon Zero Dawn. Take the place of Aloy, a curious girl raised by the stern but kind huntsman Rost.</description></item><item><title>Little Big Adventure – Twinsen's Quest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-adventure-twinsens-quest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-adventure-twinsens-quest/</guid><description>Game Description Little Big Adventure – Twinsen&amp;rsquo;s Quest, a reimagining of the classic adventure game, opens up new horizons of exciting virtual travel. This is a unique opportunity to plunge into a completely new world, full of exciting effects, rich musical compositions and deep gameplay mechanics.
According to the plot, you have to go on a journey with Twinsen, an ordinary inhabitant of the Citadel Island. His calm life changes after a disturbing dream about the end of his planet and a meeting with the forbidden goddess Sendell, after which our hero finds himself imprisoned in a psychiatric clinic.</description></item><item><title>PARKOUR CIVILIZATION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parkour-civilization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parkour-civilization/</guid><description>Game Description Parkour Civilization invites players into a high-stakes world where every jump or wall run tests their accuracy and timing. At its core, the game challenges you to master increasingly difficult parkour tracks. Every successful jump propels you forward, and every fall serves as a reminder of the unforgiving nature of this fast-paced environment. The path from beginner to expert comes through practice, persistence, and the willingness to accept failure as part of the process.</description></item><item><title>Shave and Stuff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</guid><description>Game Description In Shave and Stuff, gamers find themselves in a lively and practical simulator, where two roles come to the fore - a hairdresser and a tattoo artist. The title combines hairdressing and paint work, which promotes creativity and experimentation. Whether performing precision cutting tasks or plunging into the complex world of body art, users are immersed in a world of tools, techniques and client preferences. A constant flow of tasks and light humor provide the basis for an original approach to customization and self-expression.</description></item><item><title>XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</guid><description>Game Description XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION transports gamers to a high-octane world where the classic game of pinball meets hostile forces for an intense blend of arcade action. The adventure follows the path of its predecessor, Demon&amp;rsquo;s Tilt, and brings familiar gameplay mechanics while adding many new challenges. Each new table offers a new set of obstacles, targets and bonuses that force users to be on their guard. Pinball here is not just about throwing a ball, it is a battle against time, enemies and your own reflexes.</description></item><item><title>Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</guid><description>Game Description Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is a naval combat game in which you control two warring factions: NATO forces and representatives of the Warsaw Pact. Take part in the naval conflicts of the 80s. Control a huge number of different ships, use all modern types of weapons and technologies. Your main task in Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is to defeat the enemy army.</description></item><item><title>HeistGeist</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</guid><description>Game Description HeistGeist immerses gamers in the cyberpunk universe, putting them in the shoes of Alexandra, a cunning thief who overcomes the consequences of a failed mission. The title revolves around the challenge of assembling a diverse team of specialists to carry out complex heists. Each heist presents tactical obstacles and opportunities, turning each mission into a unique puzzle. Users take part in battles based on a card-based battle system that brings an innovative twist to the traditional strategy genre.</description></item><item><title>Locuras en el Banverso</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</guid><description>Game Description Locuras en el Banaverso is a single-player platformer that takes gamers on a chaotic adventure through a bizarre multiverse. The game follows the eccentric YouTuber El Bananero, who not only plays the role of the main character, but also voices him. From the very beginning, El Bananero finds himself in an unexpected situation - he is kidnapped by none other than Santa Claus and his gang of henchmen. As fate would have it, the kidnapping turns into an escape through a portal that leads him into the depths of the multiverse.</description></item><item><title>Terror of the Seven Seas</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</guid><description>Game Description Terror of the Seven Seas is a game that immerses gamers in the complex maritime life of an era of exploration and piracy. The game takes place in a vast open world and offers a wide range of entertainment - from participating in large-scale naval battles to treasure hunting. Users take on the roles of various characters, each with their own unique responsibilities and abilities. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a captain leading a ship through stormy seas, an officer commanding a crew, a merchant transporting goods across vast oceans, or an explorer reaching into the unknown, there is something for every type of adventurer.</description></item><item><title>Gods Wars: Infinity Epic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gods-wars-infinity-epic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gods-wars-infinity-epic/</guid><description>Game Description Gods Wars: Infinity Epic is a pixelated roguelike that invites gamers into a world filled with relentless combat, strategic decision-making and rich customization. From the very beginning, the adventure game offers significant flexibility, allowing gamers to create their characters according to their playstyle and preferences. The plot is simple and at the same time fascinating: users will have to overcome waves of monsters, defeat powerful bosses and ultimately challenge the formidable evil gods.</description></item><item><title>Metal Slug Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description The Metal Slug Tactics player chooses his warriors to create a suitable powerful team capable of stopping the hostilities. Run n' Gun has roguelike elements as well as intense combat. The continuation of the series of the same name allows you to look at the war from a new angle with a greater share of adrenaline, gaining experience after each fight, which helps to unlock additional skills or weapons.</description></item><item><title>Warlords Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Warlords Battle Simulator is a game that places gamers in the role of generals who must lead armies in strategic and often unpredictable battles. In this tactical roguelike auto-action game, success largely depends on how well users manage resources, select units and place them on the battlefield. Each faction - be it the Kingdom, Greenskins, Undead or Barbarians - offers a unique set of units and commanders, each with special abilities that can change the tide of battle.</description></item><item><title>Emberdrift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emberdrift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emberdrift/</guid><description>Game Description Emberdrift is a fast-paced roguelike platformer that focuses on movement and upgrades. From the very beginning, gamers find themselves in an ever-changing world that requires quick reflexes and the ability to find new opportunities. The gameplay is built around speed, requiring users to navigate through a variety of levels with a range of mechanics designed to keep them on their toes. As players move through a randomly generated world, they can slide, wall jump, move diagonally, and even grab onto surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Rusty's Day Off: Episode One - Janitor on Duty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-day-off-episode-one-janitor-on-duty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-day-off-episode-one-janitor-on-duty/</guid><description>Game Description Rusty&amp;rsquo;s Day Off: Episode One - Janitor on Duty offers an original take on the first-person shooter (FPS) genre. The gamer will have to step into the shoes of Rusty, a janitor who is tasked with sorting out a situation at a workplace where a malfunction has occurred due to rogue robots. It&amp;rsquo;s not just running and gunning, there&amp;rsquo;s more to it than that. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to solve puzzles, interact with strange gadgets, and figure out how to stay alive while coping with mechanical chaos.</description></item><item><title>Sofie: The Echoes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sofie-the-echoes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sofie-the-echoes/</guid><description>Game Description Sofie: The Echoes is an adventure game that immerses gamers in an exciting storyline. The main character, Sophie, goes on a quest, guided by personal interests. In search of her husband and son, she goes through a world full of difficulties and trials. In this world, the boundaries between reality and echoes of the past are blurred. Every moment in the adventure feels weighty as users follow Sophie’s path through treacherous landscapes and emotional turmoil.</description></item><item><title>Monster High Skulltimate Secrets</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-high-skulltimate-secrets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-high-skulltimate-secrets/</guid><description>Game Description Monster High Skulltimate Secrets invites users to go on an exciting adventure with the iconic characters of the franchise. The story centers on Draculaura, Frankie Stein and Clawed Wolf, who go on a search and try to eliminate the evil spirits that are haunting their school. This dynamic trio act as guides and companions, guiding gamers through various challenges and puzzles. Gameplay involves collecting keys from monsters hidden throughout the campus, each of which is needed to open an ancient door.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>Quadrober Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Quadrober Simulator invites users to test themselves as a four-legged creature in a diverse environment. There is a lot of choice in this game. Users can choose from a variety of animals, each with specific traits and skills. These choices set the stage for a unique journey through different ecosystems. As gamers navigate these landscapes, they are faced with opportunities to explore, survive, and interact with the environment. Gameplay revolves around several key activities, including hunting, foraging, and building shelters.</description></item><item><title>Quarterstaff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quarterstaff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quarterstaff/</guid><description>Game Description Quarterstaff is a turn-based action strategy game that invites gamers into a fantasy realm full of intrigue and conflict. Set against the backdrop of a land under siege by a ruthless sorcerous conqueror, the adventure revolves around the character of Kalresh, a wizard skilled in the arts of magic and acrobatics. Having taken control of Kalresh, users are tasked with liberating the kingdom through a series of strategic battles.</description></item><item><title>Red Dead Redemption</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption/</guid><description>Game Description The beginning of the 20th century was not easy in the Wild West in Red Dead Redemption. John Marston was previously a member of a gang of thugs, but decided to end his bloody occupation. The guy did not manage to start a quiet life - the hero was taken under the “guardianship” of government services, whose agents forced him to work for them. The character&amp;rsquo;s family was under their guns, and if they refused, John&amp;rsquo;s relatives would be killed.</description></item><item><title>Vengeance Hunters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</guid><description>Game Description Vengeance Hunters is a side-scrolling beat-&amp;lsquo;em-up that captures the essence of classic arcade action. Here users can choose one of several characters, each of which has different abilities and fighting styles. These choices play an important role in how gamers approach gaming challenges. Going through various stages, users encounter many enemies, each of which has unique behavior and attack style. With a variety of characters, gamers will be able to find the fighting style that suits their preferences.</description></item><item><title>Soul Stalker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-stalker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-stalker/</guid><description>Game Description Soul Stalker is a bullet heaven-style roguelike that invites gamers into a world filled with ghostly challenges and addictive gameplay mechanics. In this game, gamers take on the role of a ghost manager as they navigate levels filled with unforgiving ghosts. Armed simultaneously with four to six types of weapons, users fight off waves of enemies trying to hinder their progress. This requires not only quick reflexes, but also strategic thinking as gamers choose how to use their arsenal against various threats.</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Nightmare</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-nightmare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-nightmare/</guid><description>Game Description In Nuclear Nightmare, gamers join a specialized team on a mission in a challenging arctic wasteland. The task is to find secret materials while overcoming various threats, including the Black Goo virus. This virus creates menacing entities that raise the stakes, forcing users to act quickly. The backdrop is a race against time as the US government prepares to launch a nuclear strike, adding urgency to every decision the team makes.</description></item><item><title>Speedollama</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</guid><description>Game Description Speedollama is a fast-paced platform shooter that takes gamers into a world where llamas battle an army of alpacas. The unusual premise draws users into a chaotic world where humor and action collide in the most unexpected ways. The goal is simple: control a llama equipped with a mining machine and destroy waves of alpaca enemies. The title features a vibrant environment filled with quirky characters and varied challenges, making every moment exciting.</description></item><item><title>Blazing Strike</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazing-strike/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazing-strike/</guid><description>Game Description Blazing Strike is a 2D fighting game that draws on the rich history of arcade games and brings new elements to the genre. Gamers can choose from 14 characters, each of which demonstrates their own fighting techniques and styles. The variety of characters makes the gameplay exciting and makes each fight unique. 11 stages to choose from allow users to get acquainted with different environments, each of which has its own flavor.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Thronefall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thronefall/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thronefall/</guid><description>Game Description Thronefall is a game that truly captures the essence of strategy and action. Here, players are tasked with balancing resources, armies, and defenses while constantly facing waves of relentless enemies that relentlessly attack their base every night. The project offers users the freedom to choose their style, allowing them to either hold positions behind fortified walls and rely on archers and catapults to repel invaders, or take charge and lead their knights into exciting combat.</description></item><item><title>Shady Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shady-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shady-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Shady Knight is a first-person hand-to-hand combat game. The environment is interactive and contains a huge amount of dynamic combat. The gameplay combines elements of platforming. You will need to go through many towers and brutally tear apart your enemies. You use a sword with which you kill your enemies. You can also kick opponents onto spikes, shoot enemies with fire, and throw swords at their bodies to pin them to walls.</description></item><item><title>Undisputed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undisputed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undisputed/</guid><description>Game Description Undisputed is a sports simulator about boxing, where a special emphasis is placed on realism. Having created his own fighter, the player will have to go from amateur matches to the professional stage. The main goal will be to obtain the eWBC world title. Achieving this title will require constant honing of your skills, learning new techniques and choosing the right strategy. You can carefully choose your approach to each enemy and not take too many risks, or you can go for the trouble and show your full potential in every battle.</description></item><item><title>Monomyth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monomyth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monomyth/</guid><description>Game Description The narrative in Monomyth takes you to dark and gloomy times, immersing you in a dark fantasy atmosphere. Strong natural forces in the form of storms devastate the surface of the earth, which is why humanity has to go underground. The world is plunging into a period of chaos and hopelessness, making it increasingly difficult for ordinary people to survive; strife and civil strife begin, followed by the decline of civilization and culture of the human race.</description></item><item><title>Aim Camp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</guid><description>Game Description Aim Camp is an adventure game that combines military simulator and interactive gameplay. It immerses gamers in a variety of training exercises aimed at honing their aiming and accuracy skills. Each exercise presents users with unique challenges, including scenarios such as close combat, sniping and drone operations. Gamers immerse themselves in these drills, where the goal is not only competition, but also a deeper understanding of accuracy.
The design of each scenario encourages a focused approach, requiring players to constantly adapt and improve their techniques.</description></item><item><title>Into the Necrovale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-necrovale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-necrovale/</guid><description>Game Description Into the Necrovale plunges you into a desperate fight for survival. As the Outsider, a doomed soul chosen by the All-Father, you hold the fate of a tormented world in your hands. Will you be his savior or his harbinger of doom? The choice is up to you. In the desolate Necroval, generations of exiled criminals fight for their existence. Hopeless, lost, forgotten - they are all bound by one rule: survive.</description></item><item><title>The Devil is in the Details</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-devil-is-in-the-details/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-devil-is-in-the-details/</guid><description>Game Description The Devil is in the Details is an adventure game that takes gamers into a labyrinth full of secrets and tension. Set in a mansion filled with traps and cursed objects, it takes participants on a journey of survival and strategy. The challenge is not only to escape, but also to clean up the environment. Gamers must find and place talismans on various cursed objects scattered throughout the mansion.</description></item><item><title>Banquet for Fools</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banquet-for-fools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banquet-for-fools/</guid><description>Game Description Banquet for Fools is a party role-playing adventure game that invites gamers into a kingdom filled with pagan rituals and mysterious secrets. In this game, users take the place of a lord among the Vollins, an elven race distinguished by their slender forms and a troubled history of relationships with deities. Rejected by their gods, these creatures turn to paganism in search of the meaning of their existence. The setting is a cursed island, shrouded in mystery, where the user&amp;rsquo;s spice farms have inexplicably lost all their inhabitants.</description></item><item><title>Halluci-Sabbath of Koishi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</guid><description>Game Description Halluci-Sabbat of Koishi immerses users in a fantasy setting where they will have to take control of the monster Satori Komeiji Koishi, who is an adventurer and a trained soldier. During the adventure, the hero meets a human witch who is looking for rare ingredients to create potions. Traveling together, the protagonists stumble upon a dangerous mushroom family and undead that they have to fight. Players will explore the forest with miasma and encounter many opponents.</description></item><item><title>Start Over</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</guid><description>Game Description Start Over is a multiplayer survival simulator set on a desert island, providing an immersive experience. You have to build a base, make the necessary equipment and defend against waves of enemies. The game features a realistic and dynamic environment where you need to adapt to constantly changing weather conditions, hunt animals, collect resources for survival and engage in trading items to earn money. As you explore the island, you can discover hidden secrets such as secret caves, ancient ruins, and even military camps.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Hanwell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-hanwell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-hanwell/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond Hanwell takes players to a post-apocalyptic London. Westminster, once a bustling hub, now serves as the backdrop to a complex journey of survival. Anomalies, a growing threat, inhabit the ruins of Hanwell. Gamers fight them using collected weapons or gadgets from the environment. The title offers more than just survival. She is a mystery. The director, a shadow figure, holds the clues. Side missions and hidden areas enrich the narrative.</description></item><item><title>Iron Meat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</guid><description>Game Description Iron Meat is a dynamic platformer made in the style of arcade shooters of the last century. The game takes place on Mars, when a group of scientists disappeared from radar without a trace. The case is entrusted to a member of an elite squad who goes in search of missing people. He must find out what really happened and who is behind this mysterious event.
The gameplay takes inspiration from classic action games such as Contra.</description></item><item><title>Mechabellum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</guid><description>Game Description Mechabellum is an epic auto battler set in a sci-fi setting that puts you in the shoes of a commander leading an army of mechs on the newly colonized planet Far-Away. Your opponents will tremble in fear as you customize and level up your units, strategically place them on the battlefield and watch them ruthlessly destroy your enemies. You&amp;rsquo;ll have an arsenal of unique &amp;lsquo;Mechs at your disposal, from the nimble light craft of Wasps to the massive Vulcans.</description></item><item><title>Ravenswatch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenswatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenswatch/</guid><description>Game Description Ravenswatch is a hardcore adventure in which you will need to explore a world captured by a terrible Nightmare. The gameplay is an isometric action role-playing game with procedurally generated locations. Battles are distinguished by their increased complexity and take place in real time. The gameplay is aimed at the player&amp;rsquo;s skill and creating a unique character build. Depending on the choice of the protagonist, weapons, equipment and a set of auxiliary items, the strategy of fights completely changes.</description></item><item><title>Shadows of Doubt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadows-of-doubt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadows-of-doubt/</guid><description>Game Description Shadows of Doubt allows gamers to plunge into the world of dark noir, which is shown in a sci-fi setting. Gamers will take control of a detective who is forced to deal with the case of a serial killer. The criminal is at large, committing hidden murders. The game is a first-person role-playing stealth adventure where you need to examine the surrounding area and interact with objects to find clues to the case.</description></item><item><title>The Forever Winter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forever-winter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forever-winter/</guid><description>Game Description The Forever Winter is a tactical survival horror shooter set in a post-apocalyptic world. Gamers navigate a landscape dominated by massive war machines locked in a relentless conflict. Here, special attention is paid to strategic decision-making and cooperation: gamers extract resources and fight for survival. The dynamic collision system ensures that enemies have their own goals and react intelligently to user actions, creating an unpredictable battlefield.
In The Forever Winter, users form squads to plunder the dead and confront terrifying war machines.</description></item><item><title>Disney Epic Mickey: Rebrushed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disney-epic-mickey-rebrushed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disney-epic-mickey-rebrushed/</guid><description>Game Description Disney Epic Mickey: Rebrushed begins with a familiar face in a world that seems a little unfamiliar. Mickey Mouse is back, and this time users follow him through the Wasteland - a place where forgotten Disney characters and stories live. As users navigate this realm, they are given tools that shape the world around them. With brush in hand, they use paints and solvents to change the environment, alter the outcome, and shape Mickey&amp;rsquo;s path.</description></item><item><title>DreadHaunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadhaunt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadhaunt/</guid><description>Game Description DreadHaunt is a 4v1 multiplayer horror and deception game in co-op and PVP. Here one of the users becomes possessed and turns into a ghost, and the rest must survive. The action takes place in a country plunged into chaos as a result of mass demonic possession. Gamers take on the role of an E-Class field agent tasked with securing, containing and protecting the source of evil to investigate and save the country.</description></item><item><title>GreedFall 2: The Dying World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/greedfall-2-the-dying-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/greedfall-2-the-dying-world/</guid><description>Game Description GreedFall II: The Dying World takes the beloved original game to new heights, offering an even more exciting and challenging adventure. The RPG takes place three years before its predecessor and takes players to the old continent of Gakan, where they take on the role of a native of Tir Fradi, a land filled with danger and corruption. Here survival and the fight for freedom and homeland become paramount.</description></item><item><title>Halls of Torment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</guid><description>Game Description Halls of Torment invites you into the world of terrifying monsters in this unique action game with roguelite elements, where you will face new challenges and dangers in each game. Dive into the dark and ruthless dungeons where the lords of the underworld await you. Find treasures and magical artifacts, and assemble a team of heroes who will help you defeat the horrors emanating from the depths of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Anomalous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomalous/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomalous/</guid><description>Game Description Anomalous takes users to the fictional and totalitarian city-state of Kosolov. Local authorities were able to brainwash the population and forced residents to work until exhaustion in order to get rich at the expense of others. One day, the leaders of an industrial and closed country began to experiment on people. They decided to increase the military potential of the power and began to conduct experiments on dead workers in order to revive them and force them to perform their duties again.</description></item><item><title>Witchfire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</guid><description>Game Description Witchfire suggests using not only weapons in the process, but also various devices in order to survive after an encounter with monsters. An arsenal consisting of dozens of different items and a variety of enemies will help gamers realize their own shooting skills. Challenge the most dangerous monsters that live in this world.
Here it is important to select the right type of weapon in accordance with the situation and type of enemy.</description></item><item><title>Lorn's Lure</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lorns-lure/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lorns-lure/</guid><description>Game Description Lorn&amp;rsquo;s Lure is a dynamic action platformer with a first-person view, which was developed using retro graphics, reminiscent of the project of the 90s of the last century. The user is invited to try himself in the role of a lost android, who is forced to challenge himself with a difficult, almost impossible challenge, exploring a giant cave that has not been explored by his people before. It is quite difficult to move around the available locations, because the player is constantly surrounded by abysses, falling into which will mean returning to the control point, of which there are very few.</description></item><item><title>Pneumata</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pneumata/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pneumata/</guid><description>Game Description In Pneumata, residents disappear without a trace in the dimly lit corridors of Clover Hill. Their screams echo through the walls and blood seeps into the cracks. Your task as a detective is twofold: unravel the hidden truth within and reconstruct your fragmented memories, or succumb to the hidden horrors. Welcome to a game that defies reality and plunges you into a cosmic nightmare. Psychological and cosmic horror: Pneumata blurs the line between reality and alternate worlds.</description></item><item><title>Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</guid><description>Game Description Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell is a first-person psychological horror game that explores themes of grief, guilt, and the paranormal. Players take on the role of Mark, a man coping with the recent loss of his wife Jane. The game begins with Mark returning to his and Jane&amp;rsquo;s old country house to prepare for her funeral. However, what is meant to be a grim homecoming quickly turns into a terrifying ordeal.</description></item><item><title>The Karate Kid: Street Rumble</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</guid><description>Game Description The Karate Kid: Street Rumble is a beat &amp;lsquo;em up title that immerses you in the world of the cult trilogy. Users step into the shoes of characters such as Daniel LaRusso, Mr. Miyagi, Ali Mills and Kumiko as they battle through various levels inspired by the films. The game has a side-scrolling format in which players face waves of enemies, including famous antagonists such as Johnny Lawrence, John Croesus and Terry Silver.</description></item><item><title>God of War: Ragnarok</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-ragnarok/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-ragnarok/</guid><description>Game Description God of War: Ragnarok continues the story of Kratos and Atreus as they explore a world inspired by Norse mythology. Events take place in ancient Norway. The events are dedicated to the beginning of Ragnarok. According to legend, it should lead to the death of all the Scandinavian gods, thereby marking the end of the world. Gameplay God of War: Ragnarok remains faithful to the original, but many new mechanics, enemies, abilities and locations have been introduced.</description></item><item><title>Toy Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Toy Tactics is a colorful action strategy game that will take you into the world of exciting strategies and physics experiments. Here you will become the main general, tasked with controlling little toy soldiers and defeating the enemy. You will have to place units on the battlefield and create various formations to guide your toy army towards victory. But don’t forget that physics plays an important role here! When the toy soldiers collide with each other, their helmets will fly in all directions, just like in a cartoon.</description></item><item><title>Wild Indigo Ranch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-indigo-ranch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-indigo-ranch/</guid><description>Game Description Wild Indigo Ranch invites you to step into the boots of a cowboy and travel to the fictional and humorous Wild West. Whether you prefer single-player play or join forces with up to three friends in online co-op, flexible options are offered. Personalization is key, allowing you to customize your character, horse, and ranch to suit your unique style.
Freedom reigns in the vast world of the game. You can roam the wild, hunt animals, search for gold mines, trade goods with other settlers, or engage in intense shootouts with bandits and lawmen.</description></item><item><title>Fera: The Sundered Tribes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</guid><description>Game Description Fera: The Sundered Tribes throws its hat into the action-RPG ring, but with a twist. You will not only have to smash the skulls of monsters, but also lead your tribe to restoration in a world devastated by magic. Imagine: A monster hunter by day, a mayor by night. The world of Fera is a post-apocalyptic mess, twisted by magic and infested with giant monsters that are eager to add your tribe to their menu of creatures.</description></item><item><title>Chains of Fury</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chains-of-fury/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chains-of-fury/</guid><description>Game Description Crazy shooter Chains of Fury with completely destructible levels. Lost or lost in the corridors? Just destroy all the walls with a shotgun! Up to 80% of the entire location will be broken, which will give complete freedom of movement. But you can’t fight with concrete alone. Aliens robots, creepy monsters and huge bosses - all this will need to be turned into bloody stains on the concrete.</description></item><item><title>Enotria: The Last Song</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enotria-the-last-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enotria-the-last-song/</guid><description>Game Description Enotria: The Last Song is not your typical push-button machine. This action RPG throws you into a world bound by a twisted, timeless game. You take on the role of Maskless, a wild card free of the scripted roles that everyone else follows. What is your task? Challenge the powerful Authors who support this disorderly spectacle. Masks are the main thing. Each of them gives you its own role and a unique set of abilities.</description></item><item><title>Hands of Necromancy 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hands-of-necromancy-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hands-of-necromancy-ii/</guid><description>Game Description Hands of Necromancy 2 is a dark fantasy first-person shooter that picks up where its predecessor left off. You can play as one of two characters, each with their own special abilities and spells. The game has reworked the necromancy system, so you can use new weapons and learn powerful spells. Transformations are important, allowing you to transform into various creatures to overcome obstacles and defeat enemies.
The game has many different environments: ancient castles, dry deserts, beautiful villages and creepy caves.</description></item><item><title>Judero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</guid><description>Game Description Judero immerses you in the world of strategic decisions and tactical battles. The title combines elements of role-playing and strategy, requiring gamers to go through various challenges and opponents. Users must manage resources, create alliances and make important decisions that will affect the outcome of their journey. In Judero, users encounter a variety of characters, each with unique abilities and history. These characters can be recruited into the player&amp;rsquo;s team, giving them various tactical advantages in battle.</description></item><item><title>Starstruck: Hands of Time</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starstruck-hands-of-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starstruck-hands-of-time/</guid><description>Game Description Starstruck: Hands of Time is an action role-playing game with rhythm game elements. Immersed in a vibrant world, you need to pick up a guitar to explore the rich environment. At the center of the story are two child guitarists. They confront three villains who want to rewrite the history of the world. The gameplay is based on time travel.
In the year 30XX, humanity will disappear from the face of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Trail of Ayash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</guid><description>Game Description The world of Trail of Ayash is based on the myths and legends of the inhabitants. An open game location allows you to freely explore the area and learn more about the life of Native Americans. The player will encounter various tribes competing with each other, participating in diplomacy, organizing wars and expansion. The main character is Ayash, a respected man in his own faction. One day, a close person frames Ayash, and after that he is expelled from the tribe.</description></item><item><title>Edge of Sanity</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/edge-of-sanity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/edge-of-sanity/</guid><description>Game Description Edge of Sanity immerses you in a chilling narrative. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about surviving the rugged Alaskan wilderness, it&amp;rsquo;s about battling with your own sanity as the harsh conditions erode your sanity. Imagine: you are cold, hungry and lost. Night falls and the only thing keeping the encroaching darkness at bay is the flickering fire. But wait, is that a growl in the distance or just the wind playing with your already frayed nerves?</description></item><item><title>Lucky Tower Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lucky-tower-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lucky-tower-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Lucky Tower Ultimate combines roguelike mechanics with a unique sense of humor. Gamers move through a dangerous tower, where every item can be used as a weapon. Here users will have to get out of the tower, overcoming various obstacles and enemies. Procedurally generated levels make each playthrough different, so no two are alike. The main character, von Vanst, continues his adventures in this part. Comedy and strategic gameplay are mixed here.</description></item><item><title>Panic In The Woods</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panic-in-the-woods/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panic-in-the-woods/</guid><description>Game Description Panic In The Woods is a survival and loot horror game that immerses gamers in a chilling woodland environment. The game can be played solo or in co-op with up to four gamers, playing as boy scouts lost in a haunted forest. The goal is simple: survive the relentless pursuit of the monstrous creature. Communication and strategy are of utmost importance. Users use walkie-talkies to coordinate their movements and exchange important information.</description></item><item><title>Surreal Farm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</guid><description>Game Description Surreal Farm is an adventure game that invites gamers into a vibrant world where imagination and strategy intertwine. Starting with a modest plot of land, gamers grow crops, care for unique animals and turn their farm into a thriving enterprise. As they progress, they discover many fantastical elements, from magical tools to surreal cultures and mythical creatures. The charm lies in the combination of casual gameplay and strategic depth.</description></item><item><title>Drill Core</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drill-core/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drill-core/</guid><description>Game Description Drill Core throws you headlong into the unforgiving depths of alien planets. You are in charge, tasked with managing a motley crew of miners and security guards. Their task? Extract valuable minerals and maintain the drill in working condition. Every swing of the pickaxe, every mounted turret - everything depends on your decisions. One wrong move can spell disaster for your team and the entire mission. But hold on, sunshine and cosmic rainbows don&amp;rsquo;t last forever here.</description></item><item><title>EVOTINCTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</guid><description>Game Description EVOTINCTION is a futuristic hacking and stealth game that puts gamers in the role of Dr. Liu, a scientist running a research facility that has been taken over by rogue AIs. The core gameplay centers on using hacking skills to overcome robotic threats and uncover secrets vital to humanity&amp;rsquo;s survival. The facility is teeming with enemies, ranging from ordinary service robots to deadly, specially created killer bots.
These robots follow specific patrol routes and work together under the guidance of a sophisticated artificial intelligence system.</description></item><item><title>Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</guid><description>Game Description Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines is a 2D action platformer that follows the adventures of Pablo and Luna. Users move through different dimensions, using unique abilities to overcome obstacles and enemies. It combines swinging, jumping and explosions to provide dynamic gameplay. In the title, gamers alternate between the characters Pablo and Luna. Pablo uses a grappling hook to progress through levels, while Luna brings her own set of skills to the table.</description></item><item><title>LOLLIPOP CHAINSAW RePOP</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lollipop-chainsaw-repop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lollipop-chainsaw-repop/</guid><description>Game Description Lollipop Chainsaw RePOP is a fast-paced hack-and-slash that follows the adventures of Juliet Starling, a high school cheerleader turned zombie hunter. Juliet will face a new wave of the undead and a mysterious outbreak that threatens her hometown. Armed with her trusty chainsaw, Juliet must fight her way through hordes of zombies, from classic Shamblers to more grotesque and dangerous creatures. The combat system is smooth and enjoyable, with a variety of combos and attacks to keep gamers on their toes.</description></item><item><title>Stardiver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</guid><description>Game Description The underwater world of Stardiver amazes with its diversity. Under the water column lies an entire civilization that has adapted to this way of existence so that other forms of life do not bother them and do not start wars. Nevertheless, for humanity, a planet completely covered with water turned out to be more than a curious subject of research.
The main character is the head of a scientific group for the study of extraterrestrial forms of civilization.</description></item><item><title>Wild Bastards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</guid><description>Game Description In Wild Bastards you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself in the captain&amp;rsquo;s chair of a ragtag spaceship filled with the galaxy&amp;rsquo;s most notorious criminals. Think space pirates with a penchant for trouble. This isn&amp;rsquo;t your grandpa&amp;rsquo;s space opera, but a roguelike shooter where every decision can mean the difference between exploding into stardom or becoming cosmic dust. The missions are spread across a series of tactical campaigns, each of which is an adventure.</description></item><item><title>Demolish and Build 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</guid><description>Game Description Demolish and Build 3 is a first-person simulator that puts you in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat of a demolition company. You will complete orders and lead your team to victory using a variety of tools and heavy equipment. This game will test your skills as you manage your business and complete every project with precision and efficiency. A completely new realistic model of destruction will make you marvel at what you see more than once, since each fragment is physically simulated.</description></item><item><title>Trap Tower Trials</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trap-tower-trials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trap-tower-trials/</guid><description>Game Description Trap Tower Trials presents a formidable challenge for gamers who will take on the role of a mysterious magician. The action takes place in a tower filled with unforgiving traps and obstacles designed to test your patience and skill. At each level of the tower, new dangers appear - from icy corridors to chambers imbued with magic - requiring precision and determination from users. The gameplay of Trap Tower Trials is linear and challenges gamers to scale unforgiving tower heights.</description></item><item><title>Elsie</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elsie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elsie/</guid><description>Game Description Elsie is a side-scrolling action platformer with simplified roguelike elements. Each subsequent playthrough is different from the previous one. With any new run, levels are created randomly from hand-crafted parts. The order of loot also always changes. The locations themselves are non-linear. Before starting, you can add or remove modifiers to increase or decrease the difficulty accordingly. In the indie game you can run, jump, dash, bounce off walls, and shoot at opponents.</description></item><item><title>Hive Jump 2: Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hive Jump 2: Survivors is a sci-fi role-playing adventure game with action elements. In this adrenaline-pumping sequel to the acclaimed action-platformer, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself the only survivor of your squad, stranded on an alien planet. Armed with only your guns and your trusty jetpack, you set out on a mission of revenge. Here you have to fight relentless waves of killer insects. What is your goal? Destroy these swarms of aliens and collect their valuable entrails.</description></item><item><title>I Am Your Beast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</guid><description>Game Description I Am Your Beast is not your average shooter. This narrative-driven game throws you headlong into a brutal conflict with the shadowy organization you once worked for. You play as Alphonse Harding, a former operative who has been lured back into the world of underground warfare. Survival and thinking quickly are key. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to navigate treacherous terrain, dodging and fighting enemies in a high-stakes chase.
Forget about going with guns at the ready.</description></item><item><title>Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</guid><description>Game Description Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland is a new action-platformer that brings beloved characters from the 1990s Nickelodeon series into a vibrant, imaginative world. Together with Tommy, Chucky, Phil and Lil, users will go on an adventure inspired by their favorite video game character, Reptar. The title features a unique co-op design that allows gamers to form teams and complete various levels located in the Pickles' home. The gameplay of Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland revolves around exploration and teamwork.</description></item><item><title>Towerborne</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</guid><description>Game Description Towerborne is an action-adventure game set in a world where humanity&amp;rsquo;s cities have been destroyed by a mysterious evil. The only refuge is the Bell Tower, a tower that holds secrets and dangers. Gamers take on the role of Ace, a hero tasked with protecting the inhabitants of the Belfry and uncovering the truth about the evil threatening humanity. Here gamers explore a huge world filled with various creatures and challenges.</description></item><item><title>Yars Rising</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yars-rising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yars-rising/</guid><description>Game Description Yars Rising is an exciting adventure game that will take gamers on an exciting journey through a dystopian future. In the role of Emi Kimura, an experienced hacker, you have to infiltrate the mysterious QoTech corporation. This shadowy organization holds secrets that could potentially change the world. The gameplay is a delightful mixture of 2D platforming, stealth and hacking. As Amy, you&amp;rsquo;ll navigate intricate levels, dodging laser bars, outsmarting security drones, and solving challenging puzzles.</description></item><item><title>Arcane Blast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</guid><description>Game Description In Arcane Blast you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself wearing the fur boots of Adrian, a cat mage on a mission. This roguelike adventure throws you into a chaotic world filled with spells, enemies, and the constant threat of a cat&amp;rsquo;s life. Do you think you can handle it? This isn&amp;rsquo;t your average walk in the park, unless that park is filled with evil goblins and fire-breathing lizards. It&amp;rsquo;s all about reflexes here.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-2/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 is a cinematic 3rd person sci-fi action game set in a dystopian future where humanity is under siege by an implacable enemy - the Tyranids. As a Space Marine, you take on the role of a superhuman warrior tasked with defending the Imperium from an impending threat. Gamers are offered the opportunity to embody the image of the greatest warrior and show their incredible skill and cruelty in epic battles on distant planets.</description></item><item><title>Zero Hour</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Hour is a multiplayer tactical first-person shooter with realistic game mechanics that replicate the behavior of real special forces units in anti-terrorist operations. The setting for the action is criminal Bangladesh, where banditry is at a high level and is not going to give up ground to law enforcement officers. The locations where clashes between groups of terrorists and special forces occur are made using real scale, which greatly helps the atmosphere and involves gamers in the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Castle of Lord Velimir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</guid><description>Game Description Castle of Lord Velimir takes users on a dangerous journey with the titular hero, a warrior seeking atonement for the sins of humanity. As Velimir journeys through the dungeons, wastelands, and mysterious underworld of Agartha, he will face countless challenges and uncover the secrets of his world. The gameplay is a mixture of strategic combat and exploration. Users must master a variety of fighting techniques to defeat a variety of enemies, each requiring a different approach.</description></item><item><title>CORPUS EDAX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corpus-edax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corpus-edax/</guid><description>Game Description CORPUS EDAX is an exciting first-person action RPG with close combat that will take you to a distant planet. Create your own character and unleash your inner warrior as you fight, sneak, or escape difficult situations. The choice is always yours - and it is always the right one. Use your body, ingenuity, and improvised weapons to make your way through this stunning new world. Thanks to the A.</description></item><item><title>Guns And Draguns</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</guid><description>Game Description Guns And Draguns is a top-down co-op shooter that plunges gamers into a dangerous fantasy dungeon. Here users will have to go through various levels, destroying fantasy monsters with weapons. The main goal is to defeat the final boss, but along the way there are enemies and obstacles that require strategic teamwork and cooperation. Gamers can choose one of seven unique characters, each of which has its own abilities.</description></item><item><title>Smells Like a Mushroom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</guid><description>Game Description Smells Like a Mushroom is a sci-fi third-person shooter that takes gamers on a journey through the Milky Way. At the center is an invasion of creatures known as Magic Mushrooms. Users take on the role of Carrotado, a brave character tasked with preventing disaster. The gameplay includes platformer and shooter mechanics, and missions take place on various planets in the solar system.
Smells Like a Mushroom&amp;rsquo;s narrative is driven by an absurd story and features both single-player and co-op modes.</description></item><item><title>Ale and Tale Tavern</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-and-tale-tavern/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-and-tale-tavern/</guid><description>Game Description Ale and Tale Tavern is a first-person, open-world co-op fantasy tavern simulator. Gamers step into the role of a tavern owner tasked with restoring an abandoned establishment to its former glory. The title offers a variety of activities including cooking, fishing, hunting and exploration. Users can complete a variety of quests, interact with unique characters, and manage various aspects of the tavern, such as decoration and crafting.
The gameplay of Ale and Tale Tavern allows you to play both alone and in co-op - up to four users can work together.</description></item><item><title>Hit of Chernobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</guid><description>Game Description Hit of Chernobyl immerses users in a post-apocalyptic environment where survival is of paramount importance. Finding themselves in an area contaminated by an unspecified disaster, gamers take on the role of an adventurer. He must navigate a landscape full of dangers, not only from the environment, but also from other characters. The world is populated by marauders, journalists and thrill seekers, each with their own motives. Finding unique artifacts becomes the main task, requiring users to overcome a landscape replete with difficulties.</description></item><item><title>Selfloss</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selfloss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selfloss/</guid><description>Game Description Selfloss is an atmospheric adventure set in a fantasy setting. The plot centers on a lonely old man, and the game itself is inspired by ancient Russian and Icelandic legends. Travel through the isometric world using your magic staff. Fight against numerous mythical creatures from Slavic fairy tales and myths. Help everyone who needs it. Pass many tests to perform a secret self-floss ritual that can heal a wounded soul.</description></item><item><title>Skoof Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Skoof Simulator will introduce gamers to the life of Skoof, an ordinary worker whose everyday life is not like a routine. The title combines simulation and adventure elements, offering a unique and sarcastic look at everyday activities. Players guide Skuf through a variety of missions, ranging from factory shifts to humorous and unexpected situations. Users will have to manage Skuf&amp;rsquo;s life, making decisions that affect the outcome of his adventures.</description></item><item><title>The Moon 2044</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</guid><description>Game Description The Moon 2044 takes place in a secret research facility on the Moon, where gamers take on the role of a genetically modified commando codenamed XV-11. The mission is to retrieve priceless samples from the depths of a lunar base that has fallen into darkness and is now overrun by hostile creatures. The facility, originally intended for experimental cancer research, hides many dark secrets that users will have to uncover.</description></item><item><title>BAKERU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bakeru/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bakeru/</guid><description>Game Description The adventure of BAKERU, set in fantasy Japan, revolves around a tanuki boy named Bakeru. His mission is to restore order after the chaos unleashed by Oracle Saitaro and his Festival Army. Armed with a mystical drum, Buckaroo sets out on a journey to free Japan from evil spirits. BAKERU takes place across 50 scenes inspired by Japanese prefectures. This vibrant world combines modern Japan with echoes of period dramas to create a captivating backdrop.</description></item><item><title>We Heist Too</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</guid><description>Game Description We Heist Too takes place in Rivadorium, a city where nothing ever stays the same. Users get used to the role of a thief, move silently through the streets, plan and carry out high-stakes robberies. This world doesn&amp;rsquo;t require much care, and from the very beginning you will notice that every corner of the city is fraught with opportunity. But the tricky part is knowing which opportunities are worth pursuing.</description></item><item><title>Sumerian Six</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerian-six/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerian-six/</guid><description>Game Description Sumerian Six is not your typical war story. Sure, it throws you right into the middle of World War II, but it&amp;rsquo;s an alternate history where whispers of folklore and conspiracy theories are as real as the Nazi threat. You take command of Enigma Squad, a strange team of scientist-soldiers. These are brainy people who can outwit and outwit their enemies. Their mission? Prevent the Third Reich from getting its hands on occult weapons.</description></item><item><title>FALLEN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallen/</guid><description>Game Description FALLEN is an adventure game that immerses gamers in a post-apocalyptic world where the main goal is survival. Users navigate desert landscapes, encountering various challenges that test their resourcefulness and decision-making skills. The title places an emphasis on exploration and interaction with the environment, requiring gamers to scavenge for supplies and manage their inventory efficiently.
In FALLEN, users encounter a variety of characters, each with their own story and motivation.</description></item><item><title>Kamikaze Lasplanes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</guid><description>Game Description Kamikaze Lassplanes is a visual novel that combines the plot of a novel with the action of a shoot-&amp;lsquo;em-up game. Set in a steampunk world, the dramatic storyline involves two powerful weapons, Lassplanes, and two girls who become them. Gamers navigate a war-torn kingdom and make choices that affect not only the fate of the kingdom, but also their own hearts.
The project introduces Alba Trosset and Hannah Brandenburg, two girls who transform into deadly warplanes.</description></item><item><title>Unstoppable: Breakout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unstoppable-breakout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unstoppable-breakout/</guid><description>Game Description Unstoppable: Breakout is an adventure game in which gamers find themselves in a chilling complex, leaving them alone and confused. Guided by the voice of a colleague, the protagonist, a researcher, must navigate dark and mysterious corridors, battling inhuman experiments and uncovering hidden secrets. The game is an intense mix of strategy and combat, requiring careful resource management and precision in every strike. The gameplay of Unstoppable: Breakout is an exciting roller coaster ride with challenging combat and boss battles.</description></item><item><title>Akimbot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/akimbot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/akimbot/</guid><description>Game Description Akimbot throws you into a metal menagerie! Teaming up rogue robot Exe with unexpected partner Shipset, this game throws down the galactic gauntlet. Imagine: you are fighting your way through hordes of robotic enemies, spaceships at the ready, and all this in order to stop a universal catastrophe. Fasten your seat belts, because this is not an easy ride. Akimbot isn&amp;rsquo;t all button-mashing chaos. It&amp;rsquo;s a strategic dance with enemies to dodge and outwit in every level.</description></item><item><title>Call of Sentinels</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Sentinels plunges you headlong into an epic struggle against the forces of darkness. Choose your champion from a growing list, each with unique skills and fighting styles. Hone your combat skills against the relentless hordes in the Arena, or take on dangerous journeys across varied landscapes in Campaign. Unleash devastating combos and master tactical maneuvers to defeat treacherous enemies and colossal bosses. Each victory unlocks valuable upgrades, expanding the hero&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and shaping his legend.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description The CarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>DEATH IN UNISON</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-in-unison/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-in-unison/</guid><description>Game Description DEATH IN UNISON is a co-op survival adventure game set in an isolated rehabilitation institute on Corton Island. Here gamers will have to survive in the fight against some of the most dangerous criminals in the world, many of whom have supernatural powers. Users must perform their prison duties alone or with a partner, relying primarily on radio communications to navigate the treacherous environment.
Gameplay in DEATH IN UNISON revolves around completing administrative tasks and protecting yourself from hostile prisoners.</description></item><item><title>ENDLESS DAYS Z</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-days-z/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-days-z/</guid><description>Game Description ENDLESS DAYS Z immerses gamers in a desolate, post-apocalyptic world devastated by DeltaVirus-7. As the leader of a group of survivors, you must overcome treacherous obstacles, collect vital samples, and confront hordes of the undead as you desperately search for a cure. The gripping narrative and intense gameplay make the game appealing to fans of survival horror and action games. The gameplay of ENDLESS DAYS Z is based on exploration, combat and resource management.</description></item><item><title>Gori: Cuddly Carnage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gori-cuddly-carnage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gori-cuddly-carnage/</guid><description>Game Description Gori: Cuddly Carnage is a dynamic action game with platformer and horror elements. You find yourself locked in with crazed toys out for blood. Using a special surf, you will have to cut circles around the location and chop up monsters. You will play as an anthropomorphic kitten riding a hoverboard. Chop unicorns and don’t get caught by a huge gorilla, eager to devour the protagonist.
The gameplay of Gori: Cuddly Carnage has been jokingly described as Skate and Slash.</description></item><item><title>Gundam Breaker 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</guid><description>Game Description GUNDAM BREAKER 4 hits the gaming scene with a bang as part of the heist gaming franchise. It&amp;rsquo;s all about building and fighting with a set of Gundam models, a concept fans are very familiar with. However, adventure games breathe new life into this formula, offering a deeper and more expansive experience. Customization is the cornerstone of the game. An extensive library of over 250 base sets provides the foundation for creating the Gunpla of your dreams.</description></item><item><title>Squirrel with a Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Squirrel with a Gun offers a unique experience. Users control a squirrel armed with a gun. Target? Collect golden acorns in a secret underground vault. The squirrel that haunts the neighbors becomes a hero. Gamers move through a sandbox filled with puzzles and enemies. The facility serves as a playground for chaos. To survive, the squirrel uses weapons, claws and teeth. The gameplay combines shooting and platforming. Users collect golden acorns - a squirrel&amp;rsquo;s obsession.</description></item><item><title>Star Command Galaxies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</guid><description>Game Description Star Command Galaxies is a space simulator in which you play as a ship captain. You need to build your own shuttle, recruit staff and go explore the randomly generated expanses of outer space. Manage your staff, collect resources, fight the alien threat and upgrade your ship. Clear the galaxy from enemies and various parasites. Fight pirates, zombies and many other opponents.
You need to monitor the status of your team.</description></item><item><title>Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/umamusume-pretty-derby-party-dash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/umamusume-pretty-derby-party-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash is a colorful spin-off that departs from the traditional racing focus. The title is evolving into a playful, party-oriented title. Gamers are immersed in a pixelated world teeming with familiar Umamusume. The Slapdash Grand Prix, the centerpiece, unfolds like a chaotic school festival. Four different events promise laughter, competition and unexpected twists. The pixel relay will spark the fun.
Time plays a crucial role in Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games' level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>PROTOCOL 11 - Episode 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/protocol-11-episode-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/protocol-11-episode-1/</guid><description>Game Description PROTOCOL 11 - Episode 1 is a journey through many worlds as Phil goes on a quest for justice. This is an exciting adventure in which gamers must return what was stolen by a strange race of invaders. The story touches on themes of friendship, love and the essence of humanity. Users mine resources, fight enemies and choose between direct combat and stealth. Gameplay involves jumping on platforms, shooting, and solving puzzles.</description></item><item><title>The Land of the Magnates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-land-of-the-magnates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-land-of-the-magnates/</guid><description>Game Description The Land of the Magnates tells the story of fallen prince Shahbaz, who is tasked with restoring a kingdom shrouded in darkness. The project does not hand the players a sword, but instead puts a sitar in their hands. This is not a hack-and-slash adventure game. No, this is a journey of melody and power, where puzzles replace sword fights. Shahbaz&amp;rsquo;s adventure takes place through fantastical landscapes. The black forest, the damned expanses, tests your courage.</description></item><item><title>9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</guid><description>Game Description 9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far is a real-time strategy game developed by Petroglyph Games, a continuation of the 8-Bit Armies series. Gamers lead modern military forces across various battlefields, participating in land, sea and air battles. The project offers more than two dozen missions, online skirmishes and cooperative play. A base construction system has been implemented in which players build structures, unlock units and launch attacks. The game is designed for both new and experienced RTS players with an easy to learn interface but a challenging skill ceiling.</description></item><item><title>Rum and Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Rum and Gun uses a pirate theme as its setting. The hero travels through the lands located in the Indian Ocean, fighting on land with people and monsters. He is trying to stop the captain, who has enlisted the help of evil forces. He also has to learn the secrets of the Drunken God. The plot is presented with jokes and self-irony. History is divided into acts.
This is an isometric shooter and action game with role-playing elements.</description></item><item><title>Selene's Unbearable Night</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selenes-unbearable-night/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selenes-unbearable-night/</guid><description>Game Description Selene&amp;rsquo;s Unbearable Night is a third-person survival horror game that immerses gamers in a tense and atmospheric atmosphere. The title tells the story of Selena, a woman who finds herself in a difficult situation and is forced to overcome various dangers in order to survive. Users will have to search for key items, solve complex puzzles and confront numerous threats in order to complete the game. Selene&amp;rsquo;s Unbearable Night&amp;rsquo;s narrative unfolds through dialogue and cinematography, offering a deep dive into the characters' motivations and backstories.</description></item><item><title>Finding Mosey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</guid><description>Game Description In Finding Mosey, your feline companion Mosey has mysteriously disappeared. You go in search of him, and your path will depend on the choice you make. Developed by youpiepoopie, this single-player third-person RPG offers a refreshing blend of exploration, storytelling, and whimsical interactions. The search begins. Imagine waking up during a peaceful hike to find Mosey nowhere to be found.
This seemingly simple premise turns into an exciting adventure.</description></item><item><title>Black Myth: Wukong</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-myth-wukong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-myth-wukong/</guid><description>Game Description Black Myth: Wukong is a role-playing game based on the famous Chinese novel Journey to the West, written back in the 16th century. The gameplay is a journey through a semi-open world, reminiscent of a metroidvania. The developers cite the Souls series as their main source of inspiration.
The story centers on a hero named Sun Wukong, who is also known as the Monkey King. He travels through a fantasy world, simultaneously fighting with various phantasmagoric creatures.</description></item><item><title>Crime Scene Cleaner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-scene-cleaner/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crime-scene-cleaner/</guid><description>Game Description Crime Scene Cleaner is an unusual simulator in which you clean up traces of a crime. As soon as the customer calls you, and usually this is the mafia boss, you need to rush to the crime scene and wield a brush, a mop and many other tools. If you find yourself in a room full of corpses and blood, pull yourself together and do the job professionally. Don&amp;rsquo;t give investigators a chance to find the killer.</description></item><item><title>Nova Drift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</guid><description>Game Description Nova Drift is a top-down action RPG adventure. The gamer has the opportunity to test his strength in piloting a space fighter, forced to fight enemies that are superior in numbers and firepower. The spaceship uses unusual technologies; it is created using biomechanics, which means that it seems to be alive and is constantly changing both in appearance and in terms of available weapons. Thanks to the addition of artificial intelligence trained in procedural random generation, the developers from a small indie formation were able to achieve almost endless replayability.</description></item><item><title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Into the Pit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/five-nights-at-freddys-into-the-pit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/five-nights-at-freddys-into-the-pit/</guid><description>Game Description Five Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s: Into the Pit immerses players in time-bending horror. Oswald, bored with everyday life, stumbles upon a portal to the past in the ball pit of an old pizzeria. His desire for thrills quickly turns into a nightmare when he finds himself trapped in a deadly game of cat and mouse. The player will have to move between different eras, piece together clues and elude relentless animatronic pursuers.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>Nine Sols</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nine-sols/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nine-sols/</guid><description>Game Description Adventures in Nine Sols take players into an oriental fantasy setting where they will have to fight against 9 Sols. The game is a 2D platformer with soulslick elements, where you have to face unique bosses. Events take place on the territory of New Kunlun, which is a refuge for survivors. The ancient gods abandoned mortals, forcing them to confront dangerous monsters. A hero named Yi has arrived from the distant past to defeat mythological creatures.</description></item><item><title>WARNO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</guid><description>Game Description Tactical battles in WARNO take place in real time, where users will be able to take control of modern combat vehicles and go to the front, plunging into the Third World War. The game is made in the genre of strategy and army command simulator, where you need to think through the movement of units and observe the events taking place. The storyline is about a coup that occurs after Gorbachev leaves, creating a tense conflict between states in 1989.</description></item><item><title>Ghost of Tsushima DIRECTOR'S CUT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ghost-of-tsushima-directors-cut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ghost-of-tsushima-directors-cut/</guid><description>Game Description In Ghost of Tsushima DIRECTOR&amp;rsquo;S CUT the twilight of the 13th century begins. The Mongol Empire massacred many peoples as part of a campaign whose goal was to conquer the East. Between mainland Japan and the mighty Mongol fleet, commanded by the legendary General Khotun Khan, lies only the island of Tsushima. And he is conquered, small villages are destroyed. Samurai Jin Sakai remained the last of the great clan.</description></item><item><title>ANIMAL WELL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-well/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-well/</guid><description>Game Description In ANIMAL WELL players must explore a vast labyrinth created in pixel art. Players will interact with the interactive environment, pick up objects and combine them with each other, solve spatial puzzles, overcome landscape obstacles and much more. The character has to move around two-dimensional locations with a side view, periodically encountering dangerous monsters. It is necessary to illuminate dark areas on the map by lighting special candles.</description></item><item><title>Rabbit and Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Rabbit and Steel is a co-op action roguelike that will take you into epic battles. Choose your class, gather your bunny friends and fight to the top of Moon Peak. Months ago, all ties with the Moonlight Kingdom were severed. It is reported that the city&amp;rsquo;s residents are attacking all newcomers. Exploratory expeditions are repulsed or go missing. Every night, a huge white tower appears in the center of the city, reaching towards the stars.</description></item><item><title>V Rising</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rising/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rising/</guid><description>Game Description Waking up in V Rising, the hero as a vampire must hunt for blood, while simultaneously avoiding direct sunlight. The survival slasher film puts you in the shoes of a bloodsucker who wakes up in his own castle and must regain his possession and authority while operating in a vast open world full of secrets. Here you have to conquer the lands of the living, unite with allies to complete the task.</description></item><item><title>Hades 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades-ii/</guid><description>Game Description Hades II, the sequel to the award-winning roguelike dungeon crawler, takes players beyond the underworld. You play as Melina, a princess of the underworld, who uses dark sorcery to fight the Titan of Time. Supergiant Games builds on the success of the original game with intense action and endless replayability. Explore a deeper mythical world rooted in Greek myth and witchcraft. The story unfolds through victories and failures, keeping you on your toes.</description></item><item><title>Abiotic Factor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abiotic-factor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abiotic-factor/</guid><description>Game Description Abiotic Factor throws you into an underworld of chaos. Scientists, humanity&amp;rsquo;s brightest representatives, become survivors when faced with a multifaceted threat. When the protective shell is breached, horrors burst to the surface, and soldiers from another dimension invade the world. Meanwhile, a secret military sect hunts for artifacts and entities, adding to the chaos.
Trapped miles underground, escape seems impossible. But you and your fellow scientists are not ordinary people.</description></item><item><title>Manor Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Manor Lords is a strategy game set in the Middle Ages. The game mechanics center on the realistic process of constructing buildings and intense fights with the enemy army. The building element is based on historical data about cities and villages. All buildings presented in Manor Lords are as authentic as possible. Landscapes and types of terrain influence the process of settlement formation.
Create trade routes, establish market relations with neighboring cities and promote the economic prosperity of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Another Crab's Treasure</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-crabs-treasure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-crabs-treasure/</guid><description>Game Description Another Crab&amp;rsquo;s Treasure is an exciting underwater adventure created by AGGRO CRAB. You take on the role of a hermit crab named Creel, who goes on a dangerous treasure hunt to get back his stolen shell. In this unique underwater kingdom, on the verge of destruction, garbage is not only part of life, but also a valuable resource used to create fashionable outfits and weapons. However, with the garbage comes a mysterious danger - &amp;ldquo;slurry&amp;rdquo; - which threatens to destroy the entire ocean.</description></item><item><title>Bellwright</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</guid><description>Game Description Bellwright throws you into a world of rebellion and intrigue. Finding yourself in prison for a heinous crime, you must not only clear your name, but also organize a revolution against a tyrannical ruler. Build and manage settlements, collect resources and recruit villagers into your ranks. Each new adept brings valuable skills, strengthening your rebellion and unlocking new technologies for your cities.
Combat is based on skill and focus.</description></item><item><title>Dead Island 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-island-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-island-2/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Island 2 is a continuation of the first-person zombie action game of the same name. The events of the game start a few months after the end of the first game. The virus has reached sunny California. The entire territory was cordoned off by US troops. Dead Island 2 includes many features that expand on the ideas of Left 4 Dead. The hero finds himself in the center of a zombie apocalypse and somehow miraculously survives.</description></item><item><title>No Rest for the Wicked</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-rest-for-the-wicked/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-rest-for-the-wicked/</guid><description>Game Description No Rest for the Wicked immerses players in a world ravaged by death and despair. Developed by Moon Studios, the creators of Ori and the Blind Forest, this action RPG promises challenging combat and deep human storytelling. The kingdom mourns the death of King Harol, leaving his untested son Magnus on the throne. Meanwhile, an ancient plague known as the Blight returns, corrupting the land and its inhabitants. Amid the chaos, Madrigal Celine, hungry for power in the church, seeks to use the crisis for his own selfish purposes.</description></item><item><title>Buckshot Roulette</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</guid><description>Game Description Two enter, one leaves. That&amp;rsquo;s the motto of Buckshot Roulette, a horror game that takes the classic game of Russian Roulette and turns it into a high-stakes shotgun game. Immerse yourself in the dark atmosphere of an underground nightclub, where metal railings beat to the beat of forgotten drum kits and the stakes couldn&amp;rsquo;t be higher. This is not Russian roulette. This is where you swap the revolver for a 12 gauge shotgun, because shotguns are just better, right?</description></item><item><title>Content Warning</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/content-warning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/content-warning/</guid><description>Game Description Content Warning throws players into the world of horror content creation. Team up with friends, create your own pixelated face using the in-game ASCII customizer, and grab your gear. Then descend into the spooky Old World using the diving bell. The Old World is crawling with creepy, physics-based monsters and cursed relics just waiting to be captured on camera. Capture as much creepy content as you can before you run out of oxygen, your camera dies, or worse, your friends become fodder for the monsters.</description></item><item><title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</guid><description>Game Description Outpost: Infinity Siege is a fun sci-fi first-person shooter with elements of base building and tower defense. You command the Mobile Outpost and go with the Protoslug Cannon to deeply explore the forbidden zone of Cygnet, where many dangers await you. Collect unique weapon units and strengthen the firepower of the outpost that is fighting with you. This game combines elements of TD, FPS and RTS at the same time, making the gameplay incredibly exciting.</description></item><item><title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragons-dogma-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragons-dogma-2/</guid><description>Game Description Dragon&amp;rsquo;s Dogma 2 takes players on a single-player adventure, immersing them in an action-packed action RPG where choices define the path. Players are encouraged to customize their experience, from the appearance of their Arisen to strategic decisions in combat and party composition. Throughout the quest, players are accompanied by pawns - mysterious creatures that simulate the multiplayer experience of a single-player adventure, enriching the gameplay with a variety of perspectives.</description></item><item><title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midnight-ghost-hunt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midnight-ghost-hunt/</guid><description>Game Description Midnight Ghost Hunt is a creepy version of hide and seek in which players will have to catch ghosts or, on the contrary, drive away people who disturbed the peace of the spirits. 4v4 confrontation takes place between friends or random users. The main task of the hunters is to catch all the evil spirits with the help of their equipment, and the ghosts are to kill all living things by any means.</description></item><item><title>Horizon Forbidden West</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-forbidden-west/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-forbidden-west/</guid><description>Game Description Horizon Forbidden West – continuation of the adventures of the hunter Aloy, from the Nora tribe. In this part, the heroine finds herself on the coast of the former United States, where she will encounter new obstacles and deadly machines. You will have to use your bow and your ward’s abilities to confront your opponents and find out the secret of the islands. Watching Aloy from a third person, the user navigates the open world, completing main and side quests.</description></item><item><title>STAR WARS: Battlefront Classic Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-battlefront-classic-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-battlefront-classic-collection/</guid><description>Game Description STAR WARS: Battlefront Classic Collection brings back the beloved online shooters, remastered for modern consoles and PC. Players can now relive classic battles from the Star Wars galaxy, both online and offline, in this new collection. The collection includes the original game, as well as a bonus map: Jabba&amp;rsquo;s Palace. The second game, Battlefront 2, includes four bonus cards and two bonus heroes: Asajj Ventress and Kit Fisto.</description></item><item><title>The Outlast Trials</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-outlast-trials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-outlast-trials/</guid><description>Game Description The Outlast Trials - first-person horror game in the Outlast universe. The difference from the main series is that you can play both alone and in a company. At the center of the story is the Murkoff company, which is engaged in inhumane and sadistic experiments. You will play as one of these crazy organizations. You can join forces with up to 4 people and try to survive this nightmare together.</description></item><item><title>Secrets of Grindea</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</guid><description>Game Description Secrets of Grindea is an interesting adventure game in which you will need to take control of a hero and go on a long journey through a huge fantasy world in search of new adventures. The game begins with character generation. You will have to create it, change its appearance using an advanced editor, and then decide on the basic skills. After this, you can begin to explore the world around you.</description></item><item><title>Sons of the Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Sons of The Forest is a first-person multiplayer horror game with survival elements. The game is a sequel to the acclaimed hit The Forest. As in the previous part, you need to explore a mysterious forest inhabited by bloodthirsty monsters. Survive by hiding from enemies and carefully study the surrounding areas. Arm yourself with powerful weapons to face numerous opponents.
The story centers on a special forces soldier with a Fight Demons tattoo.</description></item><item><title>Last Epoch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-epoch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-epoch/</guid><description>Game Description Last Epoch is an action-adventure game with a deep leveling system in a dark style, gameplay repeating the legendary Diablo. The camera view is also taken from there, it is isometric for a better overview of the surrounding areas. The story campaign for one person (multiplayer is not provided) invites you to explore the rich world of Eterra, with various picturesque places and dark dungeons. It contains many different oddities, secrets, many demons and other fiends of hell.</description></item><item><title>Myth of Empires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</guid><description>Game Description The goal of Myth of Empires is to teach the user to fight for their own place in a huge world. The game is positioned as a multiplayer sandbox in which the user creates an Empire, forming troops that participate in massive battles and sieges of cities, and also builds their own fortresses for defense.
The action takes place in the East during the era of antiquity, when many states constantly fought among themselves, which led to chaos, famine and destruction.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>Nightingale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</guid><description>Game Description Nightingale takes you on a dangerous journey through the fantastical kingdoms of the fairies. As a Realmwalker, you&amp;rsquo;ll explore, craft, build, and fight across a variety of environments, alone or with friends. This open world survival game takes you through a labyrinth of beautiful but treacherous kingdoms. Stranded after the destruction of a network of portals, you must reach Nightingale, the last human bastion. Open portals and travel through wild forests, treacherous swamps and shimmering deserts.</description></item><item><title>Blaz Blue Entropy Effect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazblue-entropy-effect/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazblue-entropy-effect/</guid><description>Game Description BlazBlue Entropy Effect is a 2D adventure game set in the BlazBlue universe, but with a different genre and style than previous fighting games. It features roguelite elements such as procedurally generated maps, permadeath, and character customization. There is also a rich plot with several endings, depending on the choice of the gamer.
In the game you can choose one of seven unique characters, each of which has its own abilities and character.</description></item><item><title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</guid><description>Game Description In Smalland: Survive the Wilds the player takes on the role of a hero who has been diminished under unexplained circumstances. The protagonist woke up in the forest, not knowing whether other people had the same fate. With a head full of questions, he begins a struggle whose goal is not only to find out the truth, but, above all, to survive in a new inhospitable world.
The player watches what is happening from the first person.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor is not your average survival game, but a single-player, addictive auto-shooting game that is sure to keep you on your toes. As a lone dwarf, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to use every weapon in your arsenal to fight off waves of deadly aliens while earning riches and unlocking powerful upgrades.
But don&amp;rsquo;t think this will be an easy task. You will have to face the harsh and unforgiving landscape of the planet Hoxes, and only your wits and weapons can protect you.</description></item><item><title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suicide-squad-kill-the-justice-league/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suicide-squad-kill-the-justice-league/</guid><description>Game Description Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is perfect for all fans of the DC universe who want to look at familiar heroes from a new angle. Now the roles have been changed, superheroes have become a danger to the local population, and a villainous squad led by the crazy Harley Quinn will have to save her. Loud explosions, massive destruction and mild madness reign in the city of Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</guid><description>Game Description Granblue Fantasy: Relink - an adventure in the vastness of the Heavenly Kingdom, where islands soar among the vast azure expanses. As the captain of a skyship, you&amp;rsquo;ll embark on a journey full of mystery, magic and camaraderie. Together with your faithful companions, such as the energetic dragon Virn and the mysterious Lyria, you will go to Estalucia - a mythical island shrouded in legends.
You have to assemble a team of four people, which will include a variety of sky wanderers who own unique weapons and fighting styles.</description></item><item><title>Tekken 8</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</guid><description>Game Description Tekken 8 is a continuation of the cult fighting game, directly continuing the story of the previous part. In the sequel, many beloved heroes return, and new fighters are introduced. A full-fledged story campaign is presented, telling the dramatic story of Jin Kazama&amp;rsquo;s family. In addition, you will find many different modes, including multiplayer battles, various tests, local co-op, the ability to customize fighters, etc.
The gameplay of Tekken 8 is based on a complex combat system based on memorizing combinations and timings of opponents.</description></item><item><title>Anomaly Agent</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomaly-agent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomaly-agent/</guid><description>Game Description Anomaly Agent is a fast-paced 2D action platformer that places players in the heart of a bustling cyberpunk metropolis. As the titular character, Anomaly, players take on the role of an agent on a mission to investigate and eliminate temporary anomalies wreaking havoc on the city. The narrative unfolds gradually, revealing a complex web of interconnected areas with their own unique challenges and mysteries.
At the core of Anomaly Agent&amp;rsquo;s appeal is its innovative combat system, which relies on Anomaly&amp;rsquo;s unique ability to manipulate time.</description></item><item><title>Enshrouded</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</guid><description>Game Description Enshrouded is an exciting game set in the kingdom of Embervale, taking players on an exciting journey through a land once devastated by a devastating magical plague. The user will have to explore the remnants of the lost kingdom, fight mutated creatures and unravel the mysterious secrets of the ancient Flame. One of the distinctive features of the project is the emphasis on the independence of the hero.</description></item><item><title>Palworld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</guid><description>Game Description Palworld offers you to find and use friends as helpers in a huge and dangerous world. The multiplayer survival game has elements of crafting, and the creatures themselves, discovered by the user in the process, become his pet friends, which help him at all stages of the passage, including the ability to move on them, construct buildings, engage in farming, production, and explore dungeons.
The user finds himself in a virtual universe inhabited by bizarre animal creatures, which in this world are simply called Friends.</description></item><item><title>Ready or Not</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ready-or-not/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ready-or-not/</guid><description>Game Description Ready or Not is a tactical shooter that positions itself as a special forces simulator. The project is designed for fans of SWAT 4. The creators tried to focus on realism and cruelty. The game has single player, co-op and PvP. The main gameplay consists of conducting a special operation within the campaign or individual missions. Before you begin, you need to listen to the briefing, study the map of the building, decide on points for the assault and select equipment.</description></item><item><title>SANABI</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sanabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sanabi/</guid><description>Game Description SANABI is a pixel action game with retro style and unique locations. The game takes place in the distant future, where cybernetic prosthetics have become the norm, even if the person has not lost a limb. After all, they can be equipped with various useful technical devices and overcome human abilities. But it has also become a convenient opportunity for criminals to gain easy access to sophisticated weapons.</description></item><item><title>Magicraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/magicraft/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/magicraft/</guid><description>Game Description Magicraft throws you into a world overrun by ancient gods. As a lone hero, you wield a legendary staff - your only hope for salvation. This roguelike focuses on spells that can be combined to create devastating effects. The developers themselves admit that the number of possibilities exceeds their own imagination!
The game world is strange and whimsical, filled with unusual creatures and riddled with a ridiculous plot. Magicraft doesn&amp;rsquo;t take itself too seriously, but rather offers a light-hearted adventure with an emphasis on fun and flashy combat.</description></item><item><title>Lethal Company</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lethal-company/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lethal-company/</guid><description>Game Description Lethal Company is a thrilling co-op horror game that plunges into the eerie depths of abandoned moons in a relentless pursuit of salvageable scrap metal. In the black reaches of space, players will find a menagerie of celestial bodies, alien life forms, and irreplaceable tools to find and use. The unique approach to gameplay ensures endless replayability, offering a variety of dangers and rewards depending on the chosen lunar expedition.</description></item><item><title>EA SPORTS FC 24</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ea-sports-fc-24/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ea-sports-fc-24/</guid><description>Game Description EA SPORTS FC 24 is designed to revolutionize virtual football. With an impressive roster of over 19,000 licensed athletes, over 30 leagues, and recreations of over 100 iconic stadiums, it&amp;rsquo;s a fan&amp;rsquo;s dream. At the heart of FIFA 24 is HyperMotion V, a revolutionary technology that uses volumetric data collected from cameras strategically placed around stadiums during more than 180 top-tier matches. Thanks to this technology, an unreal level of realism is achieved.</description></item><item><title>Rus against lizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rusy-protiv-jascherov/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rusy-protiv-jascherov/</guid><description>Game Description Rus vs. Lizards is a game in which users go on a journey to Ancient Rus' - a world plagued by an invasion of lizards and unholy creatures. In this epic adventure, you take on the role of a blessed hero, charged with the sacred duty of protecting the holy places of the Ancestors from the green plague. In the game you will find intense battles with hordes of lizards and other evil spirits, in which you will be able to show your heroic strength in the name of the Ancestors.</description></item><item><title>Starfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starfield/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starfield/</guid><description>Game Description Starfield opens a new chapter in the gaming universe after a quarter-century hiatus. Bethesda, known for such outstanding projects as The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim and Fallout 4, offers an expansive next-generation role-playing game set in outer space. In 2330, humanity expands far beyond the boundaries of our solar system: pioneers colonize distant planets, turning into a space-faring civilization. Join the ranks of Constellation, a group of intrepid space explorers on a quest to find elusive artifacts scattered across the galaxy in Bethesda&amp;rsquo;s most ambitious endeavor to date.</description></item><item><title>Bomb Rush Cyberfunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bomb-rush-cyberfunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bomb-rush-cyberfunk/</guid><description>Game Description Bomb Rush Cyberfunk is a dynamic 3D platformer that invites you to explore the world of the near future. Cyberfunk has a huge number of techniques, including high speed movement, parkour, dancing, tags, stunts and much more. This is funkstyle! Find your unique handwriting and font. Fight against law enforcement officers and claim your rights to compete in a huge dystopian metropolis.
The game is distinguished by a cartoon style, made to look like a comic book.</description></item><item><title>Tale of Immortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</guid><description>Game Description Tale of Immortal, an open-world sandbox deeply rooted in Chinese mythology and cultivation, invites players into an immersive experience where the path to immortality is paved through strategic choices and the conquest of mythical monsters from the Classic of Mountains and Seasons. Your journey as a novice Qi Refinement Stage cultivator begins in Yukong Village. A world filled with unpredictable monsters, mystical kingdoms and treasures waiting in the wings will open before you.</description></item><item><title>Keeper's Toll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</guid><description>Game Description Keeper&amp;rsquo;s Toll is a fun and challenging game that will test the skills of any gamer who enjoys the classic retro time survival genre. Featuring unique dark fantasy elements, the game boasts a carefully crafted blend of skill-based gameplay, roguelike elements, and unique mechanics that set it apart from others in the genre.
Gamers will be able to choose from six different heroes, each with their own defining mechanics, abilities, and meta progression.</description></item><item><title>Crab Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Crab Champions is one of those projects where the gamer is given control of an extraordinary hero. As you can guess from the name, the characters of the game are crabs. The setting is tropical islands - the player will be surrounded by palm trees, sand, ocean, stones and exotic animals. And also other crabs, armed to the teeth. Crab Champions can be played in three different modes: Co-op.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 4 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-4-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-4-remake/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil 4 Remake is a full-fledged remake of the cult fourth part, which is rightfully considered one of the best in the series. The developers took into account the criticism of fans after the release of the remake of the third game and did not stray far from their roots, adhering to the course taken with Resident Evil 2. The plot has not undergone drastic changes, however, some storylines have been added that were not in the original, the arcs of minor characters have expanded and, Of course, the controls have been improved and the graphics have been significantly updated.</description></item><item><title>The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-black-grimoire-cursebreaker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-black-grimoire-cursebreaker/</guid><description>Game Description The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker is an immersive, atmospheric role-playing adventure that takes you into the fictional world of Imbertal. The game focuses on classic old-school mechanics, allowing you to venture into a dark and dangerous dark fantasy setting. The main character is a cursed lord named Rothar Aekrest, who must deal with problems on his land, facing various obstacles and participating in difficult combat encounters with monsters.
When going to The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker, you have to complete a large number of tasks and gain experience that allows you to upgrade and improve your character’s characteristics or add new skills and abilities.</description></item><item><title>Hogwarts Legacy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hogwarts-legacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hogwarts-legacy/</guid><description>Game Description Hogwarts Legacy is a role-playing game based on the famous books about the boy wizard &amp;ldquo;Harry Potter&amp;rdquo;. The events of Hogwarts: Legacy take place long before the birth of the main character of the books and films. The story dates back to the 19th century, specifically in the 1800s. The game takes place in the same universe and in the same school, so fans of the original saga will find many references and meet some familiar characters.</description></item><item><title>Pizza Tower</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pizza-tower/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pizza-tower/</guid><description>Game Description Pizza Tower stands out with its pixel graphics and animation. The art imitates old cartoon series from the end of the last century. The project also boasts an energetic soundtrack. It is a 2D side-scrolling platformer. This title is the spiritual successor to the video games from the Wario Land series. In it you can walk left and right, run, accelerate, jump, make dashes, break some obstacles, ride mounts, and turn into monsters.</description></item><item><title>Hi-Fi RUSH</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hi-fi-rush/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hi-fi-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Hi-Fi RUSH tells the story of the adventures of a guy named Chai. This music lover without one arm decided to take part in the Armstrong project. Vandeley Technologies provides implants to people with physical disabilities, but in return requires them to work for themselves. The hero was supposed to become a scavenger after receiving a mechanical prosthesis. However, during the operation, a music player is accidentally implanted into his chest and gives him new powers.</description></item><item><title>Lil Gator Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lil-gator-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lil-gator-game/</guid><description>Game Description Lil Gator Game from the first minutes creates a positive atmosphere and invites you to completely immerse yourself in this friendly world. Here, users take on the role of a little crocodile who wants to make new friends. But they need help, so the character will have to get down to business, completing their quests and instructions. And given that the main location in the game is a national park, you will have to spend a lot of time exploring individual areas and finding solutions.</description></item><item><title>HELLSEED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellseed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellseed/</guid><description>Game Description The gloomy atmosphere in HELLSEED is filled with riddles and secrets that the protagonist must cope with. The main character finds himself in Italy in 1980, in the small province of Turin. Users will take on the role of a private investigator who is investigating a strange case. Doctors from a psychiatric hospital are worried about a missing employee who was last at home. Players will explore the estate of the missing doctor, starting from the rooms of his desolate apartment, studying objects and analyzing the situation.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-darktide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-darktide/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Darktide is a co-op first-person shooter. Events take place in the huge city of Tertium on the planet Atom Prime. The cult of insane heretics Admonition is trying to capture him. Four heroes, together with the forces of the Inquisition, must resist Chaos and stop the bloodthirsty horde of the living dead and save the inhabitants from extermination.
Since this is a classic co-op shooter, the gameplay is primarily focused on shooting and killing demonic enemies using melee weapons.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging into ZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>SIGNALIS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/signalis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/signalis/</guid><description>Game Description The space horror film SIGNALIS is made in the style of anime. The indie project is a representative of the old-school survival horror genre. We play as a girl named Elster. She wakes up in a pressure chamber on a ship where something terrible happened. The main character is a Replica - a kind of android analogue. She periodically sees visions of others and picks up strange radio signals.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</guid><description>Game Description Mount and Blade 2 Bannerlord is a role-playing game with elements of medieval wars, the action of which takes place 200 years before the start of Part 1. In this sequel you will find an improved combat system and an enlarged game world - Calradia. Fight with hundreds of troops under your command and take direct part in the battles as one of the soldiers. You can storm enemy fortresses and destroy fortifications with siege weapons in Mount &amp;amp; Blade II: Bannerlord.</description></item><item><title>Vampire Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Survival in the Vampire Survivors universe is based on minimalist gameplay, where you have to move around the map and knock out as much gold as possible. The main task for the protagonist is to advance through the levels generated in roguelight style. You need to try to survive the night, fighting off monsters and higher undead. Vampires will hunt for the protagonist, not giving him the opportunity to rest at a rest or come up with a future plan of action.</description></item><item><title>CULTIC</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultic/</guid><description>Game Description Death in CULTIC is the beginning of a mysterious path, so you shouldn’t be afraid of it. The player will have to muster up the courage to fight through hordes of perverted cultists in order to gain the upper hand in this battle. As the character progresses, he encounters hundreds of NPCs with completely frozen minds, who are guided by blind faith in their ideals. The cultists are further corrupted by an immortal and invisible entity that seeks sole domination of the world.</description></item><item><title>Escape the Backrooms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-backrooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-backrooms/</guid><description>Game Description Atmospheric horror Escape the Backrooms offers cooperative gameplay for up to 4 gamers. A group of people find themselves in a huge and very strange room, from where it is not so easy to find a way out. Users are required to actively interact with each other via voice chat to coordinate actions. It is very important not to separate - you need to move in such a way that users can see each other.</description></item><item><title>Marvel's Spider-Man Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/marvels-spider-man-remastered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/marvels-spider-man-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description Marvel&amp;rsquo;s Spider-Man Remastered is an open-world action-adventure game set in New York City. Supervillains break free in the form of characters such as Mister Negative, Rhino, Scorpio, Vulture and Electro. But before he can track them down, Peter Parker contacts William Fisk. After he arrests a businessman, a gang war breaks out. Now only Spider-Man can stop the crime raging in the city. Marvel&amp;rsquo;s Spider-Man Remastered includes an extensive expansion for The City That Never Sleeps.</description></item><item><title>Cult of the Lamb</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cult-of-the-lamb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cult-of-the-lamb/</guid><description>Game Description In Cult of the Lamb, finding himself in the lands belonging to the false prophets, the gamer is invited to found his own cult, creating a powerful community of admirers. In an adventure game with roguelike elements, the player needs to spread his word to the forest dwellers, gradually making various forays into countries and regions in order to try to expand the sphere of influence of his religion, making it cover all regions.</description></item><item><title>Teardown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</guid><description>Game Description Teardown is a robbery simulator in a variety of conditions prepared by indie developers from Tuxedo Labs. Stylistically, the project was made using a voxel graphic component. This solution made it possible to implement complete destructibility of all available objects in the location. This freedom opens up the possibility of performing operations in a variety of ways, improvising on the fly. The gamer will have at his disposal explosives and a sledgehammer for destroying all kinds of surfaces to penetrate the territory, as well as several types of vehicles of different sizes for loading valuables and other things that need to be stolen according to the terms of a particular task.</description></item><item><title>Elden Ring</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring/</guid><description>Game Description Elden Ring is an open world role-playing game from the creators of Dark Souls and Bloodborne, in collaboration with writer George R.R. Martin. The gameplay is a third-person action RPG where you explore the expanses of a fantasy world, equip yourself with a variety of weapons and fight powerful enemies. In the game, even one enemy poses a serious threat. Battles are based on timing and parries. Carefully study the monsters' patterns to effectively counterattack their attacks.</description></item><item><title>Total War: WARHAMMER 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-3/</guid><description>Game Description Gameplay Total War: WARHAMMER 3 is a mixture of turn-based strategy and RTS. It is necessary to gather an army and move it around the global map, capturing all areas. By extracting resources and recruiting units, you will need to create settlements. You can enter into diplomacy with different factions, enter into alliances with them, or declare war. The economic part of Total War: Warhammer 3 is presented by TBS mechanics, while battles take place in real time.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light 2: Stay Human</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</guid><description>Game Description Dying Light 2: Stay Human starts 15 years after humanity became infected with a terrible virus. Many have turned into zombies who scour in search of living flesh, and the few survivors wage a daily struggle for existence. People are divided into several warring factions, which during the day make forays from shelters to find resources, and at night they hide from bloodthirsty monsters. The world has returned to its primitive state, where everyone fights only for their own lives.</description></item><item><title>God of War (2022)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-2022/</guid><description>Game Description God of War 2022 is an action-adventure game with a third-person view. This project is both a sequel to the previous part and a restart of the entire universe of the famous, cult slasher about the adventures of Kratos – a Spartan warrior, the protagonist of all 8 games in the “God of War” series, fighting against various gods and mythical creatures in a fit of rage and revenge.</description></item><item><title>Monster Hunter Rise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Hunter Rise is a role-playing adventure set in the fictional village of Kamura. The territory is presented in the form of a vast mountainous area with studied hunting equipment and the original culture of the inhabitants. Players will play the role of hunters, and before starting the game they will have to choose one of several types of weapons, armor or special abilities.
The world is filled with ancient ruins, shrines, dungeons and other locations.</description></item><item><title>Battlefield 2042</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-2042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-2042/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 2042 is a tactical action game, the main conflict of which is the confrontation between Russia and the United States in the world of the near future. Humanity has exhausted almost all of the Earth&amp;rsquo;s resources. Now the mighty superpowers have entered the race for the planet&amp;rsquo;s last fossils. Germany lost ground and the EU collapsed. The world is in the midst of a Second Great Depression. The gameplay is a first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Gunfire Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description The shooter Gunfire Reborn contains elements of a roguelike and role-playing game. The player can choose to control several heroes with individual abilities. The game has a huge amount of randomness, from procedurally generated locations to dropped guns and loot. Gunfire Reborn is designed for both one and a company of up to 4 people.
The game features 100 different types of items. Various mechanics will encourage you to study each fighter presented, who are more or less suitable for a specific situation and location.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>MADNESS: Project Nexus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/madness-project-nexus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/madness-project-nexus/</guid><description>Game Description MADNESS: Project Nexus is a three-dimensional dynamic shooter with a side view, as well as a huge number of opponents and violence that happens on the monitor screen. The arcade controls are easy to remember, allowing you to quickly start enjoying the gameplay. This project from indie developers is a driving mixture of beat&amp;rsquo;em&amp;rsquo;up and slasher using not only melee weapons, but also firearms with different damage.
The main feature of the gameplay is the ability to play cooperatively on one personal computer.</description></item><item><title>Webbed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/webbed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/webbed/</guid><description>Game Description The story of Webbed revolves around a happy little spider who tries to save her boyfriend from a huge and annoying bird. Take control of the spider and overcome difficult obstacles until you reach the main character&amp;rsquo;s beloved. Navigate through dangerous locations where predators live or difficult deadly objects are located.
Explore the dangerous desert using your character&amp;rsquo;s abilities and your wits. Visit the tropics, slums and dungeons, where you will encounter original obstacles and enemies.</description></item><item><title>Subnautica: Below Zero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica-below-zero/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica-below-zero/</guid><description>Game Description A game about the underwater world, which became a continuation of the original game, completely borrowing the engine. The world of Subnautica: Below Zero is inhabited not by simple creatures similar to those in the previous part, but by aliens who are more interesting to fight, and their world is much more beautiful than our reality. Adventures will be with you at every step, but do not forget that the world of the game was recognized as a real horror setting, where it is light and bright only in the first hundreds of meters of immersion in depth.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-village/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-village/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil Village continues the adventures of Ethan from the Seven. The Roman numeral hidden in the title on the posters hints that this is not a spin-off, but the eighth part of the series. This is already the tenth project in the main line. Winters was able to escape from the cannibal mansion and save his wife Mia. They got away from the American outback and decided to live an ordinary life.</description></item><item><title>Totally Accurate Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Totally Accurate Battle Simulator is a crazy tactical war game, heavily tied to physics. The battles take place in real time using weapons from different eras. The game is built on the laws of physics, so you can witness the most incredible combat in the history of video games!
One of the main features of the game is its caricature and the creation of the most insane atmosphere of battles.</description></item><item><title>It Takes Two</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/it-takes-two/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/it-takes-two/</guid><description>Game Description The co-op adventure It Takes Two follows two central characters: Cody and May. They decided to get a divorce, which is why they found themselves in a surreal environment, turning into dolls. Now they have to go through hundreds of obstacles and dangers while exploring a new environment. A story about the eternal problems of relationships and how the main characters will reunite after overcoming a ton of obstacles on their own path.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm Doctor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</guid><description>Game Description Rhythm Doctor is an indie game in which you need to treat patients to the rhythm of music. The music in the game has healing properties. Each patient has unusual problems based on music theory: polyrhythms, hemiols, atonality, syncopation, etc. Rhythm Doctor helps you learn music theory through gameplay. The game contains: more than 20 levels with their own stories; each chapter is a rhythmic concept; many doctors and unique patients; single and cooperative mode; about 50 different visual effects and backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Valheim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</guid><description>Game Description Valheim is an open world survival game where you build your own base and fight mythical creatures from Scandinavian folklore. The game takes place in Valheim, the tenth Viking world. The hero&amp;rsquo;s goal is to reach the gates of Valhalla. By killing various monsters and monsters, you earn the blessing of the gods.
The hero will visit various corners of the world: dense forests, snow-capped mountains and much more.</description></item><item><title>Cyberpunk 2077</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyberpunk-2077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyberpunk-2077/</guid><description>Game Description Cyberpunk 2077 is an action role-playing game, the events of which unfold in the futuristic city of Night City, located on the West Coast of the United States. You will play as a protagonist named V (or V). The sex, gender and appearance of the hero must be set independently. Depending on the choice of class, the character&amp;rsquo;s background differs. There are three of them: Nomad, Child of the Street and Corporate.</description></item><item><title>Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</guid><description>Game Description Squad is a military tactical first person shooter game. This is a multiplayer game with an emphasis on realism. An important role is assigned to team interaction between users. This project does not have a story campaign or single player modes. Instead, players in it capture points, destroy weapons depots, or hold the defense.
The title was originally called Project Reality. This was a modification for the second &amp;ldquo;Battle&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Phasmophobia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phasmophobia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phasmophobia/</guid><description>Game Description Phasmophobia is a cooperative horror game designed for four players. The plot is built around paranormal phenomena, where a group of researchers is trying to prove with the help of special equipment that spirits and ghosts exist. You have to collect as much evidence as possible to find out what type of evil entity you are dealing with. Having studied the strengths and weaknesses of otherworldly forces, begin to expel demons.</description></item><item><title>Hades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades/</guid><description>Game Description In the roguelike Hades you will constantly engage in epic battles. Upgrade new abilities by fighting enemies. Gifts can be acquired by meeting the gods of Olympus, who will be happy to give you a piece of their power. Complete the instructions of Zeus, Athena, or simply get to know them to master new skills or equipment. Every time you meet a new character, you will witness some interesting event.</description></item><item><title>ULTRAKILL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultrakill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultrakill/</guid><description>Game Description ULTRAKILL is a game inspired by classic and modern shooters. You will find yourself in a future where people have become extinct. Now the main thing on the planet has become machines whose fuel is blood. There was little valuable liquid left on the surface of the Earth, and so robots began to explore the underground world in search of living creatures. Game Features: Fight multiple enemies. Destroy the risen dead, demonic creatures and other profit seekers.</description></item><item><title>Risk of Rain 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</guid><description>Game Description Risk of Rain 2 is a continuation of the classic online game, which has become better and more complex than the original. The player will challenge the cruel world alone or team up with friends to defeat hordes of monsters, collect the necessary relics and escape from the terrifying planet. With each new attempt, you will be able to better understand the behavior of your opponents and defeat them outright with your skills, even when they are outnumbered.</description></item><item><title>Horizon Zero Dawn Complete Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-zero-dawn-complete-edition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-zero-dawn-complete-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Horizon Zero Dawn is an action game in the world of a post-apocalyptic future, in which the world is inhabited by robotic dinosaurs that destroyed modern civilization. The few surviving people formed into small primitive tribes and resist mechanical monsters using primitive weapons combined with high technology.
The main character of Horizon Zero Dawn is a girl named Aloy. She was raised by a man named Rast, who is an Outcast.</description></item><item><title>The Henry Stickmin Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-henry-stickmin-collection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-henry-stickmin-collection/</guid><description>Game Description The Henry Stickmin Collection - a collection of games about the adventures of Henry Stickmin. This is a series of humorous adventure games that give you freedom of choice. The Henry Stickmin Collection is an updated classic, represented by 6 different games in the series. Both canon endings are included, as well as completely new end credits.
Choice is at the core of The Henry Stickmin Collection&amp;rsquo;s gameplay. At each stage of the adventure you make a choice.</description></item><item><title>There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</guid><description>Game Description There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is a humorous adventure game where you have to click on every element available in the locations. You are taken on an amazing adventure through different video game universes. The visual style of the game is made in a 2D pixel style.
Each of the numerous characters in There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is voiced and played by professional actors. On your way there are many puzzles that need to be solved in an unconventional way.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic is a co-op shooter with fast-paced gameplay in which you will fight with other users against alien monsters. The game is made in a sci-fi style and has procedurally generated levels in which you will fight. The mission can be completed by 1 to 4 players. Act as one. Dig, explore the area and shoot with enemies waiting for you in huge numbers around every corner.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 3 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-3-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-3-remake/</guid><description>Game Description [s][/s] Resident Evil 3: Remake is positioned as a remake of the original Resident Evil 3: Nemesis, released back in 1999. The time gap between the reissue and the original is 20 years. During this time, Capcom managed to radically rethink the series and enrich it with various innovations both in plot and gameplay, since progress does not stand still.
If Resident Evil 2 in 2019 offered the player a slower and more intense gameplay, steeped in horror, then the new product in 2020 looks a little different.</description></item><item><title>GTA 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gta-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gta-4/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 4 became a revolutionary, breakthrough game in the series of criminal action games with a conditionally open world and almost complete freedom of action. It is not only technically and plot-wise different from its predecessors, but also sets a new standard of quality for all representatives of this and other genres. It is worth noting that the concept of GTA has gone far beyond the scope of this franchise, and some mechanics from this series of games are used in projects from other studios.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life: Alyx</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-alyx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-alyx/</guid><description>Game Description Half-Life: Alyx became the first AAA quality game in history for virtual reality devices, the passage of which can be enjoyed on a PC only with the help of an appropriate device, namely a VR headset from Steam and related gadgets. The plot is a spin-off, the events of which unfold in the interval between the actions of the first and second parts. The Black Mesa Incident allowed Alliance forces to gain a foothold on the planet, leaving the remaining humans trapped in the cities.</description></item><item><title>DOOM Eternal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-eternal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-eternal/</guid><description>Game Description DOOM Eternal, a first-person shooter, continues the campaign of DOOM (developed in 2016). Our hero is the Doom Slayer. He will kill mutants and monsters on the territory of Mars, the attached spaceship, its satellites and Earth. In many ways, the plot scenes are taken from the second part of the series. The main addition to the game was moving through the levels. If earlier we could move to the next level only after finishing it, then in the new part it will be possible to “climb” to another location where the events of the next level take place.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 3 is a continuation of the acclaimed series of shooters, containing tons of loot. The player will take on the role of one of the Vault Hunters and set off to explore the expanses of Pandora. All heroes have their own tree of characteristics, unique abilities and character. The gameplay allows you to go through the adventure solo or enlist the help of friends.
The protagonist of Borderlands 3 learned to climb ledges and make tackles.</description></item><item><title>Ori and the Will of the Wisps</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ori-and-the-will-of-the-wisps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ori-and-the-will-of-the-wisps/</guid><description>Game Description Ori and the Will of the Wisps is an adventure platformer with stunning hand-drawn graphics. You will find yourself in distorted lands that you must save from evil and overcome all the obstacles prepared by fate for the main character.
You will take control of the little spirit Ori, who knows a lot about the obstacles and pitfalls of this world. Your owl friend Ku is in trouble after another flight.</description></item><item><title>Black Mesa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-mesa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-mesa/</guid><description>Game Description Black Mesa is a remake of the cult shooter Half-Life, which at one time turned out to be a breakthrough in the world of video games and made the name of Valve. They worked on this project for eight whole years, during which the creators tried to transfer the old game to the new Source engine with varying success. As a result, they managed to achieve the desired effect and in May 2015 the game was released.</description></item><item><title>Senren＊Banka</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</guid><description>Game Description Senren＊Banka is primarily aimed at anime fans. The project uses the appropriate style (including chibi art) and Japanese voice acting. The plot combines romantic, tragic, mystical and humorous elements. The story revolves around supernatural incidents. A group of young people are trying to hide them from ordinary people.
The premise in Senren＊Banka: A Thousand Colors of Love is as follows. A guy named Arichi Masaomi comes to the provincial town of Hoori in the summer.</description></item><item><title>Red Dead Redemption 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption-2/</guid><description>Game Description Red Dead Redemption 2 is a third-person shooter adventure game set in the Wild West in 1899. The action involves the Dutch Van Der Linde gang, which is being pursued by lawmen after a botched ferry robbery. The player will take control of Arthur Morgan, one of the gang members.
Some time after the unsuccessful prank, the gang decides that it is time to retire and live the rest of their lives like ordinary people, not bandits.</description></item><item><title>Halo: The Master Chief Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halo-the-master-chief-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halo-the-master-chief-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Halo: The Master Chief Collection is a complete collection of the cult shooter series about the Master Chief. The collection includes all numbered games in the series that were released before Halo: Infinite. At the same time, the developers have improved the visual component of the game, providing 4k resolution and HDR support for modern monitors.
The story tells of the confrontation between the United Nations Space Command and the religious alien alliance Covenant.</description></item><item><title>Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-jedi-fallen-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-jedi-fallen-order/</guid><description>Game Description In the epic game Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order you will find amazing adventures, new challenges, modern graphics and high-quality laser sword battles! Immerse yourself in this saga of the Jedi and intergalactic war, in which you will play one of the key roles. The story takes place after Episode III, 5 years after the ominous Order 66. You will take on the role of a young Jedi Padawan who barely managed to escape from a trap created by the Sith.</description></item><item><title>Age of Empires 2: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Empires 2: Definitive Edition is a re-release of the classic real-time strategy game released in 1999 under the name &amp;ldquo;The Age of Kings&amp;rdquo;. The game is famous for the fact that the player develops his civilization from the Stone Age to the Modern Age. The gameplay is based on the fact that it is necessary to hire peasants, gather troops, erect buildings, study maps, develop the era and explore new capabilities, technologies and, most importantly, destroy the enemy.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>People Playground</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/people-playground/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/people-playground/</guid><description>Game Description People Playground is an indie game, a kind of murder simulator in different ways. Here you can simply drag mannequins of creatures across the screen and throw them from a height, or create dangerous situations with your own hands - accidents, torture chambers, obstacle courses. There are 5 types of creatures available for destruction: a fragile person, a heavier and stronger robot, a gorse (spider), a regular and improved turret.</description></item><item><title>Total War: THREE KINGDOMS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Total War: THREE KINGDOMS is the first game in the series that recreates epic conflicts in Ancient China. The game combines a turn-based campaign of empire building and conquest with epic real-time battles. 190 AD. A beautiful but fragmented country awaits a new emperor and a new life. The player will have to unify China, create the next great dynasty and leave a legacy that will endure for millennia.</description></item><item><title>Beat Saber</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beat-saber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beat-saber/</guid><description>Game Description A musical game designed for the good taste of the player Beat Saber. The levels are a small interactive location where blocks of 2 colors fly towards the player. The player must cut these blocks. The difficulty of the game is that the number of blocks and the method of destruction are always different. For example, in some levels you will have to chop them with a sword of a certain color, in others you will have to hit them from the right side.</description></item><item><title>MORDHAU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mordhau/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mordhau/</guid><description>Game Description MORDHAU is a hack and slash game. Fights take place online on the company’s servers; offline you can train your skills in fights against artificial intelligence. A training session is also available, in which you will learn the basic mechanics and get your initial gold capital.
The name refers to a special German grip on the weapon, which, by the way, is available for selection. The main, but not the only feature is a fencing system that is as close to reality as possible, created through consultations with experts.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the average ratings for the 10th part of the franchise, Mortal Kombat 11 became a continuation of the story, and the developers tried to improve and add a lot of new things to players. The eleventh fighting game in the Mortal Kombat universe has new gameplay, plot, graphics, and character relationships that reveal the story as it progresses. We arrive in the world after the defeat of Shinnok, who was defeated by Cassie Cage.</description></item><item><title>Katana ZERO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/katana-zero/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/katana-zero/</guid><description>Game Description Katana ZERO is an extraordinary and dynamic platformer in the genre of science fiction and action, created in the best traditions of pixel graphics. The plot of the game tells us about a dystopian city, the main character lives in the third quarter, his name is Zero. He was severely wounded in the war, causing him to lose his memory. At night he has nightmares about past battles, and during the day he has to visit a psychotherapist.</description></item><item><title>Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sekiro-shadows-die-twice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sekiro-shadows-die-twice/</guid><description>Game Description Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice is an incredibly challenging action game that makes feudal Japan look dark, burning, and beautiful at the same time. The third-person stealth action game combines the features of RPGs and the themes of Souls games. Well-designed graphics of feudal Japan allow us to plunge into the difficult process of returning our master of the Ashina clan. The leader of the opposition - Genichiro - kidnapped a samurai from Shinobi, and now we must cope with a huge number of his followers in order to save the teacher, master, master and good friend who paid us well in a past life.</description></item><item><title>Devil May Cry 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/devil-may-cry-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/devil-may-cry-5/</guid><description>Game Description Devil May Cry 5 is a new third-person slasher for fans of the series. Dante and Nero return to the game universe to defeat all the demons, but will they have a different task? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look. The developers did not touch the game mechanics; they only significantly changed the speed of the battle. If shooters have a subgenre - FPS - then this slasher is an analogue.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of Space Engineers is that you will build space stations, ships, and begin to study neighboring planets and passing asteroids, where you will find many useful resources. Control is carried out from the perspective of a person, a ship, a base, a flying station, and you can change the camera view from both the third and first person.
When you create a world, the game automatically generates a random sequence of planets on which you can find valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Luna Nights</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-luna-nights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-luna-nights/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Luna Nights is a platformer that immerses you in the atmosphere of gothic mysticism. The main character is Sakuya Izaei, who works as a senior maid for the vampire Remilia Scarlet. The girl was calmly doing housework when the mistress deprived her of her powers and sent her to the “Magical Space.” Sakuya is looking for her way home and is eager to find out what her treacherous boss is up to.</description></item><item><title>Metro Exodus: Gold Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The events of Metro Exodus - a first-person shooter with elements of stealth and horror - take place in the same areas as the previous parts. The Russian Federation and the Republic of Kazakhstan are still waging a fierce war for life inside, in underground territories, with representatives of hostile clans, factions and monsters who devour, rather than kill, their prey. Artyom leaves the Order after the battle for D6.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 2 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description RESIDENT EVIL 2 / BIOHAZARD RE:2 - a complete rework, allowing players to enjoy modern graphics, a new engine, enemies, weapons and a much more advanced game story. Follow the story of police officer Leon S. Kennedy and student Claire Redfield.
Due to an unknown outbreak of a virus, the entire city of Raccoon City was enveloped in monsters, people began to turn into strange creatures, and then kill the survivors.</description></item><item><title>Bloons TD 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</guid><description>Game Description Bloons TD 6 (Bloons Tower Defense 6) is a 2018 action strategy game where the player will have to defend a fortress with the help of monkeys. The goal of the game is to destroy a stream of fast-moving balloons. The fewer goals missed, the greater the chances of winning. The balls differ in appearance and characteristics - new ones have been added in this part: purple, reinforced and impenetrable.</description></item><item><title>DayZ</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</guid><description>Game Description The multiplayer sandbox DayZ is a reworked version of the mod of the same name for Arma 2. The game is distinguished by its extremely realistic setting and hardcore survival in a post-apocalyptic environment. The game takes place in the fictional post-Soviet country of Chernarus. After the outbreak of an unknown virus, most of the population has turned into zombies, and the survivors are forced to fight for their lives and valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency: Sandstorm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency: Sandstorm is a sequel to a multiplayer shooter built on deathmatches in confined spaces, with the ability to use light vehicles. The game has been significantly improved and expanded. The key to victory lies only through well-coordinated teamwork.
The action takes place in the Middle East, on the ruins of settlements and military bases. You need to carefully choose your weapon and explore the territory, because without caution and tactics you can quickly catch a bullet in the forehead.</description></item><item><title>DUSK</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dusk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dusk/</guid><description>Game Description DUSK is a canonical first-person shooter created in a retro style. The plot is quite simple and clear - there is a small town called DUSK, in its vicinity ruins were discovered that have mystical properties. Many scientists and soldiers came here, studying strange objects and everyone gradually went crazy. They became possessed, and the government surrounded the entire area with a wall. A brave hero was found who entered the forbidden territory in search of these unique artifacts, but was captured by occultists and hung on hooks.</description></item><item><title>Kenshi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</guid><description>Game Description Kenshi forces you to survive from the very first minutes of the game. An impressive RPG with an open world and the ability to create your own squad, the remaining player privileges are gradually revealed to us. For example, you can build your own buildings in any location, conquer them from other factions, create your own business, sell goods in peaceful settlements, craft whatever you want, explore the environment and do whatever you want.</description></item><item><title>Among Us</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/among-us/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/among-us/</guid><description>Game Description Among Us (Among As) is a multiplayer game designed for 4 to 10 people on the server at the same time for exciting gameplay with a variety of scenarios. The setting of the project is boundless outer space, in which maps with different structures of surrounding objects are located. Casual controls and the ability to play on a local network in cross-platform mode make it possible to invite a noisy group to spend time together on the Among Us project.</description></item><item><title>BATTLEFIELD 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-5/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 5 is a first-person shooter, the fifteenth game in the Battlefield series. Unlike previous games in the series, Battlefield 5 sacrifices historical accuracy for the sake of the player: weapon handling, for example, has been noticeably improved, making the game more like an arcade shooter. Most of the changes made to BFV are solid improvements over its predecessor.
War Stories is a series of single-player missions introduced in Battlefield V, where the player is invited to become an eyewitness to tragic events.</description></item><item><title>Assassins Creed Odyssey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-odyssey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-odyssey/</guid><description>Game Description For the first time in the history of the series, you will be able to choose a character for whom you will administer justice and change history. Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed Odyssey is the first slasher RPG in the history of the developers, in which we do not play as an assassin, but choose a real warrior of Ancient Greece! We are offered two characters to choose from: Alexios or Kassandra.</description></item><item><title>SCUM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</guid><description>Game Description SCUM is another survival game set in a completely open world. The developers tried to make the gameplay and the story of the characters so absurd that the very fact of some actions causes disgust. The plot reveals to us a modern society that wants nothing more than to “watch the spectacle.” The well-known producer TEC1 organized a show with the name - Scam - where people are thrown out in an open location, forced to survive without everything, and after that they are gradually introduced to a series of difficulties: a zombie epidemic, robots, dangerous animals, or money with the promise that once they get out , players will be able to spend them to buy freedom in the new society.</description></item><item><title>MONSTER HUNTER: WORLD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-world/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of MONSTER HUNTER: WORLD has been slightly reworked compared to the previous part. We don&amp;rsquo;t just kill monsters, make new equipment, but now weapons are divided into several classes, and, in fact, at the beginning of the game we are something like a “neutral character”. In the new ecosystem, hunters have emerged who will create incredibly difficult conditions for the existence of monsters. Dragons, flying dinosaurs (not like dragons), and other creatures inhabit this eco-system.</description></item><item><title>Dead Cells</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-cells/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-cells/</guid><description>Game Description A stunning rogue-like platformer with metroidvania elements - Dead Cells - features a real fight between the hero and constantly changing levels on the territory of the castle. Our hero is a creature who is trying to get out of the castle&amp;rsquo;s maze. He will try over and over again to cope with constantly generated opponents. But in random places on the map you will find many weapons with random characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Yakuza 0</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yakuza-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yakuza-0/</guid><description>Game Description As a dialogue-heavy role-playing game that explores a deep story, Yakuza 0 claims to be a game that combines friendship, self-love, and the search for true calling. The Yakuza is the largest mafia group in Japan, which controls everything that can be controlled. Events begin in 1988, when two Yakuza characters - Kazuma Kiryu and Goro Majima - take part in a battle for a small industrial plot in the center of Kamurocho.</description></item><item><title>DARK SOULS: REMASTERED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description DARK SOULS: REMASTERED is an already iconic Japanese action/RPG released in 2011. The development was carried out by From Software. A remastered version was released in May 2018 at the instigation of QLOC. So, what are the acclaimed “Dark Souls”? Firstly, this is a high-quality action RPG, with a third-person view. At the very beginning, you will need to set a number of characteristics for your character: appearance and class.</description></item><item><title>Conan Exiles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</guid><description>Game Description Conan Exiles is an amazing multiplayer survival game with RPG and action elements. Employees of the Norwegian company Funcom worked on the project. The project was released at the end of spring 2018. Stunning graphics are a rare quality that developers of various MMORPG games pay attention to. But this time everything happened exactly the opposite. Funcom, 10 years before Conan Exiles, had already released a similar game called Age Of Conan.</description></item><item><title>The Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forest/</guid><description>Game Description A survival simulator on an inhabited island - The Forest - was made in graphics that were new for that time, opening up completely ambiguous gameplay for the protagonist. We play as a character who finds himself on an inhabited island and now must survive under any conditions. Attacking cannibal natives, animals, lack of food, water and shelter - these are all just little things. A plane crashed not far from your island, and you are the only survivor in these conditions.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</guid><description>Game Description Finally, the plot of Far Cry 5 has reached America. Crazed fanatics unleashed their might on the state of Montana. A first-person shooter with action elements brings us to a reality in which even the movements of dogs will be more than real. The modernization of the shooter took several years, so the development studio warns us in advance that the game is based on religious motives. Age limit: 18+.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer: Vermintide 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-vermintide-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-vermintide-2/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer: Vermintide 2 is a first-person slasher with abilities, magic, character upgrades, a variety of weapons and meat, combining a unique combat system of 5 different factions. The modernized first part is made on a new graphics engine, allowing us to see every severed limb; look at dead enemies and collect dropped loot around them, not paying attention to graphical inaccuracies.
The plot of Warhammer: Vermintide 2 revolves around Helmgarth Castle, surrounded by a small settlement.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-come-deliverance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-come-deliverance/</guid><description>Game Description The plot of Kingdom Come: Deliverance takes place in a simple European village. We play as the son of a blacksmith. Our name is Henry. The civil war affected not only the political upheaval, but also ordinary villages and people like yours. Friends, family and your entire lineage have been slaughtered by brutal mercenaries in a sinister plot. We miraculously managed to survive, so we take the last sword forged by our father and march against the army of godless people!</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>Celeste</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celeste/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celeste/</guid><description>Game Description Madeline must climb Celeste . No one knows why she needs this, but the characters around her gradually reveal this secret to us. The game is a complex platformer that combines a storyline, pixel graphics, character leveling and aspects of human existence buried in dialogue scripts.
The heroine will fight with ghosts in abandoned cities, with her demons while she walks into the wasteland; will explore the secret corners of his soul while learning a new location and ways to climb the mountain more painlessly.</description></item><item><title>Subnautica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica/</guid><description>Game Description In the world of Subnautica, your ship has crashed in an oceanic area, and there is only one straight line - down to the bottom. The landscapes around you are illuminated by the sun, the coral reefs shimmer beautifully under the sun as you slowly sink towards the endless darkness of space. Exploring a huge open world allows you not only to plunge under the water and look at the inhabitants of this ocean, but also to build your own underwater base there and build a research center on it.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulator CarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>Assassin's Creed Origins</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-origins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-origins/</guid><description>Game Description The story of the third-person slasher is fully explored in Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed Origins. Only in this part we are told and described in detail how the brotherhood of Assassins was actually created, why the entire caste of killers hid for several hundred years, and how the principles of the brotherhood were formed.
The plot begins with the fact that we kill one of the pharaohs who own an entire pyramid, hundreds of subjects and countless hired killers.</description></item><item><title>Middle-earth: Shadow of War - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The action takes place in the fictional world of the writer Tolkien. The Middle Lands are full of adventures for our player, so the plot unfolds from half of them. Events introduce us to the continuation of the previous part. Talion and Celebrimbor forge a new ring, which Sauron does not know about - he will not be able to influence it. The new ring carries with it another responsibility: in Middle-earth: Shadow of War, Celebrimbor loses his freedom in exchange for a new One Ring.</description></item><item><title>A Hat in Time</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-hat-in-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-hat-in-time/</guid><description>Game Description In the 3D platformer A Hat in Time we will have to play as a girl who both looks and is called Hat Girl. She goes on an interplanetary journey to return home, but ends up in the city of the Mafia. At this location, a Mafioso gets into our ship and completely inspects the ship, but after checking, he scatters “time particles”, and then spreads them throughout the entire Mafia planet.</description></item><item><title>Cuphead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cuphead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cuphead/</guid><description>Game Description In Cuphead we choose one of two heroes and set off to conquer a world that looks like very old cartoons, with tons of weapons, special moves and immortality. A classic, in the truest sense of the word, platformer, in which everything is set in the world of the 1930s. The music is jazz accompaniment, the graphics are standard Disney of the time, and the bosses are neither good nor evil.</description></item><item><title>Stick Fight: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Stick Fight: The Game is a multiplayer platformer with fighting game elements. Players control colorful people, overcoming obstacles and fighting each other. The main gameplay consists of moving, jumping and reacting quickly. On the path of the heroes there will be deadly obstacles that will take the lives of all those who hesitated even a little and did not react to the situation. Game features: from 2 to 4 players over a local or online network; physics-based combat system; about 100 well-developed and detailed locations; includes a level editor; various ranged and melee weapons; procedurally generated and contextual animations based on the system Totally Accurate Battle Simulator.</description></item><item><title>Total War: WARHAMMER 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-2/</guid><description>Game Description Total War: WARHAMMER 2 is a turn-based strategy that invites you to immerse yourself in the gloomy campaign of the New World. The gameplay is highlighted by large-scale battles between six races. Enter the battlefield to save or destroy the world. Total War Warhammer 2 consists of two parts: a turn-based campaign in the open world and tactical battles in real time.
Play both in single mode and take part in multiplayer battles.</description></item><item><title>ARK: Survival Evolved</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</guid><description>Game Description The world of ARK: Survival Evolved is a setting full of dangers, in which not only dinosaurs, but also other creatures will try to kill you. People become especially dangerous. The game does not have any interesting plot, but there is a huge open world in which you have to build your base, hunt with a group of people (your friends), attack, defend, make weapons and explore the area.</description></item><item><title>VTOL VR</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vtol-vr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vtol-vr/</guid><description>Game Description VTOL VR is a military flight simulator with a first-person view and in the surroundings of the near future. The game requires a VR headset and a motion controller. The title allows you to freely rotate your head while sitting in the virtual cockpit. Modes include training, campaign and free flight. There are a lot of tasks here. In addition to other aircraft, ships, tanks, anti-aircraft and artillery installations act as opponents and allies.</description></item><item><title>Slime Rancher</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slime-rancher/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slime-rancher/</guid><description>Game Description A funny open-world first-person shooter - Slime Rancher is a mixture of genres in one complex picture, which the developers called - Boundless Outland. We plunge into a special experimental environment. Our hero&amp;rsquo;s name is Beatrix LeBeau, and he is a farmer. Armed with courage, madness and a funny vacuum cleaner, he decides to stay on the planet of the Boundless Outlands, because a certain Hobson Twillgers left us his farm.</description></item><item><title>The Long Dark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</guid><description>Game Description A game about survival in a world without electricity. The Long Dark is eternal darkness in locations, gorgeous graphics from developers who love the sky and stars as their second home. Players were pleased that the entire gameplay is divided into two modes. The first is a story-based passage of 5 episodes, the total duration of which is 60-70 hours, depending on how the plot is followed. The second mode is survival in an excellent open world, where you will have to keep an eye on the contents of your backpack, check for items, collect skins, fry meat, take refuge in shelters, furnish your own house or a small corner in a house for survivors, where the owner of this establishment will shelter you.</description></item><item><title>Ravenfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</guid><description>Game Description The team-tactical shooter Ravenfield will allow you to plunge into furious battles, where you have everything - from tanks to fleets. There is a complete lack of storyline and even multiplayer. The latter fact is extremely unusual for projects of this genre. It would seem that it is interesting to play against bots and when there are no real users on the map. This omission at first glance is more than compensated for by a fairly developed artificial intelligence - opponents and allies behave extremely intelligently and together with them you can perform a variety of tactics using numerous commands and options.</description></item><item><title>Little Nightmares</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-nightmares/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-nightmares/</guid><description>Game Description Little Six is ​​a girl who was brought on board the ship as a servant. She, like many nomes - the characters of the game - hides her face for unknown reasons. In the game we have to get out from the lowest sector to the upper decks, but the levels will not immediately allow us to do this. First, the player needs to know that sinister hands will always hunt for us.</description></item><item><title>NieR: Automata</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</guid><description>Game Description An open-world action-adventure game, NieR: Automata tells the story of androids 2B, 9S and A2 as they battle a dystopia created by powerful machines. All of humanity was evicted from their planet by mechanical creatures that arrived from another world.
In an attempt to retake the Earth from aliens, people send combat robots to somehow resist the invaders. This must be the final attempt, the last hope to get your home back.</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Wildlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the new part - Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands - truly inspires what the developers tried to convict all players of. It must be said, but there is no plot in a third-person shooter. You independently write the story of your team, which is initially aimed at destroying the cartel that trades and produces drugs. But more on that later.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s worth discussing the inner world of Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands.</description></item><item><title>Hollow Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollow-knight/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollow-knight/</guid><description>Game Description The classic action-platformer gives us several hours of exciting travel into underground cities to creatures that have only guarded wealth for the last thousand years, being possessed by it. Our hero in Hollow Knight is one of those who believe in legends. He goes to the dungeons under Mudmouth to gain riches, fame, general respect and popularity among the knights who did not gather the strength to descend, but will it really be so?</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 7: Biohazard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil 7: Biohazard is a survival horror game that continues the famous series of games, one of the founders of the genre. The release is timed to coincide with the twentieth anniversary of the universe. An option is available to play using a virtual reality helmet and control of special complete controllers from VR glasses.
The seventh part was a return to the roots of the first games in the series, because, unlike parts 5 and 6, which were focused on action, shooting and the plot taking place in different parts of the world, this project has the main location in the form of a small estate of the Baker family, which gives the atmosphere is claustrophobic and increases the degree of fear.</description></item><item><title>Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</guid><description>Game Description Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun is a tactical stealth action game set in the Japanese Edo era (1603-1868). A conspiracy led by Kage-sama is carried out against the new shogun, after he was able to unite the lands of Japan. In order not to destroy the world, the ruler instructs his henchman samurai named Mugen to track down Kage-sama and his organization. For these purposes, the hero enlists the support of four companions - masters of secrecy and penetration.</description></item><item><title>Killing Floor 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</guid><description>Game Description A cooperative first-person shooter in which there are only two modes - survival and battle in the territory. Killing Floor 2 does not have a plot, but there is sharp FPS on several maps, where each player chooses the desired role for himself - a zombie or a department fighting an epidemic. In addition to the fact that the gameplay differs on both sides of the barricades, players can buy additional weapons, make skins and show who can stand up best on the map.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim Special Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim-special-edition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim-special-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Skyrim has become one of the favorite games on two continents of our planet. The first/third person slasher captivated players not only with its open-world RPG content, but also with its graphics, sounds, characters, features, and, of course, dragons.
Our character in The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim Special Edition begins the same story, but you immediately notice that everything around him is completely different. If in the original version of the game we move along a snowy road, now the colors of the autumn forest prevail, maintaining the same atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Titanfall 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/titanfall-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/titanfall-2/</guid><description>Game Description Titanfall 2 is a first-person shooter in a fantasy future setting. Continuation of the first game, released in 2014. In this part, in addition to online battles, there is a single-player campaign about Jack Cooper, a soldier who does not have his own titanium, but wants to get it. At the center of the story is the conflict between the militia, assembled from the common people, and the giant corporation IMC.</description></item><item><title>Battlefield 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-1/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 1 is a first-person shooter in the setting of the First World War. The game is the 15th in the series of the same name. The plot is divided into five chapters and begins with a prologue. The story takes place in 1918 and is told from the perspective of tankman Daniel Edwards, who controls the Black Bass tank. Before the war, he was an ordinary driver, but now he has to break through the German line.</description></item><item><title>No Man's Sky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</guid><description>Game Description Travel on an intergalactic level has become too simple and ordinary. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly difficult to create a game that captivates with its graphics, but the developers of No Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky, an indie adventure game with an open world and a wonderful RPG base, were able to recreate the image of space. Distant, limitless, completely open and so human.
We play as a character, but then our gameplay switches to an entire space station or ship.</description></item><item><title>DOOM (2016)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-2016/</guid><description>Game Description DOOM 2016, unlike DOOM Ethernal, has less dynamics, but is more related to the horror genre. We can say that it began the evolution of the series towards speed and platforming, and it is considered closer in spirit to the series than its brother released in 2020. It was the first step towards a global rethinking of the franchise.
The game takes place inside the corridors of a giant research complex.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve Together is a survival simulator in an unknown world, where our character, pre-selected in the editor, wakes up and immediately goes to look for firewood, because Maxwell said so. The game is cooperative, since the story passage is divided into 2 parts. The first is survival. It is built on three phases of the day: day, evening and night.
During the day, your character calmly survives, collects items, crafts new ones, eats and carries out orders for Maxwell.</description></item><item><title>DARK SOULS 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-3/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of DARK SOULS 3 provides all the same opportunities that were in the second part. For us, a third-person slasher with elements of stealth and survival remained at the same level in terms of combat, but the entire combat system was made more dynamic. So much so that sometimes we don’t have time to jump away to recharge our skill, and they already kill us. The real hassle and face of the game genre is difficulty at every turn.</description></item><item><title>Enter the Gungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enter-the-gungeon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enter-the-gungeon/</guid><description>Game Description In Enter the Gungeon you will remember such a genre as bullet hell or “hell of bullets”. The main characters explore the Gungeon and try to find a legendary artifact - a weapon that can kill the past. To do this, you need to fight your way through hordes of monsters and defeat formidable bosses. Loot, secrets, penny-pinching merchants and shopkeepers, new equipment and more loot - the recipe for a good game.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</guid><description>Game Description The game Hot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades can be called a full-fledged weapons simulator. You need to go to the training ground, which contains a huge selection of different firearms: pistols, machine guns, shotguns, rocket launchers, grenades, etc. You can use any available ammunition, training on targets and taking the highest positions on the leaderboard. Afterwards you can go and set off fireworks.
Targets can be not only static within the walls of a gray pavilion, but also moving in open space.</description></item><item><title>Grim Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grim-dawn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grim-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description The gloomy dawn in Grim Dawn showed that the fabric of the created universe was too weak, so Cairn accepted robbers, bandits, magicians and a bunch of all kinds of creatures and undead into its embrace. Dark times have come to the territory of Cairn. But after that, people did not give up trying to attack their enemies, and called aliens into the world. They opened portals for them and let in several individuals to receive ether.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Our task in Rise of the Tomb Raider is to get ahead of your enemies, go on your first expedition and watch interactive videos, of which there are at least 1.5 hours of gameplay in the game. Lara Croft goes to the unknown world of the city of Kitezh. A secret organization called “Trinity” is also heading there. The principle of the game about Lara is an adventure game mixed with the adventure romance of the first journey, in which we kill with a bow, collect important items, and sometimes survive in the wild.</description></item><item><title>NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-4/</guid><description>Game Description Familiar to many fans of the Naruto series, NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM 4 transcends the fighting game genre, taking the game to the next level. In the final part, we will find out who will win in the confrontation between Naruto and Sasuke. We will learn a lot of details about the 4th Shinobi War, and also go over some aspects of the anime that were missed in previous parts.</description></item><item><title>XCOM 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</guid><description>Game Description Twenty years ago, people signed an act of complete surrender of the earth to the aliens. Another civilization has shown that there is no hope for salvation, and therefore alien invaders have taken over the entire planet. At the beginning of XCOM 2 we are shown a video from the current ruler of the planet (in fact, this is a staged, drawn character, he is controlled by aliens), who says that today is the day when the aliens captured us, and the earth plunged into peace; Today we celebrate 20 years of freedom.</description></item><item><title>Scrap Mechanic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</guid><description>Game Description Scrap Mechanic is a multiplayer engineering sandbox that offers you to design various mechanisms and compete with friends. The game world revolves around a mechanic who maintains robots on an agricultural planet. He makes sure that they are working properly: that they are cultivating the land on time, sowing, collecting raw materials, which the hero then sends to the central planets, where people live ordinary lives. But one day the spaceship crashed, and the robots around went crazy.</description></item><item><title>The Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</guid><description>Game Description The island on which The Isle takes place has a rich and varied environment that is randomly generated. All artifacts, items and events will be located in different places with each new launch. Players must team up to effectively explore the area, which contains many secrets, including various quest items that further advance the plot. The map contains an area of ​​16x16 square kilometers. Multiplayer survival game The Isle allows you to play with three different factions in three different modes:</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</guid><description>Game Description A new installment in the first-person shooter, Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Rainbow Six Siege is a game of multiplayer destruction. We will not just destroy the map to which we and our friends were sent, but we will build traps, plant a bomb, and all this at a distance of a bow shot. The technical equipment of the new part is made specifically so that you can blow up everything in the open location of each level.</description></item><item><title>Just Cause 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</guid><description>Game Description Just Cause 3 is a continuation of the famous franchise about the adventures of a specially trained agent named Rico Rodriguez. This part of the series did not deviate from the style and genre of previous games in the universe where the mercenary nicknamed “Scorpio” lives. The end of the trilogy is made with the same driving action, open world, a large number of tricks and devices available in the protagonist’s arsenal, and an adventure plot in which the fate of an entire state will be at stake.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</guid><description>Game Description Fallout 4 is a sequel to the famous role-playing game series in a post-apocalyptic setting. The player wakes up from cryosleep and discovers that he is the only survivor of Vault 111. Having made it to the surface, he finds himself in the Wasteland - a world destroyed by nuclear war. The gameplay includes: a free open world with hundreds of locations to explore, a huge number of NPCs, companions and quests, as well as interaction with many factions, including the Institute, the Brotherhood of Steel, the Minutemen and agents of the Underground; S.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter Call of Duty: Black Ops III demonstrates the blurred relationship between ordinary people and technology. In it you will forever forget that the new generation of soldiers is not a fiction, but a reality that will overtake us in the near future. Humanity has created technology to be leaders in the coming war, but will it be? The game shows this in three modes: story campaign, multiplayer shooter at scenario locations, and also in zombie mode.</description></item><item><title>Broforce</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</guid><description>Game Description Broforce is a powerful paramilitary organization that is called upon when the world is in danger due to an excessive number of evil forces. Take control of dozens of different brothers to counter terrorist attacks and save civilians. Destroy your opponents with napalm, shooting, lightning and other various character skills.
Broforce is a 2D shooter platformer with pixel graphics. You will move around locations, destroying opponents in every possible way.</description></item><item><title>Metal Gear Solid 5: The Phantom Pain</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-5-the-phantom-pain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-5-the-phantom-pain/</guid><description>Game Description Metal Gear Solid 5: The Phantom Pain is a continuation of the famous series of stealth shooters from the recognized master of game design and production Hideo Kojima. The plot taking place in this game becomes a prequel to the very first game in the universe - Metal Gear. It forms a complete picture with the prologue released a little earlier - Metal Gear Solid V: Ground Zeroes.</description></item><item><title>BeamNG drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</guid><description>Game Description BeamNG.drive is a car simulator that simulates the behavior of cars during collisions. Excellent physics, realistic controls and spectacular accidents are the main features of the game. The simulator allows you to find out what the consequences will be if, for example, the steering wheel of a Ferrari jams and the car flies into the oncoming lane, where it collides with a 40-ton truck. Or assess the damage to an army jeep whose brakes jammed when it was going down a hill at a speed of 90 km/h, flew off the road and crashed into a tree.</description></item><item><title>The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-3-dikaja-ohota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-3-dikaja-ohota/</guid><description>Game Description The legendary third-person slasher series - The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt, which tells us the story of Geralt of Rivia, who becomes one of the few characters in the central series of action-packed books. We start the game remembering the events of the second part. But let&amp;rsquo;s not talk about them. Our hero is a born killer, capable of killing and ending the lives of thieves, criminals, assassins, kings, leaders, generals and monsters living throughout the map.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 5 has received dozens of awards for its open world, and almost the most expensive multi-platform project in history is Grand Theft Auto V. The story opens before us in the same fictional state - San Andreas, made 1 to 1 as Southern California. We play as three robber friends who have spent their entire adult lives stealing cars, robbing small shops and people on the street. One day someone decides to get involved in organized crime, which they have been fighting for the last 5 years.</description></item><item><title>Dark Souls 2: Scholar of the First Sin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-2-scholar-of-the-first-sin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-2-scholar-of-the-first-sin/</guid><description>Game Description DARK SOULS 2: Scholar of the First Sin takes the dark atmosphere and addictive gameplay to a whole new level of quality. As before, you, in the role of a wandering soul, have to wander through a dark and mysterious world, use tactics during battle even with simple opponents, and always remain on guard, since danger comes from everywhere - these are the rules of this eerie world.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</guid><description>Game Description Elite Dangerous is an online multiplayer game, the third part of the &amp;ldquo;Elite&amp;rdquo; franchise, which began in 1984. The player is given complete freedom to explore and travel, and has the opportunity to influence the storyline. The action takes place thousands of years later in the distant future on the territory of several million star galaxies. Most of the stars, planets, asteroids and other cosmic bodies that exist in the real world.</description></item><item><title>Cities: Skylines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</guid><description>Game Description The city-planning simulator - Cities: Skylines - is in the best traditions of the real game, in which its own physical laws were created to transfer them into gaming reality. On the territory of your new city, it will be taken into account that the profile road is built in one way, and the road at the airport - in another. It will count if you correctly lay the pipeline for the heating system, and also if you can show people that they live in a real paradise, and not just a metropolis where they want to buy them at the expense of shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</guid><description>Game Description A terrible virus grows into a global problem in Dying Light. Starting from the city of Harran in Latin America, the infection is decimating the entire world, turning those infected into the walking dead. The hero must survive in such circumstances and try to correct the situation. As an undercover operative, Kyle Crane receives his most important assignment. He needs to find a guy named Suleiman in order to take away from him an important file that he stole.</description></item><item><title>Geometry Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Geometry Dash is a 2D arcade game aimed at hardcore level completion. You will take control of a unique character, which can be in the form of a geometric figure, to pass the most difficult levels and open up new opportunities in the gameplay. Here you will find more than 100 original and challenging missions, as well as the opportunity to create your own main character and share your results on the leaderboard.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa is a car simulator developed based on test drives of cars using a model of real behavior. Includes both single player and multiplayer modes.
The developers presented a variety of licensed cars and tracks, which were specially digitized specifically for the race to convey maximum authenticity to their prototypes. The machines can be customized to your individual taste, because&amp;hellip; the creators have added an extensive set of settings and support for modifications.</description></item><item><title>The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-binding-of-isaac-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-binding-of-isaac-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth is a remake of the original title, allowing you to embark on exciting adventures with additional innovations and improved graphics. The game has been optimized, allowing for stable FPS on most devices. The picture looks more colorful, thanks to hand-drawn pixel characters and environments that increase the quality of the visual component. The effects of shots and enemy deaths have become more detailed, creating tangible dynamics on the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/</guid><description>Game Description The main character - Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor - will fight Sauron and avenge his family. One day, Sauron kidnapped Talion to sacrifice him and summon Celebrimbor, the spirit of the main elf in the world of the Lord of the Rings. However, this spirit helps Talion to resurrect, gives him new abilities and sends him into battle. The protagonist&amp;rsquo;s enemies are Sauron and his dark lords: the Hammer, the Black Hand and the Tower.</description></item><item><title>Metro 2033 Redux</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</guid><description>Game Description Metro 2033 Redux is a first-person shooter with a deep story and horror elements. The developers questioned not the simple existence of people underground, but the relationships between them. Has the main threat always been with us, in people? In the world of the post-apocalypse, we play as a character named Artem. He grew up underground, in the Moscow metro. In 2013, the world was hit by the terrible consequences of the latest epidemic.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-online/</guid><description>Game Description The game The Elder Scrolls Online offers you to go through a number of locations for several warring factions, playing both alone and in real time with other players. The plot tells how Molag Bal, known as the Prince of Violence, decides to take over the entire kingdom of Tamriel and enslave ordinary citizens. The gamer will have to face the forces of evil and defeat him.
Throughout the game world of The Elder Scrolls Online, there are several factions available, each of which is endowed with certain properties.</description></item><item><title>South Park: The Stick of Truth (game)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-igra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-igra/</guid><description>Game Description The funny events of South Park take us into the world of the game South Park: The Stick of Truth, where we play the role of a newcomer who has ambitions and a desire to build a circle of friends in a new city. As soon as we enter the game, famous fourth graders start swinging swords and casting random spells. One of these brings chaos and evil into this world, which we have to cope with.</description></item><item><title>One Finger Death Punch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</guid><description>Game Description One finger death punch is an arcade fighting game in the style of beat&amp;rsquo;em up, in which you can feel like a real martial arts master. In this game we have to fight off crowds of enemies that have surrounded the main character and are advancing from opposite sides. The game design is made in 2D, and all the characters are drawn people, which adds simplicity to the game, but at the same time makes it unusual.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency is a first-person shooter, in which the developers focused on playing in cooperative or multiplayer mode, about the Iraq War. The protagonist is a member of the US PMC, and he is fighting against Iraqi insurgents. The player chooses one side at the beginning of the match, and after that a brutal fight begins between the two factions. The basis of the game is a confrontation between two teams, which include 16 people.</description></item><item><title>Metal Gear Rising: Revengeance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-rising-revengeance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-rising-revengeance/</guid><description>Game Description Metal Gear Rising: Revengeance is a plot branch from the original universe of the recognized genius Hideo Kojima. The game is in the slasher genre, unlike other Metal Gear projects. The plot is dedicated to the story of the cyber ninja Raiden, the protagonist of the second part.
4 years have passed since the collapse of the evil Sons of Patriots corporation. The military units, given freedom of action, plunged the world into chaos and constant divisions of power zones.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Rush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Rush is a project in the &amp;ldquo;tower defense&amp;rdquo; genre, in the style of the Middle Ages, interspersed with magic, creatures that do not exist in real life, like trolls, and real-time control of heroes with a choice of the direction and course of their attacks. This game received recognition on many platforms and later reached personal computers.
The gameplay is standard for the genre, the advantage over other projects is the refined balance and exciting, moderately difficult levels that challenge and force you to change battle tactics and constantly be on the alert.</description></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: Season 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-2/</guid><description>Game Description The Walking Dead: The Game. Season 2 – the continuation of the “Walking Dead” franchise does not lag behind the first part and begins its story 2 years after the previous events. Now in The Walking Dead: Season Two, the user plays as a 10-year-old girl, Clementine, who is once again trying to find shelter and survive in a mortal world filled with living corpses. Having lost all his old friends, a brave child begins a journey on his own.</description></item><item><title>The Wolf Among Us</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</guid><description>Game Description The Wolf Among Us is an episodic graphic novel based on the Fable comics series created by Bill Willingham. The game&amp;rsquo;s plot acts as a prequel to the main story. The game is divided into 5 episodes, where every decision made by the player has a consequence and affects the overall one. history.
The gameplay is point-and-click, but some sections contain action and fights, which are QTE scenes. All the characters presented in the game are heroes of famous fairy tales, who, with the help of spells, can exist in the world of people or “Simps”, as they are called here.</description></item><item><title>Arma 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</guid><description>Game Description In Arma 3 we regain our independence by playing as a neutral side of this war. Inside the universe of the third Arma - 2030. Key opponents are still fighting for independence in economic and commodity terms. Among the enemies, a new structural organization CSAT appears, acting as a military-political alliance. While the crisis rages in Europe, the United States is at odds with China in the Pacific.</description></item><item><title>Outlast (+Whistleblower)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outlast-whistleblower/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outlast-whistleblower/</guid><description>Game Description Outlast (+Whistleblower) - DLC for the game of the same name, which added more content and a new storyline. The addition contains a backstory of the events that happened in the original, where Miles Upshur played the game. The journalist went to the Mount Massive mental hospital, where, for information received, there were many violations. Here he encountered a crowd of terrible psychos - monsters who had taken over the hospital.</description></item><item><title>Total War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</guid><description>Game Description In Total War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition we are allowed to play as one of Caesar&amp;rsquo;s three followers. This is Octavian, the adopted son of a former ruler who is obliged to become the ruler of Rome; Mark Antony is Caesar&amp;rsquo;s loyal friend and best military leader; and Lepidus, the man through whom Caesar achieved universal recognition. After Caesar was killed, chaos erupted within the Roman Empire. The foreign policy of the empire maintained proper balance, while civil war was taking place inside, and the territory was divided into three parts.</description></item><item><title>PayDay 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</guid><description>Game Description Re-join the PayDay 2 gang as Dallas, Hoxton, Chains or Wolfe, who have come to Washington to rob and make a lot of money. Put the mask on your favorite hero and set off to carry out your next crime, in which you will need to overcome many obstacles before reaching your goal.
Now you will have a wide variety of contracts to choose from, from which you can choose any one.</description></item><item><title>Age of Empires 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Empires 2 is a re-release of the classic real-time strategy game with many different improvements. Many years later, this game still remains unique and serves as an example for many strategy developers to follow. In the game, the player will have to take control of a small settlement of a certain faction and lead it to victory and prosperity. Events take place in the Middle Ages, roughly starting from the fall of the Roman Empire and up to the Renaissance.</description></item><item><title>BioShock Infinite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</guid><description>Game Description BioShock Infinite is a first-person shooter with multiple mechanics of a role-playing adventure in the style of science fiction and steampunk. The game will take place in 1912 in an alternative universe, in the flying city of the United States of America - Columbia. You need to control the private detective Booker Devitt, who has a task to find a cute girl named Elizabeth. Immediately after it is found, the main characters find themselves in the very epicenter of the war.</description></item><item><title>Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Tomb Raider is a restart of the series telling about the adventures of Lara Croft. The ship on which the girl&amp;rsquo;s crew was sailing was wrecked. On the island she is captured and left tied in a cave. The adventurer frees herself from her bonds and goes to look for the crew members.
The player can choose the difficulty, which affects the course of battles. A vast world opens up before the gamer, divided into several locations.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter - Far Cry 3 - will teach you how to survive in the wild conditions of the open world, more or less value relationships with good people, and show you what real madness is. The series rewarded us with enough action, showing that a huge arsenal of weapons is just part of what can be given to players in return for their desire to enjoy a completely open world and a good story.</description></item><item><title>Super Hexagon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</guid><description>Game Description Super Hexagon does not contain any plot. This is a dynamic arcade game with a top view. From the outside it looks like an endless game. But in fact, it can be passed. It will not be easy to reach the end, since the title is very hardcore. The project uses a minimalistic visual style.
The gameplay is about survival in the arena. In Super Hexagon it is hexagonal in shape.</description></item><item><title>Hotline Miami</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotline-miami/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotline-miami/</guid><description>Game Description Hotline Miami is a 2D top-down action game created by two incredibly hardworking and talented young people under the auspices of the same computer game development studio - Dennaton Games. The international release of this project took place in October 2012. The developers admitted that they took their inspiration from the Hollywood crime action films of the 80s.
The game, as the name implies, takes place in the city of Miami, in the first half of the 80s.</description></item><item><title>Castle Crashers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</guid><description>Game Description Castle Crashers is an arcade action game in which players will take control of powerful characters and fight monsters. Create a squad by choosing from 25 characters to fight your way through castles against your enemies. Compete with other users or monsters living throughout the continent. The plot will unfold at a ball in the king&amp;rsquo;s castle. During the fun, an evil sorcerer stole a precious magic stone and four princesses, who must be rescued by the knights and fight the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 2 is a shooter with a view from the perspective of the protagonist and leveling up abilities and passive improvements, as in the role-playing adventure genre. A direct continuation of the story of the original game. The main differences from the first part are a greater emphasis on the plot component and the addition of a more advanced weapon editor with many possible modifications that open up as you progress.</description></item><item><title>Batman: Arkham City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-city/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-city/</guid><description>Game Description Batman: Arkham City is an action-adventure game with a third-person view, based on one of the most popular heroes of comics, cartoons, films and toys, Batman. This project is an expanded edition of the original game. The media product was developed by Rocksteady Studios. The official release took place in early autumn 2012.
The game world is five times larger in area than in the previous Batman: Arkham Asylum.</description></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: Season One</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-one/</guid><description>Game Description The Walking Dead: Season One is an interactive story divided into 6 episodes with elements of a point-n-click adventure and with QTEs in action scenes, telling the story of Lee Everett, a prisoner who was being transported in a police station when the zombie apocalypse began. car to another place of serving his sentence, but due to an attack on the vehicle by the dead, he managed to escape.</description></item><item><title>Saints Row: The Third</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</guid><description>Game Description The Third Street Saints are a large and large group in the universe of the game Saints Row: The Third. The third-person shooter with its crazy plots gave the game&amp;rsquo;s heroes their own brand of sneakers, a carbonated drink and a logo, and now they have to fight the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crime syndicate, whose people are scattered around the world and do their work in the “shadows”. Since the main characters have long captured Stillwater, the Syndicate demands offerings from them in the form of tribute for the criminal leadership.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim/</guid><description>Game Description The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim is rightfully considered a legendary game. Even now, many years after its release, it continues to conquer new users who come to it based on recommendations or out of their own interest. In the role of a warrior named Dovahkiin, the gamer will find himself in a huge world full of mysteries, unexpected turns and battles.
Here it is not possible to follow the path of a straightforward passage.</description></item><item><title>Terraria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</guid><description>Game Description Terraria is a simulator of construction, life, survival, an interesting storyline and everything that could be combined into a game with the Sand Box style. Simple 8-bit graphics take us into a randomly generated world generated by the game itself. The open map is almost endless if you dig deep into the world, but you will be stopped by armies of monsters or underground knights. Terraria is not as simple as it seems.</description></item><item><title>The Witcher 2 Assassins of Kings</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-2-ubijcy-korolej/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-2-ubijcy-korolej/</guid><description>Game Description The computer game &amp;ldquo;The Witcher 2 Assassins of Kings&amp;rdquo; is an expanded limited edition of the impressive continuation of the 2008 giant of the world of role-playing video games &amp;ldquo;The Witcher&amp;rdquo;. The development of this project was carried out by the famous studio CD PROJEKT RED. The announcement came in May 2011. Geralt of Rivia is the greatest of the line of witchers, wielding a sword better than others, almost the only one who can resist the forces of darkness, while being something between an ordinary person and a monster.</description></item><item><title>Portal 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/portal-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/portal-2/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person puzzle game Portal 2 received an official announcement only in the spring of 2011, after several postponements. This project is a direct continuation of the original part, which received the highest reviews from critics and gamers around the world. The game was developed by the legendary company Valve, which needs no introduction.
The game&amp;rsquo;s plot continues the line begun in the first part of the &amp;ldquo;Portal&amp;rdquo; series.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade: Warband</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</guid><description>Game Description Mount &amp;amp; Blade: Warband is a standalone add-on that brings many improvements and innovations to the game. New textures, object and character models, as well as sophisticated visualization settings. Change FSAA anti-aliasing, tone mapping and other effects in the settings. Modernized animations, improved combat system and the spirit of the heroes. People will flee if they are in imminent danger or, conversely, fight to the last if their morality is high.</description></item><item><title>Batman: Arkham Asylum Game of the Year Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-asylum-game-of-the-year-edition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-asylum-game-of-the-year-edition/</guid><description>Game Description In Batman: Arkham Asylum the protagonist will still have to fight the Scarecrow, capture territories that belonged to the Joker or other villains, and in return we will be treated to 4 new maps: Crime Alley, Scarecrow&amp;rsquo;s Nightmare, Night Stalker and Complete Madness.
The founder of the legendary series, Batman: Arkham Asylum is a stealth action game with a third-person view and an open world. In the role of the Dark Knight of Gotham, the gamer can freely explore the Arkham psychiatric hospital and the island on which it is located, fight enemies using a convenient and spectacular combat system, and an arsenal of all kinds of gadgets.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</guid><description>Game Description In Left 4 Dead 2 we have a choice between 4 characters. The coach is a massive African American; Nick is an avid gambler, a trickster and a master of theft; Rochelle is a black 29-year-old Depeche Mode fan and journalist; Ellis is a racing fan and car enthusiast. The cooperative first-person shooter captivated many players for several years, providing ample ground for exterminating zombies in 5 game campaigns, which take place in swamps, cities, caves and closed locations.</description></item><item><title>LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lego-star-wars-the-complete-saga/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lego-star-wars-the-complete-saga/</guid><description>Game Description LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga is the legendary LEGO game based on the Star Wars universe. The player is given a unique opportunity to become a participant in the events of his favorite film epic, feel all the experiences of the heroes and choose the Dark or Light Side. All LEGO games have cartoon graphics, which is beneficial and creates the right atmosphere.
The gameplay cannot be called varied, but it does not get boring.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</guid><description>Game Description The first part of Left 4 Dead has 6 campaigns, several levels in each. The history and chronology of the chapters are interconnected, which will prevent the gamer from getting confused in the plot. At the beginning of each area, characters will appear at a checkpoint, where they can pick up weapons and ammunition and set off on their further journey.
The United States of America has been gripped by an unknown virus that turns people into terrible monsters with bouts of aggression and rage.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life 2: Episode Two</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2-episode-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2-episode-two/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the newly released Half-Life 2: Episode Two at one time created a stir all over the world. Openly moving with one goal - to deliver information about the Alliance to the Resistance base - was a shocking task that players rushed into one after another. In the first-person shooter, we will continue to play as Gordon Freeman with Alixa Vance. Long journeys in the game are accompanied by frequent changes of scenes: now we are fighting against mutants, now we are solving puzzles, now we are watching an interactive film about the characters’ journey and their conversations.</description></item><item><title>Portal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/portal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/portal/</guid><description>Game Description Portal is a first-person adventure puzzle game. The plot takes place in the Aperture scientific laboratory, into which the main character, Chell, ended up. She is the one who must test a new weapon that allows you to create portals. Throughout the entire passage, the heroine will be pursued by the GLaDOS robot, telling her what to do and where to go.
The first levels will be educational, they will tell you how to use the device.</description></item><item><title>Garry's Mod</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</guid><description>Game Description Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod is a game and physics sandbox. The main game mode is aimless and provides the player with a freely customizable world powered by the Source engine. The player creates non-player characters with various interaction objects. Special tools and tools allow you to construct new objects in reality, fix beams, iron, objects. Changing facial expressions is also available.
Thanks to the flexible engine, users create their own modifications: Spacebuild, Wiremod, Elevator: Source, DarkRP, Prop Hunt and others.</description></item><item><title>STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</guid><description>Game Description STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack is a collection of real-time strategies based on the Star Wars plot. You will play the role of an army manager on one of the sides in an intergalactic civil war. Command units of the Empire, Rebels, Republic or other civilizations.
In Star Wars Empire at War, you will command your team, completing tasks and freeing planets from enemies. Visit Tatooine, Kashyyyk, Dagobah or other hot spots in the galaxy.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter, which instantly became the voice of the generation - Half-Life 2 - gave players hope for the third part. The game has received so many awards that there is no point in describing them in the context of the description. The plot reveals to us the continuation of the first part. Gordon Freeman takes up his mount again, but now the graphics have become more realistic, there are more locations, and the plot is even deeper.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment, Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>POSTAL 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-2/</guid><description>Game Description POSTAL 2 is a first-person shooter full of dark humor, references, blood and other hardcore stuff like desecrating graves or putting cats on a machine gun as a silencer. The plot develops in a strange town - Paradise. The main character of Postal 2 will be a character named Dude. He tries to live an ordinary life without doing anything illegal.
At the beginning of the story, he gets a job at the computer game development office Running with Scissors.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</guid><description>Game Description Counter-strike is a legendary multiplayer shooter, the founder of one of the most popular series in the history of the gaming industry.
The concept is simple but ingenious. Two teams - terrorists and special forces - are trying to destroy each other on the map. Terrorists have the ability to plant a bomb at one of the key points. and the counterterrorism department tries to predict which point the opponents will attack.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life (1998)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-1998/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-1998/</guid><description>Game Description Half-Life (1998) - sci-fi shooter. One of the first games where the plot was completely presented using cutscenes in the engine. One of the main features of Half-Life was the artificial intelligence of enemies, which was striking in its elaboration. The story of Half-Life begins at the Black Mesa research facility in the mountains of New Mexico.
Control takes place for the young physicist Gordon Freeman, who is researching anomalous materials.</description></item><item><title>Coven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</guid><description>Game Description Going to the gloomy world of Coven, you have to deal with a large number of enemy creatures and deal with their elimination. The universe takes you into an atmospheric medieval fantasy world, where witches and other mythical creatures live alongside people. The first episode is available in the game, where you will take on the role of a young girl. The heroine is burned at the stake during the 1600s, mistaken for a witch and a fiend.</description></item><item><title>Instinct</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/instinkt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:27 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/instinkt/</guid><description>Game Description The shooter Instinct tells an alternative story of the events that took place in the Yangangdo Mountains, which took place in reality on September 13, 2004. The developers had their own version, which they used as the basis for the game. A strange explosion occurs in a North Korean province called Yangangdo. Terrible experiments were carried out in secret laboratories located near a huge mountain. During the research, scientists tested an alien virus called Instinct.</description></item><item><title>Neuro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuro/</guid><description>Game Description Neuro is a three-dimensional action game that gives the player the feeling of being inside a fictional world in the role of a psionicist who can use his abilities for combat purposes. The story told in this brainchild of the developers &amp;ldquo;Revolt Games&amp;rdquo; is a prequel to their other project called &amp;ldquo;Homeplanet&amp;rdquo;. The last missions of the single-player campaign develop in parallel with the start of their last game.</description></item><item><title>7 Days to Die</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</guid><description>Game Description In 7 Days to Die you will need the ability to loot, kill other players, take loot, build buildings, craft items, shoot accurately and keep track of time, because in the open world there is a night in which zombies and other undead sharpen their attention . A horror first-person shooter that combines city building, multiplayer, survival, tower defense and character leveling in an RPG style. Despite the fact that a severe epidemic has struck the world, you will be able to kill animals to take their meat and skin.</description></item><item><title>Alaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Action RPG Alaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms takes the player into the magical Middle Ages. The story begins in the Valley of Storms - a place where four legendary peoples intersect: Humans, Elves, Dwarves and Orcs. It is here that the cruel god Alaloth is imprisoned. From the very kingdom of the dead, he poisons all kingdoms with his evil. Soon monsters, storms, diseases and mighty dragons will strike this world.</description></item><item><title>Batman: Arkham Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-knight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-knight/</guid><description>Game Description In Batman: Arkham Knight - a third-person action game, we eliminate this problem, and the Scarecrow himself too. After the events of the last part of Batman, Gotham City finally has a normal, friendly environment. Fights, robberies and murders continue, but if the protagonist does not hear about them, it means that everything is covered up by the police, or these are just rumors. Suddenly the Scarecrow appears and says that during the last incident he only used 100 grams of his drug.</description></item><item><title>BattleBlock Theater</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battleblock-theater/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battleblock-theater/</guid><description>Game Description BattleBlock Theater is a platformer with cartoon graphics and a side view. It has a simple plot, because it is far from the main one in this genre. The player takes on the role of a prisoner who goes through various levels of the theater with one goal - to save Hatty Hattington. The gameplay is not complicated at first glance: level progression is linear, jumps are simple and standard for the genre, and there are a couple of types of enemy attacks.</description></item><item><title>Blade and Sorcery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</guid><description>Game Description Blade and Sorcery is a first-person fantasy action game focused on realistic hand-to-hand combat physics. You play as a hero who knows how to fight with melee and long-range weapons, as well as magical abilities. There are three classes to choose from: Warrior, Ranger and Wizard. The gameplay is adapted for virtual reality helmets Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift and Windows Mixed Reality.
The gameplay is based on body physics and fair hitboxes.</description></item><item><title>Bodycam</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</guid><description>Game Description Bodycam throws you headlong into a hyper-realistic multiplayer battlefield. Powered by Unreal Engine 5, this all-new shooter promises a next-gen experience that will redefine your expectations. Teamwork is key here. Every bullet counts, and the victory or defeat of your squad depends on your every decision.
Forget playing Rambo. Bodycam requires strategic thinking and coordinated attacks. Team up with your teammates, map out a plan of action, and use your arsenal to outmaneuver your opponents.</description></item><item><title>Brotato</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</guid><description>Game Description In the shooter Bratato you have to take control of a potato using a variety of guns while fighting alien creatures. The gameplay includes roguelite genre elements. Locations are procedurally generated, and each run can take up to 30 minutes of real time. There are dozens of types of weapons and additional items of equipment to choose from, allowing you to progress at your own pace and combine the effects of items.</description></item><item><title>Clone Drone in the Danger Zone</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clone-drone-in-the-danger-zone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clone-drone-in-the-danger-zone/</guid><description>Game Description Clone Drone in the Danger Zone is an exciting arcade game in which the player will play as a person whose mind has been transferred into an iron robot! The player enters the arena with the only task - to survive. It is worth considering that each opponent is endowed with individual characteristics and skills, so winning will not be easy. Each blow is under the close attention of a robot commentator, who will cover the course of the battle and your actions throughout it.</description></item><item><title>Company of Heroes 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</guid><description>Game Description The events of Company of Heroes 2 unfold before us in snowy Norilsk, where one of the largest Stalinist Gulags is located. NKVD officer Churkin comes here, who understands that he will not survive the next Stalinist purge of officers. In the Gulag he finds his comrade from the front, who is serving his sentence and preparing to be shot. Isakovich is the name of the character, he wrote a tome with the real actions of the commanders of the Red Army, for which he was sentenced to death.</description></item><item><title>Cruelty Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Cruelty Squad is an immersive simulator that includes elements of stealth and first-person shooter. You will need to penetrate the depths of a high-tech corporation to stop its atrocities. A huge arsenal of weapons is available, including shotguns, darts, pistols, launchers and much more. The difficulty increases with each new stage. It is necessary to take part in intense firefights with a huge number of different enemies.
It is possible to emerge victorious from a fight without death.</description></item><item><title>Dave The Diver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</guid><description>Game Description Dave The Diver - a sea adventure about a diver named Dave. Events take place in a mysterious place called the Blue Hole. During the day, the protagonist explores the ocean, diving to the very bottom in search of treasures, and at night he manages a sushi restaurant. Dave is partnered with 3 charismatic friends to help him on his adventures. Each character has an individual character, introducing dynamics into the relationships between the characters.</description></item><item><title>Dead by Daylight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</guid><description>Game Description Dead by Daylight is an asymmetrical cooperative horror game inspired by youth slashers. The story centers on four survivors facing off against a fifth player who controls a bloodthirsty maniac. The defending team&amp;rsquo;s job is to do everything possible to ensure they aren&amp;rsquo;t dead by dawn. Finding yourself in the same location with the killer, you need to use the environment and interact with your partners, trying to resist the monster.</description></item><item><title>Detroit Become Human</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/detroit-become-human/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/detroit-become-human/</guid><description>Game Description Detroit: Become Human is a rather interesting game in the interactive cinema genre. It is based on the Quantic Dream graphics core, so the excellent graphics component immediately catches your eye. It is impossible not to note the titanic work of the animators, who created truly gorgeous animations and scenes that were plausible from the point of view of anatomy and physics.
The game takes place in the future, in an era of highly developed technology, where androids have already firmly taken their place next to people as loyal and multifunctional humanoid servants.</description></item><item><title>Duck Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/duck-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/duck-game/</guid><description>Game Description Duck Game is an action game developed by Landon Podbielski and published by Adult Swim Games. You can play alone or with friends online. Duck Game gives us both options.
The game received extremely positive reviews from both professional critics and gamers, as well as from ordinary people. A simple 2D fighting game with multiplayer simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t get bad reviews. True, some are indignant about the name of the game because the name, according to some players, does not reflect anything.</description></item><item><title>Gunpoint</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunpoint/</guid><description>Game Description Gunpoint takes the user to the near future, where many interesting spy things have been invented. Richard Conway works as a spy for hire, performing a variety of tasks. One day he gets a special copy - hyperpants. This item of clothing helps you jump over huge distances, and also help you fall from a height without harm to your health. The protagonist receives a new task - to investigate the murder of an employee of a weapons company.</description></item><item><title>Hearts of Iron 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the fact that Hearts of Iron 4 is famous for its realism, the new part has completely redesigned the focus tree for individual countries and nationalities. The strategy, dedicated to the Second World War, invites you to play in countries such as Italy, Ethiopia, Spain, Japan and China. Two scenarios that differ in their dates: 1936 and 1939. In one of them you will take part in the Second Italo-Ethiopian War and the Spanish Civil War, and in the second you will see how Japan invaded China, and the Second World War was fought.</description></item><item><title>Human: Fall Flat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/human-fall-flat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/human-fall-flat/</guid><description>Game Description Human: Fall Flat is an adventure puzzle game with amazing physics and engine. Take control of Bob, who every time has a dream from which he must find a way out. Usually such dreams are accompanied by colorful locations in which he needs to get to a certain point and solve many difficult problems.
Explore the open world in your own way. Climb any building, rock, tree or other object, going through the same place differently each time.</description></item><item><title>INSIDE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inside/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inside/</guid><description>Game Description A side-view platformer - INSIDE - tells the story of a small and unarmed boy who, through an unknown means, ended up in a closed, scary space. The physics of the game and the gameplay invite us to go through the platformer to the last level with a lot of deaths, puzzles, solving difficult problems and good visuals, combined with the atmosphere and the usual soundtrack.
The death of our hero is an endlessly scary animation.</description></item><item><title>It's Only Money</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</guid><description>Game Description It&amp;rsquo;s Only Money will immerse gamers in the realistic story of a resident of the underworld, who, by order of the mayor of Rockhaven, was thrown into a huge pit. But don&amp;rsquo;t despair! Together with other inhabitants of the underground, you can return to the surface and begin your path to wealth and power. You must steal from the rich, fight tycoons, and regain control of the city block by block.</description></item><item><title>Just Shapes &amp; Beats</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-shapes-amp-beats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-shapes-amp-beats/</guid><description>Game Description Just Shapes &amp;amp; Beats offers gameplay based on the sound of music and beats. The difficulty level of the game depends on the rhythm of the soundtrack. The user takes control of a blue square; Many difficulties await him ahead. In the process, the hero is helped by friends, with whom he fights enemies. The game supports online and local co-op with 4 players in Story Mode and Challenge Runs.</description></item><item><title>Legend of Mortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</guid><description>Game Description In Legend of Mortal you have to become a nobody in the Tang Man sector. Not a prophetic hero, not a legendary warrior - you&amp;rsquo;re just trying to survive in a world on the edge of the abyss. But even lowlifes have it tough, right? This is what Legend of Mortal is all about: your decisions determine the fate of you and those around you. Think of it this way: every meeting, every battle, every seemingly insignificant conversation is a twist in the kaleidoscope.</description></item><item><title>LOCKDOWN Protocol</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lockdown-protocol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lockdown-protocol/</guid><description>Game Description LOCKDOWN Protocol throws players into a high-stakes world of deception and cooperation. The title combines real-time action and communication, creating a dynamic experience for groups of three to eight people. The idea is simple: players cooperate to complete tasks within a strict time limit. Beneath the surface of unity, however, lies a sinister undercurrent. Trust is a fragile commodity in this environment. Every interaction offers a chance to gather information or sow discord.</description></item><item><title>Muse Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Muse Dash is a dynamic rhythm game in anime style, where you will visit many colorful locations, dance to the rhythm of fiery songs and send enemies into outer space. At the center of the story are three charismatic beauties. Having chosen one of the heroines, you need to fight with various creatures in the rhythm of the dance. The action will take place on a colorful background accompanied by dynamic dance music.</description></item><item><title>Neon White</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</guid><description>Game Description Neon White is a first-person adventure platformer with card game elements. The gameplay stands out for its incredible dynamics and speed. It is necessary to quickly react to situations and the environment, because enemies, traps, obstacles and other dangers await you at every turn. Events develop behind the pearly gates of Paradise.
The task in the game is simple and trivial - you need to destroy all the demons in Heaven.</description></item><item><title>Outer Wilds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outer-wilds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outer-wilds/</guid><description>Game Description Outer Wilds is a first-person action-adventure game based on the popular Groundhog Day theme. Events take place on the fictional planet Kamelok, which is destroyed by a star explosion 22 minutes after the start of the game. But the story is just beginning. The user finds himself in a “time loop”, which allows you to gradually develop the plot, travel through the planetary system and meet new characters. After a “reboot” of life, all accumulated information remains available.</description></item><item><title>Raft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</guid><description>Game Description Raft is a first-person survival sandbox in which the player will have to survive on a small raft and explore new lands. The main character will begin his journey by waking up hungry and dehydrated on a small wreck of a ship. Get food and drink by catching garbage floating past the hero on the waves. To catch the item, you can use the hook. Find useful items and materials to craft a mug, light a fire, and filter sea water.</description></item><item><title>Sea of ​​Thieves</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-of-thieves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-of-thieves/</guid><description>Game Description Sea of ​​Thieves – seas, ships and a bottle of rum. Immerse yourself in the world of piracy, ship battles, treasure hunting and fun. Create your character, team up with other players, and assemble a team of pirates. A huge open world opens up before you, full of riddles, secrets and adventures. The gameplay of Sea of ​​Thieves is rich in content: The endless ocean and deserted islands - assemble a team of your kind, surf the seas and oceans enjoying the sunset over the waves, sing pirate songs and drink strong rum from barrels in the hold.</description></item><item><title>Starbound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</guid><description>Game Description Starbound is a 2D side-scrolling indie RPG adventure with graphics that reference the classic 8-bit titles of the last century. The project has become widespread thanks to the ability to play with a friend in co-op mode on different platforms, as well as a well-developed system of achievements and rewards that motivate you to improve your own skills and collect all kinds of items for crafting and collecting. The surrounding world is presented in the form of open territories, where there are no prohibitions on colonizing unknown planets or performing secondary tasks; you can even not touch the story campaign at all.</description></item><item><title>Stray</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray/</guid><description>Game Description Stray takes the player to the distant future, the world of cyberpunk. The story follows the adventures of a lost cat looking for his way home. A stray animal found itself in the fortified city of Kowloon, from which it is not easy to find a way out. People have not lived here for a long time, and the streets are filled with robots. Find out the secrets of a long-abandoned settlement.</description></item><item><title>TEKKEN 7</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</guid><description>Game Description TEKKEN 7 is a side-scrolling 3D fighting game that tells the true story of the Mishima clan&amp;rsquo;s feud. In the storyline we learn why Heitachi killed his wife, for what reasons Kazuya Mishima survived. The basis of the game&amp;rsquo;s action is a fighting game based on love, family relationships with friendly fights.
Each battle in Tekken 7 is a separate branch in the plot, so after the end of the battle (victory in it), we see a small interactive video of the creation of the entire universe, Kazuya growing up, and the formation of the Mishima clan.</description></item><item><title>Terrordrome - Reign of the Legends</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrordrome-reign-of-the-legends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrordrome-reign-of-the-legends/</guid><description>Game Description Terrordrome - Reign of the Legends is a dynamic and bloody fighting game, the action of which takes place in an alternative version of our reality, where characters from books, urban legends, cryptozoology, mythology and folklore exist. All heroes of Terrordrome are monsters and villains. The game shows a hypothetical world where all the scary stories heard turned out to be true. There is a story campaign for Alex Van Helsing.</description></item><item><title>Wayfinder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayfinder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayfinder/</guid><description>Game Description Wayfinder is an online action role-playing adventure game in which gamers become Wayfinders, using unique abilities to fight the hostile force that has taken over their world. The game emphasizes co-op, allowing users to team up with friends to enhance their abilities and manage their adventures. The world of Evenor, in which the action takes place, has been destroyed, and gamers will have to navigate it, collecting valuable materials and creating items that will help them in their search.</description></item><item><title>Wobbly Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbly-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wobbly-life/</guid><description>Game Description Wobbly Life is a bright and dynamic sandbox that relies on an open world and body physics. The gameplay is tailored for local and online co-op. Team up with friends to compete in various mini-games and competitions. There is a single-player game aimed at developing your hero. Earn money and spend it on new skins, clothes, equipment and much more.
You will explore the vastness of Wobbly Island, controlling cute characters that resemble children&amp;rsquo;s toys.</description></item></channel></rss>