<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Visual Novel on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novel/</link><description>Recent content in Visual Novel on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fearbonding</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</guid><description>Game Description ** Fearbonding ** represents Hinata, a demon for whom fear has a tangible quality, like sweet, viscous honey. The lack of genuine horror makes his meeting with the Kosuke, a personality with obvious instability, determining the moment. This meeting encourages Hinata, focusing his demonic existence on the goal: to subordinate this person and cultivate his fear. He seeks to make Kosuke with his new instrument for the extraction of this resource so necessary for food.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Island: Missing Amy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</guid><description>Game Description ** Mystery Island: Missing Amy ** tells about the hell, the researcher, looking for sister, mysteriously missing months ago. The plot unfolds when hell receives a selfie from a loved one; The picture captures the missing girl on a remote island, where sea water has a bloody red color. This frame encourages hell to take a sea trip to search for a relative and study the location from a mysterious message.</description></item><item><title>Star Knightess aura</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</guid><description>Game Description ** Star Knightess aura ** - Anime -Nella, the main character of which is a girl with an unusual name of the aura. She falls into a fantastic world called Roya. The heroine is cursed by the king of demons. Its task is to deal with otherworldly monsters every night. At the same time, it is very important not to lose yourself. The girl has insanity and she begins to consider herself a completely different person.</description></item><item><title>Threefold Recital</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</guid><description>Game Description ** Threefold Recital ** invites gamers to move to bright eastern fantasy, where the overgrown city of Bluscles stands on the threshold of a new era. Once the city was warmed in the rays of the Golden Age, and now it is mired in political instability and tension. Title draws a picture of the world where ancient magic and modern technologies are intertwined, creating a unique mixture that drives the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description ** Anime City ** transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.</description></item><item><title>Midori no Kaori</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</guid><description>Game Description Midori no Kaori is an adventure game based on the art of peaceful store management. In this relaxed environment, gamers will create and manage their own establishment, drawing on elements of Japanese culture to shape their vision. The title doesn&amp;rsquo;t focus on fast-paced action or intense competition, but rather encourages players to create a space that reflects their personal taste. There are no strict goals or deadlines, making it a refreshing alternative to many other games that prioritize speed or performance.</description></item><item><title>Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</guid><description>Game Description Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing immerses users in battles between armies that take place during the Dark Middle Ages. The game is made in the genre of real-time strategy, where you have to deal with printing and solving multi-task missions. The protagonist is a guy named Paul who wants to prevail over the evil forces. Gameplay mechanics allow you to test the typing speed of users, where the ability to type the necessary keys blindly is useful in order to keep control over the events that are happening.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Class of '09: The Flip Side</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</guid><description>Game Description Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side is the final chapter of the visual novel series that follows the characters&amp;rsquo; lives as they navigate their post-high school struggles. This installment puts the spotlight on Jack, a character who was previously seen in a supporting role. The adventure focuses on her experiences and the emotional difficulties she faces, which contrasts with the more light-hearted approach of the previous protagonist, Nicole. The narrative structure of Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side allows gamers to make choices that affect the storyline and offers multiple endings depending on the decisions made.</description></item><item><title>Ace Attorney Investigations Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Ace Attorney Investigations Collection, a collection of two games featuring the famous prosecutor Miles Edgeworth, invites users to step into his shoes and go on an exciting investigation. Unlike the courtroom drama of the original series, this collection focuses on the detective work that precedes the trial. Gamers will have to collect evidence, interview witnesses and solve intricate mysteries using logical deduction. The collection includes various quality of life improvements to make gameplay more enjoyable.</description></item><item><title>Kamikaze Lasplanes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</guid><description>Game Description Kamikaze Lassplanes is a visual novel that combines the plot of a novel with the action of a shoot-&amp;rsquo;em-up game. Set in a steampunk world, the dramatic storyline involves two powerful weapons, Lassplanes, and two girls who become them. Gamers navigate a war-torn kingdom and make choices that affect not only the fate of the kingdom, but also their own hearts.
The project introduces Alba Trosset and Hannah Brandenburg, two girls who transform into deadly warplanes.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</guid><description>Game Description Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way is a story about two young women. Studio SPRITE created this cinematic romance. Mina, a loner, withdraws from the world. School becomes a battlefield for her. Her hideout? A room filled with dried flowers. Captive of her thoughts, she wanders through endless days. Meanwhile, Ran, born into wealth, discovers the emptiness beneath the gilded cage. Her perfect life is falling apart.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Dynasty takes place in 1800s America. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to build his own ranch, providing himself with wealth and food. Over time, other settlers, workers and friends will join the main character. Each minor character has their own qualities, characteristics and mannerisms. Many of them will turn out to be bandits, and only the gamer can decide who is sent to the gallows.
Having become determined, the central character set out to build a Wild West dynasty, moving further across the Pacific region of America.</description></item><item><title>Who is Abby</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</guid><description>Game Description Who is Abby begins with Tom, a man determined to find his missing sister. The title immerses users in an intense psychological thriller where mystery and exploration go hand in hand. With every step, Tom plunges deeper into the mystery of Abby&amp;rsquo;s disappearance, revealing a story shrouded in mystery and darkness. As you take on the role of Tom, the journey becomes personal, with each discovery adding another piece to the puzzle of Abby&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty is a visual novel set in China during the turbulent reign of the Chongzhen Emperor. Players take on the role of Liang, a former merchant turned bandit tasked with escorting four girls to the prosperous city of Luoyang. The journey is fraught with danger and moral problems. Liang struggles with the truth behind his mission when one of the girls, Sui, reveals a terrifying secret: their goal is not a luxurious life, but an encounter with a monstrous pig demon.</description></item><item><title>Altushka for skufa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</guid><description>Game Description In the game Altushka for skufa the state provides a tart for skufa through a special service using personal data. For men who have reached forty years of age, do not have a wife and have a stable outlook on life, the project provides the opportunity to receive a legal altushka through the online service Skufuslugi, using the password from your account.
The game is an immersive first-person scoof simulator created by comic artist Vitaly Terletsky and the author of viral anime videos RIKANI in a short time.</description></item><item><title>Knowledge, or know Lady</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</guid><description>Game Description Knowledge, or know Lady throws you into the heart of a unique dating simulator. As the only guy at an all-girl university, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself caught up in a whirlwind of romance and college life. Will you succumb to the charms of the beauties around you or forge your own path to become a campus legend? Ladies School Prince unfolds through your eyes, offering a first-person perspective. Your</description></item><item><title>KinitoPET</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</guid><description>Game Description KinitoPET promises a world of endless fun and communication with your virtual assistant Kinito. This early 2000s wonder can walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games, making him a friend like no other. But beneath the surface of this seemingly perfect companion lies a disturbing truth. Step into &amp;ldquo;Eternal Fun!&amp;rdquo;, and Kinito will become your personal assistant, ready to fulfill your every request. Its cutting-edge technology promises a &amp;ldquo;truly unique experience&amp;rdquo; designed just for you.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Slay the Princess is a dark and daring adventure that will put your skills to the ultimate test, combining the genres of psychological horror and dating simulator. Your mission is simple: kill the princess and save the world from destruction. But don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by her charms and promises. She will stop at nothing to stop you from completing your task. Make your way through the dense forest and find the hut at the end of the path.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>Persona 5 Royal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 5 Royal is the official expansion for the fifth part of the Japanese role-playing video game of the same name, which contains even more unique personas, as well as a lot of interesting quests and items. The plot centers on a seemingly ordinary high school student who goes with his family to Tokyo, where he enrolls in a new school. Soon the main character begins to see inexplicable dreams, in which someone tells the guy that a monstrous catastrophe will befall him in the near future.</description></item><item><title>Mirror 2: Project X</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror 2: Project X follows the adventures of Dinkudin Naoto, who collaborates with the FBI (Federal Bureau of Research and Conservation). The hero searches for mystical manifestations and otherworldly creatures that sometimes appear in the world. The plot begins with a story with a Demon that infects the body of one of the victims. During the proceedings and investigation of the case, the protagonist will find out the motivations and goals of the creatures in order to make a choice to support or destroy the monster.</description></item><item><title>Milk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of milk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description The narrative adventure Milk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of mil continues the story of the previous part. The player finds himself in a crazy and mysterious world filled with different combinations of unusual colors and surreal events. On a new journey, you will again have to help the young girl become a little happier. Initially she will be terrified, but as she progresses she will meet new people and realize her own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Doki Doki Literature Club Plus!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</guid><description>Game Description Doki Doki Literature Club Plus! is a visual novel, the plot tells the story of a student who joins a literature club. Most of the passage is focused on interactions with the girls who are part of the team. The gameplay is similar to other projects in this genre. The player gets few interactive moments. Only occasionally do elections appear that significantly affect the further passage.
The scenes in Doki Doki consist of static 2D images with drawn anime characters.</description></item><item><title>Firework</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/firework/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/firework/</guid><description>Game Description The dark journey of the boy in Firework allows gamers to find themselves in dangerous environments where they must survive and solve difficult puzzles. The game presents the opportunity to go investigate a mysterious fire that killed many people. The main character, named Lin Lixun, goes to explore the territory where the disaster occurred. In the process of clarifying the circumstances, the young policeman is forced to deal with mysterious phenomena and confusing facts that overlap with each other.</description></item><item><title>Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk is a short visual novel with a deep message and unusual execution, made by the efforts of one developer, one of the indie creators. The visual design of the single-player campaign, which is the only game mode, is made using only two colors - purple and black. For completing a short story, which will take about 15 minutes, the developer has prepared three rewards, implementing a small list of achievements.</description></item><item><title>ATRI -My Dear Moments-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</guid><description>Game Description ATRI -My Dear Moments- is a visual novel with a well-developed plot that leaves food for thought after completing the single-player campaign. Casual control is carried out using the keys on the mouse, allowing you to enjoy reading a work with anime-style slides even for people who are not familiar with games. Recognized masters of this genre worked on the story, which allowed the project to receive many prestigious awards and the love of an audience that loves visual novels.</description></item><item><title>Persona 4 Golden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 4 Golden is a role-playing game about a group of friends who are able to summon demons from the other world. To do this, it is enough to shoot yourself in the temple. The events take place in the small Japanese town of Inaba. The children in Persona 4 are teenagers going through puberty. The heroes are investigating a mysterious series of murders.
The gameplay of Persona 4 Golden contains elements of a visual novel.</description></item><item><title>The Test</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</guid><description>Game Description The Test is a psychological horror with elements of a visual novel, role-playing adventure, and immersive sim with a lot of text monologues inside the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s head. The player gets the opportunity to directly influence what is happening using a decision-making system of varying degrees of importance. The isometric camera allows you to get the best view of the two-dimensional space where all the action of the single-player campaign takes place with a well-developed plot about mental suffering.</description></item><item><title>Senren＊Banka</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</guid><description>Game Description Senren＊Banka is primarily aimed at anime fans. The project uses the appropriate style (including chibi art) and Japanese voice acting. The plot combines romantic, tragic, mystical and humorous elements. The story revolves around supernatural incidents. A group of young people are trying to hide them from ordinary people.
The premise in Senren＊Banka: A Thousand Colors of Love is as follows. A guy named Arichi Masaomi comes to the provincial town of Hoori in the summer.</description></item><item><title>Disco Elysium: The Final Cut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</guid><description>Game Description Disco Elysium is an RPG in which a detective must use his skills to conduct a unique investigation. The player will have to interrogate well-developed characters, investigate murders, and, if desired, take bribes. You can become either the savior of the city or the worst disaster for all humanity. Game Features: Unique branched dialogue system. Wide freedom of choice both in the story narrative and in additional tasks. Well-developed characters with their own stories and personalities.</description></item><item><title>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</guid><description>Game Description Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy is a re-release of three parts of lawyer simulators combined with adventure. Here the player will not only defend a person in court, but will also begin to investigate the circumstances of the crime, exploring the place, finding evidence, interrogating witnesses. At the trial, the user will listen to both sides, question, look for contradictions in their words, using found objects. The lawyer will be able to defend himself, even if there is only one piece of evidence proving the innocence of the accused, and will also delay time to collect more information.</description></item><item><title>Mirror</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror is a visual novel that perfectly combines erotic content, an RPG component, an interactive plot and battles in which you take a direct part. The whole game is built on the “three in a row” principle. In the casual combination of characters, you will only take part in the battle on the Match 3 battlefield. That is, you will win if you can score more points. The game features three heroines who will oppose you throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>STEINS;GATE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</guid><description>Game Description STEINS;GATE is a visual novel made in an anime style, which is reflected in the appearance of the characters in the single-player campaign. The game received a lot of positive reviews due to its deep dramatic plot, which is not often found in the video game entertainment industry. The narrative is filled with sad moments that touch the soul and make you empathize with the main characters, who are trying to save all of humanity, while paying a terrible price.</description></item><item><title>VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</guid><description>Game Description VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action is an adventure simulator of a bartender in the setting of a dystopian future, where humanity finds itself under the control of huge corporations dictating the rules of life, and nanorobots controlling every area of ​​human activity and the implementation of laws and regulations adopted new world government. Stylistically, this project refers to Japanese games of the last century. The gameplay consists of communicating with bar visitors and providing them with high-quality service in order to build warm, friendly relationships with them.</description></item><item><title>The Wolf Among Us</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</guid><description>Game Description The Wolf Among Us is an episodic graphic novel based on the Fable comics series created by Bill Willingham. The game&amp;rsquo;s plot acts as a prequel to the main story. The game is divided into 5 episodes, where every decision made by the player has a consequence and affects the overall one. history.
The gameplay is point-and-click, but some sections contain action and fights, which are QTE scenes. All the characters presented in the game are heroes of famous fairy tales, who, with the help of spells, can exist in the world of people or “Simps”, as they are called here.</description></item><item><title>CLANNAD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clannad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clannad/</guid><description>Game Description CLANNAD is a visual novel in anime style. The story follows a second grade student who begins a new school year at Hikarizaka School. On his way to school, he meets a girl, Nagisa. It turns out that she is constantly alone and has no friends at all. Depending on the actions you take, the course of the story changes. By helping a girl make friends, you build good relationships with some characters, but at the same time spoil them with others.</description></item></channel></rss>