<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Adventures on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/</link><description>Recent content in Adventures on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Good Heavens!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</guid><description>Game Description ** Good HEAVENS! ** It takes place in the Severe Kingdom of Xant-Rar, a bizarre afterlife, where souls live on floating islands. This songwriter with the open world allows gamers to pave their own path in the world, crowded with bizarre capabilities. Imagine: you have lived a good life, have left the earthly path and got into Xant -Rar - a place intended for the fulfillment of all your desires throughout eternity.</description></item><item><title>Ribby: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description ** Ribby: The Game ** - this is not a typical role -playing adventure. Forget about the extermination of dragons or collecting a million gold coins. Here is the hero - Ribbie, a kind girl, who has lost and seeking the house. Title combines elements of role -playing games and visual novels, creating a unique experience. Of course, the main goal is to return Ribbie home, but this is only the top of Lilia.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description ** Salvus: aries ** throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item></channel></rss>