<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Adventures on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/</link><description>Recent content in Adventures on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lumber and Plunder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lumber-and-plunder/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lumber-and-plunder/</guid><description>Game Description Lumber and Plunder sends players to a remote island, according to rumors, hiding a long -forgotten treasure. The main lesson is the extraction of resources from the environment, for example, the cutting of trees in the mysterious forest. The materials obtained are sold for currency invested in improving tools. Such a progression system opens access to new areas and helps to climb the central mountain, the main goal in finding a legendary treasure.</description></item><item><title>Quartet</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</guid><description>Game Description Quartet immerses in the world in which incredible adventures and unforgettable battles await you. Start your way in the world of full mysteries, hidden government intrigues and powerful magic. In this fascinating and old -school RPG you can choose one of the four stories and go through them in any order, revealing the secrets of the Quartet world. A series of train robberies, a mysterious deck of cards, deadly aircraft and an accidental magician - all this awaits you in Quartet.</description></item><item><title>SupRareld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supraworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supraworld/</guid><description>Game Description SupRartold sends a student of the guild of soliders on a journey through the man -made toy world. The local lands suffer from storms from puzzles that create obstacles to the inhabitants. To pass the final exam, the protagonist must be saved by the princess from the castle. The main task can be ignored by giving preference to other activities in a huge, interconnected environment. The study of the world occurs with a miniature perspective, and each object pursues a certain gameplay goal, being deprived of unnecessary jewelry.</description></item><item><title>Bee Simulator: The Hive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</guid><description>Game Description Bee Simulator: The Hive puts the player in the role of an insect with the task of protecting his colony from danger. A single story is focused on the actions of one bee, on which the survival of the entire swarm depends. Gamers have to move around the half-open world created on the model of the New York Central Park. Key activity includes the collection of pollen from plants, interaction with other insects and confrontation with aggressive Osami.</description></item><item><title>Liese in the City of Trials</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liese-in-the-city-of-trials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liese-in-the-city-of-trials/</guid><description>Game Description Liese in the City of Trita puts the heroine Liz in the face of a new demonic threat years after the establishment of peace. In the former possessions of the defeated lord of demons, a fortress arises, flooding the city of weight in monsters. Liz arrives in a besieged metropolis to investigate the distress source. Local residents are facing inevitable danger, and it should act until the weight fell under the onslaught of the forces of darkness.</description></item><item><title>Prospector</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</guid><description>Game Description Prospector begins with arrival at someone else&amp;rsquo;s world, having only a set of tools at its disposal. The primary task is to collect the planet’s resources for the construction of the basis for the base. Players build structures, explore the environment, and then establish automated production lines. For construction, everything is used, from primitive materials to unknown alien substances found on the landscape.
Gradually, a simple avantopost turns into a complex object with an optimized working process.</description></item><item><title>HOT ROD MAYHEM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description Hot Rod Mayhem represents car competitions on many tracks. This racing arcade contains a campaign mode, where to obtain the title of world champion, it is necessary to win in 10 separate championships. Promotion requires special tests with unique tasks that open access to the main events. After unlocking the championship, you can participate in its races so that the player can take first place in the fight against opponents.</description></item><item><title>Steal The Pig</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steal-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steal-the-pig/</guid><description>Game Description Steal The Pig is a cooperative game in which 2 players take on the roles of thieves. The main task is to transfer the pig through a series of locations filled with obstacles. The animal can wake up and try to hide, demanding coordinated actions from the partners for further advancement. This project supports a single mode, the passage of together on the same device with a divided screen, as well as online lobby for joint sessions.</description></item><item><title>Slidemagi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slidemagi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slidemagi/</guid><description>Game Description Slidemagi is a duel between the two magicians on the 10x10 board, where units move by shifting the entire grid lines. In one move, the player performs one action: moves a row or applies a spell. This solution is central to the tactical pattern of battle. Following this, all controlled fighters on the field simultaneously attack in four main directions in the presence of goals.
This tactical game offers several modes for single and multiplayer competitions.</description></item><item><title>Wheel World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</guid><description>Game Description Wheel World represents the story of Kat, a cyclist chosen by ancient spirits for a key task. The setting is on the verge of collapse, and only Glavheroin can prevent it, having made a great shift ceremony. Her journey runs through the world, saturated with a bicycle culture, where she has to resist the elite teams in competitions.
The central mission is to return the abducted legendary details, which are the main components to complete the ritual and save its world from oblivion.</description></item><item><title>Monument Valley 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monument-valley-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monument-valley-3/</guid><description>Game Description In the Monument Valley 3, players will go on a new journey, leading a student of Nur through a world built from optical illusions and mobile architecture. The main goal is to comprehend the meaning of sacred light, moving along locations with changeable gravity. For advance, it is necessary to directly manipulate buildings, rotate entire levels and change the perspective, paving routes through impossible geometry.
Features of the surrealist adventure Nur:</description></item><item><title>The Demons Told Me to Make This Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-demons-told-me-to-make-this-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-demons-told-me-to-make-this-game/</guid><description>Game Description The Demons Told Me to Make This Game begins in the city of Red Havyvs at 5:00 a.m. on October 26, 2016. This moment marks the beginning of the last day of the world: the bloody ritual ends and a spirit named a dark light appears in the void. Being this incorporeal essence, the player cannot directly interact with the physical world. The main way of influence is the instilling in the inhabitants of the city and whipping them in the ear of instructions for sending their actions.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Ascension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Ascension puts the player in the lord position with the task of creating his own possession in an empty plot of land. The initial stage includes a systematic collection of provisions and materials - basic elements for any settlement. These assets then go to the construction of the first buildings to create a stronghold in the world. Subsequently, the focus shifts the recruitment of military detachments that form an army to protect native lands and spread the influence of the outside.</description></item><item><title>DUST RADERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</guid><description>Game Description Dust Raiders puts the player in the role of the manager on the lawless, post -apocalyptic wasteland, where control over resources is the main task. The plot originates after the Sawblade attack, which led to the loss of the oil refinery, the death of the Viktor’s ally and the dissolution of the original team. Left without fuel and equipment, it is necessary to collect a functional machine from scrap metal to start recovery.</description></item><item><title>The Necromincer's Tale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-necromancers-tale/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-necromancers-tale/</guid><description>Game Description The Necromincer&amp;rsquo;s Tale is a role -playing game in the setting of dark fantasy. The adventure is presented by a top-distance. It is a nobleman to manage a nobleman living in the world of an alternative of the 18th century. The tale of the necromancer is a mystical story full of political conspiracies, dark knowledge and thirst for revenge. Exploring surrounding, everything may not be at all the same as it seems initially.</description></item><item><title>A Chamber of Stars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-chamber-of-stars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-chamber-of-stars/</guid><description>Game Description A chamber of Stars tells about the life of the performer Starr - a musician who has passed through decades of cultural shifts and personal transformation. After many stage images, the change of genres and public scandals, the artist remains a significant figure in the public consciousness. The anticipation of the new album is growing, according to rumors, preparing to become his main work. This journey explores the internal universe of personality, asking the question of what part of yourself can be conveyed through creativity in the world, constantly creating your own myths about you.</description></item><item><title>Lost Child</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-child/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-child/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Child begins with Andrey’s awakening inside the endless labyrinth of corridors. His memory is erased, and the physical space around is distorted with each movement. Voices are reported from darkness, accompanied by childish screams and the appearance of ominous shadows. These phenomena give rise to uncertainty in their source: whether it is hallucinations, scraps of the past or someone&amp;rsquo;s cruel experiment. The further path is a study of this anxious and dynamic environment.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Gloom's Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dr-glooms-lab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dr-glooms-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Dr. Gloom’s Lab puts a player in the future of Jackson Blair, a character who goes to a secluded research center. The plot originates at the entrance, offering a first -person gameplay in which the study becomes a key element of promotion. Gamers have to find and distribute limited reserves for survival, moving through the internal spaces of the structure. The central goal is the consistent clarification of events inside the complex and a collision with the direct consequences of its previous operations.</description></item><item><title>Mysteries of Fangclaw</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mysteries-of-fangclaw/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mysteries-of-fangclaw/</guid><description>Game Description Mysteries of Fangclaw begins after a friend betrays Bakster Hemlock and imprisones him in an abandoned gold mine. The player’s main goal is to contribute to the survival of the protagonist, exploring the underground passages and the entities that are opposing there. Promotion in the plot is associated with a mission to collect creatures of creatures and make decisions that determine life or death in the conditions of a change of day and night.</description></item><item><title>Return to ash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/return-to-ash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/return-to-ash/</guid><description>Game Description Return To Ash begins with the awakening of the main character, Ashley, in a quiet and bright hospital ward. She discovers the disappearance of her physical ailments, and an absolute white void extends outside the window. This visual novel represents a narrative focused on the study of posthumry, with an emphasis on interpersonal ties and consequences of actions. The player’s elections directly affect the development of the plot, determining the path of Ashley in this unfamiliar dimension.</description></item><item><title>Revengeful Ghost</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revengeful-ghost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revengeful-ghost/</guid><description>Game Description Revengeful Ghost introduces Kayiti Tsujisava, a second grade student of a high school, whose twin sister Akane disappears after a message on his phone-scrap. This communication contained a video that became central in subsequent events. Soon after the loss of Akan, another student from his school takes scores with life, jumping off the roof. This second incident forces Cayiti to go to the educational institution to clarify the connection between these cases.</description></item><item><title>Limscape: The Liminal Space Explorer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/limscape-the-liminal-space-explorer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/limscape-the-liminal-space-explorer/</guid><description>Game Description Limscape: The Liminal Space Explorer offers the first -person trip to quiet, terrible environment. In this project, gamers move according to locations that demonstrate signs of linearity, striving for the exit. This gameplay develops from simple movement, including actions such as swimming, jumping, squats and climbing. Such activity translate the study from horizontal routes to vertical obstacles, increasing the player’s immersion and its interaction with unique conditions.
Gamers also select and throw objects, further strengthening their influence on the world.</description></item><item><title>Loot of Baal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/loot-of-baal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/loot-of-baal/</guid><description>Game Description Loot of Baal works from the side panel of the screen, allowing you to play at the same time with other computer tasks. Players collect and send a detachment of mercenaries for battles with demons and obtaining treasures on randomly generated combat locations. The project offers hundreds of fighters, each with unique skills, and a collection of more than 1000 different things for the search. This concept of gameplay facilitates the promotion, because the key adventure occurs in a separate area of the display and does not require constant attention.</description></item><item><title>Three Kingdoms Mushouden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/three-kingdoms-mushouden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/three-kingdoms-mushouden/</guid><description>Game Description Three Kingdoms Mushouden transfers gamers in 182 of our era, on the threshold of the uprising of yellow dressings. The imperial court is covered by a deep internal confusion and fractional straightforwardness, which interferes with the work of officials, condemning the people into difficult trials. Players choose either a unique hero or a commander from the annals; They have to form troops and conclude alliances. Such preparations are carried out against the background of growing chaos, giving the opportunity to change the course of history.</description></item><item><title>Snow Plowing Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-plowing-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-plowing-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Snow Plowing Simulator is a relaxing and atmospheric simulator in which cleaning the territory from snow becomes an exciting adventure! Forget about the difficulties of winter cleaning - here you can enjoy snowy beauty and study the surroundings using various tools and vehicles. Start with a simple shovel, and then advance to more serious machines and interchangeable plows systems to complete more and more complex tasks in all corners of the city and mountainous areas.</description></item><item><title>Covenant of Solitude</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</guid><description>Game Description Covenant of Solitude introduces the story of a young man named Fort, who secretly owns the gift to command monsters in a secluded settlement of the leaves. The carriers of such a force are called ginns - their fate is full of persecution, fear and exploitation from others. The familiar way of life of the hero breaks off when the war breaks into his house, flooding the streets with blood and forcing the fort to accept his essence.</description></item><item><title>Lunar Eclipse</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunar-eclipse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunar-eclipse/</guid><description>Game Description Lunar Eclipse begins when the fair -haired main character wakes up in her house, where she has lived all her life, now characterized by deep silence and the absence of its inhabitants. This sudden emptiness and a change in the familiar situation encourage her to look for the reasons for the widespread disappearance. Its promotion includes movement by locations with weak lighting and deserted corridors, areas that hide unknown dangers.</description></item><item><title>Kill the Clock</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-the-clock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-the-clock/</guid><description>Game Description Kill the Clock immerses players in the role of the vengeful protagonist, moving along the gloomy European streets of the mid-1900s and finding that his sworn enemy is already killed by an unknown attacker. Accused of this atrocity, the player must reveal the riddle of the death of his enemy. The investigation occurs inside the repeating temporary cycle, forcing the protagonist to live the same seven -day to live again, while each round offers another option for a deprivation of life, which must be unraveled before the time is overturned, in the intricacies of insidious deception.</description></item><item><title>VOID War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</guid><description>Game Description Void War puts a player at the head of an ancient starship, sending him on a journey to the heart of a dying empire. This ship is described as a powerful and formidable gun filled with secret technologies. The tasks include the reflection of the attacks of crazy cultists, cowardly cosmopirates and xenophobic imperial soldiers. The detection of powerful artifacts allows you to turn a starship into a frightening combat vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Ricave</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ricave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ricave/</guid><description>Game Description Ricave sends a player to an escape from a changeable dungeon, where the movement occurs step by step around the cells. The battles suggest the use of the environment: you can encounter opponents in poisonous water or lure them to barrels with explosives. The state of the character monitors specific ailments, including diseases, bleeding and fractures. The damage here is local: the loss of the leg slows down, the eye injury leads to blindness, and the lack of hands limits the interaction with objects for all creatures.</description></item><item><title>Clink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</guid><description>Game Description Clink puts a player in the role of a woman living in voluntary solitude in an old house only with her cat and buried memories. The central conflict lies in the question of whether its experiences are symptoms of a prescribed disease or a manifestation of something otherworldly. One morning, the familiar way of the heroine is broken: one of the doors is locked, the key disappeared, and a metal ringing echoed in his head.</description></item><item><title>Fearbonding</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</guid><description>Game Description Fearbonding represents Hinata, a demon for whom fear has a tangible quality, like sweet, viscous honey. The lack of genuine horror makes his meeting with the Kosuke, a personality with obvious instability, determining the moment. This meeting encourages Hinata, focusing his demonic existence on the goal: to subordinate this person and cultivate his fear. He seeks to make Kosuke with his new instrument for the extraction of this resource so necessary for food.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Island: Missing Amy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</guid><description>Game Description Mystery Island: Missing Amy tells about the hell, the researcher, looking for sister, mysteriously missing months ago. The plot unfolds when hell receives a selfie from a loved one; The picture captures the missing girl on a remote island, where sea water has a bloody red color. This frame encourages hell to take a sea trip to search for a relative and study the location from a mysterious message.</description></item><item><title>Cauldron</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</guid><description>Game Description Cauldron is a role project with an emphasis on a system of improvement and the implementation of mini-stories. In the role of NIX, a character who finds himself in a world immersed in darkness will have to explore the environment and look for allies. The structure implies the cycle: the commission of actions leads to strengthening the party, which opens the way to the study of new areas and obtaining content.</description></item><item><title>Roadcraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roadcraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roadcraft/</guid><description>Game Description Roadcraft is a simulator in which gamers take on the role of the head of a company engaged in the restoration of territories affected by natural disasters. The main task is to use various types of construction equipment for clearing blockages, restoring roads and repairing damaged infrastructure.
The Title offers a detailed approach to the problems that arise in the elimination of the consequences of natural disasters, offering tasks such as replacing faulty equipment and deploying resources columns to create the necessary materials for reconstruction.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2 - fishing simulator, offering to participate in a huge number of tests and demonstrate many different techniques. Use a wide set of tools and gear: feeder, overlap, spinning, classic float and much more. Continuation of the game significantly improves the graphic component, adds many mechanics, tools and improves all aspects of the gameplay. More and better - the basic principle of Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2.</description></item><item><title>Doloc Town</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</guid><description>Game Description Doloc Town - this is a farm simulator in the conditions of post -apocalypse. The player accepts the role of a beginner whose task is to build an existing economy in the desert territory. The environment pushes to the study of its predominantly unexplored areas. Key activity includes the landing of cultures, the construction of the necessary structures and the consistent search for information about the past of this changed world.</description></item><item><title>Best Served Cold</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</guid><description>Game Description The Best Served Cold puts a gamer at the Knightsp Rack, an underground bar, working during the dry law in the alternative European city of Bukovia. You take on the role of a bartender responsible for the preparation of cocktails for visitors to the institution. Intections go beyond the maintenance, including direct clashes with persons identified as criminals and the need to navigate in dangerous situations.
The main actions include the investigation of the murders taking place in this environment while maintaining the work of the bar.</description></item><item><title>Freeride</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/freeride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/freeride/</guid><description>Game Description Adventures in Freeride will allow you to look at the mysterious world of spirits, where players will be able to test the skills of telekinesis, taking under the control of the protagonist. In the process of passage, you will have to perform a variety of actions that affect the general story of the narrative and allow you to analyze the character and personality of the user. The game is made in the form of role adventura, where you have to explore three -dimensional locations and communicate with secondary characters.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>Age of Reforming: The Frelands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</guid><description>Game Description Age of reforging: The Frelands is a cruel world of the Middle Ages in an alternative world where magic exists, and the gods are quite real and if they are enough to pray and make generous gifts, they can even bless the asking person. There reigns tyranny and lawlessness, and survival is being built in trade. The more successful the seller, the easier he lives, the rest was terribly unlucky.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remastered/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remastered is a large-scale processing on the Unreal Engine 5 engine, completely transforming the appearance of an open world of a cult action-RPG. Title takes 25 times more disk space thanks to comprehensively processed and improved landscape textures. Also, the mechanisms of lighting and background shading were seriously revised with the addition of volumetric effects that change the type of premises and night locations.</description></item><item><title>White Knuckle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/white-knuckle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/white-knuckle/</guid><description>Game Description In White Knuckle, gamers will have to overcome the destructive structure of the Sub-STRUCTURA 17. It is based on a mechanic based on a pulse that requires accuracy and quick reflexes. Each step matters, because one wrong movement can send a gamer to a dark abyss below. The essence is to manage resources and inventory, which is becoming more and more important as users lift their limits higher and higher.</description></item><item><title>Lushfoil Photography Sim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lushfoil-photography-sim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lushfoil-photography-sim/</guid><description>Game Description Lushfoil Photography SIM is an incredibly beautiful and relaxing game in which the player can simply relax as much as he needs. She does not drive the user forward, allowing him to admire the views, relaxes the natural sounds of the noise of leaves, water or the creak of snow. If desired, you can completely turn off the musical accompaniment and plunges into the virtual world, so similar to the real one.</description></item><item><title>Promise Mascot Agency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</guid><description>Game Description Promise Mascot Agency offers the gamer to plunge into the life of Kaso-Machi, a damned Japanese town. The main character, Michi, is in exile and must establish the work of the agency of urban masks. Key tasks include hiring these creatures, resolving the problems that arise due to their actions, and clarifying the causes of the protagonist link. Communication with a kick, a living finger with a complex character, is also part of the gameplay while you are trying to make your agency the best in the region through the study of the world and plot events.</description></item><item><title>The Talos Principle: Reawakened</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-talos-principle-reawakened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-talos-principle-reawakened/</guid><description>Game Description The Talos Principle: Reawakened returns gamers to the exciting world of puzzles and philosophical research. This is an updated publication - a rethinking of the original, designed to propose a deeper and more extensive experience. This is not just a remister - this is a complete processing in which new content and improved mechanics appeared, but at the same time, fidelity has remained loyal to what made the original so attractive.</description></item><item><title>Emissary Zero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emissary-zero/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emissary-zero/</guid><description>Game Description Emissary Zero is a title in which a group of people under cover of darkness enters an unfamiliar building. With minimal tips from a remote manager, they are looking for something called the moon, hoping to leave him intact. The structure is unpredictable, it shifts as they move, forcing them to navigate in space, which refuses to be understandable. Each sound alone becomes a potential threat; Together, coordination becomes both a tool and a risk.</description></item><item><title>inzoi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inzoi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inzoi/</guid><description>Game Description Inzoi is a life -symbol game in which gamers assign the role of the creator and observer in a detailed virtual community. In a dynamic environment, users can interact with various characters known as Zoe. These characters are not connected by actions recorded in the script, but act of their own free will, controlled by more than 400 mental elements that form their behavior and solutions. Result? A constantly developing world in which rumors spread, trends and even diseases appear.</description></item><item><title>Trolls vs Vikings: Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trolls-vs-vikings-reborn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trolls-vs-vikings-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description Trolls vs Vikings: Reborn unfolds the conflict in the fantasy world, where the player has to push the forces of trolls with viking opponents and Scandinavian gods. The main action is to manage troll detachments to protect the territory from advancing opponents on a field divided into cells. This strategy in real time requires the tactical placement of units and the use of magical abilities. Survival under the onslaught of constant attacks depends on adaptation to enemy constructions and using the unique skills of each troll.</description></item><item><title>Card Survival: Fantasy Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Card Survival: Fantasy Forest is a survival simulator that immerses in the very heart of the ancient forest. Title takes users to a world where nature is not only living, but also has its own mind. Here, gamers build a house, overcome daily difficulties and interact with a rich ecosystem full of wild animals, magical creatures and unpredictable forces. Every day brings new difficulties associated with survival: from hunger and health management to solving problems with the weather and seasons.</description></item><item><title>The Stamp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-stamp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-stamp/</guid><description>Game Description The Stamp is an interactive literature where players help a friend named Vincent. His long -standing interest in esotericism grew into an all -consuming passion, now determining its existence. In the walls of the house of Vincent, Gamer encounters memories, analyzes various documents and must accept the consequences arising directly from the research of his friend. This investigation requires to collect fragments of information to understand the whole picture of what is happening.</description></item><item><title>AVOWED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/avowed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/avowed/</guid><description>Game Description AVOWED is an adventure role -playing role -playing game, the actions of which unfold on a magic continent called Eora. The developers are people who gave the world such hits as Fallout: New Vegas and The Outer Worlds. The game makes the main emphasis on a journey through the bright world, battles with monsters and skeletons, pumping a hero, etc. It is also necessary to take part in the real war.</description></item><item><title>Dead Dragons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Dragons launches history 100 years after the victory of people over the dragons - the events that allegedly brought the world. Now rumors about the return of these creatures encourage the protagonist to investigate the case of a mysterious girl associated with the dragon race. This task develops into a conflict that decides the fate of the whole world and raises the main question of the survival of one of the species in the upcoming confrontation.</description></item><item><title>Novus orbis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/novus-orbis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/novus-orbis/</guid><description>Game Description Novus orbis is a Roguelike designer of decks, inviting gamers to the world, where selected cards and how you play them determine your path. The essence is to master the combo. Each card has its value, and their effect depends on how you arrange them - play the cards in the correct order to maximize their strength, or mix them to get a potentially different result. This emphasis on the strategy gives Tita depth, forcing you to be on the alert while you are guided in complex mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Keep Driving</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-driving/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-driving/</guid><description>Game Description Keep Driving immerses in the atmosphere of freedom of a long, slow trip to the procedurally generated world. The action takes place in the early 2000s, you are behind the wheel of your first car, a long road and a festival are ahead, which you need to get to the other end of the country. Passing along the highway and dirt roads, you are faced with difficulties, both from the environment and from the bizarre hitchhiker, looking for a passage.</description></item><item><title>Stray Path</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray-path/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray-path/</guid><description>Game Description Stray Path combines Freecell mechanics and strategic adventure gameplay. Gamers begin with the choice of one of several characters and plunge into the world, which is different each time. The Title offers a random set of enemies, tests and awards, all this is regulated by the cards that you pull. Each card is a new decision, whether it is a battle, avoiding a meeting or choosing equipment. The choice you make affects the outcome of your trip.</description></item><item><title>Threefold Recital</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</guid><description>Game Description Threefold Recital invites gamers to move to bright eastern fantasy, where the overgrown city of Bluscles stands on the threshold of a new era. Once the city was warmed in the rays of the Golden Age, and now it is mired in political instability and tension. Title draws a picture of the world where ancient magic and modern technologies are intertwined, creating a unique mixture that drives the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of QUD-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Luma Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/luma-island/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/luma-island/</guid><description>Game Description Luma Island sends users on a trip full of research, discoveries and tests. Regardless of whether you go alone or unite with friends, this adventure is a world full of possibilities. The island offers a wide range of classes - from the construction of the farm of his dreams to the discovery of hidden treasures and solving confusing puzzles. This is a game in which you can plunge into a bright world, constantly discovering something new for yourself and moving forward at your own pace.</description></item><item><title>Skufs against lizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skufy-protiv-jascherov/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skufy-protiv-jascherov/</guid><description>Game Description Skufs against lizards immerse gamers into the life of Skuf Cicetus, an ordinary guy whose world turns upside down as a result of an unexpected invasion of reptiles. History begins with the fact that one night the Skuf hears a strange sound and discovers that his city, Olycnishchensk, is captured by lizards. These are not ordinary garden creatures, but evil, aggressive invaders who came from nowhere. Armed only with his ingenuity and by the fact that he can capture along the road, Skuf takes responsibility to fight off the scaly horde.</description></item><item><title>Eden Crafters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</guid><description>Game Description Eden Crafters throws glove in the hands of survival and automation lovers. In this cooperative adventure with the open world, players will turn to turn a hostile planet into a hospitable refuge for humanity. Think about this as a space project of reconstruction - harsh conditions, fluids of the house of dreams. Task? Overcome the unpleasant habits of the planet and build a new house for humanity. Imagine radioactive zones and insidious landscapes are not the best real estate.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>The Phantom Fellows</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-phantom-fellows/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-phantom-fellows/</guid><description>Game Description The Phantom Fellows is the story of Oliver Kobblestone and Englbert Piclander, the two best friends who are in their own way understand the difficulties of life and the afterlife. Oliver is a living character, and Englbert is a ghost, and together they manage the service of paranormal investigations in the fictional town of Elderberry, Colorado. Thanks to this partnership, players receive a mixture of humor and intrigues, exploring various places in the city, interacting both living and dead.</description></item><item><title>Rats in a Cage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rats-in-a-cage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rats-in-a-cage/</guid><description>Game Description Rats in a Cage proposes to solve puzzles in the form of a corporate certification. The player will manipulate colleagues, strategically placing coffee or spreading gossip, changing their routes and assigning other people&amp;rsquo;s merits to himself. The whole process oversees artificial intelligence, actively interfering with passage and sometimes interacting with elements outside the game window.
Such a gameplay constantly experiences the willingness to sacrifice others for the sake of personal benefits and career growth.</description></item><item><title>Chef RPG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chef-rpg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chef-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Chef RPG gives a completely new idea of ​​what a culinary culinary can be. So, users get the role of a wandering chef, who has an important mission - to revive the legendary Le Sex restaurant. Once this place was a real magnet for travelers and everyone who wanted to eat and take a breath, and now this is nothing more than an abandoned building. It is time to return to him former glory, developing his own business and going to a new level in terms of cooking.</description></item><item><title>Intravenous 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</guid><description>Game Description Intravenous 2 immerses you in the world of cruel intrigues and intense action. Play for Sean, desperately trying to save his abducted father, and Steve, a grumbling former military with a dark past. Their unlikely union is based on a common goal: to pass the labyrinth of the underworld, complete secrets, lies and mortal danger.
But how you can handle this insidious Odyssey depends only on you. Will you be a ghost, fluttering in shadows and manipulating environment in your interests?</description></item><item><title>Depersonalization</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</guid><description>Game Description Depersonalization may interest amateurs of anime, Howard Lovecraft and Tactical Japanese Role Games. This is a mixture of TRPG, horror and visual novel. When creating their project, Chinese developers were inspired by the world of space horrors created by an eminent writer. Their creation boasts a detailed and designed pixel 2D graphic in anime style. The project is divided into several modules. Each of them has various finals and branches.</description></item><item><title>Fish Hero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fish-hero/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fish-hero/</guid><description>Game Description Fish Hero is an adventure based on physics, focused on parking, where players control the water being outside its natural element. The key task is to throw the character up to reach the top. Progress entirely depends on the development of a special slap movement, which allows you to move through the platforms and gain a height. This action is the only method for moving through a three -dimensional world that requires accurate calculation and understanding of inertia.</description></item><item><title>The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS is a step-by-step game where survival depends on spatial thinking. Each enemy and type of weapons act according to a unique scheme on the battlefield, forming a tactical environment from intersecting zones of defeat. Success is maneuvering for the operation of enemy vulnerability, while trying to cover the maximum area with his own arsenal. Any movement, the use of an object or attack completes the move, giving opponents the opportunity to deliver a response.</description></item><item><title>Tavern Talk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</guid><description>Game Description Tavern Talk throws you into the very heart of the fantasy kingdom, but not as a powerful warrior or clever robber. Here you will take into your hands the reins of the reign of a cozy tavern Wayfarer&amp;rsquo;s Inn. But this is not an ordinary bartender simulator. The “Traveler” tavern is filled with a whisper and secrets of adventure seekers - your regulars. This is not just thirsty souls who want to drink a mug of ale.</description></item><item><title>Tradesman: Deal to Dealer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tradesman-deal-to-dealer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tradesman-deal-to-dealer/</guid><description>Game Description Tradesman: Deal to Dealer offers gamers to become merchants, moving around the world, which is both a market and a minefield. You will travel through a variety of landscapes, buying a cheap and selling more expensive - classic merchants. But there is something more than it seems at first glance. Here you are in wait for the danger - imagine the bandits watching your wagon with exotic fish while you are yearning for a cold man in the village of Crubgrog.</description></item><item><title>Isles of Sea and Sky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/isles-of-sea-and-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/isles-of-sea-and-sky/</guid><description>Game Description Isles of Sea and Sky - a strategic adventure with a huge number of puzzles for logic, attentiveness and ingenuity. The project, developed by two programmers, uses pixel graphics and a camera located on top, which refers to some classic games with a similar theme and visual side. There is support for gamepads without additional configuration.
The casual management will make life easier for beginners, but the complex tasks posed to the user will gradually become increasingly confusing and incomprehensible at first glance.</description></item><item><title>The Mildew Children</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-mildew-children/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-mildew-children/</guid><description>Game Description The visual novel The Mildew Children tells of a secluded village, where children in isolation practice ancient pagan customs. The settlement rotates around the Kirfel, a young witch who, together with her sisters, takes on the role of the keeper of rituals. Players move along the winding paths of the settlement, revealing its dark background and the causes of a kind of social structure.
The game takes place in twelve chapters, conducting players through burial grounds, dense forests and weathered houses, which are dotted with the landscape.</description></item><item><title>Expections: A Mudrunner Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</guid><description>Game Description Expections: A Mudrunner Game throws you headlong into unknown territories, putting you at the head of research missions at insidious landscapes. Get ready for an off -road adventure based on physics, where every centimeter of progress requires the courage, strategy and masterful ownership of your strong all -terrain vehicle. Imagine how you will overcome the deserts sifted by the sun, thick forests clinging to your tires, and snowy peaks that experience you for strength.</description></item><item><title>Hellcard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellcard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellcard/</guid><description>Game Description Hellcard is made in the same style as the original book of demons. Their universe is also common. The first game was a simplified diabloid and narrated about the fight against evil awakened in the catacombs under the city. The spin-off changed the genre, turning from Hack and Slash into a step-by-step card RPG. One of the chips in the form of cardboard graphics has not gone away. The elements of the sideline remained.</description></item><item><title>Noctuary</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</guid><description>Game Description Noctuary - an alloy of visual novel and adventure action, which immerses abortor in the bright world, following the intertwined travels of Fanny and Alina. Being novice arbarars, the duet passes through the rich tapestry of characters, quests and enemies in this colorful kingdom. Distinguished by the inventive mechanics of the battle, the game allows you to smoothly switch the characters between fanchia and Alina, each of which is endowed with various skills and styles of battle.</description></item><item><title>Higurashi whether They Cry Hou+</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</guid><description>Game Description Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ is the final part of its franchise, representing 4 new chapters for playing players. The people who were in the grip of Hinamidzava are now exempted from fate, which riveted them to the repeating events of June 1983. Despite this permission, the story of the region is not completed, and this project proposes to explore many previously hidden worlds.
The narrative Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ departs from the established secret, representing alternative scenarios full of both psychological stress and unexpected humor.</description></item><item><title>Lost Hope: Backrooms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Hope: BackRooms offers a single first -person adventure in the alarming locations of backstage. Key classes include navigation for these confusing, interconnected places and active interaction with the environment for solving logical puzzles, which contributes to the development of the main plot. The area often demonstrates strange and inexplicable phenomena, which are difficult to immediately comprehend. Gamers have to carefully study these elements in order to reveal the secrets hidden in this tense journey.</description></item><item><title>Concealed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</guid><description>Game Description Concealed begins with the fact that Maine Jiannan returns to the secondary school of Diinlin after the student exchange program. Her return to school life is interrupted when classmates begin to disappear without explanation. These events are correlated with old, unsolved matters and city legends circulating in the territory of the educational institution for years. Maine Jiannan has to face incidents and find a way to reveal the secrets hidden behind the facade of the school.</description></item><item><title>Back to the Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description The prison atmosphere in Back to the Dawn shows the life of an anthropomorphic animal that is forced to fight for the right to exist in a zone. Gamers will explore prison laws, rules and locations in which a protagonist finds himself. The main character will pump and make new acquaintances, relying on his own social skills. It will be possible to use cunning and intelligence to solve many problems, where the main task is an attempt to escape from imprisonment.</description></item><item><title>For the king 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/for-the-king-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/for-the-king-2/</guid><description>Game Description For The King 2 is a continuation of an unforgettable adventure RPG with elements of the board game and Roguelike, where you can defeat the formidable queen alone or together with three comrades. You have to explore the world and increase your level in order to reveal the secrets of the past and overthrow the despotistical queen. Try to avoid the queen fanatical guards who control everything around, and combine their forces with their apostates to conquer this world.</description></item><item><title>AI Roguelite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-roguelite/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-roguelite/</guid><description>Game Description AI Roguelite is a text role -playing game where artificial intelligence generates all content and controls all game mechanics. The system determines each location, a non -game character, an enemy and an object that a player faces. In addition, recipes for creating things and fundamental rules of interaction also come from the neural network. As a result, the gamer has to explore the Universe, 100 percent consisting of elements created by a large language model, which provides a procedural adventure as a procedurally generated.</description></item><item><title>Call Hating</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-hating/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-hating/</guid><description>Game Description In Call Hating, an aging and forgetful employee working from the house is faced with a technological crisis after a smartphone breakdown and the Internet disconnect. The main task of the player is to use outdated equipment from the home office to pass the hellish telephone menu. The path to restoring the connection lies through interaction with the acquired technology and solve a series of problems. This mission is served as an urgent need, and the goal must be achieved at all costs.</description></item><item><title>Contraband Police</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</guid><description>Game Description Contraband Police - The simulator of the border guard in the first person. The player in the role of the commander of the border post makes an inspection of transport for the presence of smuggling on the border of the third world countries. The inspection tasks include: checking documents: inspection and permit for entry criminals &amp;hellip; or take a bribe. What? Nobody heard this! To carry out reports on the successful completion of tasks through the mail; the accumulated experience can be spent on pumping the department, buying new equipment or training dogs;</description></item><item><title>KYNSEED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kynseed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kynseed/</guid><description>Game Description KYNSEED is a role -playing game in an adventure genre and a life simulator in an open world. The game saw the light in 2018 and has already managed to find its own fan base. The essence of the passage is to completely immerse into the invented world, filled with various inhabitants, who have their own affairs and habits. The player is invited to interact with these characters, simultaneously equipping his own life.</description></item><item><title>Out of Ore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</guid><description>Game Description In Out of Ore, gamers have to take many heavy equipment under their control, with the help of which it will be possible to extract ore, move the ground, dig pits, build or repair buildings and much more. It is necessary to test yourself as a driver of construction equipment, which is intended for various purposes. The main character goes on the plot for the very north of the country where there is a small base from Company Mining Corp.</description></item><item><title>Mars Base</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</guid><description>Game Description Mars Base will appreciate all fans of science fiction, as Gamer goes to the world of the future, in which travels between planets became possible. Humanity makes a desperate attempt to colonize Mars, but the first settlers will be in a serious danger. The protagonist is one of those who fell into the very first expedition and is obliged to build a huge complex on the surface of the Red Planet, which will make a person’s life away from the ground.</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Way of the Hunter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</guid><description>Game Description Way of the Hunter gives an excellent opportunity to become the owner of his own hunting house in the middle of a deaf forest and periodically go hunting in search of extreme and valuable production. This simulator offers a very realistic experience, as it takes into account many factors and allows you to plunge into a huge completely open virtual world, which looks like alive. It exists regardless of the action of the user - the weather, the time of day changes dynamically, and all the animals sleep, eat, move in search of a safer place.</description></item><item><title>Alchemia: Creatio ex nihilo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemia-creatio-ex-nihilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemia-creatio-ex-nihilo/</guid><description>Game Description Alchemia: Creatio Ex Nihilo combines several genres. This is a head-headed game, a step-by-step strategy and a simplified corgorate. The action takes place in the fantasy world, where magic is adjacent to alchemy. The hero travels through the forgotten kingdom, finds artifacts (available 30 species), collects materials, opens recipes (there are 40 varieties here), crafts weapons from them and fights with its help with different monsters. The user can choose a route for his ward on a fork.</description></item><item><title>Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</guid><description>Game Description Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga tells about the events that erupted after the conflict between the Empire of Veridia and Tanra. They fought for a long time, and in the end all these events led to the fact that the first empire remained in losses. However, thanks to the young ruler of Florin, a shaky, but peace finally formed. Everyone began to gradually recover until something terrible happened.</description></item><item><title>Keplerth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the futuristic Indo-video trigger Keplerth unfold in the distant future-on the previously unknown planet Kepler. According to the genre, the project can be attributed to the simulator of survival with the possibility of construction and RPG elements. According to the plot, people built a large spaceship, which was supposed to transport the colonists on board to the nearest planet suitable for life. But there is a disaster, as a result of which the ship crashes on an unknown planet.</description></item><item><title>Idle Calibur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</guid><description>Game Description Idle Calibur combines a study of the open world with tactical RPG tactical and real -time mechanics in real time. The gameplay is focused on the construction of a city, which serves to recruit heroes with special abilities. Battles can be automatically due to IDLE function, or you can take direct manual control of your detachments during the fight. Key tasks include the collection of forces to attack other settlements on the world map and participate in structured tests with bosses for development.</description></item><item><title>Sands of Salzaar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</guid><description>Game Description Sands of Salzaar is a strategic game whose actions unfold in the Salzaara desert. Fight with numerous hostile factions, gathering your own army and developing your city. Choose your character, profession and faction, on whose side your army will have to fight. The eastern land is filled with various secrets and you have to solve them all.
Sands of Salzaar events talk about an exotic old empire that once ruled the desert.</description></item><item><title>Icarus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</guid><description>Game Description Icarus is a first -person survival that will send you to explore the secrets of one distant planet. You wake up from cryosn after your shuttle made a forced landing on the surface of a mysterious planet. Now you need to stay alive, surviving in unusual conditions. Collect resources, craft items and play both alone and along with other players. The gameplay Ikarus can be described as cooperative action with survival elements.</description></item><item><title>Mud and Blood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mud-and-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mud-and-blood/</guid><description>Game Description The rethought project MUD and Blood is a shootout between the two sides of the conflict, where the user has to observe the events. The setting transfers during the Second World War, where soldiers converge in battles. The updated engine and improved artificial intelligence allows you to try out the old classic flash game, filled with innovations in terms of functions and a graphic component that immerses gameplay into the process.</description></item><item><title>Snowrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</guid><description>Game Description The main difference between Snowrunner and many other cargo simulators is that there are no even roads, highways and autobahns. Only snow, dirt and insurmountable obstacles. The game meets with interesting and diverse tasks, vast cards and, most importantly, a wide choice of transport: SUVs, tractors, all -terrain vehicles and trucks. After choosing a cargo and a car, you should go on a road that is not going to be easy.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Bunny</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</guid><description>Game Description Tiny Bunny is a black and white visual novel containing a considerable amount of horror and sappress. Get lost in the forest, in no case can you hear his voice, otherwise death will follow. The events of the game occur in winter. Something follows you and constantly walks between the trees. There are rumors about constant screams from the forest, and the board with the losses of children is replenished each time.</description></item><item><title>The Catacombs of Solaris Revisited</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-catacombs-of-solaris-revisited/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-catacombs-of-solaris-revisited/</guid><description>Game Description The Catacombs of Solaris Revisited invites the player to move along the procedure -created and abstract labyrinth with first -person view. This nonlinear space is a promising labyrinth, a manipulating perception of a three -dimensional environment on a two -dimensional screen and creating surrealistic effects. The main task is personal in nature: to find a special room in constantly changing catacombs, which seems to be the most attractive to the gamer.</description></item><item><title>Empyrion - Galactic Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Empyrion - Galactic Survival shows the world of the future. In the 24th century, in the ice of Antarctica, they find a spacecraft of aliens. Scientists investigated the object and discovered the technology of the hyperdrod. Earthlings send an expedition to the planet Empirion, which is in the Andromeda nebula. The crew gets to the destination, but tolerates the crash and cannot return home.
In survival mode, the player leaves the rescue capsule and is alone against the hostile world.</description></item><item><title>Travellers Rest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/travellers-rest/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/travellers-rest/</guid><description>Game Description Travellers Rest gives the opportunity to live the life of an innkeeper. You own a small tavern that you dream to turn into a noisy and crowded place in the district. But to achieve this goal, you need to work a lot. Build a bro -up and cook the most delicious beer. Manage the farm and serve only the best products on the table. Satisfy customer requests and gain popularity so that a whole kingdom speaks of your institution!</description></item><item><title>Stoneshard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</guid><description>Game Description Come in the role of a harsh mercenary in a harsh, ruined war, kingdom. Take part in step -by -step battles and examine the RPG elements of Stoneshard, available in the gameplay. You can perform contracts, secondary and plot missions. Heal the wounds, purchase equipment and improve the protagonist as soon as you wish.
Freely move around the big and seamless world. Explore the villages lying in the ruins, go down to the dungeons or look into abandoned tracts.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Truckker: Extended Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-trucker-extended-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-trucker-extended-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Galaxy Truckker: Extended Edition - a strategy about truckers from distant space. The gameplay was based on the same tough. You will build cosmic shuttles, evade asteroids and enter into battle with a huge number of enemies. The main task is to earn as many cosmicredites as possible.
The life of a cosmic trucker is not easy. The Galaxy Truckker game process: Extended Edition offers a branch scenario, the events of which depend on your moral elections.</description></item><item><title>Wayward</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</guid><description>Game Description Survive in the wild in Wayward, traveling around the open world. The protagonist has no basic specialization, as he passes, he pumps skills and becomes capable of everything. To get new characteristics, you have to interact with objects and the world around you. You have the opportunity to play as you want.
The world is endless and generated randomly. Objects, chests, opponents, dangers, dungeons and tasks are also created by chance.</description></item><item><title>Dungeonmans</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeonmans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeonmans/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeonmans The Heroic Adventure Roguelike - a traditional horned in which you explore the dungeons, fight with a variety of monsters and collect lutus. You have to develop your academy in order to open new opportunities and skills. Go to the adventure and take part in step -by -step battles. A fascinating fantasy story awaits you, telling about the confrontation of good and evil.
Gameplay Dungeonmans The Heroic Adventure Roguelike:</description></item><item><title>Ribby: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Ribby: The Game - this is not a typical role -playing adventure. Forget about the extermination of dragons or collecting a million gold coins. Here is the hero - Ribbie, a kind girl, who has lost and seeking the house. Title combines elements of role -playing games and visual novels, creating a unique experience. Of course, the main goal is to return Ribbie home, but this is only the top of Lilia.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description Salvus: aries throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item><item><title>HAVEN: Secret of Caledria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/haven-secret-of-caledria/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:42 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/haven-secret-of-caledria/</guid><description>Game Description The game process Haven: Secret of Caledria is inspired by the classic JRPG of the 90s. All the key features of the gameplay are observed: a journey through a large open world in the company of partners, the implementation of numerous quests, a study of the dungeons and step -by -step battles. It will take about 20 hours of real time to pass the main storyline.
Hample Haven: Secret of Caledria is inspired by such cult projects as Lufia, Breath of Fire, Suikoden and Chrono Trigger.</description></item><item><title>Shrom and Gloom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shroom-and-gloom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:41 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shroom-and-gloom/</guid><description>Game Description Shrom and Gloom - a card game that combines the elements of a skewer and Dungen Crooler. Players have to go down into the gloomy dungeons to fight terrible monsters and try to find the King of the Void himself. A huge number of enemies and complex tests will meet on the way. A special mechanics is an element of KKI, which allows you to engage in a fight with the enemy using a deck of cards.</description></item><item><title>Animal Shelter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-shelter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-shelter/</guid><description>Game Description Animal Shelter offers the player to open his own animal shelter. Choose homeless animals on the streets, and provide medical care. Take care of your wards and make sure that they get along well with each other. Life on the street leaves prints on the body of animals. Process scratches and stick patcharies. Trinch the wounded paws and observe how the pet is recovering. Buy your patient well using a hose and a sponge.</description></item><item><title>Dustland Delivery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</guid><description>Game Description Dustland Delivery puts users in the post -apocalyptic world, where they have to build an empire of delivery. The center of the game is profit, survival and strategic decisions. Gamers start with a truck and gain a team, each of which has unique skills. The purpose of the game? Build cities by successful delivery of goods, competing with rivals and overcoming dangers. The world is inexorable. Users move in an insidious area, control resources and make a critical choice.</description></item><item><title>Good Heavens!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</guid><description>Game Description Good HEAVENS! It takes place in the Severe Kingdom of Xant-Rar, a bizarre afterlife, where souls live on floating islands. This songwriter with the open world allows gamers to pave their own path in the world, crowded with bizarre capabilities. Imagine: you have lived a good life, have left the earthly path and got into Xant -Rar - a place intended for the fulfillment of all your desires throughout eternity.</description></item><item><title>Ifsunsets</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ifsunsets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ifsunsets/</guid><description>Game Description IFSUnsets is an adventure role -playing adventure for survival in which gamers fall into a complex situation. The game begins with the fact that users find themselves on the island after a shipwreck. This initial scenario lays the basis for research and survival. During the day, users can collect supplies and resources scattered across the island. This stage of collecting resources is very important for preparing for dangers that are hidden after sunset.</description></item><item><title>Shattehed Pixel Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shattered-pixel-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shattered-pixel-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Shattehed Pixel Dungeon is an adventure in gloomy dungeons where users will take on the role of an adventurer. The setting is made in the style of dark fantasy, where you have to face various monsters. The game was made in the genre of Rolewal Rowlian Adventure, showing the journey of 4 characters. Levels in a single campaign are made in a randomized form, filling each time randomly locations with opponents and rooms in which the protagonist will be able to get.</description></item><item><title>Soul Apocalypto</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-apocalypto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-apocalypto/</guid><description>Game Description Soul Apocalypto is a role -playing game that includes systems of several strategic sucks. The gameplay combines team battles with the collecting of creatures and some mechanics of collecting decks, with a view of both from above and from a third party. The main lesson is the call of various companions for creating a personalized combat detachment. Progress directly depends on the choice of these fighters and their layout in a group that can explore the open world.</description></item><item><title>Sunrider Legends Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Sunrider Legends Tactics will put a player at the head of the Navy leading his ships along the seas of the fantasy world in the era of sails. You have to command the courts in step -by -step battles, making tactical decisions on maneuvers, positioning and the use of weapons against enemy armades. The adventure will require solving strategic problems in the open sea and participation in special plot events.</description></item><item><title>The Darkest Files</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-darkest-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-darkest-files/</guid><description>Game Description The Darkest Files unfolds in post -war Germany in 1956, in the period marked by the consequences of World War II and a complex process of searching justice. The user rises in place Esther Katz, a young prosecutor who joins the special unit of Fritz Bauer, who is instructed to investigate war crimes committed many years ago.
In this role, the gamer will have to find hidden evidence, to navigate in a society that does not want to recognize his past, and to confront criminals, who are now occupied by leading posts.</description></item><item><title>Tick ​​Hop</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</guid><description>Game Description Tick ​​Hop is a 2D platformer that requires the accuracy of movements, where a gamer assumes the role of the keeper of time. The journey includes the passage of the stages, each of which consists of temporary fragments. The main goal is to solve riddles, opening the aspects of the past to restore the future. The reverse reference system in this project requires quick actions to move through chronological spaces.</description></item><item><title>Under a New Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Under a New Sun begins after a catastrophic failure of the ship, who left the player on an unknown planet. Awakening from cryosn occurs among fragments, completely solitude under a stranger sky. The mission to search for a new house for humanity failed, and the fate of the crew remains a mystery. The path begins in the middle of the wreckage of the vessel, in a world where the earthly flora has taken roots next to local views.</description></item><item><title>Vault of the void</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vault-of-the-void/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vault-of-the-void/</guid><description>Game Description Vault of the Void is a well -planning contractions, where users need to collect abyss stones and make their way through the fantasy worlds of emptiness. We&amp;rsquo;ll have to fight against various monsters and aggressive creatures that penetrate the universe of people. The game is an atmospheric map of the Rowlaik project, where the users will be able to influence the storyline and the events taking place with their actions and decisions during the passage.</description></item><item><title>Zero Escape: The Nonary Games</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Escape: The Nonary Games is a collection of high -resolution visual novels developed by Spike Chunsoft. The mysterious plot involves us in the role of one of the nine abducted people and play the game on the stake of which life is standing.
The game has undergone updates and is now equipped with high graphics, more modern intuitive controls, as well as many new functions, including Japanese and English voice acting!</description></item></channel></rss>