<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Adventures on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/</link><description>Recent content in Adventures on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fearbonding</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</guid><description>Game Description ** Fearbonding ** represents Hinata, a demon for whom fear has a tangible quality, like sweet, viscous honey. The lack of genuine horror makes his meeting with the Kosuke, a personality with obvious instability, determining the moment. This meeting encourages Hinata, focusing his demonic existence on the goal: to subordinate this person and cultivate his fear. He seeks to make Kosuke with his new instrument for the extraction of this resource so necessary for food.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Island: Missing Amy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</guid><description>Game Description ** Mystery Island: Missing Amy ** tells about the hell, the researcher, looking for sister, mysteriously missing months ago. The plot unfolds when hell receives a selfie from a loved one; The picture captures the missing girl on a remote island, where sea water has a bloody red color. This frame encourages hell to take a sea trip to search for a relative and study the location from a mysterious message.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description ** Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2 ** - fishing simulator, offering to participate in a huge number of tests and demonstrate many different techniques. Use a wide set of tools and gear: feeder, overlap, spinning, classic float and much more. Continuation of the game significantly improves the graphic component, adds many mechanics, tools and improves all aspects of the gameplay. More and better - the basic principle of Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2.</description></item><item><title>Doloc Town</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</guid><description>Game Description ** Doloc Town ** - this is a farm simulator in the conditions of post -apocalypse. The player accepts the role of a beginner whose task is to build an existing economy in the desert territory. The environment pushes to the study of its predominantly unexplored areas. Key activity includes the landing of cultures, the construction of the necessary structures and the consistent search for information about the past of this changed world.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description ** Starvaders ** a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remastered/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description ** The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remastered ** is a large-scale processing on the Unreal Engine 5 engine, completely transforming the appearance of an open world of a cult action-RPG. Title takes 25 times more disk space thanks to comprehensively processed and improved landscape textures. Also, the mechanisms of lighting and background shading were seriously revised with the addition of volumetric effects that change the type of premises and night locations.</description></item><item><title>The Talos Principle: Reawakened</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-talos-principle-reawakened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-talos-principle-reawakened/</guid><description>Game Description ** The Talos Principle: Reawakened ** returns gamers to the exciting world of puzzles and philosophical research. This is an updated publication - a rethinking of the original, designed to propose a deeper and more extensive experience. This is not just a remister - this is a complete processing in which new content and improved mechanics appeared, but at the same time, fidelity has remained loyal to what made the original so attractive.</description></item><item><title>Threefold Recital</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</guid><description>Game Description ** Threefold Recital ** invites gamers to move to bright eastern fantasy, where the overgrown city of Bluscles stands on the threshold of a new era. Once the city was warmed in the rays of the Golden Age, and now it is mired in political instability and tension. Title draws a picture of the world where ancient magic and modern technologies are intertwined, creating a unique mixture that drives the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description ** Anime City ** transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description ** Caves of QUD **-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description ** Pinball Spire ** challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Contraband Police</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</guid><description>Game Description ** Contraband Police ** - The simulator of the border guard in the first person. The player in the role of the commander of the border post makes an inspection of transport for the presence of smuggling on the border of the third world countries. ** The inspection tasks include: ** checking documents: inspection and permit for entry criminals &amp;hellip; or take a bribe. What? Nobody heard this! To carry out reports on the successful completion of tasks through the mail; the accumulated experience can be spent on pumping the department, buying new equipment or training dogs;</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description ** WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] ** - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</guid><description>Game Description ** Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga ** tells about the events that erupted after the conflict between the Empire of Veridia and Tanra. They fought for a long time, and in the end all these events led to the fact that the first empire remained in losses. However, thanks to the young ruler of Florin, a shaky, but peace finally formed. Everyone began to gradually recover until something terrible happened.</description></item><item><title>Ribby: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description ** Ribby: The Game ** - this is not a typical role -playing adventure. Forget about the extermination of dragons or collecting a million gold coins. Here is the hero - Ribbie, a kind girl, who has lost and seeking the house. Title combines elements of role -playing games and visual novels, creating a unique experience. Of course, the main goal is to return Ribbie home, but this is only the top of Lilia.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description ** Salvus: aries ** throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item><item><title>Good Heavens!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</guid><description>Game Description ** Good HEAVENS! ** It takes place in the Severe Kingdom of Xant-Rar, a bizarre afterlife, where souls live on floating islands. This songwriter with the open world allows gamers to pave their own path in the world, crowded with bizarre capabilities. Imagine: you have lived a good life, have left the earthly path and got into Xant -Rar - a place intended for the fulfillment of all your desires throughout eternity.</description></item></channel></rss>