<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>races on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/</link><description>Recent content in races on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Liftoff: Micro Drones</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff: Micro Drones is a drone simulator. The game is dedicated to FPV thrones and FPV quadrocopters. This is the name of the model equipped with a camera, allowing their owners to observe the flight with first -person view. For those who prefer to watch actions from the outside, there is an opportunity to change the camera angle. This video game contains 6 really existing UAVs from well -known manufacturers, some of which are allowed to modify.</description></item><item><title>RECHARGE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</guid><description>Game Description RECHARGE is a simulation-arcade racing experience in which the player controls radio-controlled machines. The gameplay was built on a physical model of behavior and allows the customization of vehicles. Gamers compete on tracks created based on professional RC tracks and other locations, including beaches and entertainment parks. The project is intended for use with several input devices, supporting both standard gamepads and specialized controllers.
These features create the basis for individual and competitive races.</description></item><item><title>Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions - this is a racing game with the participation of Muscles from the European Park. There are 8 characters to choose from, including the main characters of Ed and Eddo from the Grand Prix of Europe. Railways take place on the tracks laid around the attractions of the continent. You can withstand computer counterparts or challenge three friends in local mode with the separation of the screen by arranging a direct competition in driver’s skills.</description></item><item><title>Wheel World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</guid><description>Game Description Wheel World represents the story of Kat, a cyclist chosen by ancient spirits for a key task. The setting is on the verge of collapse, and only Glavheroin can prevent it, having made a great shift ceremony. Her journey runs through the world, saturated with a bicycle culture, where she has to resist the elite teams in competitions.
The central mission is to return the abducted legendary details, which are the main components to complete the ritual and save its world from oblivion.</description></item><item><title>Descenders Next</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/descenders-next/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/descenders-next/</guid><description>Game Description Descenders Next is a sports action combining Roguelike mechanics with third -person views. Ryders use snowboards and mauntinboards to move along spacious, procedurally created locations. The project offers an open world study in several biomes: from snowy peaks to winding ground routes and specially equipped parks. Each race offers a new path, since internal mechanics create unique routes for every attempt.
This approach also includes the elements of Tower Defense and the first -person type for certain classes, providing a diverse game process.</description></item><item><title>Frog Jump</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</guid><description>Game Description Frog Jump puts players under the control of amphibians with the aim of vertical climbing through the three -dimensional world. They have to move according to a complex design, using jumps and climbing to go from one site to another. The entire level is designed around this movement up, representing a continuous navigation task. The first princess’s kiss receives a victory that reached the top.
This platformer can be held alone or in a multi -user competition for 8 competitors over the network.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>Drive Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Rally is an arcade game about rally races that transfers gamers during the glory of the 1990s. Having focused on speeds, skill and exciting sensations of an open road, Advencura offers nostalgic experience for fans of classic rally races. Users take on the role of a rally racer, competing in various iconic places around the world. From the dusty deserts of Africa to the snowy peaks of Scandinavia - each area offers unique trials and opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Retrowave 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</guid><description>Game Description Retrowave 2 places a player under the control of the supercar of the 1980s, moving along an endless highway surrounded by neon lights and palm trees. The project draws inspiration in an idealized, futuristic interpretation of that era, causing a sense of nostalgia for a period that never existed. This atmosphere provides a complete immersion in the world of Syntveyva. The main lesson is the piloting of transport along the road system on a retro -futuristic background, where aesthetics are built around synthesizer music.</description></item><item><title>Get to work</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/get-to-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/get-to-work/</guid><description>Game Description Get To Work is a rapid satirical game in which players take on the role of a young man who decided to achieve success in the corporate world, overcoming obstacles on roller skates. The main character is not just an ordinary character, he is equipped with roller skates on his arms and legs, which makes him rush through the streets at great speed. This is a chaotic journey when you are trying to jump over the abysses, evade ramps and avoid other dangers.</description></item><item><title>Hydroplane: Riptide Racers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hydroplane-riptide-racers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hydroplane-riptide-racers/</guid><description>Game Description Hydroplane: Riptide Racers is dedicated to racing on high-speed boats through the Utaika channels. Opponents compete on water tracks, trying to take first place in the races. For each victory, the necessary details used to assemble a unique boat are awarded. This racing game process, based on competitions and construction, allows you to open new equipment through the dominance in the races and improve your transport.
Rails at Hydroplane: Riptide Racers are held against the backdrop of a variety of landscapes in the original areas of the city.</description></item><item><title>Le Mans Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Le Mans Ultimate - The official game FIA ​​World Enduraance Championship and &amp;ldquo;24 hours of Le Man&amp;rdquo;, promises exciting experience to both experienced riders and beginners. Runned in early access, the game offers to try the exciting season of 2023 with official cars, legendary tracks and online media. Sit behind the wheel of ultramodern hypercars from manufacturers such as Toyota, Ferrari and Porsche, and recreate the battles on prestigious tracks.</description></item><item><title>Visco Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Visco Collection presents 7 arcade titles from the 1980s and 1990s. This collection contains projects of several genres, including Shoot ‘Em Up, fighting, sports and racing. The presented software supports single and local multiplayer modes for competitive or joint passage. Each Title demonstrates the special style of the arcade gameplay of that time with unique goals and mechanics that players have to study.
The Visco Collection contains Andro Dunos-Side-Squash Shoot ‘Em Up, which encounters you with elaboration ships and large-scale bosses.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>Driftwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</guid><description>Game Description Driftwood is a fascinating journey into the world of high -speed descent on Longboard. The main character is Eddie, a cool sliven who loves to ride in beautiful landscapes. This game provides an ideal balance of speed and control, bringing a feeling of relaxation and calm, despite a high -speed action.
The project offers minimalistic experience, focusing on skating on magnificent landscapes, and not on building a story campaign.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Sailor NG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-sailor-ng/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-sailor-ng/</guid><description>Game Description Virtual Sailor NG is a simulator with the open world, concentrated on the management of water vessels. The physical system of the project reproduces marine dynamics and behavior of various boats on the water. This allows gamers to direct vessels anywhere within the environment, which opens up scope for research. Players master all forms of sailing, using the first -person species and 6 degrees of freedom. Both single and multiplayer regime are available.</description></item><item><title>MX VS ATV Legends</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</guid><description>Game Description MX VS ATV Legends shows what intensive and at the same time dangerous racing competitions can be. Here, users are invited to participate in mass races on the proposed routes. Each location is full of surprises, so you need to carefully monitor the behavior of the vehicle so as not to fly from the distance at the most inopportune moment. Moreover, each type of transport has its own unique characteristics, and even the most experienced riders will need time to adapt and get used to the manner of behavior.</description></item><item><title>My Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</guid><description>Game Description My Garage is a simulator simulator with a first -person view. In it you can not only repair cars, but also ride them. During travel by transport, you can switch the camera angle. In Indo Tailet, weather conditions are changing. The change of day and night is also available. When driving in the dark, you can turn on the headlights.
My Garage has an open world. It consists of mountains, forests, a field, rivers and attractions, like a lighthouse.</description></item><item><title>Wrench</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</guid><description>Game Description Wrench is an auto mechanic simulator with an emphasis on realism. The task of this game is to clarify the breakdown of the car and the subsequent elimination of problems. Most cars will arrive from racing tracks, so some problems will make your head break.
Your career growth begins with the position of a younger assistant who is engaged in the replacement of car liquids and tires. As you pass, the game will teach you professional skills, allowing you to move along the career ladder and move to your goal.</description></item><item><title>Drive Beyond Horizons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Beond Horizons Refuses the line path and throws gamers into a huge, constantly changing world. Fasten the belts and get ready for the study - the procedurally generated landscapes make each game unique. Leave the comfort zone and choose your own route. Travel through spacious deserts, lush forests, on any roads (or their absence). But this is not just an excursion trip. Drive Beond Horizons is fraught with many secrets and difficulties that have to be solved.</description></item><item><title>Redline Crooks</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/redline-crooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/redline-crooks/</guid><description>Game Description In Redline Crooks, the player drives the vehicles of prisoners, from sportsmen to loaders, making a fierce attempt to break free and enrich himself. The main task is to avoid prison, destroying the pursuing police officers and the destroyed environment. A key ability to accelerate makes it possible to develop extreme speed for breaking through obstacles at the cost of the strength of the machine.
Recipe for a successful escape from justice in Redline Crooks:</description></item><item><title>Underground Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</guid><description>Game Description Underground Garage is a car symbulator with elements of a mechanic that allows not only to take part in the races, but also to completely create his own car from scratch. It is allowed to both buy ready -made models, exploring the secondary market, and create cars from scratch. Restoring transport or pumping cars, it is necessary to take part in illegal races, showing your superiority as a mechanic and demonstrating the skills of a first -class driver.</description></item></channel></rss>