<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Races on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/</link><description>Recent content in Races on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Le Mans Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description **Le Mans Ultimate ** - The official game FIA ​​World Enduraance Championship and &amp;ldquo;24 hours of Le Man&amp;rdquo;, promises exciting experience to both experienced riders and beginners. Runned in early access, the game offers to try the exciting season of 2023 with official cars, legendary tracks and online media. Sit behind the wheel of ultramodern hypercars from manufacturers such as Toyota, Ferrari and Porsche, and recreate the battles on prestigious tracks.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description **ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS ** - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>Drive Beyond Horizons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</guid><description>Game Description **Drive Beond Horizons ** Refuses the line path and throws gamers into a huge, constantly changing world. Fasten the belts and get ready for the study - the procedurally generated landscapes make each game unique. Leave the comfort zone and choose your own route. Travel through spacious deserts, lush forests, on any roads (or their absence). But this is not just an excursion trip. Drive Beond Horizons is fraught with many secrets and difficulties that have to be solved.</description></item></channel></rss>