<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>races on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/</link><description>Recent content in races on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/races/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy Delivery Co.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-delivery-co/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-delivery-co/</guid><description>Game Description In Easy Delivery Co. The player takes on the role of the driver-who travels along the picturesque mountain town with severe weather conditions. The main task is to deliver parcels to local residents on a compact kei-kare. Remuneration of labor is significantly lower than the minimum, forming the economic background of the situation in which the hero found himself. The open world allows you to explore the surroundings outside the main routes, and the physics of transport affects the controllability of the machine on a different relief.</description></item><item><title>Jetrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</guid><description>Game Description Jetrunner combines first -person parkour with dynamic shooting in the framework of futuristic sports. Opponents move along the arenas created by hand, using a combination of running, jumping, sliding and firing for promotion. The fully voiced story campaign is dedicated to the history of the newcomer-sensation of Nina White, rising along the competitive ladder. Her path describes battles and challenges in an attempt to achieve legendary status in this discipline.</description></item><item><title>Flow</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flow/</guid><description>Game Description The player in Flow initiates drifts in picturesque locations where the style exceeds clean speed. Each level is divided into two special phases that challenge control and stability. The initial stage, Lead the Way, allows the driver to lay his own path in turns, while the car with AI repeats his movement. Then the roles change in the Chase The Flow segment, which requires a gamer to pursue AI, which paves the perfect trajectory and correspond to its rhythm to complete the race.</description></item><item><title>Liftoff: Micro Drones</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff: Micro Drones is a drone simulator. The game is dedicated to FPV thrones and FPV quadrocopters. This is the name of the model equipped with a camera, allowing their owners to observe the flight with first -person view. For those who prefer to watch actions from the outside, there is an opportunity to change the camera angle. This video game contains 6 really existing UAVs from well -known manufacturers, some of which are allowed to modify.</description></item><item><title>RECHARGE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</guid><description>Game Description RECHARGE is a simulation-arcade racing experience in which the player controls radio-controlled machines. The gameplay was built on a physical model of behavior and allows the customization of vehicles. Gamers compete on tracks created based on professional RC tracks and other locations, including beaches and entertainment parks. The project is intended for use with several input devices, supporting both standard gamepads and specialized controllers.
These features create the basis for individual and competitive races.</description></item><item><title>Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions - this is a racing game with the participation of Muscles from the European Park. There are 8 characters to choose from, including the main characters of Ed and Eddo from the Grand Prix of Europe. Railways take place on the tracks laid around the attractions of the continent. You can withstand computer counterparts or challenge three friends in local mode with the separation of the screen by arranging a direct competition in driver’s skills.</description></item><item><title>Wheel World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wheel-world/</guid><description>Game Description Wheel World represents the story of Kat, a cyclist chosen by ancient spirits for a key task. The setting is on the verge of collapse, and only Glavheroin can prevent it, having made a great shift ceremony. Her journey runs through the world, saturated with a bicycle culture, where she has to resist the elite teams in competitions.
The central mission is to return the abducted legendary details, which are the main components to complete the ritual and save its world from oblivion.</description></item><item><title>Descenders Next</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/descenders-next/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/descenders-next/</guid><description>Game Description Descenders Next is a sports action combining Roguelike mechanics with third -person views. Ryders use snowboards and mauntinboards to move along spacious, procedurally created locations. The project offers an open world study in several biomes: from snowy peaks to winding ground routes and specially equipped parks. Each race offers a new path, since internal mechanics create unique routes for every attempt.
This approach also includes the elements of Tower Defense and the first -person type for certain classes, providing a diverse game process.</description></item><item><title>Frog Jump</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</guid><description>Game Description Frog Jump puts players under the control of amphibians with the aim of vertical climbing through the three -dimensional world. They have to move according to a complex design, using jumps and climbing to go from one site to another. The entire level is designed around this movement up, representing a continuous navigation task. The first princess’s kiss receives a victory that reached the top.
This platformer can be held alone or in a multi -user competition for 8 competitors over the network.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>Motogp25</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motogp25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motogp25/</guid><description>Game Description MotogP25 immerses players in the atmosphere of the 2025 motorcycle season. Gamers choose pilots and compete on the routes of the official calendar using motorcycles modeled for the current championship. The project has a system of judges MotoGP Stewards to control the tracking on the track during the races, and the sound support is recorded from the real bikes participating in the championship.
Gamers interact with MotogP25, building a racing career.</description></item><item><title>Tower Unite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-unite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-unite/</guid><description>Game Description Tower Unite is a very unusual MMO. Here, users walk and get acquainted on a large central hub called Plaza and Island. In fact, this is such a large amusement park. At the same time, one can play here alone.
The project was first made on the basis of Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod. Over time, it turned into a full -fledged separate product. The game allows gamers to create their own creativity inside it and share with others.</description></item><item><title>Drive Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Rally is an arcade game about rally races that transfers gamers during the glory of the 1990s. Having focused on speeds, skill and exciting sensations of an open road, Advencura offers nostalgic experience for fans of classic rally races. Users take on the role of a rally racer, competing in various iconic places around the world. From the dusty deserts of Africa to the snowy peaks of Scandinavia - each area offers unique trials and opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Energy Supercross 25 - The Official Video Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-energy-supercross-25-the-official-video-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-energy-supercross-25-the-official-video-game/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Energy Supercross 25 - The Official Video Game represents the official 2025 supercross season for players. Gamers gain access to the current list of professional racers and compete on the tracks that recreated real places of the championships. The project uses Unreal Engine 5 for its work. This technological basis allows you to implement updated mechanics associated with simulating a motorcycle control.
The gameplay in the Monster Energy Supercross 25 - The Official Video Game offers physics and dynamic surfaces of tracks that change with each circle.</description></item><item><title>Get to work</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/get-to-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/get-to-work/</guid><description>Game Description Get To Work is a rapid satirical game in which players take on the role of a young man who decided to achieve success in the corporate world, overcoming obstacles on roller skates. The main character is not just an ordinary character, he is equipped with roller skates on his arms and legs, which makes him rush through the streets at great speed. This is a chaotic journey when you are trying to jump over the abysses, evade ramps and avoid other dangers.</description></item><item><title>Le Mans Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Le Mans Ultimate - The official game FIA ​​World Enduraance Championship and &amp;ldquo;24 hours of Le Man&amp;rdquo;, promises exciting experience to both experienced riders and beginners. Runned in early access, the game offers to try the exciting season of 2023 with official cars, legendary tracks and online media. Sit behind the wheel of ultramodern hypercars from manufacturers such as Toyota, Ferrari and Porsche, and recreate the battles on prestigious tracks.</description></item><item><title>Visco Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Visco Collection presents 7 arcade titles from the 1980s and 1990s. This collection contains projects of several genres, including Shoot ‘Em Up, fighting, sports and racing. The presented software supports single and local multiplayer modes for competitive or joint passage. Each Title demonstrates the special style of the arcade gameplay of that time with unique goals and mechanics that players have to study.
The Visco Collection contains Andro Dunos-Side-Squash Shoot ‘Em Up, which encounters you with elaboration ships and large-scale bosses.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>Driftwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</guid><description>Game Description Driftwood is a fascinating journey into the world of high -speed descent on Longboard. The main character is Eddie, a cool sliven who loves to ride in beautiful landscapes. This game provides an ideal balance of speed and control, bringing a feeling of relaxation and calm, despite a high -speed action.
The project offers minimalistic experience, focusing on skating on magnificent landscapes, and not on building a story campaign.</description></item><item><title>MX VS ATV Legends</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</guid><description>Game Description MX VS ATV Legends shows what intensive and at the same time dangerous racing competitions can be. Here, users are invited to participate in mass races on the proposed routes. Each location is full of surprises, so you need to carefully monitor the behavior of the vehicle so as not to fly from the distance at the most inopportune moment. Moreover, each type of transport has its own unique characteristics, and even the most experienced riders will need time to adapt and get used to the manner of behavior.</description></item><item><title>Motor Town: Behind the Wheel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motor-town-behind-the-wheel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motor-town-behind-the-wheel/</guid><description>Game Description Motor Town: Behind the Wheel is a car simulator that focuses on realistic physics and individual behavior of machines. A large open world presented in low polygonal style is available for research. Explore the streets of the city both by car and on foot, take part in racing races, tunen transport and much more.
At your disposal of Maslkar. Just roll around the world, take with you on the trip of fellow travelers, go to the warehouse where you can do the sorting or delivery of goods to earn money.</description></item><item><title>My Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</guid><description>Game Description My Garage is a simulator simulator with a first -person view. In it you can not only repair cars, but also ride them. During travel by transport, you can switch the camera angle. In Indo Tailet, weather conditions are changing. The change of day and night is also available. When driving in the dark, you can turn on the headlights.
My Garage has an open world. It consists of mountains, forests, a field, rivers and attractions, like a lighthouse.</description></item><item><title>Snowrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</guid><description>Game Description The main difference between Snowrunner and many other cargo simulators is that there are no even roads, highways and autobahns. Only snow, dirt and insurmountable obstacles. The game meets with interesting and diverse tasks, vast cards and, most importantly, a wide choice of transport: SUVs, tractors, all -terrain vehicles and trucks. After choosing a cargo and a car, you should go on a road that is not going to be easy.</description></item><item><title>Automobilista 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automobilista-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automobilista-2/</guid><description>Game Description Automobilista 2 is a continuation of the video game of the same name, which displays a series of car races to a new level. An important innovation compared to the first part is the transition to the eminent Project Cars engine called Madness. This contributed to the addition of advanced graphic technologies, including a realistic weather change, precisely recreated carriers and tracks, and many other functions.
In the project, you will face a variety of single modes - Custom Race and Test Day.</description></item><item><title>Wrench</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</guid><description>Game Description Wrench is an auto mechanic simulator with an emphasis on realism. The task of this game is to clarify the breakdown of the car and the subsequent elimination of problems. Most cars will arrive from racing tracks, so some problems will make your head break.
Your career growth begins with the position of a younger assistant who is engaged in the replacement of car liquids and tires. As you pass, the game will teach you professional skills, allowing you to move along the career ladder and move to your goal.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Day Racer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rainy-day-racer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rainy-day-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Rainy Day Racer sends drivers to the wet streets of the Scottish city, where strong rains are constantly pouring. The main occupation is the races for a while, with the main goal - to overcome the ring routes for the shortest period. Movement in urban conditions requires control over the machine with an ongoing bad weather. Each attempt is a single competition with a stopwatch, aimed exclusively to establish a personal record or ahead of other riders in the leaders table.</description></item><item><title>Revhead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revhead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revhead/</guid><description>Game Description In the REVHEAD car racing simulator, the user will have to design his own car. The protagonist has a friend named Charlie who is well versed in creating cars. He invites the central character to Australia to help him with something. It will be necessary to win the competition and get recognition from Charlie, then it will create improved transport.
There is an opportunity to sell and buy cars, as well as trade in various details and customization items.</description></item><item><title>Automation - The Car Company Tycoon Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automation-the-car-company-tycoon-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automation-the-car-company-tycoon-game/</guid><description>Game Description Automation - The Car Company Tycoon Game is the simulator of the owner of the car concerns. A good product if you like to disassemble and redo cars in your own way. To design a car starting from the engine and ending with the suspension, body, as well as other parts. In this game there is a company where we will be the head of the campaign for the production of machines and will be part of the market from the end of World War II and now on our days.</description></item><item><title>The Crew</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew/</guid><description>Game Description The Crew is a racing match simulator that makes it possible to create its own unique sports car. The plot tells you about the professional racer Alex Taylore. He and his older brother were organizing illegal races. Some time later, the FBI staff found them. Police kill the founder of this event, and the brothers are imprisoned. The heroes are offered to reduce the term, but in return they will have to work in law enforcement agencies.</description></item><item><title>Haste: Broken Worlds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/haste-broken-worlds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/haste-broken-worlds/</guid><description>Game Description Haste: Broken Worlds presents the world with a rapid action from a third person, the action of which unfolds in a setting, which is on the verge of collapse. The user will have to take on the role of Zoe, which rushes along the procedurally generated levels, trying to escape from the decay of the world surrounding it. Each of the ten fragments is a series of levels that need to be passed in a certain order, and each time the journey unfolds differently, due to the accident of procedural generation.</description></item><item><title>Underground Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</guid><description>Game Description Underground Garage is a car symbulator with elements of a mechanic that allows not only to take part in the races, but also to completely create his own car from scratch. It is allowed to both buy ready -made models, exploring the secondary market, and create cars from scratch. Restoring transport or pumping cars, it is necessary to take part in illegal races, showing your superiority as a mechanic and demonstrating the skills of a first -class driver.</description></item></channel></rss>