<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>shooters on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooters/</link><description>Recent content in shooters on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bazar Simulator: The Wan Story</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bazar-simulator-the-wan-story/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bazar-simulator-the-wan-story/</guid><description>Game Description Bazar Simulator: The Wan Story will throw players in the role of Wang, who arrived in Bokeron City to control the bazaar of his uncle. While his uncle, Van Lun, is passionate about slot machines, Van’s father, Yussef, acts as a mentor in business. However, the outlet itself stores secrets leading to cooperation with the local mafia and a hidden conspiracy. This situation forces the protagonist to combine daily commerce with investigations regarding his own family, combining the management of the shop full of intrigues.</description></item><item><title>Jetrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</guid><description>Game Description Jetrunner combines first -person parkour with dynamic shooting in the framework of futuristic sports. Opponents move along the arenas created by hand, using a combination of running, jumping, sliding and firing for promotion. The fully voiced story campaign is dedicated to the history of the newcomer-sensation of Nina White, rising along the competitive ladder. Her path describes battles and challenges in an attempt to achieve legendary status in this discipline.</description></item><item><title>GEARS of WAR: Reloaded</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gears-of-war-reloaded/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gears-of-war-reloaded/</guid><description>Game Description GEARS of WAR: Reloaded provides access to the original Title, which passed the procedure for a comprehensive reprint, preserving the essence of the original. This version is distinguished by the introduction of technical improvements, among which it appears to support the image output in resolution 4K and the possibility of reaching the screen update up to 120 frames per second, which ensures the smoothness of the visual series.</description></item><item><title>Turretgirls</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turretgirls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turretgirls/</guid><description>Game Description Turretgirls offers to manage an operative with a turret reflecting the attacks of extraterrestrial forces from unstable wormholes. The main mission is to protect the generator, the only source of energy for planetary superweapies. Acting with a fixed rail platform, the heroine is opposed to the swarm of alien invaders that threaten the entire installation. The survival of the planet depends on this single defense against the invasion horde, since the retreat is impossible.</description></item><item><title>Hordelord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hordelord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hordelord/</guid><description>Game Description Hordelord throws a player on the closed arenas against the consistent waves of hostile creatures. Gamers use destructive weapons and high mobility to move the location and reprisals against opponents. The task is to score the maximum number of points for getting into the world tables of leaders, relying on accurate shooting and a system for fixing murders. The gameplay is distinguished by constant violence, concentrating on the suppression of opponents with speed and fire power.</description></item><item><title>World War Z vr</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-war-z-vr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-war-z-vr/</guid><description>Game Description World War Z VR is a single -user first -person shooter that places people in the world captured by the undead. It has to withstand the enormous clusters of zombies in cruel combat clashes. This action adapts the basis of its predecessor, a title with a base of players exceeding 25 million people. Survival depends on the movement along the territories infected by the dead and the use of firearms to eliminate the hordes of advancing opponents.</description></item><item><title>The House of the Dead 2: Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-the-dead-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-the-dead-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description The House of the Dead 2: Remake is a rail shooter where gamers in the role of secret agents of James or Gary cleans the city. This game offers a single passage or local cooperative regime for the destruction of hordes of hostile creatures that block the path. The first -person gameplay immerses the operatives in cruel clashes with the hostile inhabitants of the metropolis. The main goal is to survive and find out the source of the flash, moving through the captured streets and buildings.</description></item><item><title>Earth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</guid><description>Game Description Earth is a site-scrolling space shooter created for 16-bit equipment. The project transfers the player the pilot of the warship Azuso Takanashi in her campaign against alien invaders. Its central goal is to protect the Earth in a series of combat scripts. This title is a 2D-player with the main character, whose events unfold in the futuristic science fiction universe. The gameplay is presented from the arcade perspective.</description></item><item><title>Reflex Unit: Strike Ops</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</guid><description>Game Description Reflex Unit: Strike Ops immerses in the future, destroyed by cataclysm and captured by powerful corporations. The player is headed by an elite detachment opposing the despotistical corporation Neotech, operating the remnants of civilization. The key gameplay consists in managing specialized equipment during various tactical operations. The tasks include daring rescue sorties, collecting key resources and direct attacks on enemy bases to undermine the power of the regime and struggle for freedom of the population.</description></item><item><title>CONTRACT Rush DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contract-rush-dx/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contract-rush-dx/</guid><description>Game Description Contract Rush DX represents a 2D-world, built on the battles in the style of run and shoot and platform navigation. The player will have to choose from the list of characters to perform missions in manually drawn environment. The action mixes the shooting with the study, and cartoon aesthetics are combined with frank blood images during battles. The central gaming cycle requires to accept and execute contracts, which promotes deep into the numerous conflicts of the world.</description></item><item><title>Demon Hunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demon-hunt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demon-hunt/</guid><description>Game Description Demon Hunt is an action in which players pilot furs through landscapes flooded demons. The process is built on a combination of firing with the view of the Bullet Hell under the Rogue-Lite. Gamers go hunting, faced with numerous opponents and strong bosses in every sortie. During the battles, it is necessary to survive, collect resources and defeat the main enemy. This structure guarantees that each race in the game offers different trials and opportunities for development.</description></item><item><title>Killing Floor 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-3/</guid><description>Game Description Killing Floor 3 throws you headlong into the gloomy 2091. The shadow megacorporation created a monstrous army of bioenginery creatures entitled &amp;ldquo;Zeda&amp;rdquo;. You join NightFall, a rebel group with a serious mentality to &amp;ldquo;kill with fire&amp;rdquo;. As a specialist NightFall, you will unite with four other gamers to destroy these Zedov in a tireless struggle for survival. This is not a single riot. In Killing Floor 3, the main thing is to work in a team and achieve success.</description></item><item><title>Look mum no computer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/look-mum-no-computer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/look-mum-no-computer/</guid><description>Game Description Look Mum No Computer is a twin-style shooter, the action of which takes place in the Saldersworth universe. Players take on the role of Sam, working together with the cosmo-cosmo companion to combat mechanisms that have gone under control. The mission requires penetrating these devices to repair them and direct confrontation of chaos. The journey includes the execution of quests from the inhabitants of the machine worlds and a fight with large -scale bosses.</description></item><item><title>Neon Abyss 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-abyss-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-abyss-2/</guid><description>Game Description Neon Abyss 2 makes gamers pass procedurally generated levels. The game takes place in a futuristic cyberpunk setting, the title offers a unique mixture of Roguelike mechanics and a stressed platformer action. Users examine the depths of the abyss - a chaotic environment filled with enemies, traps and secrets that are waiting in the wings.
Each passage is a new challenge, since the levels in the Title are generated randomly, which prevents two identical ones.</description></item><item><title>Robocop: Rogue City - Unfinished Business</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/robocop-rogue-city-unfinished-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/robocop-rogue-city-unfinished-business/</guid><description>Game Description Robocop: Rogue City - Unfinished Business - this is a separate addition, the action of which takes place after stripping Detroit from criminal groups. Hope for a calm life appears with the construction of Omnitower, a new residential complex from OCP. However, this peaceful undertaking interrupts the capture of the building with a detachment of elite mercenaries, who turned it into an impregnable fortress.
Robokop has to storm the tower in order to neutralize the threat and restore the legality, using all his arsenal for this.</description></item><item><title>Mycopunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mycopunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mycopunk/</guid><description>Game Description Mycopunk puts players in the New Atlas Hazard Crew, a detachment of robots hired by Saxon Corporation. This group of exterinators is directed to fight a fungal threat that is spreading through the planet. The crew performs these tasks to ensure its existence and avoid disposal. These instructions also help to find out the details of the planetary biological disaster and the role of Saxon in it.
The gameplay in Mycopunk is built on the implementation of missions and deep customization of equipment.</description></item><item><title>OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</guid><description>Game Description OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression is a flight shooter in which players use continuous fire to neutralize enemy forces. The story of the Title is submitted after 30 plot chapters, describing the war between the human faction and the essence of the fat bird from the parallel world. Combat operations take place on various three -dimensional locations, each with a unique relief that affects the tactical approach to clashes.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Gloom's Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dr-glooms-lab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dr-glooms-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Dr. Gloom’s Lab puts a player in the future of Jackson Blair, a character who goes to a secluded research center. The plot originates at the entrance, offering a first -person gameplay in which the study becomes a key element of promotion. Gamers have to find and distribute limited reserves for survival, moving through the internal spaces of the structure. The central goal is the consistent clarification of events inside the complex and a collision with the direct consequences of its previous operations.</description></item><item><title>Shooty Shooty Robot Invasion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shooty-shooty-robot-invasion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shooty-shooty-robot-invasion/</guid><description>Game Description Shooty Shooty Robot Invasion puts the player under the control of the female protagonist with the task of eliminating mechanical forces and communicating with the population. Pravdous goals include the extermination of many robots and conducting conversations with the inhabitants of the world. These dialogs, along with animated screensavers, serve to develop the plot and emphasize the absurdity of what is happening. The environment was created with the help of thousands of hand -drawn spells.</description></item><item><title>Project Silverfish</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-silverfish/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-silverfish/</guid><description>Game Description Project Silverfish places the hero inside the hostile alienation zone in search of powerful artifacts and exotic weapons. This universe is fraught with forgotten nightmares, both man -made and supernatural. The character will go down to the lost dungeons of the Cold War in search of resources and the new arsenal. The gameplay is based on first -person mechanics and requires ingenuity, as well as the use of various survival tools.</description></item><item><title>Suit for Hire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suit-for-hire/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suit-for-hire/</guid><description>Game Description Suit for Hire as if throwing users into a first -class action movie, where they have to go through a series of locations in the role of a killer, leaving a mountain of corpses. There is no deeply prescribed plot, serious development of characters or complex mechanics. There are only pure action and arsenal of techniques with which you can eliminate the next portion of goals. In addition, the scene is constantly changing, due to which you will have to get used to the new environment again.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fairy Tale: Dreamland Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-fairy-tale-dreamland-survivors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-fairy-tale-dreamland-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Dark Fairy Tale: Dreamland Survivors puts a player under the control of Pinocchio, a puppet who has trapped in a hostile and distorted space of nightmares. The character moves around this world by controlling one hand, while the system is automatically introduced to creatures from rethought fairy tales. The promotion depends on the collection and absorption of more than 100 different forbidden dreams of dreams, each of which modifies offensive and defensive capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine - Master Crafted Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-master-crafted-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-master-crafted-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine - Master Crafted Edition puts the player in the center of large -scale conflict, where battles and constant pressure do not leave time for respite. Captain Titus from the Order of Ultramarinov heads a detachment of hardened fighters sent to restrain the invasion of the orcs on an industrial planet. These worlds produce equipment and weapons for the endless war of mankind, and the loss of one of them can lead to catastrophic consequences.</description></item><item><title>Popucom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/popucom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/popucom/</guid><description>Game Description Popucom opens a joint journey for researchers on an unknown planet. Adventurers reach this celestial body to study its territory with his comrades. The process of passage is built on a change of flowers, the use of shells in the type of three in a row and relics of artifacts for overcoming difficulties, maintaining the movement forward and assistance in the revival of the world. This sortie contains various circumstances and a lot of aspects for detecting involved players.</description></item><item><title>Mindkatt: first stud</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mindkattfirst-strike/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mindkattfirst-strike/</guid><description>Game Description mindkatt: first strike represents a setting in which cats with developed intelligence use mechanical structures to interact in human society. This project puts players in a futuristic environment, where despotistical orders reign. These cats, having passed serious mental evolution, are in contact with the world through robotic devices. Their life in this difficult era, subject to people, forms the core of history.
In the general world, Mindkatt: First Strike, human groups are kept under the control of Mindkatt - a developed type of cats facing slavery.</description></item><item><title>Regulators</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/regulators/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/regulators/</guid><description>Game Description Regulators sets before a detachment of mercenaries the task of stripping the city from mutating villains with weapons, gadgets and special abilities. The team penetrates into buildings from streets, roofs or sewers to fulfill the goals leading to the scientist, commander of the antagonists. The situation began after the fall of an asteroid that released the alien substance of the UZ. It was soon found that this material has narcotic potential and causes mutations in all its exposure, including the detachment fighters themselves.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-call-of-prypiat-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-call-of-prypiat-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition puts the player in the role of Major Degtyarev, an intelligence officer sent to the cover under the cover. Its task is to find out the causes of the failure of the military operation and the disappearance of the detachment. Events unfold in the Pripyat region, where everything is permeated with dangers: anomalies, radiation, hostile groups and an unstable situation.
In Stalker: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition, each action has consequences.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-clear-sky-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-clear-sky-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky - Enhanced Edition transfers a gamer to the role of a mercenary named Scar, forced to survive among warring groups, unstable abnormalities and deadly emissions. The action takes place to the events of the previous title of the series, demonstrating the origins of the territorial split in the zone. The basis of the mechanics is the system of wars of fractions - with its help, the user is able to change the alignment of forces between armed formations.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chornobyl - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-shadow-of-chornobyl-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-shadow-of-chornobyl-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chornobyl - Enhanced Edition transferred gamers to the alienation zone around the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, where anomalies, armed groups and mutants act outside the law framework. Movement in this territory depends on food supplies, the level of radiation, the number of cartridges and relations with other characters. Plot tasks can be performed in different ways using research, shootings and dialogs. The environment is a constant danger, which requires attention to details, and not following the finished routes.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy HighWays</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-highways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-highways/</guid><description>Game Description Galaxy Highways puts a player at the head of a star pilot after the discovery of alien gate to mankind led to the destruction of the Earth. The surviving representatives of civilization founded the colony of the last hope - a settlement, which is constantly threatened by the same alien force, striving to detect it. As a pilot of the special forces, the main function is to protect the colony by completing tasks, including attacks on enemy attitudes, the defense of friendly caravans and the seizure of aliens for research.</description></item><item><title>Chambers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chambers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chambers/</guid><description>Game Description Chambers Simits a gamer in a role -playing shooter with a wild West setting with its own features. The plot puts the protagonist in the world, split by the war for a drink, where the antagonists, known as the Reds, seized power. These enemies divided the territory into separate zones - cameras. The main character moves around this world in search of a specific coffin. An unusual environment combines the elements of the western with gloomy humor and horror.</description></item><item><title>Tank Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Tank Squad transfers players during the Second World War, to the most intense territories, whose fate will affect the outcome of the clash. The user will visit the role of captain of the tank detachment, taking part in the iconic battles of that time. Scenarios will include historical battles for a single -user or cooperative passage of three participants at the same time.
In the multiplayer, each gamer is able to control their own team, or unite among themselves and become a separate crew member.</description></item><item><title>Deadzone: Rogue</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deadzone-rogue/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deadzone-rogue/</guid><description>Game Description Deadzone: rogue immerses the gamer into events on board the ISS-X vessel, located in deep space, where the protagonist recovers without memories. Faced with the upcoming legions of hostile vehicles, the character is forced to enter into battles from the first person in the compartments of the ship, from machine departments to the Kardzer. Survival depends on the movement of these locations and collisions with numerous mechanical opponents.</description></item><item><title>Within the Cosmos</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/within-the-cosmos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/within-the-cosmos/</guid><description>Game Description Within the Cosmos is a first -person science fiction role -playing advent of which takes place in 2278. Gamers wake up in a secluded star system, where they face a split human society. This society fights with a growing threat from androids, which leads to serious stress. The background is the star system of Adallio, where users were once part of a mission launched by the united space agency of the Earth.</description></item><item><title>Gruel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</guid><description>Game Description Gruel - this is an exciting first -person shooter in which chaos reigns in the endless arena. Users move around the unpredictable temple, faced with a series of constantly changing rooms filled with bizarre enemies. Each step forward is a new challenge that makes reflexes and adapt to the limit. Traditional shooting mechanics fades into the background, and improvisation becomes a key point.
Movement is constantly, fluctuations lead to disaster, and the only way out is a passage.</description></item><item><title>Democrators</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desecrators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desecrators/</guid><description>Game Description Desecrators offers Gamer the role of the cosmic marauder, operating in the Galaxy Milky Way in 4096. Humanity has erected numerous large structures in mastered star systems, from deep processing stations to orbital complexes, often containing valuable technologies, weapons and resources. On board the Nightingale FTL Cracer, the character acts as a well-known defiler, making raids on the selected objects.
The task is to accumulate a destructive arsenal and sufficient technologies to try to storm the legendary storage facilities of the Galactic Treasury, but this path runs through the galaxy full of dangers for all prey hunters.</description></item><item><title>Diddy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</guid><description>Game Description Diddy begins with a mission to destroy a dark party held in a private estate. Players in the Company of Eminam and 51 Centers must stop the owner’s atrocities and stop the meeting. The main task is the salvation of Justin B, who is in the territory after the accumulation of a state fraud. The detachment confronts the army of Selebri, acting as a guards, ready to defend the estate and its owner.</description></item><item><title>Endless Alice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-alice/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-alice/</guid><description>Game Description endless alice - this is an adventure from a third person with an intriguing combination of elements of the Rowlaik and visual design, inspired by anime. Title invites gamers to explore a huge, constantly changing world, where each solution can determine their path. Six characters to choose from, each of which offers its own set of abilities and styles of battle, allow users to combine them in accordance with their style.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl is a first-person shooter in a post-apocalyptic world. The events of the game will develop in the exclusion zone formed as a result of the disaster at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. In 2006, a new catastrophe occurred, which led to various physical, chemical and biological processes, creating many anomalies, artifacts and generating a large number of mutants.
The gameplay is a classic FPS with elements of a role-playing game, immersive sim and horror.</description></item><item><title>Bullet Runner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</guid><description>Game Description The dynamic shootouts inBullet Runner show the adventures of a pixelated man who is forced to resist against a crowd of evil opponents. The game is a top-down action shooter where you have to fight with various opponents. The project is filled with fast and active gameplay, where users can test the speed of their reaction to current events. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to move around the map and shoot enemies using a wide arsenal of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>NIMRODS: GUNCRAFT Survivor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nimrods-guncraft-survivor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nimrods-guncraft-survivor/</guid><description>Game Description In Nimrods: Guncraft Survivor, gamers have to take on the role of consumable clones, which are entrusted with testing an outlandish weapon in the galaxy, teeming with chaos. The plot creates the basis for a unique combination of action and creativity. As part of the test detachment of the manufacturer of weapons, participants are sent in search of new technologies and resources for alien landscapes. Each entry is a combination of survival tasks and craft opportunities, emphasizing the importance of experiments.</description></item><item><title>Sulfur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sulfur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sulfur/</guid><description>Game Description Sulfur is an adventure adventure, in which the elements of the first -person shooter are combined with traditional role -playing games and mob. Gamers take on the role of a character, moving around a complex world, filled with problems and capabilities. The gameplay is focused on battles and research, forcing users to think strategically, faced with various enemies. Each collision requires a different approach, which makes the adaptation key.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Kvark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kvark/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kvark/</guid><description>Game Description KVARK, the first-person shooter (FPS), immerses the players in the fascinating storyline, the action of which takes place in the alternative Czech Republic of the 1980s. The action of the game unfolds within the destructive underground object, offering an exciting journey through the dimly lit tunnels, replete obstacles and formidable opponents, which makes the players experience their skills for strength.
For the company &amp;ldquo;Quark&amp;rdquo;, security is of paramount importance, and our commitment is unshakable to it.</description></item><item><title>Kill Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Kill Knight paves his way to the arena of action-players, promising a cruel ballet from trials and strategy. Fasten the belts because this adventure throws you into a deep abyss - quick reflexes and acute thinking - your only life circles. Forget about sitting aside and interrupting enemies one by one. Here the aggressive style of the game is encouraged, but do not shoot with a fright. Resource management is a key point.</description></item><item><title>Witchfire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</guid><description>Game Description Witchfire suggests using not only weapons in the process, but also various devices in order to survive after an encounter with monsters. An arsenal consisting of dozens of different items and a variety of enemies will help gamers realize their own shooting skills. Challenge the most dangerous monsters that live in this world.
Here it is important to select the right type of weapon in accordance with the situation and type of enemy.</description></item><item><title>Hive Jump 2: Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hive Jump 2: Survivors is a sci-fi role-playing adventure game with action elements. In this adrenaline-pumping sequel to the acclaimed action-platformer, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself the only survivor of your squad, stranded on an alien planet. Armed with only your guns and your trusty jetpack, you set out on a mission of revenge. Here you have to fight relentless waves of killer insects. What is your goal? Destroy these swarms of aliens and collect their valuable entrails.</description></item><item><title>Rum and Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Rum and Gun uses a pirate theme as its setting. The hero travels through the lands located in the Indian Ocean, fighting on land with people and monsters. He is trying to stop the captain, who has enlisted the help of evil forces. He also has to learn the secrets of the Drunken God. The plot is presented with jokes and self-irony. History is divided into acts.
This is an isometric shooter and action game with role-playing elements.</description></item><item><title>Intravenous 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</guid><description>Game Description Intravenous 2 immerses you in the world of cruel intrigues and intense action. Play for Sean, desperately trying to save his abducted father, and Steve, a grumbling former military with a dark past. Their unlikely union is based on a common goal: to pass the labyrinth of the underworld, complete secrets, lies and mortal danger.
But how you can handle this insidious Odyssey depends only on you. Will you be a ghost, fluttering in shadows and manipulating environment in your interests?</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>Exophobia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</guid><description>Game Description Exophobia is a first -person pixel shooter in which you will go to explore a spaceship. The shuttle fell to the surface of an unknown planet. Here you will encounter the hordes of alien opponents. The game is made in retro-stylistic, drawing inspiration in arcade shooters of the 80s.
Explore the station and find out the background of the inhabitants of the planet, as well as try to find out what caused the shipwreck.</description></item><item><title>Acre Crisis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/acre-crisis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/acre-crisis/</guid><description>Game Description Acre CRISIS transfers players in 1992, placing them in the AKR area in the jungle of the Amazon. The Brazilian Military Police Brigade is going to this area to investigate a series of deaths caused by wild animals, as well as reports of a meeting with cryptids. Upon arrival, the soldiers were in direct confrontation with a group of hungry dinosaurs, which was very different from their initial task.</description></item><item><title>Genome Guardian</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/genome-guardian/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/genome-guardian/</guid><description>Game Description Genome Guardian transfers gamers to the environment, where a microscopic becomes a scene for a high -octane action. This is a game where the usual meets the unusual, offering the world filled with microscopic organisms, some of which are harmless, while others are far from the case. A distinctive feature is that it is based on the mixing and selection of DNA nucleotides to create bio -weapons, which serves you the main protection from the hostile environment.</description></item><item><title>Incursion Red River</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incursion-red-river/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incursion-red-river/</guid><description>Game Description Incursion Red River immerses you in the ruthless world of modern Vietnam, devastated by civil war. In the role of a mercenary of private military corporations (PMCs), profitable on chaos, you will participate in tense tactical shootings, reveal hidden truths and fight for survival in history, which unfolds in the course of the game. Combat with two friends for a cooperative game or go alone, like a lone wolf.</description></item><item><title>Macross -shooting Insight-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/macross-shooting-insight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/macross-shooting-insight/</guid><description>Game Description Macross -shooting Insight - This is a title in which the rapid action of the sword fighting is embodied in a fascinating form. The control of the transformable Veritech fighters, immersing gamers into high -tied missions with lateral scrolling, is based. Target? To fight the formidable forces of Zentradi is a task that requires accuracy, quick reflexes and confident ownership of various mechanics that the game offers. Are you a fan of the Mecha genre or just like good Sidskrollers, this adventure will not leave a place for boredom.</description></item><item><title>Fossilfuel 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fossilfuel-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fossilfuel-2/</guid><description>Game Description Fossilfuel 2 throws players into a flooded research center in Alaska, teeming with prehistoric predators. Jack Allen, a participant in the ill -fated expedition, must pave his way through dangerous puzzles, flooded tunnels and frightening darkness. Armed with the arsenal of deadly weapons, gamers pave their way through dinosaurs in terrible details on the Unreal Engine 5 engine.
Equipment for underwater swimming becomes necessary when players plunge into underwater sections, confronts water threats along with their ground colleagues.</description></item><item><title>Empty Shell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empty-shell/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empty-shell/</guid><description>Game Description Empty Shell will send you to the very heart of a dark and dangerous industrial environment at a secret facility on the Japanese island. You have to perform a “recovery operation”, which you know a little about, but this is only the beginning. You will find yourself at an object that was abandoned for decades, but something is wrong in it. Solve dark secrets, dig in the documents and magazines of the 1950s and find out the stories of the people who worked there.</description></item><item><title>The Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</guid><description>Game Description In The Front, your task, as a resistance fighter, boils down to go into the past in order to prevent the formation of a tyrannical empire that threatens the very existence of mankind. The game is a craft shooter with an open world, immersing a player in a post -apocalyptic sandbox, teeming with mutants and hostile groups.
In this terrain destroyed by the war, you have to fight with tyrannical imperial forces, exiles, bandits and rebels in an epic battle, which will determine the future of mankind.</description></item><item><title>El Paso, Elsewhere</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/el-paso-elsewhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/el-paso-elsewhere/</guid><description>Game Description El Paso, Elsewhere immerses players in dynamic shootings with werewolves, vampires and other evil spirits that make his way to the surface of the planet. Events transfer to the territory of a small Texas settlement under the name El Passes, where he will have to fight terrible opponents. The main character finds himself in a small three -story hotel hiding the secret deep underground. Players will have to go down to dark basements to go through 46 combat missions and destroy hellish creatures.</description></item><item><title>Railgunners</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</guid><description>Game Description Railgunners puts players in the script of a rail shooter, where humanity is fighting an alien invasion. This title represents battles through customizable complexity parameters, allowing gamers to regulate the intensity of contractions. Gamers move in a two -dimensional perspective with lateral scrolling, faced with hundreds of enemy units in numerous conflict zones. The main task includes a breakthrough through the vast lines of the enemy in order to get to the mother vessel of the aliens and begin its destruction.</description></item><item><title>Payday 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-3/</guid><description>Game Description Payday 3 - The second continuation of the original multiplayer game dedicated to the life of robbers and their sorties to dangerous crimes for making money and respect in gang circles, an analogue of levels from other projects. By increasing authority, new types of weapons and customization items will be unlocked, allowing you to create a unique appearance of the protagonist. This part of the franchise uses the Unreal Engine 4 engine.</description></item><item><title>Eon Fighter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eon-fighter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eon-fighter/</guid><description>Game Description Eon Fighter is an action game with a top view with Roguelite systems where the player pilots the fighter through the hostile sectors of the cosmos. The gameplay is focused on a collision with continuous waves of opponents and collecting resources for promotion. In the role of the last representative of mankind, it is necessary to carry out tasks, confronts the constant enemy. The structure of the Shoot &amp;lsquo;Em Up genre requires continuous movement and tactical ingenuity to survive in the conditions of the onslaught.</description></item><item><title>Gorebox</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gorebox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gorebox/</guid><description>Game Description Gorebox is an exciting sandbox that allows you to reveal its creative potential and create a world full of tense moments on the basis of physics. Various types of weapons and explosives are offered a choice, as well as a special device called Reality Crusher, which makes it possible to interact with surrounding objects. In addition, you can configure your character using skins and accessories, as well as create or explore user cards through the built -in editor and workshop.</description></item><item><title>My Friendly Neighborhood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-friendly-neighborhood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-friendly-neighborhood/</guid><description>Game Description My Friendly Neighborhood immerses users for the role of a simple repairman Gordon, which is forced to cope with gloomy and revived puppets attacking the hero during the play &amp;ldquo;Our friendly neighborhood.&amp;rdquo; The protagonist is forced to survive and cope with various puzzles to find a way out of the trap. The MFN game is an action horror where you have to cope with dynamic levels, using a variety of weapons for self -defense.</description></item><item><title>Silica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</guid><description>Game Description Silica is a dynamic alloy of action and a science fiction strategy that revolves around a fierce struggle for power over a Baltarus, a planet who is replete with quartz crystals, desired for all fractions. Players can manage their armies as commanders from orbit or plunge into battle with their heads as an infantry, vehicles or various insect -like aliens.
Silica allows gamers to choose their game style without limiting them to specific rules.</description></item><item><title>Total Conflict: Resistance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</guid><description>Game Description Total Conflict: Resistance is an incredible mixture of global strategy, tactics and an action in the first person that provides incredible battles, many types of armored vehicles, weapons and armor, as well as unique mechanics to immerse you in exciting gameplay. You have to take part in events, manage units, create your army and produce or purchase armored vehicles and weapons. You can also build fortifications, outposts and settlements, manage military operations in the first person, as well as in tactical mode.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2019</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2019/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2019 - Restation of the first part of the Modern Warfare series released in 2007. The plot tells about the war in Syria and Iraq. The cooperative game tells about the conflict in the east of Ukraine. The gameplay includes 5 groups: SAS, al-Katala, CIA, Urzikstan militia and the RF Armed Forces.
Actions will take place in two fictional powers: Castovia and Urzyikostan. The main character is a familiar character of the original Call of Duty character - Captain John Price.</description></item><item><title>Psychosis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psychosis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psychosis/</guid><description>Game Description psychosis is a retro-game in the Survival-Horror style, in which the gamer has to fight with demons and his own reason in the endless hell. In this psychological horror, you will have to fight with a breathtaking gameplay for an hour to survive in the surrounding perverted world.
The plot begins with the fact that after midnight the protagonist arrives a mysterious phone call. The voice on the other end of the line urgently asks the hero to come as soon as possible, because they all left.</description></item><item><title>EXOME</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exome/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exome/</guid><description>Game Description EXOME may be of interest to lovers of playing games with friends. The multiplayer is designed for 2-4 users. For those who like single more, there is an opportunity to play alone. This is a cooperative shooter with a third person with elements of survival and horror. When using optical sights, the camera angle during firing for a short time changes from the eyes. The project is made on the Unreal Engine 5 engine.</description></item><item><title>171</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/171/</guid><description>Game Description The sandbox 171 stands out against the background of other GTA clones with its entourage. The action takes place in Brazil. The creators offer to ride on the suburbs of San Paulo. Poor areas with narrow streets, graffiti on the walls, dirt and garbage add a special flavor of the local atmosphere.
The player controls his character with a third -person view. During shooting on the street, the camera is transferred by the hero’s shoulder.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging intoZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>Gloomwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gloomwood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gloomwood/</guid><description>Game Description Gloomwood is not just an indie chorror in the first person. The game offers to survive in the open world. The project has stealth elements. The Title boasts the elaborate sound system, which is believably spreads the noise during the movement of the user. Gloomwood transfers gamer to the Gothic city, in which the Victorian era and steampunk were intertwined. The user explores it freely, choosing ways independently. The protagonist was stolen and transported to a gloomy metropolis, whose inhabitants mysteriously disappeared somewhere.</description></item><item><title>Way of the Hunter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</guid><description>Game Description Way of the Hunter gives an excellent opportunity to become the owner of his own hunting house in the middle of a deaf forest and periodically go hunting in search of extreme and valuable production. This simulator offers a very realistic experience, as it takes into account many factors and allows you to plunge into a huge completely open virtual world, which looks like alive. It exists regardless of the action of the user - the weather, the time of day changes dynamically, and all the animals sleep, eat, move in search of a safer place.</description></item><item><title>Like Dreamer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/like-dreamer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/like-dreamer/</guid><description>Game Description Like Dreamer acts in a virtual space that operates as a social network in the Bullethell genre-a concept called Bullet-Shell SNS. Players control the character, passing through the streams of shells launched by other users on many digital locations. The main goal is to accumulate a larger number of likes and subscribers from the intra -game audience awarded for performance during the gameplay.
This mechanics allows gamers to build a reputation and increase their recognition on the internal social platform.</description></item><item><title>Surroundead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surroundead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surroundead/</guid><description>Game Description Surroundead is a survival simulator in the open world where the apocalypse happened. In the indie project, you can switch between the view from the first and third-party. Its three -dimensional graphics are made in Low Poly style. According to the plot, a zombie virus appeared on Earth. For 5 years, people fought to him unsuccessfully. As a result, the planet has changed forever. Along the devastated streets, living dead began to roam, and civilization in its level of development rolled back to dark times.</description></item><item><title>SCP: 5k</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scp-5k/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scp-5k/</guid><description>Game Description SCP: 5k - cooperative shooter in the first person with the elements of the horror. Play both alone and unite with friends. The game is represented by hardcore complexity. Particular attention is paid to the detailed environment and plot. The team can have up to four people. Go to a complex and saturated adventure!
The story of SCP: 5k talks about how a foreign creature was discovered in the human psyche, which is responsible for all negative features: pain, cruelty, etc.</description></item><item><title>Gunfire Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description The shooterGunfire Reborn contains elements of a roguelike and role-playing game. The player can choose to control several heroes with individual abilities. The game has a huge amount of randomness, from procedurally generated locations to dropped guns and loot. Gunfire Reborn is designed for both one and a company of up to 4 people.
The game features 100 different types of items. Various mechanics will encourage you to study each fighter presented, who are more or less suitable for a specific situation and location.</description></item><item><title>Honkai Impact 3RD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/honkai-impact-3rd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/honkai-impact-3rd/</guid><description>Game Description Honkai Impact 3RD is a role-playing game with Hak-N-Slash elements, in which players manage three heroes called Valkyrie at once. The fighting is realized in real time. You can move freely across the battle of the battle, switching on the go between the characters. Each protagonist has its own unique features and skills. Combining their capabilities, it is necessary to look for effective tactics against enemies. The project is closely related to Genshin Impact.</description></item><item><title>Tunguska: The Visim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tunguska-the-visitation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tunguska-the-visitation/</guid><description>Game Description After the fall of the meteorite, in Tunguska: The Visitation begins the invasion of mutants. Having fallen to the ground in the Tunguska area, the alien body caused the transformation of all local residents. As a result, a special zone is formed here, the main goal in which is to survive and survive against enemies. The game often has to make a difficult choice, on the result of which its own existence depends.</description></item><item><title>Easy Red 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</guid><description>Game Description Easy Red 2 is a first -person shooter with elements of a strategy that immerses in an authentic atmosphere of World War II. The gameplay can plunge into tense and cruel battles, where the main thing is planning and tactics. The gameplay relies on realism. Take a break through the tanks and the enemy’s huge army. Do not fall into the explosion zone and look for ways to survive on the battlefield with your partners.</description></item><item><title>Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</guid><description>Game Description Squad is a military tactical first person shooter game. This is a multiplayer game with an emphasis on realism. An important role is assigned to team interaction between users. This project does not have a story campaign or single player modes. Instead, players in it capture points, destroy weapons depots, or hold the defense.
The title was originally called Project Reality. This was a modification for the second &amp;ldquo;Battle&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Endless Furry Killer 2020</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</guid><description>Game Description The conflict in Endless Furry Killer 2020 puts a player against the endless waves of anthropomorphic opponents. The gamer has to move through two -dimensional arenas with a view of the top intended for continuous battles. The key lesson lies in the shooting of goals in a tense struggle for life with a constant stream of enemies. Such a gameplay requires constant movement and aiming to defeat non -aloscorizing resistance.</description></item><item><title>Pyro Fighters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pyro-fighters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pyro-fighters/</guid><description>Game Description Pyro Fighters sets the fighters to recapture the attack of an alien army at long levels. Each character is armed with flamethrower - a universal tool for attack and movement. If you direct the weapon down, reactive traction is created for flight. The same stream of flame destroys enemies, which forces to constantly choose between the retention of heights and fire. Monitoring the only resource underlies each clash and requires a competent distribution of forces in stressful conditions.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 76</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</guid><description>Game Description According to the plot ofFallout 76, the first people came out of shelters after a nuclear war. They set off to explore the Wasteland, where mutants are already lying in wait. The player will be able to visit 6 regions, each of which has its own types of dangerous animals and landscape. Among the scorched desert there are also wooded areas with red trees. What is most surprising is that quite recently the desert territories were inhabited by those who were able to survive the apocalypse on the surface.</description></item><item><title>Zompiercer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zompiercer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zompiercer/</guid><description>Game Description Conceptively Zompiercer is a sandbox with an open detailed world, but the whole thing is played as a first-person shooter about survival during the zombie apocalypse. The planet is covered by a virus. People mutated in bloodthirsty walking corpses. Not many managed to survive, but you are lucky more than the rest. Or not? Survival is just beginning!
The game from an independent developer under the nickname DDDIMANN is not a comprehension not by the setting, but by the scale and the implementation of ideas.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 3 is a continuation of the acclaimed series of shooters, containing tons of loot. The player will take on the role of one of the Vault Hunters and set off to explore the expanses of Pandora. All heroes have their own tree of characteristics, unique abilities and character. The gameplay allows you to go through the adventure solo or enlist the help of friends.
The protagonist of Borderlands 3 learned to climb ledges and make tackles.</description></item><item><title>Metro Exodus: Gold Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The events ofMetro Exodus - a first-person shooter with elements of stealth and horror - take place in the same areas as the previous parts. The Russian Federation and the Republic of Kazakhstan are still waging a fierce war for life inside, in underground territories, with representatives of hostile clans, factions and monsters who devour, rather than kill, their prey. Artyom leaves the Order after the battle for D6.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 2 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description RESIDENT EVIL 2 / BIOHAZARD RE:2 - a complete rework, allowing players to enjoy modern graphics, a new engine, enemies, weapons and a much more advanced game story. Follow the story of police officer Leon S. Kennedy and student Claire Redfield.
Due to an unknown outbreak of a virus, the entire city of Raccoon City was enveloped in monsters, people began to turn into strange creatures, and then kill the survivors.</description></item><item><title>DayZ</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</guid><description>Game Description The multiplayer sandboxDayZ is a reworked version of the mod of the same name for Arma 2. The game is distinguished by its extremely realistic setting and hardcore survival in a post-apocalyptic environment. The game takes place in the fictional post-Soviet country of Chernarus. After the outbreak of an unknown virus, most of the population has turned into zombies, and the survivors are forced to fight for their lives and valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Hyperspace Dogfights</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hyperspace-dogfights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hyperspace-dogfights/</guid><description>Game Description Hyperspace Dogfights is a two -dimensional horned focused on jet battles. It is necessary to break through through the waves of opponents, using acceleration to bypass threats, as well as gravity for occupying a profitable position. A special hyperople-decline helps to fly through dense fire. Each departure becomes unique thanks to the collection and installation of more than 300 items that modify the characteristics of the fighter, which allows you to create unlike each other assemblies.</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: WW2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-ww2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-ww2/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the new part of Call of Duty: Wwii unfold during the Second World War. The developers again returned to the origins, adding to the old plot campaigns the schedule of our time, the gameplay of the last parts and the voice acting from the professional studio within the company. The basis of the plot is a landing in Normandy. The narrative of the European Theater of Acts of the Second World War begins with it.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Duty: Modern Warfare Remastered - reprinting the popular game about hostilities in the hot spots of the planet. Now the gamers have the opportunity to go through the familiar episodes “Everything in camouflage”, “Charlie is not a surf”, “Permission to eliminate the crew” only with improved textures, a more clear picture, which is extremely close to reality by physics, overwritten sound and other technologies of our time.</description></item><item><title>Brigand: Oaxaca</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</guid><description>Game Description Brigand: Oaxaca is a first -person shooter hybrid, immersive simulator and role -playing game. The project has three -dimensional low -polygonal graphics. Due to her, the title resembles computer action of the late 90s and early 2000s. The action takes place in a world where nuclear apocalypse happened. Events unfold on the territory of the Mexican state of Ohak. Indi-game combines elements of different settings. In it, the gunshot weapons are adjacent to Voodoo magic, and not only mutters, but also demons roam the wastelands.</description></item><item><title>Unturned</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unturned/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unturned/</guid><description>Game Description Unturned combines a zombie-player and a sandbox with survival elements. In the single, the user studies locations, destroys the undead, looking for a useful lutus. In the multiplayer, the user is engaged in about the same, but also fights with living opponents. There is also a separate regime of the royal battle.
Players who kill other gamers for no reason become bandits. You can become a hero, having taken up the shooting of criminals.</description></item><item><title>NEKO Navy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neko-navy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neko-navy/</guid><description>Game Description In Neko Navy, gamers are taken under the management of flying cats, opposing a whole army of various opponents. The main conflict of this scroll-player is unfolding at seven dynamic levels with horizontal scrolling, filled with continuous air battles. Six unique cat pilots are available to choose from, each of which acts as an avatar of the player and has its own characteristics.
The storyline consistently leads to a special final event designed to resolve the main intrigue and complete the main story.</description></item><item><title>Ravenfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</guid><description>Game Description The team-tactical shooterRavenfield will allow you to plunge into furious battles, where you have everything - from tanks to fleets. There is a complete lack of storyline and even multiplayer. The latter fact is extremely unusual for projects of this genre. It would seem that it is interesting to play against bots and when there are no real users on the map. This omission at first glance is more than compensated for by a fairly developed artificial intelligence - opponents and allies behave extremely intelligently and together with them you can perform a variety of tactics using numerous commands and options.</description></item><item><title>Super Destronaut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</guid><description>Game Description Super Destronaut puts a player at the head of one warship, opposing built alien invaders built. Gamers control their horizontal axis vessel in the lower part of the screen, which is a design borrowed from the Arcadian shooters of the 1980s. The main task is to methodically disassemble the waves of opponents, descending along the specified trajectories, where each eliminated enemy replenishes the general account.
During clashes, defeated aliens can leave temporary amplifiers that directly increase the rate of fire or scatter of shells, providing a tactical advantage for cleaning the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light: The Following</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-the-following/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-the-following/</guid><description>Game Description Dying Light: The Following provides the players with an extensive game world, a large arsenal of weapons, modifications, secondary and plot tasks, as well as dozens of gameplay hours. Visit in the post-apocalyptic world, teeming zombies and other bloodthirsty creatures in the action of the first person.
Pour blood in epic battles! Use dozens of ways to kill zombies, as well as interact with surrounding objects that allow the enemies to eliminate opponents.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Our task inRise of the Tomb Raider is to get ahead of your enemies, go on your first expedition and watch interactive videos, of which there are at least 1.5 hours of gameplay in the game. Lara Croft goes to the unknown world of the city of Kitezh. A secret organization called “Trinity” is also heading there. The principle of the game about Lara is an adventure game mixed with the adventure romance of the first journey, in which we kill with a bow, collect important items, and sometimes survive in the wild.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</guid><description>Game Description Fallout 4 is a sequel to the famous role-playing game series in a post-apocalyptic setting. The player wakes up from cryosleep and discovers that he is the only survivor of Vault 111. Having made it to the surface, he finds himself in the Wasteland - a world destroyed by nuclear war. The gameplay includes: a free open world with hundreds of locations to explore, a huge number of NPCs, companions and quests, as well as interaction with many factions, including the Institute, the Brotherhood of Steel, the Minutemen and agents of the Underground; S.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooterCall of Duty: Black Ops III demonstrates the blurred relationship between ordinary people and technology. In it you will forever forget that the new generation of soldiers is not a fiction, but a reality that will overtake us in the near future. Humanity has created technology to be leaders in the coming war, but will it be? The game shows this in three modes: story campaign, multiplayer shooter at scenario locations, and also in zombie mode.</description></item><item><title>Broforce</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</guid><description>Game Description Broforce is a powerful paramilitary organization that is called upon when the world is in danger due to an excessive number of evil forces. Take control of dozens of different brothers to counter terrorist attacks and save civilians. Destroy your opponents with napalm, shooting, lightning and other various character skills.
Broforce is a 2D shooter platformer with pixel graphics. You will move around locations, destroying opponents in every possible way.</description></item><item><title>Touhou kanjuden ~ legacy of lunatic kingdom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Kanjuden ~ Legacy of lunatic Kingdom opens as city legends become tangible events throughout Gansko. The rumor that the Apollo program never reached the moon is gaining strength against the backdrop of the appearance of an enemy army from the lunar capital. At the same time, metal spiders begin to cross the mountains, moving with an even, leisurely step. These machines have a functional, non -biological form, and the earth under them loses vitality: the fog is dissipated, and the vegetation fades.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Army Trilogy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-army-trilogy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-army-trilogy/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Army Trilogy - this game is a collectible gaming collection created in the style of a three -dimensional bloody shooter, which are narrated from a third -person.
The plot of the game tells us about the resurrection of Hitler, who was aroused with the help of a deal with Satan. He begins to create an entire army of a zombie-soldier, which, after his death, are full of aggression, thirst for blood and revenge.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency is a first-person shooter, in which the developers focused on playing in cooperative or multiplayer mode, about the Iraq War. The protagonist is a member of the US PMC, and he is fighting against Iraqi insurgents. The player chooses one side at the beginning of the match, and after that a brutal fight begins between the two factions. The basis of the game is a confrontation between two teams, which include 16 people.</description></item><item><title>Contagion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contagion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contagion/</guid><description>Game Description Contagion - a fascinating zombie at the first person, created in the best traditions of action with a completely open world. The plot tells us about the world into which the virus penetrates and absorbs everyone without a trace. Everyone who fell under his actions turned into half -dead carcasses that crave blood. We take the role of the character, for the large -scale cleansing of human lands from the zombie.</description></item><item><title>BioShock Infinite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</guid><description>Game Description BioShock Infinite is a first-person shooter with multiple mechanics of a role-playing adventure in the style of science fiction and steampunk. The game will take place in 1912 in an alternative universe, in the flying city of the United States of America - Columbia. You need to control the private detective Booker Devitt, who has a task to find a cute girl named Elizabeth. Immediately after it is found, the main characters find themselves in the very epicenter of the war.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 2 is a shooter with a view from the perspective of the protagonist and leveling up abilities and passive improvements, as in the role-playing adventure genre. A direct continuation of the story of the original game. The main differences from the first part are a greater emphasis on the plot component and the addition of a more advanced weapon editor with many possible modifications that open up as you progress.</description></item><item><title>Saints Row: The Third</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</guid><description>Game Description The Third Street Saints are a large and large group in the universe of the gameSaints Row: The Third. The third-person shooter with its crazy plots gave the game&amp;rsquo;s heroes their own brand of sneakers, a carbonated drink and a logo, and now they have to fight the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crime syndicate, whose people are scattered around the world and do their work in the “shadows”. Since the main characters have long captured Stillwater, the Syndicate demands offerings from them in the form of tribute for the criminal leadership.</description></item><item><title>Garry's Mod</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</guid><description>Game Description Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod is a game and physics sandbox. The main game mode is aimless and provides the player with a freely customizable world powered by the Source engine. The player creates non-player characters with various interaction objects. Special tools and tools allow you to construct new objects in reality, fix beams, iron, objects. Changing facial expressions is also available.
Thanks to the flexible engine, users create their own modifications: Spacebuild, Wiremod, Elevator: Source, DarkRP, Prop Hunt and others.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment,Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Mother Hub</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mother-hub/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mother-hub/</guid><description>Game Description Mother Hub - this is not a typical shooter. This game throws you headlong into a hopeless situation - humanity on the edge of the abyss, and only you keep the reins of government. Each of your solution, each path you have chosen can become the difference between survival and oblivion. Fasten, because here the choice has consequences. Here it is not just that you need to press the trigger.</description></item><item><title>Coven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</guid><description>Game Description Going to the gloomy world ofCoven, you have to deal with a large number of enemy creatures and deal with their elimination. The universe takes you into an atmospheric medieval fantasy world, where witches and other mythical creatures live alongside people. The first episode is available in the game, where you will take on the role of a young girl. The heroine is burned at the stake during the 1600s, mistaken for a witch and a fiend.</description></item><item><title>Clockwork Ambrosia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clockwork-ambrosia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clockwork-ambrosia/</guid><description>Game Description Clockwork Ambrosia Submits you into the world of secrets and chaos. Take control of Iris, a fearless engineer, and go to the shadow depths of the distant island. The research colony has discovered ambrosia - a substance that can rewrite the rules of invention. But something went wrong. Now silence hung in the air. Iris will have to navigate this interconnected world, fighting with monstrous creations and mechanized monsters.</description></item><item><title>Dracomaton</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dracomaton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dracomaton/</guid><description>Game Description Dracomaton begins with the awakening of a small robot named Eklips at an abandoned factory inhabited by faulty training bots and storing secrets about space dragons. The main task of the player is to climb the tower, overcoming locations with a view of the top, filled with bumpy fire of hostile mechanisms. The key aspect of survival is the ability to transform the physical shell of the robot, allowing to instantly change its entire combat arsenal.</description></item><item><title>Market Garden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/market-garden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/market-garden/</guid><description>Game Description Market Garden is a one-user first-person shooter whose action takes place during the airborne operation of the Second World War. The project offers a linear campaign conducting a gamer through historical clashes with an emphasis on infantry battles. In Title, there are intentionally absent elements as open worlds, microtransactions and cosmetic skins. Battles contain blood scenes and violence, demonstrating deaths on the battlefield.
Such a gaming design is completely concentrated on key mechanics of shooting and the development of a single narrative.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Nomad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-nomad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-nomad/</guid><description>Game Description Mr. Nomad immerses in a world, where survival depends on the only camp, serving as a mobile refuge. The main task is to build a fortified base around this van to reflect constant raids of the horde of zombies. The basis of gameplay is a two -level construction system that allows you to place ground fortifications and at the same time dig a safe bunker under them. This underground space serves as a protected area for growing a crop and storing valuable supplies far from external threats.</description></item><item><title>Operator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</guid><description>Game Description Operator is an exciting game where you become a secret operative performing dangerous tasks around the world. A realistic experience of tactical battle awaits you, where your every decision matters. The game contains a unique system of physical interaction, which allows you to manipulate objects and weapons naturally. This adds a feeling of presence and realism, without the need to use VR-Schles.
A special emphasis in the operator is placed on a multi -user cooperative regime.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item><item><title>Soul of the Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-of-the-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-of-the-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Soul of the Dungeon is an action with a view of the top, which makes the opponents resist the hordes in a hostile location. The gameplay is tied to survival in a series of attacks, collecting gold from defeated enemies and investing resources in pumping skills. Such progress is necessary, because each next wave is complicated, introducing more formidable rivals. The key task is built on constant adaptation and honing of combat techniques for the confrontation of the growing threat.</description></item></channel></rss>