<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Shooters on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooters/</link><description>Recent content in Shooters on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Witchfire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</guid><description>Game Description Witchfire suggests using not only weapons in the process, but also various devices in order to survive after an encounter with monsters. An arsenal consisting of dozens of different items and a variety of enemies will help gamers realize their own shooting skills. Challenge the most dangerous monsters that live in this world.
Here it is important to select the right type of weapon in accordance with the situation and type of enemy.</description></item><item><title>Hive Jump 2: Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hive Jump 2: Survivors is a sci-fi role-playing adventure game with action elements. In this adrenaline-pumping sequel to the acclaimed action-platformer, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself the only survivor of your squad, stranded on an alien planet. Armed with only your guns and your trusty jetpack, you set out on a mission of revenge. Here you have to fight relentless waves of killer insects. What is your goal? Destroy these swarms of aliens and collect their valuable entrails.</description></item><item><title>Rum and Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Rum and Gun uses a pirate theme as its setting. The hero travels through the lands located in the Indian Ocean, fighting on land with people and monsters. He is trying to stop the captain, who has enlisted the help of evil forces. He also has to learn the secrets of the Drunken God. The plot is presented with jokes and self-irony. History is divided into acts.
This is an isometric shooter and action game with role-playing elements.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging into ZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>Gunfire Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description The shooter Gunfire Reborn contains elements of a roguelike and role-playing game. The player can choose to control several heroes with individual abilities. The game has a huge amount of randomness, from procedurally generated locations to dropped guns and loot. Gunfire Reborn is designed for both one and a company of up to 4 people.
The game features 100 different types of items. Various mechanics will encourage you to study each fighter presented, who are more or less suitable for a specific situation and location.</description></item><item><title>Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</guid><description>Game Description Squad is a military tactical first person shooter game. This is a multiplayer game with an emphasis on realism. An important role is assigned to team interaction between users. This project does not have a story campaign or single player modes. Instead, players in it capture points, destroy weapons depots, or hold the defense.
The title was originally called Project Reality. This was a modification for the second &amp;ldquo;Battle&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 76</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</guid><description>Game Description According to the plot of Fallout 76, the first people came out of shelters after a nuclear war. They set off to explore the Wasteland, where mutants are already lying in wait. The player will be able to visit 6 regions, each of which has its own types of dangerous animals and landscape. Among the scorched desert there are also wooded areas with red trees. What is most surprising is that quite recently the desert territories were inhabited by those who were able to survive the apocalypse on the surface.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 3 is a continuation of the acclaimed series of shooters, containing tons of loot. The player will take on the role of one of the Vault Hunters and set off to explore the expanses of Pandora. All heroes have their own tree of characteristics, unique abilities and character. The gameplay allows you to go through the adventure solo or enlist the help of friends.
The protagonist of Borderlands 3 learned to climb ledges and make tackles.</description></item><item><title>Metro Exodus: Gold Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The events of Metro Exodus - a first-person shooter with elements of stealth and horror - take place in the same areas as the previous parts. The Russian Federation and the Republic of Kazakhstan are still waging a fierce war for life inside, in underground territories, with representatives of hostile clans, factions and monsters who devour, rather than kill, their prey. Artyom leaves the Order after the battle for D6.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 2 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description RESIDENT EVIL 2 / BIOHAZARD RE:2 - a complete rework, allowing players to enjoy modern graphics, a new engine, enemies, weapons and a much more advanced game story. Follow the story of police officer Leon S. Kennedy and student Claire Redfield.
Due to an unknown outbreak of a virus, the entire city of Raccoon City was enveloped in monsters, people began to turn into strange creatures, and then kill the survivors.</description></item><item><title>DayZ</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</guid><description>Game Description The multiplayer sandbox DayZ is a reworked version of the mod of the same name for Arma 2. The game is distinguished by its extremely realistic setting and hardcore survival in a post-apocalyptic environment. The game takes place in the fictional post-Soviet country of Chernarus. After the outbreak of an unknown virus, most of the population has turned into zombies, and the survivors are forced to fight for their lives and valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>Ravenfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</guid><description>Game Description The team-tactical shooter Ravenfield will allow you to plunge into furious battles, where you have everything - from tanks to fleets. There is a complete lack of storyline and even multiplayer. The latter fact is extremely unusual for projects of this genre. It would seem that it is interesting to play against bots and when there are no real users on the map. This omission at first glance is more than compensated for by a fairly developed artificial intelligence - opponents and allies behave extremely intelligently and together with them you can perform a variety of tactics using numerous commands and options.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Our task in Rise of the Tomb Raider is to get ahead of your enemies, go on your first expedition and watch interactive videos, of which there are at least 1.5 hours of gameplay in the game. Lara Croft goes to the unknown world of the city of Kitezh. A secret organization called “Trinity” is also heading there. The principle of the game about Lara is an adventure game mixed with the adventure romance of the first journey, in which we kill with a bow, collect important items, and sometimes survive in the wild.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</guid><description>Game Description Fallout 4 is a sequel to the famous role-playing game series in a post-apocalyptic setting. The player wakes up from cryosleep and discovers that he is the only survivor of Vault 111. Having made it to the surface, he finds himself in the Wasteland - a world destroyed by nuclear war. The gameplay includes: a free open world with hundreds of locations to explore, a huge number of NPCs, companions and quests, as well as interaction with many factions, including the Institute, the Brotherhood of Steel, the Minutemen and agents of the Underground; S.</description></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-duty-black-ops-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter Call of Duty: Black Ops III demonstrates the blurred relationship between ordinary people and technology. In it you will forever forget that the new generation of soldiers is not a fiction, but a reality that will overtake us in the near future. Humanity has created technology to be leaders in the coming war, but will it be? The game shows this in three modes: story campaign, multiplayer shooter at scenario locations, and also in zombie mode.</description></item><item><title>Broforce</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</guid><description>Game Description Broforce is a powerful paramilitary organization that is called upon when the world is in danger due to an excessive number of evil forces. Take control of dozens of different brothers to counter terrorist attacks and save civilians. Destroy your opponents with napalm, shooting, lightning and other various character skills.
Broforce is a 2D shooter platformer with pixel graphics. You will move around locations, destroying opponents in every possible way.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency is a first-person shooter, in which the developers focused on playing in cooperative or multiplayer mode, about the Iraq War. The protagonist is a member of the US PMC, and he is fighting against Iraqi insurgents. The player chooses one side at the beginning of the match, and after that a brutal fight begins between the two factions. The basis of the game is a confrontation between two teams, which include 16 people.</description></item><item><title>PayDay 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</guid><description>Game Description Re-join the PayDay 2 gang as Dallas, Hoxton, Chains or Wolfe, who have come to Washington to rob and make a lot of money. Put the mask on your favorite hero and set off to carry out your next crime, in which you will need to overcome many obstacles before reaching your goal.
Now you will have a wide variety of contracts to choose from, from which you can choose any one.</description></item><item><title>BioShock Infinite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</guid><description>Game Description BioShock Infinite is a first-person shooter with multiple mechanics of a role-playing adventure in the style of science fiction and steampunk. The game will take place in 1912 in an alternative universe, in the flying city of the United States of America - Columbia. You need to control the private detective Booker Devitt, who has a task to find a cute girl named Elizabeth. Immediately after it is found, the main characters find themselves in the very epicenter of the war.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 2 is a shooter with a view from the perspective of the protagonist and leveling up abilities and passive improvements, as in the role-playing adventure genre. A direct continuation of the story of the original game. The main differences from the first part are a greater emphasis on the plot component and the addition of a more advanced weapon editor with many possible modifications that open up as you progress.</description></item><item><title>Saints Row: The Third</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</guid><description>Game Description The Third Street Saints are a large and large group in the universe of the game Saints Row: The Third. The third-person shooter with its crazy plots gave the game&amp;rsquo;s heroes their own brand of sneakers, a carbonated drink and a logo, and now they have to fight the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crime syndicate, whose people are scattered around the world and do their work in the “shadows”. Since the main characters have long captured Stillwater, the Syndicate demands offerings from them in the form of tribute for the criminal leadership.</description></item><item><title>Garry's Mod</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/garrys-mod/</guid><description>Game Description Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod is a game and physics sandbox. The main game mode is aimless and provides the player with a freely customizable world powered by the Source engine. The player creates non-player characters with various interaction objects. Special tools and tools allow you to construct new objects in reality, fix beams, iron, objects. Changing facial expressions is also available.
Thanks to the flexible engine, users create their own modifications: Spacebuild, Wiremod, Elevator: Source, DarkRP, Prop Hunt and others.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment, Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Coven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</guid><description>Game Description Going to the gloomy world of Coven, you have to deal with a large number of enemy creatures and deal with their elimination. The universe takes you into an atmospheric medieval fantasy world, where witches and other mythical creatures live alongside people. The first episode is available in the game, where you will take on the role of a young girl. The heroine is burned at the stake during the 1600s, mistaken for a witch and a fiend.</description></item></channel></rss>