<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Racing on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/racing/</link><description>Recent content in Racing on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Victory Heat Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Victory Heat Rally is a retro racing game inspired by arcade games of the last century, such as Hang-On and OutRun. You have to take control of small cars to rush along various difficult tracks at high speed. The gameplay is hardcore and pays homage to the classic games of yesteryear.
To fully master the mechanics of Victory Heat Rally, you will need to learn how to glide around the track, take corners correctly, and feel the road.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Jam Showdown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Jam Showdown is an adrenaline-pumping off-road racing experience that is sure to get your heart racing. Gamers can get behind the wheel of iconic monster trucks and compete in a variety of challenging environments. From dirt tracks to stadiums, the game offers a variety of racing arenas. The project has ten different modes and is designed for users of any level of training. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned veteran or just a new rider, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games' level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>Mon Bazou</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</guid><description>Game Description While repairing a car inMon Bazou, players have to deal with a variety of everyday problems that affect the life of the main character. The protagonist is a guy who dreams of turning his old car into a racing car that can compete with professional drivers and reach great speed. The game is made in the form of a simulator, where users have to take on the role of a novice racer who will live the everyday routine and do simple things, trying to earn a living.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>BeamNG drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</guid><description>Game Description BeamNG.drive is a car simulator that simulates the behavior of cars during collisions. Excellent physics, realistic controls and spectacular accidents are the main features of the game. The simulator allows you to find out what the consequences will be if, for example, the steering wheel of a Ferrari jams and the car flies into the oncoming lane, where it collides with a 40-ton truck. Or assess the damage to an army jeep whose brakes jammed when it was going down a hill at a speed of 90 km/h, flew off the road and crashed into a tree.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 5 has received dozens of awards for its open world, and almost the most expensive multi-platform project in history isGrand Theft Auto V. The story opens before us in the same fictional state - San Andreas, made 1 to 1 as Southern California. We play as three robber friends who have spent their entire adult lives stealing cars, robbing small shops and people on the street. One day someone decides to get involved in organized crime, which they have been fighting for the last 5 years.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa is a car simulator developed based on test drives of cars using a model of real behavior. Includes both single player and multiplayer modes.
The developers presented a variety of licensed cars and tracks, which were specially digitized specifically for the race to convey maximum authenticity to their prototypes. The machines can be customized to your individual taste, because&amp;hellip; the creators have added an extensive set of settings and support for modifications.</description></item></channel></rss>