<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Racing on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/racing/</link><description>Recent content in Racing on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zaccaria Pinball</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</guid><description>Game Description Zaccaria Pinball is the digital incarnation of pinball machines, offering an extensive collection of tables divided into several categories. Enthusiasts have access to both classic electro-mechanical (EM) devices, like Nautilus or Universe, and more modern solid-state (SS) versions, including Time Machine and Devil Riders.
In addition to authentic recreations, the project includes completely redesigned tables such as Space Shuttle 2016 and Farfalla 2017, as well as unique themed designs presented in the Award category, where you can find The Mummy and Aliens.</description></item><item><title>Tokyo Xtreme Racer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Tokyo Xtreme Racer is a racing game set against the backdrop of Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s vibrant underground street racing scene. The game immerses users in a world where speed and skill reign, and the ultimate goal is to defeat your opponents in intense one-on-one battles. Unlike traditional racing games, the title introduces a unique twist where the main goal is not to take first place, but to destroy the opponent&amp;rsquo;s Spirit Points (SP).</description></item><item><title>HOT ROD MAYHEM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description Hot Rod Mayhem represents car competitions on many tracks. This racing arcade contains a campaign mode, where to obtain the title of world champion, it is necessary to win in 10 separate championships. Promotion requires special tests with unique tasks that open access to the main events. After unlocking the championship, you can participate in its races so that the player can take first place in the fight against opponents.</description></item><item><title>JDM: Japanese Drift Master</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</guid><description>Game Description JDM: Japanese Drift Master is a colorful car simulator that will take you into the exciting world of drifting on the streets of Japan. A huge open world with varied landscapes, from serene lakes to bustling city areas, offers endless opportunities for exploration, racing and, of course, the art of drifting itself. What sets the game apart is the freedom it gives players to customize their cars, allowing them to truly make it their own.</description></item><item><title>My Summer Car</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</guid><description>Game Description My Summer Car is a life simulator of a Finnish, a 19-year-old boy who lives in a dacha in picturesque forests. His relatives on vacation in Tenerife, the whole house, and most importantly, garage, at his disposal. Created on Unity, thanks to the flexibility of this engine, and it became possible to add so much mechanic, which are below.
Your main occupation will be the restoration of the ancient Satsuma AMP car made on the basis of a real car - Datsun 100a.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Victory Heat Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Victory Heat Rally is a retro racing game inspired by arcade games of the last century, such as Hang-On and OutRun. You have to take control of small cars to rush along various difficult tracks at high speed. The gameplay is hardcore and pays homage to the classic games of yesteryear.
To fully master the mechanics of Victory Heat Rally, you will need to learn how to glide around the track, take corners correctly, and feel the road.</description></item><item><title>Rally Arcade Classics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Rally Arcade Classics takes gamers into the heart of rally racing history, bringing classic arcade gaming to the world of motorsports. With 44 cars from four different decades - the 70s, 80s, 90s and 00s - you&amp;rsquo;ll get a look at the cars that helped shape the rally scene. There&amp;rsquo;s a wide variety of iconic cars here, each offering its own set of challenges and driving features. In addition to the impressive list of cars, there are 48 tracks, each designed for a different type of racing.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Jam Showdown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Jam Showdown is an adrenaline-pumping off-road racing experience that is sure to get your heart racing. Gamers can get behind the wheel of iconic monster trucks and compete in a variety of challenging environments. From dirt tracks to stadiums, the game offers a variety of racing arenas. The project has ten different modes and is designed for users of any level of training. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned veteran or just a new rider, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games' level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>Expections: A Mudrunner Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</guid><description>Game Description Expections: A Mudrunner Game throws you headlong into unknown territories, putting you at the head of research missions at insidious landscapes. Get ready for an off -road adventure based on physics, where every centimeter of progress requires the courage, strategy and masterful ownership of your strong all -terrain vehicle. Imagine how you will overcome the deserts sifted by the sun, thick forests clinging to your tires, and snowy peaks that experience you for strength.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>Brick Rigs</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</guid><description>Game Description Brick Rigs is a sandbox that allows you to create a variety of vehicles, and then enjoy realistic driving and destruction physics. You need to build cars using various blocks. The Brick Rings toolkit allows you to create a dragster, a fire truck, a forklift, a helicopter, an airplane or even a tank - it all depends on your imagination and skill.
Gameplay Brick Rigs is a full-fledged construction set with which you can create any type of transport.</description></item><item><title>Mon Bazou</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</guid><description>Game Description While repairing a car inMon Bazou, players have to deal with a variety of everyday problems that affect the life of the main character. The protagonist is a guy who dreams of turning his old car into a racing car that can compete with professional drivers and reach great speed. The game is made in the form of a simulator, where users have to take on the role of a novice racer who will live the everyday routine and do simple things, trying to earn a living.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</guid><description>Game Description Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game is an adventure game in which the player is invited to travel around the world by car. The universe around the main character experienced a terrible apocalypse, turning into a desert. Graphically, the project is made using low-detail textures to create its own style. The locations where the gamer is present are created randomly thanks to the use of artificial intelligence in the process of generating territories, which is responsible for randomizing the environment.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>Starlink: Battle for Atlas</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starlink-battle-for-atlas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starlink-battle-for-atlas/</guid><description>Game Description Starlink: Battle for Atlas is an adventure game in which you become a space pilot to rid the Atlas system of the villains Grax and the Forgotten Legion. You will lead your Starlink squad and take a stand against despotism to save the entire galaxy from powerful invaders. There are four ships to choose from to participate in the competition: Zenith, Neptune, Pulse, Lance.
The game provides a choice of six pilots, including Mason, Judge, Chase, Hunter, Levi, Razor, who have their own skills and characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Liftoff: FPV Drone Racing</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff FPV Drone Racing is a training ground for quadcopter pilots. The game is a training ground for both beginners and an obstacle course for experienced gamers. Professionals can test their strength in a new environment, and people who have recently become interested in this sport can hone their skills before taking on real prototypes.
In Liftoff FPV Drone Racing, users can take their first steps towards the sport of quadcopter racing.</description></item><item><title>The Crew 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</guid><description>Game Description In The Crew 2 you can ride anything, as long as you have money for this equipment. The game includes several game modes in the genre of a sports racing simulator from a third/first person: free, cooperative, career, multiplayer mode. A free race usually takes place on a separate map. We choose one unlocked vehicle element and try to win the race. In this simulator you can sail on a boat, drive a fast, high-speed car, or fly on an airplane.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>Street Legal Racing: Redline</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</guid><description>Game Description Street Legal Racing: Redline is a car mechanic simulator that allows you to assemble a car completely from scratch. At the same time, street racing with assembled vehicles is available. New parts can affect the characteristics of the car, which are responsible for acceleration, handling and maximum speed. Street Legal Racing does not provide package upgrades. The rider must install each individual part himself.
The game has many features:</description></item><item><title>BeamNG drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</guid><description>Game Description BeamNG.drive is a car simulator that simulates the behavior of cars during collisions. Excellent physics, realistic controls and spectacular accidents are the main features of the game. The simulator allows you to find out what the consequences will be if, for example, the steering wheel of a Ferrari jams and the car flies into the oncoming lane, where it collides with a 40-ton truck. Or assess the damage to an army jeep whose brakes jammed when it was going down a hill at a speed of 90 km/h, flew off the road and crashed into a tree.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 5 has received dozens of awards for its open world, and almost the most expensive multi-platform project in history isGrand Theft Auto V. The story opens before us in the same fictional state - San Andreas, made 1 to 1 as Southern California. We play as three robber friends who have spent their entire adult lives stealing cars, robbing small shops and people on the street. One day someone decides to get involved in organized crime, which they have been fighting for the last 5 years.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa is a car simulator developed based on test drives of cars using a model of real behavior. Includes both single player and multiplayer modes.
The developers presented a variety of licensed cars and tracks, which were specially digitized specifically for the race to convey maximum authenticity to their prototypes. The machines can be customized to your individual taste, because&amp;hellip; the creators have added an extensive set of settings and support for modifications.</description></item><item><title>Tick ​​Hop</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</guid><description>Game Description Tick ​​Hop is a 2D platformer that requires the accuracy of movements, where a gamer assumes the role of the keeper of time. The journey includes the passage of the stages, each of which consists of temporary fragments. The main goal is to solve riddles, opening the aspects of the past to restore the future. The reverse reference system in this project requires quick actions to move through chronological spaces.</description></item></channel></rss>