<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>RPG on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/rpg/</link><description>Recent content in RPG on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/rpg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Arc Line</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/new-arc-line/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/new-arc-line/</guid><description>Game Description New Arc Line is a game that invites gamers to venture into a city where the line between magic and technology is not just thin, it&amp;rsquo;s practically non-existent. Set in the sprawling steam-powered metropolis of Newark, it immerses players in a world where secrets lurk in every corner and power is as fickle as the magic and the machines that power it. The city is a place of contradictions: elegant but corrupt, vibrant but mired in inequality.</description></item><item><title>Renaissance Kingdom Wars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/renaissance-kingdom-wars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/renaissance-kingdom-wars/</guid><description>Game Description Renaissance Kingdom Wars is a rich blend of grand strategy and real-time strategy set against the backdrop of 1510. At the beginning of the game, you have nothing but a name - you are just a mercenary captain with dreams of greatness. Rise through the ranks, from lord to king, and make your mark on a vast world spanning Europe, Africa and the Middle East.
The main thing in Renaissance Kingdom Wars is making strategic decisions.</description></item><item><title>Sin Slayers: Reign of The 8th</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sin-slayers-reign-of-the-8th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sin-slayers-reign-of-the-8th/</guid><description>Game Description Sin Slayers: Reign of The 8th immerses users in a dark, unforgiving world, where every corner is fraught with new dangers and moral dilemmas. In this turn-based strategy game, players take on the role of a group of adventurers, each representing one of the Seven Deadly Sins. Their mission? Confront monstrous enemies, travel through dark and twisted places, and ultimately confront the formidable Eighth Sin - Fate.
This latest installment in the Sin Slayers series expands on the formula of its predecessor, introducing new regions, improved mechanics, and an even deeper story that will force players to question not only the fate of their characters, but the very nature of sin.</description></item><item><title>ATLYSS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atlyss/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atlyss/</guid><description>Game Description ATLYSS is an open world RPG adventure game that introduces gamers to a vast and surreal universe. It is filled with a variety of creatures and mysterious locations, inviting users to explore every corner of it. Users can choose how they interact with the world: collaborate with others or cope with difficulties alone. The dynamic nature allows them to adapt their style, fostering a sense of responsibility for their experiences.</description></item><item><title>Scourge of the village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scourge-of-the-village/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scourge-of-the-village/</guid><description>Game Description Scourge of the Village takes gamers on an eerie journey through a mountain village shrouded in mystery and supernatural elements. Set against the backdrop of Chinese folk horror, the plot revolves around an investigation that goes wrong. Chen Xi, a trainee reporter, begins investigating a wastewater discharge incident at a factory, but soon finds himself in a much more alarming situation. As she navigates the twisted paths of reality and dreams, the boundaries between the two worlds blur, and what was once an investigation into environmental crimes turns into a struggle to understand the tragic history of the village.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Clawler</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Clawler brings a fresh twist to the roguelike formula. It combines the familiar thrills of dungeon crawling with claw machine mechanics that put a twist on traditional gameplay. You navigate treacherous environments, but instead of directly grabbing weapons and armor, you rely on the claw to get you the loot you need. This adds strategic thinking, because every item you take out of the car can play a decisive role in the next battle or encounter.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl is a first-person shooter in a post-apocalyptic world. The events of the game will develop in the exclusion zone formed as a result of the disaster at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. In 2006, a new catastrophe occurred, which led to various physical, chemical and biological processes, creating many anomalies, artifacts and generating a large number of mutants.
The gameplay is a classic FPS with elements of a role-playing game, immersive sim and horror.</description></item><item><title>Incantation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incantation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/incantation/</guid><description>Game Description Incantation is a first-person horror game that immerses gamers in the eerie world of Chen Village, where danger and mystery are never left behind. As the main character, a mother desperately searching for her missing daughter, users will have to navigate the web of secrets, rituals and cults that seem to seep from every crack in the village walls. The plot unfolds gradually, and with each step more and more information is revealed about the strange forces operating in the village.</description></item><item><title>My Hotel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</guid><description>Game Description Users in My Hotel have to try their hand at being a novice businessman who is going to set up a small hotel and gradually develop it. You will have to buy a dirty and in terrible condition of a house in which you can arrange rooms for living and set up a reception. It is necessary to wash all the floors, clean the furniture from dust and do everything possible to make an attractive and prestigious appearance for the building.</description></item><item><title>TIME SOUL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/time-soul/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/time-soul/</guid><description>Game Description TIME SOUL is an action-platformer with a unique approach to the usual souls-like genre. In a universe where time is both weapon and enemy, gamers will battle through procedurally generated worlds filled with treacherous platforms, unexpected obstacles and formidable enemies. Moving forward, users will fight with the guardians of time, collect fragments and clocks, trying to prevent the complete collapse of time. It&amp;rsquo;s a race against time, literally, as the ultimate goal is to defeat the Time Lord within a limited time of 60 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Codex Lost</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/codex-lost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/codex-lost/</guid><description>Game Description Codex Lost is an open-world role-playing adventure game that immerses gamers in a realm where magic, mystery and danger intertwine. Against the backdrop of a fractured world, users take on the role of the Guardian, a figure tasked with finding stolen grimoires and saving a reality on the brink of collapse. The stakes are high and the journey is filled with challenges, but what really sets the title apart is its focus on freedom, discovery and strategic combat.</description></item><item><title>Everholm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everholm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everholm/</guid><description>Game Description Everholm, a delightful indie game, is an RPG that seamlessly blends farming, friendship, and mystery. The plot centers on a girl, Lilly, who finds herself on a magical island, where everyone recognizes her, but her own memories elude her. As she delves deeper into the story, she discovers a startling truth - her sister, Melanie, has gone missing, and the island holds the key to her whereabouts. One of the hallmarks of Everholm is its open-ended nature, allowing players to determine the pace of their adventure.</description></item><item><title>HeistGeist</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</guid><description>Game Description HeistGeist immerses gamers in the cyberpunk universe, putting them in the shoes of Alexandra, a cunning thief who overcomes the consequences of a failed mission. The title revolves around the challenge of assembling a diverse team of specialists to carry out complex heists. Each heist presents tactical obstacles and opportunities, turning each mission into a unique puzzle. Users take part in battles based on a card-based battle system that brings an innovative twist to the traditional strategy genre.</description></item><item><title>Mirthwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</guid><description>Game Description Mirthwood is a fun medieval fantasy sandbox game that combines the charm of a life simulation with the thrill of an RPG. It offers gamers the opportunity to create their own adventure in a new country, escaping their war-torn homeland. The game offers two main paths: settle down and build a farm, trade with other cities and start a family; or explore a huge open world and fight bandits, monsters and other dangers.</description></item><item><title>Gods Wars: Infinity Epic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gods-wars-infinity-epic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gods-wars-infinity-epic/</guid><description>Game Description Gods Wars: Infinity Epic is a pixelated roguelike that invites gamers into a world filled with relentless combat, strategic decision-making and rich customization. From the very beginning, the adventure game offers significant flexibility, allowing gamers to create their characters according to their playstyle and preferences. The plot is simple and at the same time fascinating: users will have to overcome waves of monsters, defeat powerful bosses and ultimately challenge the formidable evil gods.</description></item><item><title>Metal Slug Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description The Metal Slug Tactics player chooses his warriors to create a suitable powerful team capable of stopping the hostilities. Run n' Gun has roguelike elements as well as intense combat. The continuation of the series of the same name allows you to look at the war from a new angle with a greater share of adrenaline, gaining experience after each fight, which helps to unlock additional skills or weapons.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>Quadrober Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Quadrober Simulator invites users to test themselves as a four-legged creature in a diverse environment. There is a lot of choice in this game. Users can choose from a variety of animals, each with specific traits and skills. These choices set the stage for a unique journey through different ecosystems. As gamers navigate these landscapes, they are faced with opportunities to explore, survive, and interact with the environment. Gameplay revolves around several key activities, including hunting, foraging, and building shelters.</description></item><item><title>The Scourge | Tai Wang</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-scourge-tai-uong/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-scourge-tai-uong/</guid><description>Game Description The Scourge | Tai Uong is a puzzle RPG that takes gamers into the eerie setting of Saigon, Vietnam, capturing the essence of urban legends from the 1990s. The story centers on a protagonist who must navigate a tragic family history and is haunted by a dark, supernatural presence that is the result of past choices. Users will have to go through a series of complex puzzles, exploring various locations of the city, in an effort to uncover hidden truths and confront otherworldly threats.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Necro Story</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/necro-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/necro-story/</guid><description>Game Description Necro Story provides users with a unique opportunity to step into the shoes of a slightly evil necromancer. The title combines elements of humor and the conventions of traditional role-playing games, inviting gamers into a world where the undead and dark magic are part of everyday life. The narrative unfolds with the help of a ghostly white magician who brings playfulness to the often dark theme of necromancy. Together they embark on a journey through the underworld to save humanity from an impending threat.</description></item><item><title>Monomyth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monomyth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monomyth/</guid><description>Game Description The narrative in Monomyth takes you to dark and gloomy times, immersing you in a dark fantasy atmosphere. Strong natural forces in the form of storms devastate the surface of the earth, which is why humanity has to go underground. The world is plunging into a period of chaos and hopelessness, making it increasingly difficult for ordinary people to survive; strife and civil strife begin, followed by the decline of civilization and culture of the human race.</description></item><item><title>Into the Necrovale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-necrovale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-necrovale/</guid><description>Game Description Into the Necrovale plunges you into a desperate fight for survival. As the Outsider, a doomed soul chosen by the All-Father, you hold the fate of a tormented world in your hands. Will you be his savior or his harbinger of doom? The choice is up to you. In the desolate Necroval, generations of exiled criminals fight for their existence. Hopeless, lost, forgotten - they are all bound by one rule: survive.</description></item><item><title>Banquet for Fools</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banquet-for-fools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banquet-for-fools/</guid><description>Game Description Banquet for Fools is a party role-playing adventure game that invites gamers into a kingdom filled with pagan rituals and mysterious secrets. In this game, users take the place of a lord among the Vollins, an elven race distinguished by their slender forms and a troubled history of relationships with deities. Rejected by their gods, these creatures turn to paganism in search of the meaning of their existence. The setting is a cursed island, shrouded in mystery, where the user&amp;rsquo;s spice farms have inexplicably lost all their inhabitants.</description></item><item><title>exclusive memory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</guid><description>Game Description Exclusive Memory draws gamers into a narrative where every choice and interaction can change the storyline. The protagonist finds himself in a maze of memories, each of which serves as a puzzle box that needs to be opened. As users delve deeper, they uncover layers of the character&amp;rsquo;s past, encountering various figures that are pieces of a larger puzzle. These interactions not only move the narrative forward, but also provide insight into the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s psyche, shaping his journey.</description></item><item><title>Halluci-Sabbath of Koishi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</guid><description>Game Description Halluci-Sabbat of Koishi immerses users in a fantasy setting where they will have to take control of the monster Satori Komeiji Koishi, who is an adventurer and a trained soldier. During the adventure, the hero meets a human witch who is looking for rare ingredients to create potions. Traveling together, the protagonists stumble upon a dangerous mushroom family and undead that they have to fight. Players will explore the forest with miasma and encounter many opponents.</description></item><item><title>Ravenswatch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenswatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenswatch/</guid><description>Game Description Ravenswatch is a hardcore adventure in which you will need to explore a world captured by a terrible Nightmare. The gameplay is an isometric action role-playing game with procedurally generated locations. Battles are distinguished by their increased complexity and take place in real time. The gameplay is aimed at the player&amp;rsquo;s skill and creating a unique character build. Depending on the choice of the protagonist, weapons, equipment and a set of auxiliary items, the strategy of fights completely changes.</description></item><item><title>Shadows of Doubt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadows-of-doubt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadows-of-doubt/</guid><description>Game Description Shadows of Doubt allows gamers to plunge into the world of dark noir, which is shown in a sci-fi setting. Gamers will take control of a detective who is forced to deal with the case of a serial killer. The criminal is at large, committing hidden murders. The game is a first-person role-playing stealth adventure where you need to examine the surrounding area and interact with objects to find clues to the case.</description></item><item><title>Alchemist: The Potion Monger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemist-the-potion-monger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemist-the-potion-monger/</guid><description>Game Description Alchemist: The Potion Monger invites users into a world where alchemy reigns. This first-person simulation game combines RPG elements, immersing gamers in a realm rich with ingredients and potions waiting in the wings. From the moment you step out of the cozy alchemy hut, you will be overcome with a sense of adventure. The environment is rife with opportunities to collect rare materials and brew unique drinks. Each exploration leads to discoveries that expand your alchemical repertoire and keep gameplay fresh and exciting.</description></item><item><title>GreedFall 2: The Dying World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/greedfall-2-the-dying-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/greedfall-2-the-dying-world/</guid><description>Game Description GreedFall II: The Dying World takes the beloved original game to new heights, offering an even more exciting and challenging adventure. The RPG takes place three years before its predecessor and takes players to the old continent of Gakan, where they take on the role of a native of Tir Fradi, a land filled with danger and corruption. Here survival and the fight for freedom and homeland become paramount.</description></item><item><title>Halls of Torment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</guid><description>Game Description Halls of Torment invites you into the world of terrifying monsters in this unique action game with roguelite elements, where you will face new challenges and dangers in each game. Dive into the dark and ruthless dungeons where the lords of the underworld await you. Find treasures and magical artifacts, and assemble a team of heroes who will help you defeat the horrors emanating from the depths of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Witchfire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/witchfire/</guid><description>Game Description Witchfire suggests using not only weapons in the process, but also various devices in order to survive after an encounter with monsters. An arsenal consisting of dozens of different items and a variety of enemies will help gamers realize their own shooting skills. Challenge the most dangerous monsters that live in this world.
Here it is important to select the right type of weapon in accordance with the situation and type of enemy.</description></item><item><title>God of War: Ragnarok</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-ragnarok/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-ragnarok/</guid><description>Game Description God of War: Ragnarok continues the story of Kratos and Atreus as they explore a world inspired by Norse mythology. Events take place in ancient Norway. The events are dedicated to the beginning of Ragnarok. According to legend, it should lead to the death of all the Scandinavian gods, thereby marking the end of the world. Gameplay God of War: Ragnarok remains faithful to the original, but many new mechanics, enemies, abilities and locations have been introduced.</description></item><item><title>Wild Indigo Ranch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-indigo-ranch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-indigo-ranch/</guid><description>Game Description Wild Indigo Ranch invites you to step into the boots of a cowboy and travel to the fictional and humorous Wild West. Whether you prefer single-player play or join forces with up to three friends in online co-op, flexible options are offered. Personalization is key, allowing you to customize your character, horse, and ranch to suit your unique style.
Freedom reigns in the vast world of the game. You can roam the wild, hunt animals, search for gold mines, trade goods with other settlers, or engage in intense shootouts with bandits and lawmen.</description></item><item><title>Fera: The Sundered Tribes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fera-the-sundered-tribes/</guid><description>Game Description Fera: The Sundered Tribes throws its hat into the action-RPG ring, but with a twist. You will not only have to smash the skulls of monsters, but also lead your tribe to restoration in a world devastated by magic. Imagine: A monster hunter by day, a mayor by night. The world of Fera is a post-apocalyptic mess, twisted by magic and infested with giant monsters that are eager to add your tribe to their menu of creatures.</description></item><item><title>Enotria: The Last Song</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enotria-the-last-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enotria-the-last-song/</guid><description>Game Description Enotria: The Last Song is not your typical push-button machine. This action RPG throws you into a world bound by a twisted, timeless game. You take on the role of Maskless, a wild card free of the scripted roles that everyone else follows. What is your task? Challenge the powerful Authors who support this disorderly spectacle. Masks are the main thing. Each of them gives you its own role and a unique set of abilities.</description></item><item><title>Judero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</guid><description>Game Description Judero immerses you in the world of strategic decisions and tactical battles. The title combines elements of role-playing and strategy, requiring gamers to go through various challenges and opponents. Users must manage resources, create alliances and make important decisions that will affect the outcome of their journey. In Judero, users encounter a variety of characters, each with unique abilities and history. These characters can be recruited into the player&amp;rsquo;s team, giving them various tactical advantages in battle.</description></item><item><title>Starstruck: Hands of Time</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starstruck-hands-of-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starstruck-hands-of-time/</guid><description>Game Description Starstruck: Hands of Time is an action role-playing game with rhythm game elements. Immersed in a vibrant world, you need to pick up a guitar to explore the rich environment. At the center of the story are two child guitarists. They confront three villains who want to rewrite the history of the world. The gameplay is based on time travel.
In the year 30XX, humanity will disappear from the face of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Trail of Ayash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</guid><description>Game Description The world of Trail of Ayash is based on the myths and legends of the inhabitants. An open game location allows you to freely explore the area and learn more about the life of Native Americans. The player will encounter various tribes competing with each other, participating in diplomacy, organizing wars and expansion. The main character is Ayash, a respected man in his own faction. One day, a close person frames Ayash, and after that he is expelled from the tribe.</description></item><item><title>Archons: Arena</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/archons-arena/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/archons-arena/</guid><description>Game Description Archons: Arena combines deckbuilding and RPG elements, throwing gamers into a harsh world where skill, equipment and tactics are crucial. There are several character classes, each with their own special abilities, allowing users to customize their style to suit their preferences. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a secretive rogue, a stalwart knight, or a powerful sorcerer, there&amp;rsquo;s a class for you.
The main mechanic is deckbuilding, in which gamers create their decks without any random elements.</description></item><item><title>Lucky Tower Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lucky-tower-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lucky-tower-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Lucky Tower Ultimate combines roguelike mechanics with a unique sense of humor. Gamers move through a dangerous tower, where every item can be used as a weapon. Here users will have to get out of the tower, overcoming various obstacles and enemies. Procedurally generated levels make each playthrough different, so no two are alike. The main character, von Vanst, continues his adventures in this part. Comedy and strategic gameplay are mixed here.</description></item><item><title>EVOTINCTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</guid><description>Game Description EVOTINCTION is a futuristic hacking and stealth game that puts gamers in the role of Dr. Liu, a scientist running a research facility that has been taken over by rogue AIs. The core gameplay centers on using hacking skills to overcome robotic threats and uncover secrets vital to humanity&amp;rsquo;s survival. The facility is teeming with enemies, ranging from ordinary service robots to deadly, specially created killer bots.
These robots follow specific patrol routes and work together under the guidance of a sophisticated artificial intelligence system.</description></item><item><title>Hive Jump 2: Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hive Jump 2: Survivors is a sci-fi role-playing adventure game with action elements. In this adrenaline-pumping sequel to the acclaimed action-platformer, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself the only survivor of your squad, stranded on an alien planet. Armed with only your guns and your trusty jetpack, you set out on a mission of revenge. Here you have to fight relentless waves of killer insects. What is your goal? Destroy these swarms of aliens and collect their valuable entrails.</description></item><item><title>Towerborne</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</guid><description>Game Description Towerborne is an action-adventure game set in a world where humanity&amp;rsquo;s cities have been destroyed by a mysterious evil. The only refuge is the Bell Tower, a tower that holds secrets and dangers. Gamers take on the role of Ace, a hero tasked with protecting the inhabitants of the Belfry and uncovering the truth about the evil threatening humanity. Here gamers explore a huge world filled with various creatures and challenges.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-space-marine-2/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 is a cinematic 3rd person sci-fi action game set in a dystopian future where humanity is under siege by an implacable enemy - the Tyranids. As a Space Marine, you take on the role of a superhuman warrior tasked with defending the Imperium from an impending threat. Gamers are offered the opportunity to embody the image of the greatest warrior and show their incredible skill and cruelty in epic battles on distant planets.</description></item><item><title>Castle of Lord Velimir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</guid><description>Game Description Castle of Lord Velimir takes users on a dangerous journey with the titular hero, a warrior seeking atonement for the sins of humanity. As Velimir journeys through the dungeons, wastelands, and mysterious underworld of Agartha, he will face countless challenges and uncover the secrets of his world. The gameplay is a mixture of strategic combat and exploration. Users must master a variety of fighting techniques to defeat a variety of enemies, each requiring a different approach.</description></item><item><title>CORPUS EDAX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corpus-edax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corpus-edax/</guid><description>Game Description CORPUS EDAX is an exciting first-person action RPG with close combat that will take you to a distant planet. Create your own character and unleash your inner warrior as you fight, sneak, or escape difficult situations. The choice is always yours - and it is always the right one. Use your body, ingenuity, and improvised weapons to make your way through this stunning new world. Thanks to the A.</description></item><item><title>Selfloss</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selfloss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/selfloss/</guid><description>Game Description Selfloss is an atmospheric adventure set in a fantasy setting. The plot centers on a lonely old man, and the game itself is inspired by ancient Russian and Icelandic legends. Travel through the isometric world using your magic staff. Fight against numerous mythical creatures from Slavic fairy tales and myths. Help everyone who needs it. Pass many tests to perform a secret self-floss ritual that can heal a wounded soul.</description></item><item><title>Skoof Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skoof-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Skoof Simulator will introduce gamers to the life of Skoof, an ordinary worker whose everyday life is not like a routine. The title combines simulation and adventure elements, offering a unique and sarcastic look at everyday activities. Players guide Skuf through a variety of missions, ranging from factory shifts to humorous and unexpected situations. Users will have to manage Skuf&amp;rsquo;s life, making decisions that affect the outcome of his adventures.</description></item><item><title>We Heist Too</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</guid><description>Game Description We Heist Too takes place in Rivadorium, a city where nothing ever stays the same. Users get used to the role of a thief, move silently through the streets, plan and carry out high-stakes robberies. This world doesn&amp;rsquo;t require much care, and from the very beginning you will notice that every corner of the city is fraught with opportunity. But the tricky part is knowing which opportunities are worth pursuing.</description></item><item><title>Dale and Dawson Stationery Supplies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dale-and-dawson-stationery-supplies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dale-and-dawson-stationery-supplies/</guid><description>Game Description Dale and Dawson Stationery Supplies, inspired by an early 2000s office drama, immerses gamers in the mundane yet intriguing world of a seemingly typical stationery company. The title randomly assigns you one of three roles: Manager, Specialist or Slacker. Your fate is sealed and your mission begins. Targeted Gameplay: Specialists diligently complete tasks to move the company forward, and slackers imitate specialists so as not to arouse suspicion.</description></item><item><title>Megaloot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megaloot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megaloot/</guid><description>Game Description Megaloot occupies a unique niche in the world of role-playing games, requiring gamers to pay meticulous attention to inventory management. Unraveling a mysterious world in which a colossal structure has the ability to replicate objects from countless realities, the title sets the stage for an odyssey filled with strategic choices and tactical delights. Users will find more than 100 different items, each of which boasts its own characteristics. Combine them cleverly to create a dominant build - the possibilities are mind-boggling.</description></item><item><title>Call of Sentinels</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Sentinels plunges you headlong into an epic struggle against the forces of darkness. Choose your champion from a growing list, each with unique skills and fighting styles. Hone your combat skills against the relentless hordes in the Arena, or take on dangerous journeys across varied landscapes in Campaign. Unleash devastating combos and master tactical maneuvers to defeat treacherous enemies and colossal bosses. Each victory unlocks valuable upgrades, expanding the hero&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and shaping his legend.</description></item><item><title>Gundam Breaker 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</guid><description>Game Description GUNDAM BREAKER 4 hits the gaming scene with a bang as part of the heist gaming franchise. It&amp;rsquo;s all about building and fighting with a set of Gundam models, a concept fans are very familiar with. However, adventure games breathe new life into this formula, offering a deeper and more expansive experience. Customization is the cornerstone of the game. An extensive library of over 250 base sets provides the foundation for creating the Gunpla of your dreams.</description></item><item><title>Star Command Galaxies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</guid><description>Game Description Star Command Galaxies is a space simulator in which you play as a ship captain. You need to build your own shuttle, recruit staff and go explore the randomly generated expanses of outer space. Manage your staff, collect resources, fight the alien threat and upgrade your ship. Clear the galaxy from enemies and various parasites. Fight pirates, zombies and many other opponents.
You need to monitor the status of your team.</description></item><item><title>Peglin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/peglin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/peglin/</guid><description>Game Description Peglin is a side-scrolling RPG adventure with a 2D world. The player will play the role of a fictional peglin creature trying to fight dragons that steal and eat representatives of his race. The main character is a small green creature with big ears. He decided to go to the forest, where the faction&amp;rsquo;s longtime enemies live. There he will meet his enemies and take back what was stolen by the dragons.</description></item><item><title>Core Keeper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</guid><description>Game Description Going on an adventure in Core Keeper involves immersing yourself in an atmosphere of the unknown that requires exploration on behalf of an archaeologist who wants to discover as many new relics and ancient artifacts as possible. Waking up in an unfamiliar area that resembles a cave, the protagonist will have to fight through a variety of monsters and obstacles that impede progress in order to achieve his goals.</description></item><item><title>The Land of the Magnates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-land-of-the-magnates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-land-of-the-magnates/</guid><description>Game Description The Land of the Magnates tells the story of fallen prince Shahbaz, who is tasked with restoring a kingdom shrouded in darkness. The project does not hand the players a sword, but instead puts a sitar in their hands. This is not a hack-and-slash adventure game. No, this is a journey of melody and power, where puzzles replace sword fights. Shahbaz&amp;rsquo;s adventure takes place through fantastical landscapes. The black forest, the damned expanses, tests your courage.</description></item><item><title>Rum and Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rum-and-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Rum and Gun uses a pirate theme as its setting. The hero travels through the lands located in the Indian Ocean, fighting on land with people and monsters. He is trying to stop the captain, who has enlisted the help of evil forces. He also has to learn the secrets of the Drunken God. The plot is presented with jokes and self-irony. History is divided into acts.
This is an isometric shooter and action game with role-playing elements.</description></item><item><title>Finding Mosey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</guid><description>Game Description In Finding Mosey, your feline companion Mosey has mysteriously disappeared. You go in search of him, and your path will depend on the choice you make. Developed by youpiepoopie, this single-player third-person RPG offers a refreshing blend of exploration, storytelling, and whimsical interactions. The search begins. Imagine waking up during a peaceful hike to find Mosey nowhere to be found.
This seemingly simple premise turns into an exciting adventure.</description></item><item><title>Tactical Breach Wizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tactical-breach-wizards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tactical-breach-wizards/</guid><description>Game Description Tactical Breach Wizards is a tactical role-playing adventure with an isometric camera that allows you to better assess the situation in the location to make the most successful decisions. The user will be transported to an alternative universe, where a distant futuristic future has arrived. The gamer takes control of a group of soldiers who have magical abilities that allow them to be combined with shots from firearms.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Dynasty takes place in 1800s America. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to build his own ranch, providing himself with wealth and food. Over time, other settlers, workers and friends will join the main character. Each minor character has their own qualities, characteristics and mannerisms. Many of them will turn out to be bandits, and only the gamer can decide who is sent to the gallows.
Having become determined, the central character set out to build a Wild West dynasty, moving further across the Pacific region of America.</description></item><item><title>Black Myth: Wukong</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-myth-wukong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-myth-wukong/</guid><description>Game Description Black Myth: Wukong is a role-playing game based on the famous Chinese novel Journey to the West, written back in the 16th century. The gameplay is a journey through a semi-open world, reminiscent of a metroidvania. The developers cite the Souls series as their main source of inspiration.
The story centers on a hero named Sun Wukong, who is also known as the Monkey King. He travels through a fantasy world, simultaneously fighting with various phantasmagoric creatures.</description></item><item><title>Fields of Mistria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</guid><description>Game Description Fields of Mistria invites users to exchange the hustle and bustle for a charming life in the village of Mistria. Here the fields lie between a whispering forest and a sparkling sea. But in Mystria, not everything is so rosy and sunny. The recent earthquake has left its mark, and now there is a strange magic in the air. This is where you come to the rescue. In Mystria you inherit an overgrown estate - a diamond in the bowels of the earth.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>Songs of Conquest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/songs-of-conquest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/songs-of-conquest/</guid><description>Game Description The hero of Songs of Conquest is developing his own kingdom and mercilessly destroys any enemies who stand in his way. A mix of turn-based strategy and RPG, you can become the head of a huge army that uses not only weapons in battle, but also magic to conquer distant territories in order to assert their own power. The game features a level editor, 4 factions to choose from, and the ability to go on a solo adventure or challenge a friend to battle locally or online.</description></item><item><title>Rabbit and Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Rabbit and Steel is a co-op action roguelike that will take you into epic battles. Choose your class, gather your bunny friends and fight to the top of Moon Peak. Months ago, all ties with the Moonlight Kingdom were severed. It is reported that the city&amp;rsquo;s residents are attacking all newcomers. Exploratory expeditions are repulsed or go missing. Every night, a huge white tower appears in the center of the city, reaching towards the stars.</description></item><item><title>Hades 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades-ii/</guid><description>Game Description Hades II, the sequel to the award-winning roguelike dungeon crawler, takes players beyond the underworld. You play as Melina, a princess of the underworld, who uses dark sorcery to fight the Titan of Time. Supergiant Games builds on the success of the original game with intense action and endless replayability. Explore a deeper mythical world rooted in Greek myth and witchcraft. The story unfolds through victories and failures, keeping you on your toes.</description></item><item><title>Chrono Ark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</guid><description>Game Description Chrono Ark is a classic Japanese-style RPG adventure that supports high-resolution textures, but uses similar camera views and turn-based dialogue and battle system rendering. The story campaign is available for completion only in single-player mode; multiplayer is not provided in this project.
The gameplay is based on gathering a team, which includes 4 characters, for further leveling up and creating an invincible squad, ready to fight on equal terms with all opponents presented in the locations of the bizarre Distorted World.</description></item><item><title>Abiotic Factor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abiotic-factor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abiotic-factor/</guid><description>Game Description Abiotic Factor throws you into an underworld of chaos. Scientists, humanity&amp;rsquo;s brightest representatives, become survivors when faced with a multifaceted threat. When the protective shell is breached, horrors burst to the surface, and soldiers from another dimension invade the world. Meanwhile, a secret military sect hunts for artifacts and entities, adding to the chaos.
Trapped miles underground, escape seems impossible. But you and your fellow scientists are not ordinary people.</description></item><item><title>Manor Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Manor Lords is a strategy game set in the Middle Ages. The game mechanics center on the realistic process of constructing buildings and intense fights with the enemy army. The building element is based on historical data about cities and villages. All buildings presented in Manor Lords are as authentic as possible. Landscapes and types of terrain influence the process of settlement formation.
Create trade routes, establish market relations with neighboring cities and promote the economic prosperity of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Another Crab's Treasure</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-crabs-treasure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-crabs-treasure/</guid><description>Game Description Another Crab&amp;rsquo;s Treasure is an exciting underwater adventure created by AGGRO CRAB. You take on the role of a hermit crab named Creel, who goes on a dangerous treasure hunt to get back his stolen shell. In this unique underwater kingdom, on the verge of destruction, garbage is not only part of life, but also a valuable resource used to create fashionable outfits and weapons. However, with the garbage comes a mysterious danger - &amp;ldquo;slurry&amp;rdquo; - which threatens to destroy the entire ocean.</description></item><item><title>Bellwright</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</guid><description>Game Description Bellwright throws you into a world of rebellion and intrigue. Finding yourself in prison for a heinous crime, you must not only clear your name, but also organize a revolution against a tyrannical ruler. Build and manage settlements, collect resources and recruit villagers into your ranks. Each new adept brings valuable skills, strengthening your rebellion and unlocking new technologies for your cities.
Combat is based on skill and focus.</description></item><item><title>The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty is a visual novel set in China during the turbulent reign of the Chongzhen Emperor. Players take on the role of Liang, a former merchant turned bandit tasked with escorting four girls to the prosperous city of Luoyang. The journey is fraught with danger and moral problems. Liang struggles with the truth behind his mission when one of the girls, Sui, reveals a terrifying secret: their goal is not a luxurious life, but an encounter with a monstrous pig demon.</description></item><item><title>No Rest for the Wicked</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-rest-for-the-wicked/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-rest-for-the-wicked/</guid><description>Game Description No Rest for the Wicked immerses players in a world ravaged by death and despair. Developed by Moon Studios, the creators of Ori and the Blind Forest, this action RPG promises challenging combat and deep human storytelling. The kingdom mourns the death of King Harol, leaving his untested son Magnus on the throne. Meanwhile, an ancient plague known as the Blight returns, corrupting the land and its inhabitants. Amid the chaos, Madrigal Celine, hungry for power in the church, seeks to use the crisis for his own selfish purposes.</description></item><item><title>The Lost Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</guid><description>Game Description In The Lost Village you have to restore a once great sect. You take on the role of the heir to a leader who has returned to an abandoned mountain and is tasked with restoring it to its former glory. The game combines a management simulator with roguelike elements. Gamers will guide students by collecting resources, building structures and cultivating the land. Students have unique personalities and talents, allowing assignments to be specialized.</description></item><item><title>Knowledge, or know Lady</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</guid><description>Game Description Knowledge, or know Lady throws you into the heart of a unique dating simulator. As the only guy at an all-girl university, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself caught up in a whirlwind of romance and college life. Will you succumb to the charms of the beauties around you or forge your own path to become a campus legend? Ladies School Prince unfolds through your eyes, offering a first-person perspective. Your</description></item><item><title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragons-dogma-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragons-dogma-2/</guid><description>Game Description Dragon&amp;rsquo;s Dogma 2 takes players on a single-player adventure, immersing them in an action-packed action RPG where choices define the path. Players are encouraged to customize their experience, from the appearance of their Arisen to strategic decisions in combat and party composition. Throughout the quest, players are accompanied by pawns - mysterious creatures that simulate the multiplayer experience of a single-player adventure, enriching the gameplay with a variety of perspectives.</description></item><item><title>Horizon Forbidden West</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-forbidden-west/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-forbidden-west/</guid><description>Game Description Horizon Forbidden West  continuation of the adventures of the hunter Aloy, from the Nora tribe. In this part, the heroine finds herself on the coast of the former United States, where she will encounter new obstacles and deadly machines. You will have to use your bow and your wards abilities to confront your opponents and find out the secret of the islands. Watching Aloy from a third person, the user navigates the open world, completing main and side quests.</description></item><item><title>Secrets of Grindea</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</guid><description>Game Description Secrets of Grindea is an interesting adventure game in which you will need to take control of a hero and go on a long journey through a huge fantasy world in search of new adventures. The game begins with character generation. You will have to create it, change its appearance using an advanced editor, and then decide on the basic skills. After this, you can begin to explore the world around you.</description></item><item><title>Last Epoch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-epoch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-epoch/</guid><description>Game Description Last Epoch is an action-adventure game with a deep leveling system in a dark style, gameplay repeating the legendary Diablo. The camera view is also taken from there, it is isometric for a better overview of the surrounding areas. The story campaign for one person (multiplayer is not provided) invites you to explore the rich world of Eterra, with various picturesque places and dark dungeons. It contains many different oddities, secrets, many demons and other fiends of hell.</description></item><item><title>Myth of Empires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</guid><description>Game Description The goal of Myth of Empires is to teach the user to fight for their own place in a huge world. The game is positioned as a multiplayer sandbox in which the user creates an Empire, forming troops that participate in massive battles and sieges of cities, and also builds their own fortresses for defense.
The action takes place in the East during the era of antiquity, when many states constantly fought among themselves, which led to chaos, famine and destruction.</description></item><item><title>Nightingale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</guid><description>Game Description Nightingale takes you on a dangerous journey through the fantastical kingdoms of the fairies. As a Realmwalker, you&amp;rsquo;ll explore, craft, build, and fight across a variety of environments, alone or with friends. This open world survival game takes you through a labyrinth of beautiful but treacherous kingdoms. Stranded after the destruction of a network of portals, you must reach Nightingale, the last human bastion. Open portals and travel through wild forests, treacherous swamps and shimmering deserts.</description></item><item><title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</guid><description>Game Description In Smalland: Survive the Wilds the player takes on the role of a hero who has been diminished under unexplained circumstances. The protagonist woke up in the forest, not knowing whether other people had the same fate. With a head full of questions, he begins a struggle whose goal is not only to find out the truth, but, above all, to survive in a new inhospitable world.
The player watches what is happening from the first person.</description></item><item><title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</guid><description>Game Description Granblue Fantasy: Relink - an adventure in the vastness of the Heavenly Kingdom, where islands soar among the vast azure expanses. As the captain of a skyship, you&amp;rsquo;ll embark on a journey full of mystery, magic and camaraderie. Together with your faithful companions, such as the energetic dragon Virn and the mysterious Lyria, you will go to Estalucia - a mythical island shrouded in legends.
You have to assemble a team of four people, which will include a variety of sky wanderers who own unique weapons and fighting styles.</description></item><item><title>GU LONG FENGYUN LU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</guid><description>Game Description GU LONG FENGYUN LU is a massive martial arts RPG based on the classic works of Gu Long, the famous Chinese writer. The plot tells about the turbulent times of the end of the Ming Dynasty, when various heroes and factions fought for power and glory. The main character is Feng Yun, a young martial artist traveling across the country, encountering friends, enemies, love, hate, loyalty and betrayal.</description></item><item><title>Murders on the Yangtze River</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/murders-on-the-yangtze-river/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/murders-on-the-yangtze-river/</guid><description>Game Description Murders on the Yangtze River takes you to early 20th century China. Think &amp;ldquo;Ace Attorney&amp;rdquo; and historical detective. Channel your inner Sherlock Holmes as you unravel a series of mysterious cases along the banks of the legendary Yangtze River. Step into the shoes of John Shen, a law student turned detective. Grief and a thirst for justice force him to return to China after his brother&amp;rsquo;s mysterious death is ruled a suicide.</description></item><item><title>Enshrouded</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</guid><description>Game Description Enshrouded is an exciting game set in the kingdom of Embervale, taking players on an exciting journey through a land once devastated by a devastating magical plague. The user will have to explore the remnants of the lost kingdom, fight mutated creatures and unravel the mysterious secrets of the ancient Flame. One of the distinctive features of the project is the emphasis on the independence of the hero.</description></item><item><title>Palworld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</guid><description>Game Description Palworld offers you to find and use friends as helpers in a huge and dangerous world. The multiplayer survival game has elements of crafting, and the creatures themselves, discovered by the user in the process, become his pet friends, which help him at all stages of the passage, including the ability to move on them, construct buildings, engage in farming, production, and explore dungeons.
The user finds himself in a virtual universe inhabited by bizarre animal creatures, which in this world are simply called Friends.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>Magicraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/magicraft/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/magicraft/</guid><description>Game Description Magicraft throws you into a world overrun by ancient gods. As a lone hero, you wield a legendary staff - your only hope for salvation. This roguelike focuses on spells that can be combined to create devastating effects. The developers themselves admit that the number of possibilities exceeds their own imagination!
The game world is strange and whimsical, filled with unusual creatures and riddled with a ridiculous plot. Magicraft doesn&amp;rsquo;t take itself too seriously, but rather offers a light-hearted adventure with an emphasis on fun and flashy combat.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Slay the Princess is a dark and daring adventure that will put your skills to the ultimate test, combining the genres of psychological horror and dating simulator. Your mission is simple: kill the princess and save the world from destruction. But don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by her charms and promises. She will stop at nothing to stop you from completing your task. Make your way through the dense forest and find the hut at the end of the path.</description></item><item><title>Rus against lizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rusy-protiv-jascherov/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rusy-protiv-jascherov/</guid><description>Game Description Rus vs. Lizards is a game in which users go on a journey to Ancient Rus' - a world plagued by an invasion of lizards and unholy creatures. In this epic adventure, you take on the role of a blessed hero, charged with the sacred duty of protecting the holy places of the Ancestors from the green plague. In the game you will find intense battles with hordes of lizards and other evil spirits, in which you will be able to show your heroic strength in the name of the Ancestors.</description></item><item><title>Starfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starfield/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starfield/</guid><description>Game Description Starfield opens a new chapter in the gaming universe after a quarter-century hiatus. Bethesda, known for such outstanding projects as The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim and Fallout 4, offers an expansive next-generation role-playing game set in outer space. In 2330, humanity expands far beyond the boundaries of our solar system: pioneers colonize distant planets, turning into a space-faring civilization. Join the ranks of Constellation, a group of intrepid space explorers on a quest to find elusive artifacts scattered across the galaxy in Bethesda&amp;rsquo;s most ambitious endeavor to date.</description></item><item><title>The Matchless KungFu</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</guid><description>Game Description The Matchless KungFu immerses users in a world where martial arts are at the forefront. The gamer can choose the path of any warrior he likes and go on a journey through these lands. Be a loner or join a group of like-minded people - you can choose any convenient way. Only the decisions made will shape the characters story, throwing him into different circumstances, giving him complete freedom of action in certain aspects.</description></item><item><title>Sengoku Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Sengoku Dynasty tells the story of difficult life in feudal Japan. To convey everything with maximum accuracy, the developers consulted with a historical group, which provided valuable advice and confirmed records with information about the life of that period. The player will have to become the leader of one of the villages and lead it to prosperity and expansion in one of the ways.
The player will have one, almost abandoned settlement at his disposal, which he will have to restore and provide the inhabitants with everything they need.</description></item><item><title>Baldur's Gate 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldurs-gate-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldurs-gate-3/</guid><description>Game Description Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 is a continuation of the cult turn-based RPG, in which you will take control of a small squad consisting of unique characters. Each party member is of great importance to tactics and represents an individual with his own character, history and abilities. Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 invites you to explore the large open world of the Forgotten Realm.
The plot does not act as a direct continuation of the previous part, however, illithids appear in the narrative - they are also mind flayers.</description></item><item><title>Tale of Immortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tale-of-immortal/</guid><description>Game Description Tale of Immortal, an open-world sandbox deeply rooted in Chinese mythology and cultivation, invites players into an immersive experience where the path to immortality is paved through strategic choices and the conquest of mythical monsters from the Classic of Mountains and Seasons. Your journey as a novice Qi Refinement Stage cultivator begins in Yukong Village. A world filled with unpredictable monsters, mystical kingdoms and treasures waiting in the wings will open before you.</description></item><item><title>Keeper's Toll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</guid><description>Game Description Keeper&amp;rsquo;s Toll is a fun and challenging game that will test the skills of any gamer who enjoys the classic retro time survival genre. Featuring unique dark fantasy elements, the game boasts a carefully crafted blend of skill-based gameplay, roguelike elements, and unique mechanics that set it apart from others in the genre.
Gamers will be able to choose from six different heroes, each with their own defining mechanics, abilities, and meta progression.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-black-grimoire-cursebreaker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-black-grimoire-cursebreaker/</guid><description>Game Description The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker is an immersive, atmospheric role-playing adventure that takes you into the fictional world of Imbertal. The game focuses on classic old-school mechanics, allowing you to venture into a dark and dangerous dark fantasy setting. The main character is a cursed lord named Rothar Aekrest, who must deal with problems on his land, facing various obstacles and participating in difficult combat encounters with monsters.
When going to The Black Grimoire: Cursebreaker, you have to complete a large number of tasks and gain experience that allows you to upgrade and improve your characters characteristics or add new skills and abilities.</description></item><item><title>Hogwarts Legacy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hogwarts-legacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hogwarts-legacy/</guid><description>Game Description Hogwarts Legacy is a role-playing game based on the famous books about the boy wizard &amp;ldquo;Harry Potter&amp;rdquo;. The events of Hogwarts: Legacy take place long before the birth of the main character of the books and films. The story dates back to the 19th century, specifically in the 1800s. The game takes place in the same universe and in the same school, so fans of the original saga will find many references and meet some familiar characters.</description></item><item><title>Lil Gator Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lil-gator-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lil-gator-game/</guid><description>Game Description Lil Gator Game from the first minutes creates a positive atmosphere and invites you to completely immerse yourself in this friendly world. Here, users take on the role of a little crocodile who wants to make new friends. But they need help, so the character will have to get down to business, completing their quests and instructions. And given that the main location in the game is a national park, you will have to spend a lot of time exploring individual areas and finding solutions.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</guid><description>Game Description Mount and Blade 2 Bannerlord is a role-playing game with elements of medieval wars, the action of which takes place 200 years before the start of Part 1. In this sequel you will find an improved combat system and an enlarged game world - Calradia. Fight with hundreds of troops under your command and take direct part in the battles as one of the soldiers. You can storm enemy fortresses and destroy fortifications with siege weapons in Mount &amp;amp; Blade II: Bannerlord.</description></item><item><title>Persona 5 Royal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 5 Royal is the official expansion for the fifth part of the Japanese role-playing video game of the same name, which contains even more unique personas, as well as a lot of interesting quests and items. The plot centers on a seemingly ordinary high school student who goes with his family to Tokyo, where he enrolls in a new school. Soon the main character begins to see inexplicable dreams, in which someone tells the guy that a monstrous catastrophe will befall him in the near future.</description></item><item><title>Vampire Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Survival in the Vampire Survivors universe is based on minimalist gameplay, where you have to move around the map and knock out as much gold as possible. The main task for the protagonist is to advance through the levels generated in roguelight style. You need to try to survive the night, fighting off monsters and higher undead. Vampires will hunt for the protagonist, not giving him the opportunity to rest at a rest or come up with a future plan of action.</description></item><item><title>Elden Ring</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring/</guid><description>Game Description Elden Ring is an open world role-playing game from the creators of Dark Souls and Bloodborne, in collaboration with writer George R.R. Martin. The gameplay is a third-person action RPG where you explore the expanses of a fantasy world, equip yourself with a variety of weapons and fight powerful enemies. In the game, even one enemy poses a serious threat. Battles are based on timing and parries. Carefully study the monsters' patterns to effectively counterattack their attacks.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light 2: Stay Human</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</guid><description>Game Description Dying Light 2: Stay Human starts 15 years after humanity became infected with a terrible virus. Many have turned into zombies who scour in search of living flesh, and the few survivors wage a daily struggle for existence. People are divided into several warring factions, which during the day make forays from shelters to find resources, and at night they hide from bloodthirsty monsters. The world has returned to its primitive state, where everyone fights only for their own lives.</description></item><item><title>Mirror 2: Project X</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror 2: Project X follows the adventures of Dinkudin Naoto, who collaborates with the FBI (Federal Bureau of Research and Conservation). The hero searches for mystical manifestations and otherworldly creatures that sometimes appear in the world. The plot begins with a story with a Demon that infects the body of one of the victims. During the proceedings and investigation of the case, the protagonist will find out the motivations and goals of the creatures in order to make a choice to support or destroy the monster.</description></item><item><title>God of War (2022)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/god-of-war-2022/</guid><description>Game Description God of War 2022 is an action-adventure game with a third-person view. This project is both a sequel to the previous part and a restart of the entire universe of the famous, cult slasher about the adventures of Kratos  a Spartan warrior, the protagonist of all 8 games in the God of War series, fighting against various gods and mythical creatures in a fit of rage and revenge.</description></item><item><title>Monster Hunter Rise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Hunter Rise is a role-playing adventure set in the fictional village of Kamura. The territory is presented in the form of a vast mountainous area with studied hunting equipment and the original culture of the inhabitants. Players will play the role of hunters, and before starting the game they will have to choose one of several types of weapons, armor or special abilities.
The world is filled with ancient ruins, shrines, dungeons and other locations.</description></item><item><title>Gunfire Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunfire-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description The shooter Gunfire Reborn contains elements of a roguelike and role-playing game. The player can choose to control several heroes with individual abilities. The game has a huge amount of randomness, from procedurally generated locations to dropped guns and loot. Gunfire Reborn is designed for both one and a company of up to 4 people.
The game features 100 different types of items. Various mechanics will encourage you to study each fighter presented, who are more or less suitable for a specific situation and location.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Mystia's Izakaya</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Mystia&amp;rsquo;s Izakaya takes gamers to a fictional Japanese town called Gensoke, where the young and very charming owner of the local night izakaya lives. This term usually refers to a night drinking establishment where people gather, usually after a night shift, and drink alcoholic beverages. The protagonist is the beautiful Mistia Lorelei, who has a dream to make the entire establishment the most popular in the city.</description></item><item><title>Firework</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/firework/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/firework/</guid><description>Game Description The dark journey of the boy in Firework allows gamers to find themselves in dangerous environments where they must survive and solve difficult puzzles. The game presents the opportunity to go investigate a mysterious fire that killed many people. The main character, named Lin Lixun, goes to explore the territory where the disaster occurred. In the process of clarifying the circumstances, the young policeman is forced to deal with mysterious phenomena and confusing facts that overlap with each other.</description></item><item><title>Valheim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</guid><description>Game Description Valheim is an open world survival game where you build your own base and fight mythical creatures from Scandinavian folklore. The game takes place in Valheim, the tenth Viking world. The hero&amp;rsquo;s goal is to reach the gates of Valhalla. By killing various monsters and monsters, you earn the blessing of the gods.
The hero will visit various corners of the world: dense forests, snow-capped mountains and much more.</description></item><item><title>OMORI</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/omori/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/omori/</guid><description>Game Description Two realities and only one is true in the game OMORI. A psychological history of surrealism with elements of thriller and horror. The protagonist will have to travel between two dimensions. They are similar, and at the same time radically different. Each reality has its own mysteries and secrets. Explore the new (old) world, make acquaintances with friendly characters who, in another reality, will immediately attack you. Explore the memories of your own path, and finally determine which world is the real reality for you, and which is the other world.</description></item><item><title>Cyberpunk 2077</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyberpunk-2077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyberpunk-2077/</guid><description>Game Description Cyberpunk 2077 is an action role-playing game, the events of which unfold in the futuristic city of Night City, located on the West Coast of the United States. You will play as a protagonist named V (or V). The sex, gender and appearance of the hero must be set independently. Depending on the choice of class, the character&amp;rsquo;s background differs. There are three of them: Nomad, Child of the Street and Corporate.</description></item><item><title>Hades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hades/</guid><description>Game Description In the roguelike Hades you will constantly engage in epic battles. Upgrade new abilities by fighting enemies. Gifts can be acquired by meeting the gods of Olympus, who will be happy to give you a piece of their power. Complete the instructions of Zeus, Athena, or simply get to know them to master new skills or equipment. Every time you meet a new character, you will witness some interesting event.</description></item><item><title>Crusader Kings 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</guid><description>Game Description Crusader Kings 3 is a global strategy that significantly expands the capabilities of the previous part. Crusader Kings 3 covers the time period from 1066 to 1453. Unlike the second part, you wont be able to start the game at any time. The new map stretches from Spain to Burma and Mongolia, and from Scandinavia to Central Africa. The scale of the game is quadrupled. The points on the map represent not only counties, but also baronial possessions.</description></item><item><title>Horizon Zero Dawn Complete Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-zero-dawn-complete-edition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/horizon-zero-dawn-complete-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Horizon Zero Dawn is an action game in the world of a post-apocalyptic future, in which the world is inhabited by robotic dinosaurs that destroyed modern civilization. The few surviving people formed into small primitive tribes and resist mechanical monsters using primitive weapons combined with high technology.
The main character of Horizon Zero Dawn is a girl named Aloy. She was raised by a man named Rast, who is an Outcast.</description></item><item><title>There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/there-is-no-game-wrong-dimension/</guid><description>Game Description There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is a humorous adventure game where you have to click on every element available in the locations. You are taken on an amazing adventure through different video game universes. The visual style of the game is made in a 2D pixel style.
Each of the numerous characters in There Is No Game: Wrong Dimension is voiced and played by professional actors. On your way there are many puzzles that need to be solved in an unconventional way.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 76</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</guid><description>Game Description According to the plot of Fallout 76, the first people came out of shelters after a nuclear war. They set off to explore the Wasteland, where mutants are already lying in wait. The player will be able to visit 6 regions, each of which has its own types of dangerous animals and landscape. Among the scorched desert there are also wooded areas with red trees. What is most surprising is that quite recently the desert territories were inhabited by those who were able to survive the apocalypse on the surface.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-3/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 3 is a continuation of the acclaimed series of shooters, containing tons of loot. The player will take on the role of one of the Vault Hunters and set off to explore the expanses of Pandora. All heroes have their own tree of characteristics, unique abilities and character. The gameplay allows you to go through the adventure solo or enlist the help of friends.
The protagonist of Borderlands 3 learned to climb ledges and make tackles.</description></item><item><title>The Test</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-test/</guid><description>Game Description The Test is a psychological horror with elements of a visual novel, role-playing adventure, and immersive sim with a lot of text monologues inside the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s head. The player gets the opportunity to directly influence what is happening using a decision-making system of varying degrees of importance. The isometric camera allows you to get the best view of the two-dimensional space where all the action of the single-player campaign takes place with a well-developed plot about mental suffering.</description></item><item><title>SenrenBanka</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</guid><description>Game Description SenrenBanka is primarily aimed at anime fans. The project uses the appropriate style (including chibi art) and Japanese voice acting. The plot combines romantic, tragic, mystical and humorous elements. The story revolves around supernatural incidents. A group of young people are trying to hide them from ordinary people.
The premise in SenrenBanka: A Thousand Colors of Love is as follows. A guy named Arichi Masaomi comes to the provincial town of Hoori in the summer.</description></item><item><title>Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-jedi-fallen-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-jedi-fallen-order/</guid><description>Game Description In the epic game Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order you will find amazing adventures, new challenges, modern graphics and high-quality laser sword battles! Immerse yourself in this saga of the Jedi and intergalactic war, in which you will play one of the key roles. The story takes place after Episode III, 5 years after the ominous Order 66. You will take on the role of a young Jedi Padawan who barely managed to escape from a trap created by the Sith.</description></item><item><title>Disco Elysium: The Final Cut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</guid><description>Game Description Disco Elysium is an RPG in which a detective must use his skills to conduct a unique investigation. The player will have to interrogate well-developed characters, investigate murders, and, if desired, take bribes. You can become either the savior of the city or the worst disaster for all humanity. Game Features: Unique branched dialogue system. Wide freedom of choice both in the story narrative and in additional tasks. Well-developed characters with their own stories and personalities.</description></item><item><title>Unheard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unheard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unheard/</guid><description>Game Description Unheard is a well-developed detective simulator with many implemented mechanics aimed at allowing the player to understand the crimes committed in various ways. A team of indie developers worked on the project, with a rather unusual idea and implementation, who decided to use the setting of detective fiction, because the protagonist uses devices that are not available in the real world. The devices make it possible to establish some kind of invisible connection between criminals and lawmen.</description></item><item><title>Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sekiro-shadows-die-twice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sekiro-shadows-die-twice/</guid><description>Game Description Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice is an incredibly challenging action game that makes feudal Japan look dark, burning, and beautiful at the same time. The third-person stealth action game combines the features of RPGs and the themes of Souls games. Well-designed graphics of feudal Japan allow us to plunge into the difficult process of returning our master of the Ashina clan. The leader of the opposition - Genichiro - kidnapped a samurai from Shinobi, and now we must cope with a huge number of his followers in order to save the teacher, master, master and good friend who paid us well in a past life.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-spire/</guid><description>Game Description In Slay the Spire the main task of the gamer is to climb to the upper levels of a tower consisting of many rooms. During the passage, you can have one of 4 characters, collect a collection of cards, defeat intermediate enemies and defeat the main villain. The locations and forks of the tower are constantly changing, the whole process can be divided into three acts and at the end of each of them the main character must defeat the local boss.</description></item><item><title>Kenshi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</guid><description>Game Description Kenshi forces you to survive from the very first minutes of the game. An impressive RPG with an open world and the ability to create your own squad, the remaining player privileges are gradually revealed to us. For example, you can build your own buildings in any location, conquer them from other factions, create your own business, sell goods in peaceful settlements, craft whatever you want, explore the environment and do whatever you want.</description></item><item><title>Assassins Creed Odyssey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-odyssey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-odyssey/</guid><description>Game Description For the first time in the history of the series, you will be able to choose a character for whom you will administer justice and change history. Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed Odyssey is the first slasher RPG in the history of the developers, in which we do not play as an assassin, but choose a real warrior of Ancient Greece! We are offered two characters to choose from: Alexios or Kassandra.</description></item><item><title>SCUM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</guid><description>Game Description SCUM is another survival game set in a completely open world. The developers tried to make the gameplay and the story of the characters so absurd that the very fact of some actions causes disgust. The plot reveals to us a modern society that wants nothing more than to watch the spectacle. The well-known producer TEC1 organized a show with the name - Scam - where people are thrown out in an open location, forced to survive without everything, and after that they are gradually introduced to a series of difficulties: a zombie epidemic, robots, dangerous animals, or money with the promise that once they get out , players will be able to spend them to buy freedom in the new society.</description></item><item><title>MONSTER HUNTER: WORLD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-world/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of MONSTER HUNTER: WORLD has been slightly reworked compared to the previous part. We don&amp;rsquo;t just kill monsters, make new equipment, but now weapons are divided into several classes, and, in fact, at the beginning of the game we are something like a neutral character. In the new ecosystem, hunters have emerged who will create incredibly difficult conditions for the existence of monsters. Dragons, flying dinosaurs (not like dragons), and other creatures inhabit this eco-system.</description></item><item><title>Yakuza 0</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yakuza-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yakuza-0/</guid><description>Game Description As a dialogue-heavy role-playing game that explores a deep story, Yakuza 0 claims to be a game that combines friendship, self-love, and the search for true calling. The Yakuza is the largest mafia group in Japan, which controls everything that can be controlled. Events begin in 1988, when two Yakuza characters - Kazuma Kiryu and Goro Majima - take part in a battle for a small industrial plot in the center of Kamurocho.</description></item><item><title>DARK SOULS: REMASTERED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description DARK SOULS: REMASTERED is an already iconic Japanese action/RPG released in 2011. The development was carried out by From Software. A remastered version was released in May 2018 at the instigation of QLOC. So, what are the acclaimed Dark Souls? Firstly, this is a high-quality action RPG, with a third-person view. At the very beginning, you will need to set a number of characteristics for your character: appearance and class.</description></item><item><title>Conan Exiles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</guid><description>Game Description Conan Exiles is an amazing multiplayer survival game with RPG and action elements. Employees of the Norwegian company Funcom worked on the project. The project was released at the end of spring 2018. Stunning graphics are a rare quality that developers of various MMORPG games pay attention to. But this time everything happened exactly the opposite. Funcom, 10 years before Conan Exiles, had already released a similar game called Age Of Conan.</description></item><item><title>Mirror</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror is a visual novel that perfectly combines erotic content, an RPG component, an interactive plot and battles in which you take a direct part. The whole game is built on the three in a row principle. In the casual combination of characters, you will only take part in the battle on the Match 3 battlefield. That is, you will win if you can score more points. The game features three heroines who will oppose you throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer: Vermintide 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-vermintide-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-vermintide-2/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer: Vermintide 2 is a first-person slasher with abilities, magic, character upgrades, a variety of weapons and meat, combining a unique combat system of 5 different factions. The modernized first part is made on a new graphics engine, allowing us to see every severed limb; look at dead enemies and collect dropped loot around them, not paying attention to graphical inaccuracies.
The plot of Warhammer: Vermintide 2 revolves around Helmgarth Castle, surrounded by a small settlement.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-come-deliverance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-come-deliverance/</guid><description>Game Description The plot of Kingdom Come: Deliverance takes place in a simple European village. We play as the son of a blacksmith. Our name is Henry. The civil war affected not only the political upheaval, but also ordinary villages and people like yours. Friends, family and your entire lineage have been slaughtered by brutal mercenaries in a sinister plot. We miraculously managed to survive, so we take the last sword forged by our father and march against the army of godless people!</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>Finding Paradise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-paradise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-paradise/</guid><description>Game Description In the pixel quest Finding Paradise with an isometric space, there is a corporation - Sigmund Corp. Special agents - Eva Rosalin and Neil Watts - became participants in the realization of the dream of one of the people - Colin Reeds. This man is dying, so our heroes undertake to make his last wishes come true. Arriving at his house, you see how doctors prepare his body and brain, connecting Colin to a special machine that allows you to plunge into his memories and find yourself in an interactive virtual reality.</description></item><item><title>Assassin's Creed Origins</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-origins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/assassins-creed-origins/</guid><description>Game Description The story of the third-person slasher is fully explored in Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed Origins. Only in this part we are told and described in detail how the brotherhood of Assassins was actually created, why the entire caste of killers hid for several hundred years, and how the principles of the brotherhood were formed.
The plot begins with the fact that we kill one of the pharaohs who own an entire pyramid, hundreds of subjects and countless hired killers.</description></item><item><title>Middle-earth: Shadow of War - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The action takes place in the fictional world of the writer Tolkien. The Middle Lands are full of adventures for our player, so the plot unfolds from half of them. Events introduce us to the continuation of the previous part. Talion and Celebrimbor forge a new ring, which Sauron does not know about - he will not be able to influence it. The new ring carries with it another responsibility: in Middle-earth: Shadow of War, Celebrimbor loses his freedom in exchange for a new One Ring.</description></item><item><title>Divinity: Original Sin 2 - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/divinity-original-sin-2-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/divinity-original-sin-2-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description In this game, elves and other heroes gather in one flock. In Divinity: Original Sin 2 - Definitive Edition even Rivellon has undergone significant changes. The developers completely remade the entire game. No one knows where to start.
The graphics in the game became more like realistic ones for some other world. There is nothing superfluous on the screen, and procasts, magical effects and the death of other heroes look better.</description></item><item><title>ARK: Survival Evolved</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</guid><description>Game Description The world of ARK: Survival Evolved is a setting full of dangers, in which not only dinosaurs, but also other creatures will try to kill you. People become especially dangerous. The game does not have any interesting plot, but there is a huge open world in which you have to build your base, hunt with a group of people (your friends), attack, defend, make weapons and explore the area.</description></item><item><title>NieR: Automata</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</guid><description>Game Description An open-world action-adventure game, NieR: Automata tells the story of androids 2B, 9S and A2 as they battle a dystopia created by powerful machines. All of humanity was evicted from their planet by mechanical creatures that arrived from another world.
In an attempt to retake the Earth from aliens, people send combat robots to somehow resist the invaders. This must be the final attempt, the last hope to get your home back.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim Special Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim-special-edition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim-special-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Skyrim has become one of the favorite games on two continents of our planet. The first/third person slasher captivated players not only with its open-world RPG content, but also with its graphics, sounds, characters, features, and, of course, dragons.
Our character in The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim Special Edition begins the same story, but you immediately notice that everything around him is completely different. If in the original version of the game we move along a snowy road, now the colors of the autumn forest prevail, maintaining the same atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve Together is a survival simulator in an unknown world, where our character, pre-selected in the editor, wakes up and immediately goes to look for firewood, because Maxwell said so. The game is cooperative, since the story passage is divided into 2 parts. The first is survival. It is built on three phases of the day: day, evening and night.
During the day, your character calmly survives, collects items, crafts new ones, eats and carries out orders for Maxwell.</description></item><item><title>DARK SOULS 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-3/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of DARK SOULS 3 provides all the same opportunities that were in the second part. For us, a third-person slasher with elements of stealth and survival remained at the same level in terms of combat, but the entire combat system was made more dynamic. So much so that sometimes we dont have time to jump away to recharge our skill, and they already kill us. The real hassle and face of the game genre is difficulty at every turn.</description></item><item><title>Stardew Valley</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardew-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardew-valley/</guid><description>Game Description Stardew Valley is a sandbox simulator with pixel graphics and multi-platform support, but with a well-thought-out system for earning money and maintaining game balance for the player. The beginning of the game shows how our hero first comes to an abandoned farm, which he received from a deceased relative. Since the protagonist does not mind making money by planting and selling vegetables and fruits, he decides not to sell the farm, but to start equipping it.</description></item><item><title>Grim Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grim-dawn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grim-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description The gloomy dawn in Grim Dawn showed that the fabric of the created universe was too weak, so Cairn accepted robbers, bandits, magicians and a bunch of all kinds of creatures and undead into its embrace. Dark times have come to the territory of Cairn. But after that, people did not give up trying to attack their enemies, and called aliens into the world. They opened portals for them and let in several individuals to receive ether.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Our task in Rise of the Tomb Raider is to get ahead of your enemies, go on your first expedition and watch interactive videos, of which there are at least 1.5 hours of gameplay in the game. Lara Croft goes to the unknown world of the city of Kitezh. A secret organization called Trinity is also heading there. The principle of the game about Lara is an adventure game mixed with the adventure romance of the first journey, in which we kill with a bow, collect important items, and sometimes survive in the wild.</description></item><item><title>XCOM 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</guid><description>Game Description Twenty years ago, people signed an act of complete surrender of the earth to the aliens. Another civilization has shown that there is no hope for salvation, and therefore alien invaders have taken over the entire planet. At the beginning of XCOM 2 we are shown a video from the current ruler of the planet (in fact, this is a staged, drawn character, he is controlled by aliens), who says that today is the day when the aliens captured us, and the earth plunged into peace; Today we celebrate 20 years of freedom.</description></item><item><title>Darkest Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Turn-based strategy with a side view - Darkest Dungeon - developed in a dark style and with rogue-like elements. A huge number of characters will not let you calm down until everyone on the playing field creates the perfect combination for victory. Each battle with opponents is a fascinating tactical adventure, where victory is 80% knowledge of the game and 20% knowledge of logic.
Your characters are ordinary people with extraordinary health.</description></item><item><title>The Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</guid><description>Game Description The island on which The Isle takes place has a rich and varied environment that is randomly generated. All artifacts, items and events will be located in different places with each new launch. Players must team up to effectively explore the area, which contains many secrets, including various quest items that further advance the plot. The map contains an area of 16x16 square kilometers. Multiplayer survival game The Isle allows you to play with three different factions in three different modes:</description></item><item><title>Just Cause 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</guid><description>Game Description Just Cause 3 is a continuation of the famous franchise about the adventures of a specially trained agent named Rico Rodriguez. This part of the series did not deviate from the style and genre of previous games in the universe where the mercenary nicknamed Scorpio lives. The end of the trilogy is made with the same driving action, open world, a large number of tricks and devices available in the protagonists arsenal, and an adventure plot in which the fate of an entire state will be at stake.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</guid><description>Game Description Fallout 4 is a sequel to the famous role-playing game series in a post-apocalyptic setting. The player wakes up from cryosleep and discovers that he is the only survivor of Vault 111. Having made it to the surface, he finds himself in the Wasteland - a world destroyed by nuclear war. The gameplay includes: a free open world with hundreds of locations to explore, a huge number of NPCs, companions and quests, as well as interaction with many factions, including the Institute, the Brotherhood of Steel, the Minutemen and agents of the Underground; S.</description></item><item><title>Undertale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undertale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/undertale/</guid><description>Game Description In the universe of Undertale, a role-playing game with pixel graphics, a war broke out between humans and monsters. The people won and locked all the creatures from the other world in an underground wasteland. The underground world of the game tells the story of one boy who finds himself in a closed space with monsters. 7 magicians guarded the dungeon area using barrier spells, but somehow a baby got there, for whom we have to play.</description></item><item><title>The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-3-dikaja-ohota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-3-dikaja-ohota/</guid><description>Game Description The legendary third-person slasher series - The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt, which tells us the story of Geralt of Rivia, who becomes one of the few characters in the central series of action-packed books. We start the game remembering the events of the second part. But let&amp;rsquo;s not talk about them. Our hero is a born killer, capable of killing and ending the lives of thieves, criminals, assassins, kings, leaders, generals and monsters living throughout the map.</description></item><item><title>Dark Souls 2: Scholar of the First Sin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-2-scholar-of-the-first-sin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-souls-2-scholar-of-the-first-sin/</guid><description>Game Description DARK SOULS 2: Scholar of the First Sin takes the dark atmosphere and addictive gameplay to a whole new level of quality. As before, you, in the role of a wandering soul, have to wander through a dark and mysterious world, use tactics during battle even with simple opponents, and always remain on guard, since danger comes from everywhere - these are the rules of this eerie world.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</guid><description>Game Description Elite Dangerous is an online multiplayer game, the third part of the &amp;ldquo;Elite&amp;rdquo; franchise, which began in 1984. The player is given complete freedom to explore and travel, and has the opportunity to influence the storyline. The action takes place thousands of years later in the distant future on the territory of several million star galaxies. Most of the stars, planets, asteroids and other cosmic bodies that exist in the real world.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</guid><description>Game Description A terrible virus grows into a global problem in Dying Light. Starting from the city of Harran in Latin America, the infection is decimating the entire world, turning those infected into the walking dead. The hero must survive in such circumstances and try to correct the situation. As an undercover operative, Kyle Crane receives his most important assignment. He needs to find a guy named Suleiman in order to take away from him an important file that he stole.</description></item><item><title>Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/</guid><description>Game Description The main character - Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor - will fight Sauron and avenge his family. One day, Sauron kidnapped Talion to sacrifice him and summon Celebrimbor, the spirit of the main elf in the world of the Lord of the Rings. However, this spirit helps Talion to resurrect, gives him new abilities and sends him into battle. The protagonist&amp;rsquo;s enemies are Sauron and his dark lords: the Hammer, the Black Hand and the Tower.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-online/</guid><description>Game Description The game The Elder Scrolls Online offers you to go through a number of locations for several warring factions, playing both alone and in real time with other players. The plot tells how Molag Bal, known as the Prince of Violence, decides to take over the entire kingdom of Tamriel and enslave ordinary citizens. The gamer will have to face the forces of evil and defeat him.
Throughout the game world of The Elder Scrolls Online, there are several factions available, each of which is endowed with certain properties.</description></item><item><title>South Park: The Stick of Truth (game)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-igra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-igra/</guid><description>Game Description The funny events of South Park take us into the world of the game South Park: The Stick of Truth, where we play the role of a newcomer who has ambitions and a desire to build a circle of friends in a new city. As soon as we enter the game, famous fourth graders start swinging swords and casting random spells. One of these brings chaos and evil into this world, which we have to cope with.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Rush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Rush is a project in the &amp;ldquo;tower defense&amp;rdquo; genre, in the style of the Middle Ages, interspersed with magic, creatures that do not exist in real life, like trolls, and real-time control of heroes with a choice of the direction and course of their attacks. This game received recognition on many platforms and later reached personal computers.
The gameplay is standard for the genre, the advantage over other projects is the refined balance and exciting, moderately difficult levels that challenge and force you to change battle tactics and constantly be on the alert.</description></item><item><title>Project Zomboid</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</guid><description>Game Description Project Zomboid is a cross-platform game in which we will have to find a house, equip it, and start surviving in a world where a zombie apocalypse has recently occurred. We are located in Knox County. The latest epidemic infected more than 90% of the district&amp;rsquo;s residents, and they all became zombies. Difficult conditions will force us to survive, stock up on food, water, weapons and all available supplies in order to simply survive.</description></item><item><title>PayDay 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</guid><description>Game Description Re-join the PayDay 2 gang as Dallas, Hoxton, Chains or Wolfe, who have come to Washington to rob and make a lot of money. Put the mask on your favorite hero and set off to carry out your next crime, in which you will need to overcome many obstacles before reaching your goal.
Now you will have a wide variety of contracts to choose from, from which you can choose any one.</description></item><item><title>BioShock Infinite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bioshock-infinite/</guid><description>Game Description BioShock Infinite is a first-person shooter with multiple mechanics of a role-playing adventure in the style of science fiction and steampunk. The game will take place in 1912 in an alternative universe, in the flying city of the United States of America - Columbia. You need to control the private detective Booker Devitt, who has a task to find a cute girl named Elizabeth. Immediately after it is found, the main characters find themselves in the very epicenter of the war.</description></item><item><title>Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Tomb Raider is a restart of the series telling about the adventures of Lara Croft. The ship on which the girl&amp;rsquo;s crew was sailing was wrecked. On the island she is captured and left tied in a cave. The adventurer frees herself from her bonds and goes to look for the crew members.
The player can choose the difficulty, which affects the course of battles. A vast world opens up before the gamer, divided into several locations.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter - Far Cry 3 - will teach you how to survive in the wild conditions of the open world, more or less value relationships with good people, and show you what real madness is. The series rewarded us with enough action, showing that a huge arsenal of weapons is just part of what can be given to players in return for their desire to enjoy a completely open world and a good story.</description></item><item><title>Castle Crashers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</guid><description>Game Description Castle Crashers is an arcade action game in which players will take control of powerful characters and fight monsters. Create a squad by choosing from 25 characters to fight your way through castles against your enemies. Compete with other users or monsters living throughout the continent. The plot will unfold at a ball in the king&amp;rsquo;s castle. During the fun, an evil sorcerer stole a precious magic stone and four princesses, who must be rescued by the knights and fight the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/borderlands-2/</guid><description>Game Description Borderlands 2 is a shooter with a view from the perspective of the protagonist and leveling up abilities and passive improvements, as in the role-playing adventure genre. A direct continuation of the story of the original game. The main differences from the first part are a greater emphasis on the plot component and the addition of a more advanced weapon editor with many possible modifications that open up as you progress.</description></item><item><title>Saints Row: The Third</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saints-row-the-third/</guid><description>Game Description The Third Street Saints are a large and large group in the universe of the game Saints Row: The Third. The third-person shooter with its crazy plots gave the game&amp;rsquo;s heroes their own brand of sneakers, a carbonated drink and a logo, and now they have to fight the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crime syndicate, whose people are scattered around the world and do their work in the shadows. Since the main characters have long captured Stillwater, the Syndicate demands offerings from them in the form of tribute for the criminal leadership.</description></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim/</guid><description>Game Description The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim is rightfully considered a legendary game. Even now, many years after its release, it continues to conquer new users who come to it based on recommendations or out of their own interest. In the role of a warrior named Dovahkiin, the gamer will find himself in a huge world full of mysteries, unexpected turns and battles.
Here it is not possible to follow the path of a straightforward passage.</description></item><item><title>To the Moon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/to-the-moon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/to-the-moon/</guid><description>Game Description To the Moon is a philosophical story about two doctors - Eva Rosalina and Neil Watts from the Sigmund organization. The heroes make a tragic journey through the memories of a dying man. In this way they are trying to fulfill his last will, the essence of which is to let the person live his life again.
The dying person remembers the new life that he sees at death before leaving this world.</description></item><item><title>Terraria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</guid><description>Game Description Terraria is a simulator of construction, life, survival, an interesting storyline and everything that could be combined into a game with the Sand Box style. Simple 8-bit graphics take us into a randomly generated world generated by the game itself. The open map is almost endless if you dig deep into the world, but you will be stopped by armies of monsters or underground knights. Terraria is not as simple as it seems.</description></item><item><title>The Witcher 2 Assassins of Kings</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-2-ubijcy-korolej/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vedmak-2-ubijcy-korolej/</guid><description>Game Description The computer game &amp;ldquo;The Witcher 2 Assassins of Kings&amp;rdquo; is an expanded limited edition of the impressive continuation of the 2008 giant of the world of role-playing video games &amp;ldquo;The Witcher&amp;rdquo;. The development of this project was carried out by the famous studio CD PROJEKT RED. The announcement came in May 2011. Geralt of Rivia is the greatest of the line of witchers, wielding a sword better than others, almost the only one who can resist the forces of darkness, while being something between an ordinary person and a monster.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade: Warband</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</guid><description>Game Description Mount &amp;amp; Blade: Warband is a standalone add-on that brings many improvements and innovations to the game. New textures, object and character models, as well as sophisticated visualization settings. Change FSAA anti-aliasing, tone mapping and other effects in the settings. Modernized animations, improved combat system and the spirit of the heroes. People will flee if they are in imminent danger or, conversely, fight to the last if their morality is high.</description></item><item><title>VED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ved/</guid><description>Game Description VED is an action role-playing game focused on story and turn-based combat. The gameplay contains roguelike elements. The game involves exploring a mysterious island full of monsters and dangerous creatures. In the world of the game, the magic of witches operates - powerful creatures with forbidden knowledge.
The protagonist of the game is a hero named Cyrus. He comes to Micropolis with the hope of finding a new life.</description></item><item><title>7 Days to Die</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</guid><description>Game Description In 7 Days to Die you will need the ability to loot, kill other players, take loot, build buildings, craft items, shoot accurately and keep track of time, because in the open world there is a night in which zombies and other undead sharpen their attention . A horror first-person shooter that combines city building, multiplayer, survival, tower defense and character leveling in an RPG style. Despite the fact that a severe epidemic has struck the world, you will be able to kill animals to take their meat and skin.</description></item><item><title>Alaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Action RPG Alaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms takes the player into the magical Middle Ages. The story begins in the Valley of Storms - a place where four legendary peoples intersect: Humans, Elves, Dwarves and Orcs. It is here that the cruel god Alaloth is imprisoned. From the very kingdom of the dead, he poisons all kingdoms with his evil. Soon monsters, storms, diseases and mighty dragons will strike this world.</description></item><item><title>Blade and Sorcery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blade-and-sorcery/</guid><description>Game Description Blade and Sorcery is a first-person fantasy action game focused on realistic hand-to-hand combat physics. You play as a hero who knows how to fight with melee and long-range weapons, as well as magical abilities. There are three classes to choose from: Warrior, Ranger and Wizard. The gameplay is adapted for virtual reality helmets Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift and Windows Mixed Reality.
The gameplay is based on body physics and fair hitboxes.</description></item><item><title>Brotato</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</guid><description>Game Description In the shooter Bratato you have to take control of a potato using a variety of guns while fighting alien creatures. The gameplay includes roguelite genre elements. Locations are procedurally generated, and each run can take up to 30 minutes of real time. There are dozens of types of weapons and additional items of equipment to choose from, allowing you to progress at your own pace and combine the effects of items.</description></item><item><title>Dave The Diver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dave-the-diver/</guid><description>Game Description Dave The Diver - a sea adventure about a diver named Dave. Events take place in a mysterious place called the Blue Hole. During the day, the protagonist explores the ocean, diving to the very bottom in search of treasures, and at night he manages a sushi restaurant. Dave is partnered with 3 charismatic friends to help him on his adventures. Each character has an individual character, introducing dynamics into the relationships between the characters.</description></item><item><title>It's Only Money</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-only-money/</guid><description>Game Description It&amp;rsquo;s Only Money will immerse gamers in the realistic story of a resident of the underworld, who, by order of the mayor of Rockhaven, was thrown into a huge pit. But don&amp;rsquo;t despair! Together with other inhabitants of the underground, you can return to the surface and begin your path to wealth and power. You must steal from the rich, fight tycoons, and regain control of the city block by block.</description></item><item><title>Legend of Mortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</guid><description>Game Description In Legend of Mortal you have to become a nobody in the Tang Man sector. Not a prophetic hero, not a legendary warrior - you&amp;rsquo;re just trying to survive in a world on the edge of the abyss. But even lowlifes have it tough, right? This is what Legend of Mortal is all about: your decisions determine the fate of you and those around you. Think of it this way: every meeting, every battle, every seemingly insignificant conversation is a twist in the kaleidoscope.</description></item><item><title>OneShot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oneshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oneshot/</guid><description>Game Description OneShot is an adventure puzzle game with Metroidvania elements. As Niko, you interact with both the character and the world. The gameplay invites you to go through an inventive quest in which you need to find a variety of objects, combining them with each other and using them on the environment, which will allow you to advance through the plot. Stylistically, OneShot is a 2D game from a top-down perspective.</description></item><item><title>Persona 4 Golden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 4 Golden is a role-playing game about a group of friends who are able to summon demons from the other world. To do this, it is enough to shoot yourself in the temple. The events take place in the small Japanese town of Inaba. The children in Persona 4 are teenagers going through puberty. The heroes are investigating a mysterious series of murders.
The gameplay of Persona 4 Golden contains elements of a visual novel.</description></item><item><title>Shin Megami Tensei V: Vengeance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shin-megami-tensei-v-vengeance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shin-megami-tensei-v-vengeance/</guid><description>Game Description Shin Megami Tensei V: Vengeance throws you headlong into a deserted Tokyo. Remember that school life? Gone. It was replaced by Daath - a nightmare kingdom infested with demons. You, an ordinary teenager, in one minute turn into Nakhobino - non-human and non-demon. With a mysterious savior at your side, you navigate the treacherous landscape of Da&amp;rsquo;ath, caught between warring gods and demonic tyrants vying for dominance.
This expanded re-release offers a buffet of options.</description></item><item><title>Soulmask</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</guid><description>Game Description Soulmask is a mystical twist on the survival genre. Gamers eschew the usual &amp;ldquo;rags&amp;rdquo; and instead awaken clutching an ancient mask after a near-death experience. This relic is more than just a creepy wall decoration, it&amp;rsquo;s a game changer. Angry weather and wild animals won&amp;rsquo;t be your only problem. Soulmask features a vast open world that you must navigate in order to survive. Gathering resources is a must, but you can&amp;rsquo;t do it alone.</description></item><item><title>Starbound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</guid><description>Game Description Starbound is a 2D side-scrolling indie RPG adventure with graphics that reference the classic 8-bit titles of the last century. The project has become widespread thanks to the ability to play with a friend in co-op mode on different platforms, as well as a well-developed system of achievements and rewards that motivate you to improve your own skills and collect all kinds of items for crafting and collecting. The surrounding world is presented in the form of open territories, where there are no prohibitions on colonizing unknown planets or performing secondary tasks; you can even not touch the story campaign at all.</description></item><item><title>Wayfinder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayfinder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayfinder/</guid><description>Game Description Wayfinder is an online action role-playing adventure game in which gamers become Wayfinders, using unique abilities to fight the hostile force that has taken over their world. The game emphasizes co-op, allowing users to team up with friends to enhance their abilities and manage their adventures. The world of Evenor, in which the action takes place, has been destroyed, and gamers will have to navigate it, collecting valuable materials and creating items that will help them in their search.</description></item></channel></rss>