<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Arcade on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcade/</link><description>Recent content in Arcade on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dungeon Clawler</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Clawler brings a fresh twist to the roguelike formula. It combines the familiar thrills of dungeon crawling with claw machine mechanics that put a twist on traditional gameplay. You navigate treacherous environments, but instead of directly grabbing weapons and armor, you rely on the claw to get you the loot you need. This adds strategic thinking, because every item you take out of the car can play a decisive role in the next battle or encounter.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Bullet Runner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</guid><description>Game Description The dynamic shootouts inBullet Runner show the adventures of a pixelated man who is forced to resist against a crowd of evil opponents. The game is a top-down action shooter where you have to fight with various opponents. The project is filled with fast and active gameplay, where users can test the speed of their reaction to current events. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to move around the map and shoot enemies using a wide arsenal of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Social Soccer 25</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-25/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-25/</guid><description>Game Description Sociable Soccer 25 brings a new level of excitement to the world of soccer video games. It&amp;rsquo;s an adventure game that stands out in a crowded market by offering fast-paced, arcade-style gameplay that keeps users on their toes. Gone are the days of overly complex management; The title allows gamers to immerse themselves in the action without requiring a complex learning curve. Once you start, you&amp;rsquo;re ready to hit the field, and whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned gamer or just picking up a controller for the first time, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly get hooked.</description></item><item><title>Shave and Stuff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</guid><description>Game Description InShave and Stuff, gamers find themselves in a lively and practical simulator, where two roles come to the fore - a hairdresser and a tattoo artist. The title combines hairdressing and paint work, which promotes creativity and experimentation. Whether performing precision cutting tasks or plunging into the complex world of body art, users are immersed in a world of tools, techniques and client preferences. A constant flow of tasks and light humor provide the basis for an original approach to customization and self-expression.</description></item><item><title>Tetris Forever</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-forever/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-forever/</guid><description>Game Description Tetris Forever marks a milestone in the history of one of the most famous puzzle games, celebrating the 40th anniversary of Tetris. The collection contains more than 15 different versions, from early versions for Electronika 60 in 1984 to more recent ones, such as Hatris and Super Bombliss DX1, which many users may not have encountered before. The inclusion of these lesser-known games is a treat for those who are passionate about the evolution of Tetris and want to explore its varied history.</description></item><item><title>XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</guid><description>Game Description XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION transports gamers to a high-octane world where the classic game of pinball meets hostile forces for an intense blend of arcade action. The adventure follows the path of its predecessor, Demon&amp;rsquo;s Tilt, and brings familiar gameplay mechanics while adding many new challenges. Each new table offers a new set of obstacles, targets and bonuses that force users to be on their guard. Pinball here is not just about throwing a ball, it is a battle against time, enemies and your own reflexes.</description></item><item><title>Locuras en el Banverso</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</guid><description>Game Description Locuras en el Banaverso is a single-player platformer that takes gamers on a chaotic adventure through a bizarre multiverse. The game follows the eccentric YouTuber El Bananero, who not only plays the role of the main character, but also voices him. From the very beginning, El Bananero finds himself in an unexpected situation - he is kidnapped by none other than Santa Claus and his gang of henchmen. As fate would have it, the kidnapping turns into an escape through a portal that leads him into the depths of the multiverse.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>Vengeance Hunters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</guid><description>Game Description Vengeance Hunters is a side-scrolling beat-&amp;rsquo;em-up that captures the essence of classic arcade action. Here users can choose one of several characters, each of which has different abilities and fighting styles. These choices play an important role in how gamers approach gaming challenges. Going through various stages, users encounter many enemies, each of which has unique behavior and attack style. With a variety of characters, gamers will be able to find the fighting style that suits their preferences.</description></item><item><title>Speedollama</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</guid><description>Game Description Speedollama is a fast-paced platform shooter that takes gamers into a world where llamas battle an army of alpacas. The unusual premise draws users into a chaotic world where humor and action collide in the most unexpected ways. The goal is simple: control a llama equipped with a mining machine and destroy waves of alpaca enemies. The title features a vibrant environment filled with quirky characters and varied challenges, making every moment exciting.</description></item><item><title>Tech Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Tech Store Simulator immerses gamers in the fast-paced world of tech retail, giving them hands-on experience in running their own electronics store. The title&amp;rsquo;s focus is on strategic decision-making, requiring users to balance inventory management with customer satisfaction. Gamers will have to navigate the ins and outs of running a successful tech business, from stocking shelves with the latest gadgets to setting competitive prices.
Hiring and managing staff is another key aspect of the game to keep the store running smoothly and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Victory Heat Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Victory Heat Rally is a retro racing game inspired by arcade games of the last century, such as Hang-On and OutRun. You have to take control of small cars to rush along various difficult tracks at high speed. The gameplay is hardcore and pays homage to the classic games of yesteryear.
To fully master the mechanics of Victory Heat Rally, you will need to learn how to glide around the track, take corners correctly, and feel the road.</description></item><item><title>Iron Meat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</guid><description>Game Description Iron Meat is a dynamic platformer made in the style of arcade shooters of the last century. The game takes place on Mars, when a group of scientists disappeared from radar without a trace. The case is entrusted to a member of an elite squad who goes in search of missing people. He must find out what really happened and who is behind this mysterious event.
The gameplay takes inspiration from classic action games such as Contra.</description></item><item><title>Halls of Torment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</guid><description>Game Description Halls of Torment invites you into the world of terrifying monsters in this unique action game with roguelite elements, where you will face new challenges and dangers in each game. Dive into the dark and ruthless dungeons where the lords of the underworld await you. Find treasures and magical artifacts, and assemble a team of heroes who will help you defeat the horrors emanating from the depths of the earth.</description></item><item><title>The Karate Kid: Street Rumble</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</guid><description>Game Description The Karate Kid: Street Rumble is a beat &amp;rsquo;em up title that immerses you in the world of the cult trilogy. Users step into the shoes of characters such as Daniel LaRusso, Mr. Miyagi, Ali Mills and Kumiko as they battle through various levels inspired by the films. The game has a side-scrolling format in which players face waves of enemies, including famous antagonists such as Johnny Lawrence, John Croesus and Terry Silver.</description></item><item><title>Judero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/judero/</guid><description>Game Description Judero immerses you in the world of strategic decisions and tactical battles. The title combines elements of role-playing and strategy, requiring gamers to go through various challenges and opponents. Users must manage resources, create alliances and make important decisions that will affect the outcome of their journey. In Judero, users encounter a variety of characters, each with unique abilities and history. These characters can be recruited into the player&amp;rsquo;s team, giving them various tactical advantages in battle.</description></item><item><title>Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</guid><description>Game Description Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines is a 2D action platformer that follows the adventures of Pablo and Luna. Users move through different dimensions, using unique abilities to overcome obstacles and enemies. It combines swinging, jumping and explosions to provide dynamic gameplay. In the title, gamers alternate between the characters Pablo and Luna. Pablo uses a grappling hook to progress through levels, while Luna brings her own set of skills to the table.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>I Am Your Beast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</guid><description>Game Description I Am Your Beast is not your average shooter. This narrative-driven game throws you headlong into a brutal conflict with the shadowy organization you once worked for. You play as Alphonse Harding, a former operative who has been lured back into the world of underground warfare. Survival and thinking quickly are key. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to navigate treacherous terrain, dodging and fighting enemies in a high-stakes chase.
Forget about going with guns at the ready.</description></item><item><title>Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</guid><description>Game Description Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland is a new action-platformer that brings beloved characters from the 1990s Nickelodeon series into a vibrant, imaginative world. Together with Tommy, Chucky, Phil and Lil, users will go on an adventure inspired by their favorite video game character, Reptar. The title features a unique co-op design that allows gamers to form teams and complete various levels located in the Pickles&amp;rsquo; home. The gameplay of Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland revolves around exploration and teamwork.</description></item><item><title>Guns And Draguns</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</guid><description>Game Description Guns And Draguns is a top-down co-op shooter that plunges gamers into a dangerous fantasy dungeon. Here users will have to go through various levels, destroying fantasy monsters with weapons. The main goal is to defeat the final boss, but along the way there are enemies and obstacles that require strategic teamwork and cooperation. Gamers can choose one of seven unique characters, each of which has its own abilities.</description></item><item><title>Smells Like a Mushroom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</guid><description>Game Description Smells Like a Mushroom is a sci-fi third-person shooter that takes gamers on a journey through the Milky Way. At the center is an invasion of creatures known as Magic Mushrooms. Users take on the role of Carrotado, a brave character tasked with preventing disaster. The gameplay includes platformer and shooter mechanics, and missions take place on various planets in the solar system.
Smells Like a Mushroom&amp;rsquo;s narrative is driven by an absurd story and features both single-player and co-op modes.</description></item><item><title>Call of Sentinels</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Sentinels plunges you headlong into an epic struggle against the forces of darkness. Choose your champion from a growing list, each with unique skills and fighting styles. Hone your combat skills against the relentless hordes in the Arena, or take on dangerous journeys across varied landscapes in Campaign. Unleash devastating combos and master tactical maneuvers to defeat treacherous enemies and colossal bosses. Each victory unlocks valuable upgrades, expanding the hero&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and shaping his legend.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Jam Showdown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Jam Showdown is an adrenaline-pumping off-road racing experience that is sure to get your heart racing. Gamers can get behind the wheel of iconic monster trucks and compete in a variety of challenging environments. From dirt tracks to stadiums, the game offers a variety of racing arenas. The project has ten different modes and is designed for users of any level of training. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned veteran or just a new rider, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games&amp;rsquo; level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>Nova Drift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</guid><description>Game Description Nova Drift is a top-down action RPG adventure. The gamer has the opportunity to test his strength in piloting a space fighter, forced to fight enemies that are superior in numbers and firepower. The spaceship uses unusual technologies; it is created using biomechanics, which means that it seems to be alive and is constantly changing both in appearance and in terms of available weapons. Thanks to the addition of artificial intelligence trained in procedural random generation, the developers from a small indie formation were able to achieve almost endless replayability.</description></item><item><title>Balatro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</guid><description>Game Description Balatro - the word &amp;ldquo;poker&amp;rdquo; crackles with energy, whispering promises of high stakes and cunning deals. This poker roguelike beckons players into a deck-building odyssey where bluffing becomes the spell and chips become your lifeblood. Forget about limping into pots with low pairs. Here you create powerful synergies by weaving intricate combinations that unleash explosive power. Valid poker hands dance with unique wild cards, their abilities changing the course of the game like a magician.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor is not your average survival game, but a single-player, addictive auto-shooting game that is sure to keep you on your toes. As a lone dwarf, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to use every weapon in your arsenal to fight off waves of deadly aliens while earning riches and unlocking powerful upgrades.
But don&amp;rsquo;t think this will be an easy task. You will have to face the harsh and unforgiving landscape of the planet Hoxes, and only your wits and weapons can protect you.</description></item><item><title>Tekken 8</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</guid><description>Game Description Tekken 8 is a continuation of the cult fighting game, directly continuing the story of the previous part. In the sequel, many beloved heroes return, and new fighters are introduced. A full-fledged story campaign is presented, telling the dramatic story of Jin Kazama&amp;rsquo;s family. In addition, you will find many different modes, including multiplayer battles, various tests, local co-op, the ability to customize fighters, etc.
The gameplay of Tekken 8 is based on a complex combat system based on memorizing combinations and timings of opponents.</description></item><item><title>Brotato</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</guid><description>Game Description In the shooterBratato you have to take control of a potato using a variety of guns while fighting alien creatures. The gameplay includes roguelite genre elements. Locations are procedurally generated, and each run can take up to 30 minutes of real time. There are dozens of types of weapons and additional items of equipment to choose from, allowing you to progress at your own pace and combine the effects of items.</description></item><item><title>Keeper's Toll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</guid><description>Game Description Keeper&amp;rsquo;s Toll is a fun and challenging game that will test the skills of any gamer who enjoys the classic retro time survival genre. Featuring unique dark fantasy elements, the game boasts a carefully crafted blend of skill-based gameplay, roguelike elements, and unique mechanics that set it apart from others in the genre.
Gamers will be able to choose from six different heroes, each with their own defining mechanics, abilities, and meta progression.</description></item><item><title>Crab Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Crab Champions is one of those projects where the gamer is given control of an extraordinary hero. As you can guess from the name, the characters of the game are crabs. The setting is tropical islands - the player will be surrounded by palm trees, sand, ocean, stones and exotic animals. And also other crabs, armed to the teeth. Crab Champions can be played in three different modes: Co-op.</description></item><item><title>Vampire Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Survival in theVampire Survivors universe is based on minimalist gameplay, where you have to move around the map and knock out as much gold as possible. The main task for the protagonist is to advance through the levels generated in roguelight style. You need to try to survive the night, fighting off monsters and higher undead. Vampires will hunt for the protagonist, not giving him the opportunity to rest at a rest or come up with a future plan of action.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm Doctor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</guid><description>Game Description Rhythm Doctor is an indie game in which you need to treat patients to the rhythm of music. The music in the game has healing properties. Each patient has unusual problems based on music theory: polyrhythms, hemiols, atonality, syncopation, etc. Rhythm Doctor helps you learn music theory through gameplay. The game contains: more than 20 levels with their own stories; each chapter is a rhythmic concept; many doctors and unique patients; single and cooperative mode; about 50 different visual effects and backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>Muse Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Muse Dash is a dynamic rhythm game in anime style, where you will visit many colorful locations, dance to the rhythm of fiery songs and send enemies into outer space. At the center of the story are three charismatic beauties. Having chosen one of the heroines, you need to fight with various creatures in the rhythm of the dance. The action will take place on a colorful background accompanied by dynamic dance music.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the average ratings for the 10th part of the franchise,Mortal Kombat 11 became a continuation of the story, and the developers tried to improve and add a lot of new things to players. The eleventh fighting game in the Mortal Kombat universe has new gameplay, plot, graphics, and character relationships that reveal the story as it progresses. We arrive in the world after the defeat of Shinnok, who was defeated by Cassie Cage.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>TEKKEN 7</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</guid><description>Game Description TEKKEN 7 is a side-scrolling 3D fighting game that tells the true story of the Mishima clan&amp;rsquo;s feud. In the storyline we learn why Heitachi killed his wife, for what reasons Kazuya Mishima survived. The basis of the game&amp;rsquo;s action is a fighting game based on love, family relationships with friendly fights.
Each battle in Tekken 7 is a separate branch in the plot, so after the end of the battle (victory in it), we see a small interactive video of the creation of the entire universe, Kazuya growing up, and the formation of the Mishima clan.</description></item><item><title>Broforce</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/broforce/</guid><description>Game Description Broforce is a powerful paramilitary organization that is called upon when the world is in danger due to an excessive number of evil forces. Take control of dozens of different brothers to counter terrorist attacks and save civilians. Destroy your opponents with napalm, shooting, lightning and other various character skills.
Broforce is a 2D shooter platformer with pixel graphics. You will move around locations, destroying opponents in every possible way.</description></item><item><title>Geometry Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Geometry Dash is a 2D arcade game aimed at hardcore level completion. You will take control of a unique character, which can be in the form of a geometric figure, to pass the most difficult levels and open up new opportunities in the gameplay. Here you will find more than 100 original and challenging missions, as well as the opportunity to create your own main character and share your results on the leaderboard.</description></item><item><title>One Finger Death Punch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</guid><description>Game Description One finger death punch is an arcade fighting game in the style of beat&amp;rsquo;em up, in which you can feel like a real martial arts master. In this game we have to fight off crowds of enemies that have surrounded the main character and are advancing from opposite sides. The game design is made in 2D, and all the characters are drawn people, which adds simplicity to the game, but at the same time makes it unusual.</description></item><item><title>Super Hexagon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</guid><description>Game Description Super Hexagon does not contain any plot. This is a dynamic arcade game with a top view. From the outside it looks like an endless game. But in fact, it can be passed. It will not be easy to reach the end, since the title is very hardcore. The project uses a minimalistic visual style.
The gameplay is about survival in the arena. In Super Hexagon it is hexagonal in shape.</description></item><item><title>Castle Crashers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</guid><description>Game Description Castle Crashers is an arcade action game in which players will take control of powerful characters and fight monsters. Create a squad by choosing from 25 characters to fight your way through castles against your enemies. Compete with other users or monsters living throughout the continent. The plot will unfold at a ball in the king&amp;rsquo;s castle. During the fun, an evil sorcerer stole a precious magic stone and four princesses, who must be rescued by the knights and fight the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Coven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coven/</guid><description>Game Description Going to the gloomy world ofCoven, you have to deal with a large number of enemy creatures and deal with their elimination. The universe takes you into an atmospheric medieval fantasy world, where witches and other mythical creatures live alongside people. The first episode is available in the game, where you will take on the role of a young girl. The heroine is burned at the stake during the 1600s, mistaken for a witch and a fiend.</description></item></channel></rss>