<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Arcades on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/</link><description>Recent content in Arcades on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gruel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</guid><description>Game Description ** Gruel ** - this is an exciting first -person shooter in which chaos reigns in the endless arena. Users move around the unpredictable temple, faced with a series of constantly changing rooms filled with bizarre enemies. Each step forward is a new challenge that makes reflexes and adapt to the limit. Traditional shooting mechanics fades into the background, and improvisation becomes a key point.
Movement is constantly, fluctuations lead to disaster, and the only way out is a passage.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description ** Pinball Spire ** challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Ratshaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</guid><description>Game Description ** Ratshaker ** stands out with its non -standard approach to the genre of pest combat. Unlike typical games, in which strategies or battle are given the main attention, this one goes along a rather unusual path: the gamer has to subjugate a virtual rat. The process is simple, but strangely exciting: shake the rat, watch how the submission counter is growing, and continue to shake until you finish the work.</description></item></channel></rss>