<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Arcades on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/</link><description>Recent content in Arcades on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy Delivery Co.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-delivery-co/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-delivery-co/</guid><description>Game Description In Easy Delivery Co. The player takes on the role of the driver-who travels along the picturesque mountain town with severe weather conditions. The main task is to deliver parcels to local residents on a compact kei-kare. Remuneration of labor is significantly lower than the minimum, forming the economic background of the situation in which the hero found himself. The open world allows you to explore the surroundings outside the main routes, and the physics of transport affects the controllability of the machine on a different relief.</description></item><item><title>Pinata Go Boom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinata-go-boom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinata-go-boom/</guid><description>Game Description Pinata Go Boom throws a player in the role of an employee armed with bat and corporate ambitions. The main task is to break the Pignata in a series of industrial premises. To go to the next zone, it is necessary to destroy all containers. Broken Pignata releases a variety of toys and prey to be collected. The accumulated catch becomes the basis for career growth and development of skills in the hierarchy.</description></item><item><title>Disc Golf City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disc-golf-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/disc-golf-city/</guid><description>Game Description In Disc Golf City, gamers find themselves in stylized urban locations that serve as tracks. The main task is to abandon the shell in the target basket for the minimum number of attempts. The path of the drive of the disk must be laid through parks, squares and roofs, turning concrete jungle into a sports arena. The physical model controls the trajectory of the projectile and its collision with surfaces, requiring the exact calculation of the angle and the strength of each launch.</description></item><item><title>Trainatic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trainatic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trainatic/</guid><description>Game Description Trainatic offers the player to pump wagons to collect materials when driving along a railway canvas. The key task is the constant expansion of the locomotive, starting with one engine. The accession of new components increases its length and capabilities, facilitating the promotion of the procedurally generated path. This process allows you to accumulate raw materials for subsequent construction. Over time, the composition is transformed from the initial form into a massive structure that occupies a significant part of the screen.</description></item><item><title>Star Fire: Eternal Cycle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-fire-eternal-cycle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-fire-eternal-cycle/</guid><description>Game Description Star Fire: Eternal Cycle triggers a race in which the main character makes jerks and combo against alien enemies in futuristic 2.5D-gallocations. The gameplay is built on a combination of sid-scrolling battles in the spirit of Beat &amp;lsquo;Em Up and progression systems characteristic of Roguelite. Each attempt to clean the level is distinguished by a unique arrangement of enemies and procedurally generated branches of tracks. The player’s movement and attacks are designed for direct control, requiring evasions and accurate calculation of the time to win the cyberpanic opponents in the destroyed environment.</description></item><item><title>Jetrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jetrunner/</guid><description>Game Description Jetrunner combines first -person parkour with dynamic shooting in the framework of futuristic sports. Opponents move along the arenas created by hand, using a combination of running, jumping, sliding and firing for promotion. The fully voiced story campaign is dedicated to the history of the newcomer-sensation of Nina White, rising along the competitive ladder. Her path describes battles and challenges in an attempt to achieve legendary status in this discipline.</description></item><item><title>Project X: Light Years</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-x-light-years/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-x-light-years/</guid><description>Game Description In the Project X: Light Years, the user will have to pilot a modern starship through enemy territories 30 years after the initial battle. There is navigation on various locations, including asteroid fields and outposts in deep space, where it will have to be opposed by the waves of alien opponents. The main task is to collect objects that improve the firepower, speed and protection of the ship.</description></item><item><title>King's Blade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kings-blade/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kings-blade/</guid><description>Game Description King&amp;rsquo;s Blade throws a small detachment of elite warriors to break through the hordes of the Bargian Empire. This Beat &amp;lsquo;Em Up with side scrolling immerses in a gloomy fantasy world created under the influence of the Konan-Cover and Arcadian Titles universe like Golden Axe and Streets of Rage. Players have to move around the enemy lands and participate in brawls, trying to break through to the capital of the enemy.</description></item><item><title>The House of the Dead 2: Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-the-dead-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-the-dead-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description The House of the Dead 2: Remake is a rail shooter where gamers in the role of secret agents of James or Gary cleans the city. This game offers a single passage or local cooperative regime for the destruction of hordes of hostile creatures that block the path. The first -person gameplay immerses the operatives in cruel clashes with the hostile inhabitants of the metropolis. The main goal is to survive and find out the source of the flash, moving through the captured streets and buildings.</description></item><item><title>Kitchen Wars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kitchen-wars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kitchen-wars/</guid><description>Game Description Kitchen Wars collects from 2 to 8 people for restaurant rivalry, dividing gamers into warring teams. Groups from 1 to 4 people on each side work in their appointed institution. The main task is to find a balance between visitors' maintenance and interference for a competing business. Groups control their institution, simultaneously preventing opponents from direct actions.
In Kitchen Wars, the teams are focused on the preparation and delivery of orders so that customers are satisfied.</description></item><item><title>Bee Simulator: The Hive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</guid><description>Game Description Bee Simulator: The Hive puts the player in the role of an insect with the task of protecting his colony from danger. A single story is focused on the actions of one bee, on which the survival of the entire swarm depends. Gamers have to move around the half-open world created on the model of the New York Central Park. Key activity includes the collection of pollen from plants, interaction with other insects and confrontation with aggressive Osami.</description></item><item><title>Earth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</guid><description>Game Description Earth is a site-scrolling space shooter created for 16-bit equipment. The project transfers the player the pilot of the warship Azuso Takanashi in her campaign against alien invaders. Its central goal is to protect the Earth in a series of combat scripts. This title is a 2D-player with the main character, whose events unfold in the futuristic science fiction universe. The gameplay is presented from the arcade perspective.</description></item><item><title>Reflex Unit: Strike Ops</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</guid><description>Game Description Reflex Unit: Strike Ops immerses in the future, destroyed by cataclysm and captured by powerful corporations. The player is headed by an elite detachment opposing the despotistical corporation Neotech, operating the remnants of civilization. The key gameplay consists in managing specialized equipment during various tactical operations. The tasks include daring rescue sorties, collecting key resources and direct attacks on enemy bases to undermine the power of the regime and struggle for freedom of the population.</description></item><item><title>CONTRACT Rush DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contract-rush-dx/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contract-rush-dx/</guid><description>Game Description Contract Rush DX represents a 2D-world, built on the battles in the style of run and shoot and platform navigation. The player will have to choose from the list of characters to perform missions in manually drawn environment. The action mixes the shooting with the study, and cartoon aesthetics are combined with frank blood images during battles. The central gaming cycle requires to accept and execute contracts, which promotes deep into the numerous conflicts of the world.</description></item><item><title>Keytamine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keytamine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keytamine/</guid><description>Game Description Keytamine is an action focused on a rhythmic battle against the waves of opponents in the form of keyboards in the isometric world. Players enter into a fight with these opponents using a auto-clique mechanics, moving along the procedurally generated levels requiring tactical awareness. The main gameplay is built on a set of glasses, and survival and effective destruction of goals are the main tasks.
The battle is a question of timing and reaction that integrates the Bullet Hell elements as the number of enemies grows and requires constant movement and control over the arena.</description></item><item><title>RECHARGE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</guid><description>Game Description RECHARGE is a simulation-arcade racing experience in which the player controls radio-controlled machines. The gameplay was built on a physical model of behavior and allows the customization of vehicles. Gamers compete on tracks created based on professional RC tracks and other locations, including beaches and entertainment parks. The project is intended for use with several input devices, supporting both standard gamepads and specialized controllers.
These features create the basis for individual and competitive races.</description></item><item><title>Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ed-and-edda-grand-prix-racing-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Ed and Edda: Grand Prix - Racing Champions - this is a racing game with the participation of Muscles from the European Park. There are 8 characters to choose from, including the main characters of Ed and Eddo from the Grand Prix of Europe. Railways take place on the tracks laid around the attractions of the continent. You can withstand computer counterparts or challenge three friends in local mode with the separation of the screen by arranging a direct competition in driver’s skills.</description></item><item><title>HOT ROD MAYHEM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description Hot Rod Mayhem represents car competitions on many tracks. This racing arcade contains a campaign mode, where to obtain the title of world champion, it is necessary to win in 10 separate championships. Promotion requires special tests with unique tasks that open access to the main events. After unlocking the championship, you can participate in its races so that the player can take first place in the fight against opponents.</description></item><item><title>Look mum no computer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/look-mum-no-computer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/look-mum-no-computer/</guid><description>Game Description Look Mum No Computer is a twin-style shooter, the action of which takes place in the Saldersworth universe. Players take on the role of Sam, working together with the cosmo-cosmo companion to combat mechanisms that have gone under control. The mission requires penetrating these devices to repair them and direct confrontation of chaos. The journey includes the execution of quests from the inhabitants of the machine worlds and a fight with large -scale bosses.</description></item><item><title>BUCCANEERS SHIPSHAPE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buccaneers-shipshape/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buccaneers-shipshape/</guid><description>Game Description Buccaneers Shipshape is a sideling-sling beat &amp;lsquo;em up, where players pursue the goal of returning the stolen vessel and its treasure map. The gameplay is focused on battles with enemy looters and obtaining objects from civilians. The characters call on manual parrots to help during collisions. This arcade action develops through a series of levels and supports a local cooperative up to 4 participants on one system. The basis is a slasher with sword battles as central mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Noobs are coming</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noobs-are-coming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noobs-are-coming/</guid><description>Game Description Noobs Are Coming puts the player in the place of the final boss in the arena, where he will have to fight off the waves of opponents. The main task is to withstand the gradually intensifying attacks of attackers called nobs for a 30-minute round. A list of characters-bosses, which includes a giant worm, queen of spiders or seductive succubus, is offered to choose from. After that, it is necessary to create a unique assembly, equipping the hero with special skills and combined dozens of different attacks for constructing protective tactics.</description></item><item><title>Casual Sport Series: Badminton</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/casual-sport-series-badminton/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/casual-sport-series-badminton/</guid><description>Game Description Casual Sport Series: Badminton is a digital reconstruction of rocket sport. Players make a variety of techniques, such as mixes, shortened and high blows, as well as actions at the grid to control the Volan trajectory. The gameplay is focused on reflexes and strategic positioning to move the opponent along the site. The outcome of the confrontations is decided by the exact conduct of various types of attacks in a quick sequence, requiring high accuracy.</description></item><item><title>Nelumbra</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nelumbra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nelumbra/</guid><description>Game Description Nelumbra puts the player in the role of the bearer of light, character who fell into a temporary loop without memories of the past. The main task is to fight for the truth of one’s own existence, and the price of this is unknown. Survival is built on the use of rhythmic car autocat and jerks as the surrounding light is extinct, which steadily pumps stress with each action.</description></item><item><title>OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</guid><description>Game Description OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression is a flight shooter in which players use continuous fire to neutralize enemy forces. The story of the Title is submitted after 30 plot chapters, describing the war between the human faction and the essence of the fat bird from the parallel world. Combat operations take place on various three -dimensional locations, each with a unique relief that affects the tactical approach to clashes.</description></item><item><title>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 + 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tony-hawks-pro-skater-3-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tony-hawks-pro-skater-3-4/</guid><description>Game Description Tony Hawk&amp;rsquo;s Pro Skater 3 + 4 combines elements from the two previous parts of the series, representing their content in the form of a single package. The project includes a wider composition of available skaters and represents completely different parks for research. The player performs sequences of tricks in these environment, striving for the performance of specific tasks. This collection also adds fresh opportunities for tricks to the arsenal of movements, expanding the methods of interacting with the level of level.</description></item><item><title>Backyard Baseball '01</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backyard-baseball-01/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backyard-baseball-01/</guid><description>Game Description Backyard Baseball &amp;lsquo;01 is a sports simulator where users manage a baseball team. The central mechanics consists in creating a roster by selecting from 30 young athletes and 28 professional athletes of the MLB of that period. Users can participate in various formats of the game, from a single exhibition match until the full season leading to the championship. The training mode is also available for testing timing, allowing the chosen Batter to meet Mr.</description></item><item><title>Radiant: Guardians of Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/radiant-guardians-of-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/radiant-guardians-of-light/</guid><description>Game Description Radiant: Guardians of Light puts players in the fantasy world, where progress develops through a direct action. Gamers can explore helium alone or with a companion, determining the pace of their journey. The structure of this Action RPG is focused on elements combining the Hack-And-Slash approach in battle, the development of characters through experience and extensive creation of objects. Fighters constantly face a variety of opponents, preparing for subsequent meetings and significant clashes.</description></item><item><title>Click and Conquer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</guid><description>Game Description Click and Conquer represents a resource management system through military operations. The main gameplay is based on the discharge of bombs on the grid to detect disguised enemy detachments. Each opened unit brings currency that serves as a central resource for further development. The received funds are distributed to increase passive income and an increase in the destructive force of each ammunition. The cycle of expenses and savings determines the promotion of the player at affordable stages.</description></item><item><title>Suit for Hire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suit-for-hire/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suit-for-hire/</guid><description>Game Description Suit for Hire as if throwing users into a first -class action movie, where they have to go through a series of locations in the role of a killer, leaving a mountain of corpses. There is no deeply prescribed plot, serious development of characters or complex mechanics. There are only pure action and arsenal of techniques with which you can eliminate the next portion of goals. In addition, the scene is constantly changing, due to which you will have to get used to the new environment again.</description></item><item><title>Merge Maestro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</guid><description>Game Description Merge Maestro suggests placing an emoji chip on a mesh field. These elements are combined with others of the same type to create stronger and more high -level units. The main task is to overcome the advancing waves of opponents using these improved tokens. After each round, Gamer chooses a new element for its set, expanding tactical opportunities for future clashes. Such a cycle of placement and fusion forms a key game process that requires step -by -step solutions to clean the field and survival.</description></item><item><title>Rematch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</guid><description>Game Description Rematch is a competitive football, where, unlike traditional titles, he offers a unique interpretation of this sport, focusing on quick matches. Gamers control one character with a third person, focusing on individual skill and teamwork. The game is designed in such a way as to constantly keep users in suspense, focusing on speed and accuracy. Here each move matters, and the outcome is determined by how well users coordinate their actions and respond to pressure.</description></item><item><title>Soulstone Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulstone-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulstone-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Soulstone Survivors events take place in the gloomy fantasy universe, and the main characters will be the abyss hunters who strive to capture the unique stones of the soul. They have an incredible force capable of turning a carrier into a creature with which only a deity can compare by capabilities. However, it is extremely difficult to get them - for this it will be necessary to first defeat the master of the void.</description></item><item><title>Shape Shifter: Formations</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</guid><description>Game Description Shape Shifter: Formations - This is an exciting two -osti shooter with Rogue -Lite mechanics, which brings a fresh stream in the genre. In this game, gamers have to fight with the waves of geometric enemies, passing through tense scenarios of bullet adhesive hell. Whether it is a single flight or a local cooperative with a friend, Adventure offers a number of tests that will check reflexes and strategic thinking.</description></item><item><title>Coin Push RPG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coin-push-rpg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coin-push-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Coin Push RPG combines the mechanics of an arcade machine with elements of pumping characters. In the center of the process is a full-fledged simulator of a classic coin-pusher, where actions directly affect resources. Good luck drums, bonus towers and jackpotes form the rhythm of sessions and provide an influx of coins. It is these coins that launch the actions of fighters subordinates to the player.
In the Coin Push RPG project, characters do not enter the battle for free.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>Regulators</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/regulators/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/regulators/</guid><description>Game Description Regulators sets before a detachment of mercenaries the task of stripping the city from mutating villains with weapons, gadgets and special abilities. The team penetrates into buildings from streets, roofs or sewers to fulfill the goals leading to the scientist, commander of the antagonists. The situation began after the fall of an asteroid that released the alien substance of the UZ. It was soon found that this material has narcotic potential and causes mutations in all its exposure, including the detachment fighters themselves.</description></item><item><title>Tower of Babel: Survivors of Chaos</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-babel-survivors-of-chaos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-babel-survivors-of-chaos/</guid><description>Game Description Tower of Babel: Survivors of Chaos puts a gamer in the face of endless streams of hostile creatures. Subjects develop new skills and strengthen their capabilities. The main task is to climb inside the tower, striving for its top to find the fulfillment of personal, most secret desires. This desire requires a clash with continuous opposition, sometimes at a very expensive price, and adaptation of its state to battle.</description></item><item><title>The Precint</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-precinct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-precinct/</guid><description>Game Description The Precint is a police officer single -user simulator that immerses gamers into the lively urban environment of the 1980s. Having entered the place of Officer Nick Cordell Jr., users are traveling as a beginner who recently graduated from the police academy. Against the background of Averno City, an active life is in full swing, a wide range of procedured crimes is presented in it, from minor violations of the rules of the road to large robberies of banks.</description></item><item><title>Drop Duchy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drop-duchy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drop-duchy/</guid><description>Game Description Drop Duchy combines the mechanics of geometric puzzles with the construction of the territory and the management of resources. Gamers use falling figures not only to clean the lines, but also for the phased construction of possessions. The task is to collect materials and the formation of troops to confront enemy armies, while each installed block contributes to the development of the kingdom on the path to the triumph.</description></item><item><title>Maze Mice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maze-mice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maze-mice/</guid><description>Game Description MAZE MICE is an action rogal, where the current playing time depends on the input of the gamer; Time goes forward only when the character moves. It is necessary to control the avatar inside the labyrinths, collecting a point for advancement in the locations. The accumulation of points brings experience points, allowing you to increase the hero level and open access to the choice of upgrades that change its characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Tower Unite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-unite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-unite/</guid><description>Game Description Tower Unite is a very unusual MMO. Here, users walk and get acquainted on a large central hub called Plaza and Island. In fact, this is such a large amusement park. At the same time, one can play here alone.
The project was first made on the basis of Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod. Over time, it turned into a full -fledged separate product. The game allows gamers to create their own creativity inside it and share with others.</description></item><item><title>It</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</guid><description>Game Description IT&amp;rsquo;s on the Mouse combines a cafe management with a 3D platformer, providing players with control over the main characters of Holly. Being a tiny maid, she is forced to use a special navigation method in the working environment due to her growth. The gamer has to jump and run around the tables and racks to get to customers and submit orders to them. This movement system is central mechanics for receiving applications and delivery of the desired dishes.</description></item><item><title>Polterguys: Possession Party</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polterguys-possession-party/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polterguys-possession-party/</guid><description>Game Description Polterguys: Possession Party throws eight ghostly players in a competition with an indirect confrontation. The main task is to lure opponents on the path of a stray monster. Gamers control spirits capable of instilling in ordinary objects and turning them into tools of deception. Each of 10 unique levels is filled with physical traps and the dangers of the environment. Success depends on the ability to use these elements for strategic elimination of rivals, while avoiding the creature pursuing all.</description></item><item><title>Drive Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Rally is an arcade game about rally races that transfers gamers during the glory of the 1990s. Having focused on speeds, skill and exciting sensations of an open road, Advencura offers nostalgic experience for fans of classic rally races. Users take on the role of a rally racer, competing in various iconic places around the world. From the dusty deserts of Africa to the snowy peaks of Scandinavia - each area offers unique trials and opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-the-grand-master-4-absolute-eye/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-the-grand-master-4-absolute-eye/</guid><description>Game Description Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye - marks the continuation of the TGM series, originating in the arcade halls. This fourth part goes after a 20-year break between the main parts of the series, representing new elements in the established formula. The project contains content designed both for beginners unfamiliar with the specific style of the series, and for gamers with extensive experience.
Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye offers several passage options, including recently introduced ASUKA and Shiranui options.</description></item><item><title>Scholar of the Arcane Arts</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scholar-of-the-arcane-arts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scholar-of-the-arcane-arts/</guid><description>Game Description Scholar of the Arcane Arts is devoted to the use of spells interacting with each other to confront the invasion. The universe flooded five plans of magic, forcing the player to look for new forces. Knowledge is gained through the collection of magic scrolls hidden in different parts of the world. For survival, it is necessary to solve puzzles, explore the secret dungeons and destroy monsters, stereing of powerful artifacts.</description></item><item><title>Voids Vigil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voids-vigil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voids-vigil/</guid><description>Game Description Voids Vigil is an arena with an Autoboy in the Rogue -Lite style, where the action never stops. Gamers will have to clean the one who flooded the arena of the hordes of robots armed only with automatic weapons, drones and many special abilities. Title maintains interest, offering a variety of modes and complexity settings, which allows you to always find new tests. As you advanced, users should competently dispose of their koga - the key resource, which is used in stores that appear throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Gruel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</guid><description>Game Description Gruel - this is an exciting first -person shooter in which chaos reigns in the endless arena. Users move around the unpredictable temple, faced with a series of constantly changing rooms filled with bizarre enemies. Each step forward is a new challenge that makes reflexes and adapt to the limit. Traditional shooting mechanics fades into the background, and improvisation becomes a key point.
Movement is constantly, fluctuations lead to disaster, and the only way out is a passage.</description></item><item><title>Xiaomei and the Flame Dragon's Fist</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xiaomei-and-the-flame-dragons-fist/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xiaomei-and-the-flame-dragons-fist/</guid><description>Game Description In the center of Xiaomei and the Flame Dragon&amp;rsquo;s Fist is the story of Xiao May, a martial artist who is looking for his older sister of Xiao In. The narrative was built in the conflict of two schools: the heroine owns a fist of the dragon fiery, while her sister suffered the dark art of a fist of the murderer of a dark dragon. Xiao in disappeared, succumbing to the temptation of forbidden power, which made her sister go on a dangerous journey for her salvation.</description></item><item><title>Ratshaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</guid><description>Game Description Ratshaker stands out with its non -standard approach to the genre of pest combat. Unlike typical games, in which strategies or battle are given the main attention, this one goes along a rather unusual path: the gamer has to subjugate a virtual rat. The process is simple, but strangely exciting: shake the rat, watch how the submission counter is growing, and continue to shake until you finish the work.</description></item><item><title>October Panic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/october-panic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/october-panic/</guid><description>Game Description October Panic is a platform in an arcade style that requires passing five levels in one continuous session. The plot of the game begins with Rita of the resuscitator, whose occult experiments create a break in reality, flooding the streets of a small city with supernatural entities. This chaotic event releases the Horde of Creation, among which witches, werewolves, mummies, vampires and walking dead.
The player will manage the young collector of sweets named October to pave the way through the captured streets to the old ghost mansion and put an end to the annual curse.</description></item><item><title>Kill Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Kill Knight paves his way to the arena of action-players, promising a cruel ballet from trials and strategy. Fasten the belts because this adventure throws you into a deep abyss - quick reflexes and acute thinking - your only life circles. Forget about sitting aside and interrupting enemies one by one. Here the aggressive style of the game is encouraged, but do not shoot with a fright. Resource management is a key point.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Night Slashhers: Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/night-slashers-remake/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/night-slashers-remake/</guid><description>Game Description Night Slashhers: Remake is a revival of the classic Beat &amp;lsquo;Em Up genre on horror, carrying players to the world where the supernatural reigns. From the very beginning, gamers are faced with a nightmare environment inhabited by zombies and other monstrous creatures. The action takes place in seven separate stages, each of which consists of many sections requiring the user to move forward, moving from left to right. Each stage turns into the battlefield, where the screen freezes, until all enemies are destroyed, which leads to tense fights with bosses at the end of each level.</description></item><item><title>Exophobia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</guid><description>Game Description Exophobia is a first -person pixel shooter in which you will go to explore a spaceship. The shuttle fell to the surface of an unknown planet. Here you will encounter the hordes of alien opponents. The game is made in retro-stylistic, drawing inspiration in arcade shooters of the 80s.
Explore the station and find out the background of the inhabitants of the planet, as well as try to find out what caused the shipwreck.</description></item><item><title>Jrago II Guardians of Eden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jrago-ii-guardians-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/jrago-ii-guardians-of-eden/</guid><description>Game Description Jrago 2 Guardians of Eden offers players to unite in a company up to 4 people for battle with a revived darkness. Heroes form a detachment of guards in order to exterminate demonic forces and return the light to their world. The gameplay combines two -dimensional platforming and elements of the role action on a spacious card. This project, which is a direct continuation of the Jrago The Demon Hunter, expands the basic Hack and Slash mechanics within the framework of a large metroid that focuses on joint actions.</description></item><item><title>Underspace</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underspace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underspace/</guid><description>Game Description Underspace is an adventure action in the open world. The gameplay proposes to explore the open spaces of the open space, fighting with other combat shuttles, alien creatures, etc. Take the trading and pumping of your own ship. Openvorld Underspace is fully created manually.
Each star system includes its own characteristics and biomes. You have to explore the galaxy called CROFT. You can go to the adventure as alone, so with friends.</description></item><item><title>Momo and the Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</guid><description>Game Description Momo and the Mine sends a mole-protagonist to a dangerous, abandoned network of dungeons for collecting matches. The player will have to conduct a character through a series of difficult jumping tests, where accuracy is the key to survival. The gameplay requires accurate movement through the hostile surroundings filled with ghosts of tunnels. Success directly depends on mastering responsive controls to overcome each obstacle in the dilapidated structure of the mine, which creates a constant test of skill.</description></item><item><title>Corsairs Legacy - Pirate Action RPG and Sea Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corsairs-legacy-pirate-action-rpg-and-sea-battles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corsairs-legacy-pirate-action-rpg-and-sea-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Corsaires Legacy - Pirate Action RPG and Sea Battles is a pirate adventure in the open world, which makes it possible to become a real corsar, exploring the seas and oceans, as well as fighting with numerous enemies both on land and at sea. Events develop on Barbados. Playing for an adventurer, it is required to become not only a thunderstorm of the seas, but also a whole tropical archipelago.</description></item><item><title>Under Night In-Birth II Sys: Celes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-night-in-birth-ii-sysceles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-night-in-birth-ii-sysceles/</guid><description>Game Description Under Night In-Birth II Sys: Celes, the last part of the favorite fighting range, bursts on stage. This is not just a fresh layer of paint, it is a full -fledged evolution, promising a deeper and more dramatic experience of both veterans and beginners. Get ready to join the battle with 24 unique fighters, each of whom can boast of their own style of battle and a background. Three new fighters occupy a central place: Kaguya, elegant, but deadly dancer, owning two blades; Tsurugi, an unshakable wall of a warrior; And Kuon, a creature, challenging the borders of existence to the very borders.</description></item><item><title>Visco Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/visco-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Visco Collection presents 7 arcade titles from the 1980s and 1990s. This collection contains projects of several genres, including Shoot ‘Em Up, fighting, sports and racing. The presented software supports single and local multiplayer modes for competitive or joint passage. Each Title demonstrates the special style of the arcade gameplay of that time with unique goals and mechanics that players have to study.
The Visco Collection contains Andro Dunos-Side-Squash Shoot ‘Em Up, which encounters you with elaboration ships and large-scale bosses.</description></item><item><title>Subpar Pool</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subpar-pool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subpar-pool/</guid><description>Game Description Subpar Pool combines golf and billiard elements on a table of tables. The player will have to remove all balls for a limited number of blows at each procedured level, consisting of a sequence of connected surfaces. Gameplay based on physics requires strategic planning to roll objects. Classing and scattering balls often require adjusting the original plans, forcing to adapt the next move to complete the stage.
As you pass, gamers build a course, choosing cards from the deck to change experience.</description></item><item><title>Railgunners</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</guid><description>Game Description Railgunners puts players in the script of a rail shooter, where humanity is fighting an alien invasion. This title represents battles through customizable complexity parameters, allowing gamers to regulate the intensity of contractions. Gamers move in a two -dimensional perspective with lateral scrolling, faced with hundreds of enemy units in numerous conflict zones. The main task includes a breakthrough through the vast lines of the enemy in order to get to the mother vessel of the aliens and begin its destruction.</description></item><item><title>Pocket Bravey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-bravery/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-bravery/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket Bravey is a dynamic fighting game that acquaints charismatic characters with a unique battle style and abilities. The gameplay is inspired by the classic fatings of the 90s, but containing a number of modern mechanics and functions. The visual style is represented by retro design. The environment is made in bright colors that refer to various Japanese projects.
The heroes of Pocket Bravey are represented by several types of shocks, combinations, block and supervision.</description></item><item><title>Sandtrix+</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sandtrix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sandtrix/</guid><description>Game Description Sandtrix+ is a puzzle structure built around falling blocks with a special physical property. These elements do not join firmly, but are broken in a collision, turning into streams of bulk substances that obey the laws of physics. The task is to strategic placement of these figures to manage the formed sand masses. The player removes the pixels from the screen, forming a continuous horizontal line from one -color granules from one edge of the field to the other as part of the competition for glasses.</description></item><item><title>Eon Fighter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eon-fighter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eon-fighter/</guid><description>Game Description Eon Fighter is an action game with a top view with Roguelite systems where the player pilots the fighter through the hostile sectors of the cosmos. The gameplay is focused on a collision with continuous waves of opponents and collecting resources for promotion. In the role of the last representative of mankind, it is necessary to carry out tasks, confronts the constant enemy. The structure of the Shoot &amp;lsquo;Em Up genre requires continuous movement and tactical ingenuity to survive in the conditions of the onslaught.</description></item><item><title>Yet Another Zombie Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yet-another-zombie-survivors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yet-another-zombie-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Yet Another Zombie Survivors is an action roginal for those who are ready to fight with the horde of undead! Humanity can be on the verge of extinction, but this does not mean that you will fall without a fight. This is not a typical game with long scenes and complex management - here you need to immediately join the battle and see how sparks fly! Regardless of what your level of game experience you have, you will enjoy this game.</description></item><item><title>Driftwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</guid><description>Game Description Driftwood is a fascinating journey into the world of high -speed descent on Longboard. The main character is Eddie, a cool sliven who loves to ride in beautiful landscapes. This game provides an ideal balance of speed and control, bringing a feeling of relaxation and calm, despite a high -speed action.
The project offers minimalistic experience, focusing on skating on magnificent landscapes, and not on building a story campaign.</description></item><item><title>Super Jagger Bomb</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-jagger-bomb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-jagger-bomb/</guid><description>Game Description Super Jagger Bomb sets the gamer with the task of neutralizing incendiary devices on multi -level arenas. The main character in the cloak should quickly collect all the bombs in order to prevent the explosion. To move in locations, he uses running, jumping and jerking in the air. A special technique allows you to quickly fall down, which adds an element of tactical planning of the route to the process and turns it into a kind of puzzle.</description></item><item><title>MX VS ATV Legends</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mx-vs-atv-legends/</guid><description>Game Description MX VS ATV Legends shows what intensive and at the same time dangerous racing competitions can be. Here, users are invited to participate in mass races on the proposed routes. Each location is full of surprises, so you need to carefully monitor the behavior of the vehicle so as not to fly from the distance at the most inopportune moment. Moreover, each type of transport has its own unique characteristics, and even the most experienced riders will need time to adapt and get used to the manner of behavior.</description></item><item><title>Kao The Kangaroo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kao-the-kangaroo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kao-the-kangaroo/</guid><description>Game Description Kao The Kangaroo is a three-dimensional platformer with a huge amount of action scenes. The game uses cartoon graphics to transmit the beauty of a fictional universe, in which the events of a single -user story campaign take place. Casual management allows players of different ages to quickly remember the keys used and enjoy the versatile mechanic used in the gameplay. The project, developed and published by the TATE Multimedia India, combines elements of constant fights with both small opponents and large, dangerous bosses, and a thoughtful plot with some dramatic turns that make virtual personalities experience.</description></item><item><title>Battle Ax</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-axe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-axe/</guid><description>Game Description Battle Ax-arcade top-downs adventure made in retro-stylistic. Events develop on the lands of Mercia. The civilian population was hostage in the evil sorceress of Etheldred. She captured almost the entire territory of the continent, and she settled in the north of the country. Every 7 years she sends her warriors south to capture even more slaves. Throughout the continent begin to gather brave warriors, eager to join an open battle with the sorceress.</description></item><item><title>Reknum Cheri Dreamland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reknum-cheri-dreamland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reknum-cheri-dreamland/</guid><description>Game Description Reknum Cheri Dreamland starts an adventure in which Cheri’s heroine awakens from fantasies and falls into a real conflict. Her wanderings in the world of dreams will force to encounter materialized nightmares that threaten the kingdom. Progress depends on the passage of the thematic stages and the deciphering of poetic instructions of the ancestors. The study of the environment prepares for a deeper immersion in the main tests and plot lines of this game, conducting the characters through a series of difficult locations and battles.</description></item><item><title>Binky's Trash Service</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/binkys-trash-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/binkys-trash-service/</guid><description>Game Description Binky&amp;rsquo;s Trash Service lays a waste collection route that runs through a series of villainous shelters. The key task at each level is to find and clean all the garbage containers, and then get to the exit. Performing a mission requires verified movements surrounded by a complete platform obstacles. Success depends on the methodical stripping of locations and accurate control of the actions of the hero.
The gameplay in Binky&amp;rsquo;s Trash Service is built on three buttons responsible for a limited set of movements.</description></item><item><title>A Dance of Fire and Ice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-dance-of-fire-and-ice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-dance-of-fire-and-ice/</guid><description>Game Description A Dance of Fire and Ice-a rhythm explosion created by a small indie company, which has used a minimalistic style of graphic design for its brainchild so that nothing distracts from a study of exciting levels of different complexity. The player needs to constantly be on the alert and not relax for a second, because the game throws difficulties at every turn. Two planets, united by an invisible connection, fall under the control of a gamer (using a keyboard or a gamepad).</description></item><item><title>Mad Restaurant People</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</guid><description>Game Description Mad Restaurant People makes it possible to feel all the difficulty of working as a waiter. The game is presented with a top distance, which makes it possible to observe the entire hall at once. Take orders, serve customers, serve dishes in time, count the guests and much more. Mad Restaurant People is a full -fledged waiter’s simulator who will not let you relax for a second.
The gameplay requires attentiveness, reaction speed, good memory and many other important qualities.</description></item><item><title>Pro Evolution Socker 2019</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pro-evolution-soccer-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pro-evolution-soccer-2019/</guid><description>Game Description PES 2019 - one of the games that won the recognition of fans through the territory of the entire planet - Pro Evolution Soccer 2019 is a new football league hidden in the old filling. Gradually improving their brainchild, the developers came to a perfect schedule, plausible sound and real physics of movement. This part includes several additions in which you will hire professional football players for several matches and prove that the team management is your craft from birth!</description></item><item><title>Super Destronaut DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut-dx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut-dx/</guid><description>Game Description Super Destronaut DX puts the player under the control of one ship at the base of the screen, opposing the ordered waves of alien vessels descending the system. The gameplay consists of horizontal movement and firing up - a structure borrowed from classic arcade shoot ‘Em Up. Success is measured not only with survival, but also by a continuous set of glasses with multiple for the effective destruction of enemy columns.</description></item><item><title>Hyperspace Dogfights</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hyperspace-dogfights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hyperspace-dogfights/</guid><description>Game Description Hyperspace Dogfights is a two -dimensional horned focused on jet battles. It is necessary to break through through the waves of opponents, using acceleration to bypass threats, as well as gravity for occupying a profitable position. A special hyperople-decline helps to fly through dense fire. Each departure becomes unique thanks to the collection and installation of more than 300 items that modify the characteristics of the fighter, which allows you to create unlike each other assemblies.</description></item><item><title>Super Destronaut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</guid><description>Game Description Super Destronaut puts a player at the head of one warship, opposing built alien invaders built. Gamers control their horizontal axis vessel in the lower part of the screen, which is a design borrowed from the Arcadian shooters of the 1980s. The main task is to methodically disassemble the waves of opponents, descending along the specified trajectories, where each eliminated enemy replenishes the general account.
During clashes, defeated aliens can leave temporary amplifiers that directly increase the rate of fire or scatter of shells, providing a tactical advantage for cleaning the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>Touhou kanjuden ~ legacy of lunatic kingdom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Kanjuden ~ Legacy of lunatic Kingdom opens as city legends become tangible events throughout Gansko. The rumor that the Apollo program never reached the moon is gaining strength against the backdrop of the appearance of an enemy army from the lunar capital. At the same time, metal spiders begin to cross the mountains, moving with an even, leisurely step. These machines have a functional, non -biological form, and the earth under them loses vitality: the fog is dissipated, and the vegetation fades.</description></item><item><title>The Crew</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crew/</guid><description>Game Description The Crew is a racing match simulator that makes it possible to create its own unique sports car. The plot tells you about the professional racer Alex Taylore. He and his older brother were organizing illegal races. Some time later, the FBI staff found them. Police kill the founder of this event, and the brothers are imprisoned. The heroes are offered to reduce the term, but in return they will have to work in law enforcement agencies.</description></item><item><title>Touhou shinreibyou ~ ten desires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-shinreibyou-ten-desires/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-shinreibyou-ten-desires/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou shinreibyou ~ ten desires begins when strange divine perfumes begin to come from people, Yokaev and fairies. In response to this event, female protagonists of the game go to the other world, suggesting that it is the key to unraveling the phenomenon. The gameplay offers to lead the chosen heroine through a series of levels filled with flitches of shells from opponents. The task is to survive these attacks and destroy the entire opposition, completing the passage of the stage with the boss.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Searensen ~ undefined fantastic object</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-seirensen-undefined-fantastic-object/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-seirensen-undefined-fantastic-object/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Searensen ~ Undefined Fantastic Object is a scroll-player in which the player controls the human character and uses shells to win the antagonists. Any contact with enemy bullets, lasers or opponents themselves leads to a loss of life. When the player’s reserve runs out, the game ends. All items on the screen are collected when moving the controlled character to the upper boundary of the location.
Activation of the function of the slow movement attracts the nearest objects directly to the protagonist, helping in their collection during the battle.</description></item><item><title>Solitaire Battle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</guid><description>Game Description Solitaire Battle combines the mechanics of the card game with the progression of the Autobatler&amp;rsquo;s Horned. Players are faced with opponents where key interaction is a party in the solitaire of three peaks. Each card taken from the field or from the deck is converted into an offensive or defensive action, creating automated combat sequences. The main task is to strategically disassemble the layout to win enemies, while forming a set of random pool of tools that contribute to powerful synergies and encouraging new combinations in each passage.</description></item><item><title>Atomic OWL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atomic-owl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atomic-owl/</guid><description>Game Description Atomic OWL puts the player in the role of Idalgo Bladywing, a bird who went to save his comrades. The main conflict is tied to the confrontation with the sorcerer-Voron Omega Vinc, who by force subjugated his entire troupe. The plot starts 2 years after this incident that happened during the return of the detachment to Ramennaya. Idalgo begins a campaign to correct the deed, and a daring speaking blade helps him in this.</description></item><item><title>Clicker Clicker Clickker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clicker-clicker-clicker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clicker-clicker-clicker/</guid><description>Game Description Clicker Clicker Clicker begins the gameplay with a direct impact on the central pointer generating currency - clicker gold. The frequency of initial presses directly affects the speed of the appearance of numerous gold cursors falling on the screen. Interaction with these omiting objects before their disappearance brings more gold than standard clicks according to the main pointer. This mechanic forms a key gameplay cycle based on the accumulation of resources in two different but related methods.</description></item><item><title>Heli-Cats</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heli-cats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heli-cats/</guid><description>Game Description Heli-Cats puts players in a world experiencing an energy and economic crisis. Against the background of this instability, the rebellious forces begin a coordinated attack on the Alliance. The combined security alliance uses a special helicopter unit acting under the guise of a local militarized formation. Pilots Tiger and Lynx fulfill the mission to repel the invaders and clarify the causes of the conflict.
Their operations are planned so that they can renounce them in case of failure, conducting gamers through 8 arcade stages and 2 more available under special conditions.</description></item><item><title>Refind Self: The Personality Test Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/refind-self-the-personality-test-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/refind-self-the-personality-test-game/</guid><description>Game Description Refind Self: The Personality Test Game is a unique interactive science fiction in which the gameplay allows you to explore the depths of the user personality. In this 2D-visual short story, you fall in the place of the Android and find yourself on the grave of the doctor that created you. From this moment on, your journey unfolds as you are exploring different locations associated with the previous doctor, meeting along the way with various robots.</description></item></channel></rss>