<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Arcades on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/</link><description>Recent content in Arcades on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shape Shifter: Formations</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</guid><description>Game Description Shape Shifter: Formations - This is an exciting two -osti shooter with Rogue -Lite mechanics, which brings a fresh stream in the genre. In this game, gamers have to fight with the waves of geometric enemies, passing through tense scenarios of bullet adhesive hell. Whether it is a single flight or a local cooperative with a friend, Adventure offers a number of tests that will check reflexes and strategic thinking.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>Gruel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</guid><description>Game Description Gruel - this is an exciting first -person shooter in which chaos reigns in the endless arena. Users move around the unpredictable temple, faced with a series of constantly changing rooms filled with bizarre enemies. Each step forward is a new challenge that makes reflexes and adapt to the limit. Traditional shooting mechanics fades into the background, and improvisation becomes a key point.
Movement is constantly, fluctuations lead to disaster, and the only way out is a passage.</description></item><item><title>Ratshaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</guid><description>Game Description Ratshaker stands out with its non -standard approach to the genre of pest combat. Unlike typical games, in which strategies or battle are given the main attention, this one goes along a rather unusual path: the gamer has to subjugate a virtual rat. The process is simple, but strangely exciting: shake the rat, watch how the submission counter is growing, and continue to shake until you finish the work.</description></item><item><title>Kill Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Kill Knight paves his way to the arena of action-players, promising a cruel ballet from trials and strategy. Fasten the belts because this adventure throws you into a deep abyss - quick reflexes and acute thinking - your only life circles. Forget about sitting aside and interrupting enemies one by one. Here the aggressive style of the game is encouraged, but do not shoot with a fright. Resource management is a key point.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Kakatte Koi Yo!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</guid><description>Game Description kakatte koi yo! - This is a two -dimensional action platform with the possibility of local multiplayer. This is a real cat’s battle, in which you have to take control of powerful cats and master even more powerful fish to defeat your opponents in a fierce 2D platform battle. This game with charming aesthetics in the Japanese style and irresistibly cute characters is an obligatory game for any cat lover.</description></item></channel></rss>