<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>arcades on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/</link><description>Recent content in arcades on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/arcades/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Radiant: Guardians of Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/radiant-guardians-of-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/radiant-guardians-of-light/</guid><description>Game Description Radiant: Guardians of Light puts players in the fantasy world, where progress develops through a direct action. Gamers can explore helium alone or with a companion, determining the pace of their journey. The structure of this Action RPG is focused on elements combining the Hack-And-Slash approach in battle, the development of characters through experience and extensive creation of objects. Fighters constantly face a variety of opponents, preparing for subsequent meetings and significant clashes.</description></item><item><title>Rematch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</guid><description>Game Description Rematch is a competitive football, where, unlike traditional titles, he offers a unique interpretation of this sport, focusing on quick matches. Gamers control one character with a third person, focusing on individual skill and teamwork. The game is designed in such a way as to constantly keep users in suspense, focusing on speed and accuracy. Here each move matters, and the outcome is determined by how well users coordinate their actions and respond to pressure.</description></item><item><title>Shape Shifter: Formations</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shape-shifter-formations/</guid><description>Game Description Shape Shifter: Formations - This is an exciting two -osti shooter with Rogue -Lite mechanics, which brings a fresh stream in the genre. In this game, gamers have to fight with the waves of geometric enemies, passing through tense scenarios of bullet adhesive hell. Whether it is a single flight or a local cooperative with a friend, Adventure offers a number of tests that will check reflexes and strategic thinking.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>Gruel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gruel/</guid><description>Game Description Gruel - this is an exciting first -person shooter in which chaos reigns in the endless arena. Users move around the unpredictable temple, faced with a series of constantly changing rooms filled with bizarre enemies. Each step forward is a new challenge that makes reflexes and adapt to the limit. Traditional shooting mechanics fades into the background, and improvisation becomes a key point.
Movement is constantly, fluctuations lead to disaster, and the only way out is a passage.</description></item><item><title>Ratshaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratshaker/</guid><description>Game Description Ratshaker stands out with its non -standard approach to the genre of pest combat. Unlike typical games, in which strategies or battle are given the main attention, this one goes along a rather unusual path: the gamer has to subjugate a virtual rat. The process is simple, but strangely exciting: shake the rat, watch how the submission counter is growing, and continue to shake until you finish the work.</description></item><item><title>Kill Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kill-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Kill Knight paves his way to the arena of action-players, promising a cruel ballet from trials and strategy. Fasten the belts because this adventure throws you into a deep abyss - quick reflexes and acute thinking - your only life circles. Forget about sitting aside and interrupting enemies one by one. Here the aggressive style of the game is encouraged, but do not shoot with a fright. Resource management is a key point.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Exophobia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exophobia/</guid><description>Game Description Exophobia is a first -person pixel shooter in which you will go to explore a spaceship. The shuttle fell to the surface of an unknown planet. Here you will encounter the hordes of alien opponents. The game is made in retro-stylistic, drawing inspiration in arcade shooters of the 80s.
Explore the station and find out the background of the inhabitants of the planet, as well as try to find out what caused the shipwreck.</description></item><item><title>Pooool</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pooool/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pooool/</guid><description>Game Description Pooool is a puzzle based on physics, where the main task is to combine balls of the same size in limited space. Using only the mouse, the player sets the angle and strength for each throw, clicking and dragging the cursor anywhere in the screen, and then releases the button to start the projectile. In the contact of two balls of the same color and size, they merge into one, larger, increasing the final score.</description></item><item><title>Railgunners</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgunners/</guid><description>Game Description Railgunners puts players in the script of a rail shooter, where humanity is fighting an alien invasion. This title represents battles through customizable complexity parameters, allowing gamers to regulate the intensity of contractions. Gamers move in a two -dimensional perspective with lateral scrolling, faced with hundreds of enemy units in numerous conflict zones. The main task includes a breakthrough through the vast lines of the enemy in order to get to the mother vessel of the aliens and begin its destruction.</description></item><item><title>Kakatte Koi Yo!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</guid><description>Game Description kakatte koi yo! - This is a two -dimensional action platform with the possibility of local multiplayer. This is a real cat’s battle, in which you have to take control of powerful cats and master even more powerful fish to defeat your opponents in a fierce 2D platform battle. This game with charming aesthetics in the Japanese style and irresistibly cute characters is an obligatory game for any cat lover.</description></item><item><title>Battle Ax</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-axe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-axe/</guid><description>Game Description Battle Ax-arcade top-downs adventure made in retro-stylistic. Events develop on the lands of Mercia. The civilian population was hostage in the evil sorceress of Etheldred. She captured almost the entire territory of the continent, and she settled in the north of the country. Every 7 years she sends her warriors south to capture even more slaves. Throughout the continent begin to gather brave warriors, eager to join an open battle with the sorceress.</description></item><item><title>Mad Restaurant People</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</guid><description>Game Description Mad Restaurant People makes it possible to feel all the difficulty of working as a waiter. The game is presented with a top distance, which makes it possible to observe the entire hall at once. Take orders, serve customers, serve dishes in time, count the guests and much more. Mad Restaurant People is a full -fledged waiter’s simulator who will not let you relax for a second.
The gameplay requires attentiveness, reaction speed, good memory and many other important qualities.</description></item><item><title>Super Destronaut DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut-dx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut-dx/</guid><description>Game Description Super Destronaut DX puts the player under the control of one ship at the base of the screen, opposing the ordered waves of alien vessels descending the system. The gameplay consists of horizontal movement and firing up - a structure borrowed from classic arcade shoot ‘Em Up. Success is measured not only with survival, but also by a continuous set of glasses with multiple for the effective destruction of enemy columns.</description></item><item><title>Super Destronaut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/super-destronaut/</guid><description>Game Description Super Destronaut puts a player at the head of one warship, opposing built alien invaders built. Gamers control their horizontal axis vessel in the lower part of the screen, which is a design borrowed from the Arcadian shooters of the 1980s. The main task is to methodically disassemble the waves of opponents, descending along the specified trajectories, where each eliminated enemy replenishes the general account.
During clashes, defeated aliens can leave temporary amplifiers that directly increase the rate of fire or scatter of shells, providing a tactical advantage for cleaning the battlefield.</description></item></channel></rss>