<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>anime on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/anime/</link><description>Recent content in anime on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/anime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Daemon X Machina: Titanic Scion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/daemon-x-machina-titanic-scion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/daemon-x-machina-titanic-scion/</guid><description>Game Description Daemon X Machina: Titanic Scion offers to pilot a fully customized fur arsenal around the open world of an alien planet, participating in battles on Earth and in the air. Gamers examine a variety of locations, including plains and mountains, moving on foot in armor, in flight or riding a horse. The gameplay is built on the confrontation with mechanical and organic enemies in order to extract their weapons and equipment.</description></item><item><title>EVERYBODY's Golf Hot Shots</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everybodys-golf-hot-shots/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everybodys-golf-hot-shots/</guid><description>Game Description EVERYBODY&amp;rsquo;s Golf Hot Shots is based on a system of three presses to make strokes on a variety of sites. You can compete both online and in offline mode, choosing from the list of available characters for going to the Fervey. The gameplay requires an accurate calculation of time for aiming and completing a sunk for the best result. This key mechanics are used in all available formats, providing a single control scheme, regardless of whether the competition goes alone or against opponents on the lawn.</description></item><item><title>Holo Hidden - My Lovely Fans Canat Beis Hidden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/holo-hidden-my-lovely-fans-cant-be-this-hidden/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/holo-hidden-my-lovely-fans-cant-be-this-hidden/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay in Holo Hidden - My Lovely Fans Can &amp;lsquo;CANT THIS HIDden takes place at 11 stages drawn by hand and 1 bonus level. Each scene is a large -scale illustration, which needs to find hundreds of certain objects and supporters. Search items vary from obvious to skillfully disguised in the scenery. These locations also contain numerous references to the presented personalities of Hololive, embedding thematic elements directly into the search riddles for fans.</description></item><item><title>Quartet</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</guid><description>Game Description Quartet immerses in the world in which incredible adventures and unforgettable battles await you. Start your way in the world of full mysteries, hidden government intrigues and powerful magic. In this fascinating and old -school RPG you can choose one of the four stories and go through them in any order, revealing the secrets of the Quartet world. A series of train robberies, a mysterious deck of cards, deadly aircraft and an accidental magician - all this awaits you in Quartet.</description></item><item><title>Dice Gambit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</guid><description>Game Description Step -by -step battles in Dice Gambit allow us to plunge into tactical competitions, where the victory determines the cubes that affect the management of the characters. The game is designed for strategic miscalculations where a variety and excitement makes a bone throw. Each result on dits permits to obtain a limited number of actions for heroes fighting on combat arenas. The characters will be able to move, perform interactions with the environment or inflict damage to the opponents on the field.</description></item><item><title>Liese in the City of Trials</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liese-in-the-city-of-trials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liese-in-the-city-of-trials/</guid><description>Game Description Liese in the City of Trita puts the heroine Liz in the face of a new demonic threat years after the establishment of peace. In the former possessions of the defeated lord of demons, a fortress arises, flooding the city of weight in monsters. Liz arrives in a besieged metropolis to investigate the distress source. Local residents are facing inevitable danger, and it should act until the weight fell under the onslaught of the forces of darkness.</description></item><item><title>Earth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/earthion/</guid><description>Game Description Earth is a site-scrolling space shooter created for 16-bit equipment. The project transfers the player the pilot of the warship Azuso Takanashi in her campaign against alien invaders. Its central goal is to protect the Earth in a series of combat scripts. This title is a 2D-player with the main character, whose events unfold in the futuristic science fiction universe. The gameplay is presented from the arcade perspective.</description></item><item><title>The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</guid><description>Game Description The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily is a step -by -step tactical game about the Duchess of Scarlet, faced with accusation of regicide. Accused of the murder of the emperor, she concludes an alliance with Lily, the captain of the aircraft, a stream. Together they declare the war of the empire, becoming the first military streamers on the continent. The conflict grows due to a clash of impulsiveness and cold pragmatism.</description></item><item><title>Demonic Mahjong</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demonic-mahjong/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demonic-mahjong/</guid><description>Game Description Demonic Mahjong races Majong bones with a horn structure. Players have to use chips from their hands to collect combinations that meet the established rules for counting glasses. However, the main task is beyond the scope of simple accumulation of points. The final goal is to build a hand and strategies that allow you to defeat the main boss, which turns every entry into preparation for the final battle.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Mori</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-mori/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-mori/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Mori begins with the return of monsters to the world, which has long expelled them. The main task of the player is to get rid of the lands of these creatures and the victory over the great eternal dragon. The research process is built on a choice system that determines the movement and events in the dungeons. The structure is based on step -by -step mechanics combined with solutions during the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Dragonloop</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragonloop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dragonloop/</guid><description>Game Description Dragonloop is a metro-vanning that combines manipulations over time with the design of the map, enclosing a player in a repeating 5-day cycle. The main character is a woman who has lost her memory and trapped this temporary loop. Together with a satellite named Ouro, she travels around a two -dimensional world, where strange temporal changes take place. The basis of the gameplay is the study and battles in order to break out of the closed circle, change fate and reveal the truth about the situation.</description></item><item><title>Date EVERYTHING!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</guid><description>Game Description Date EVERYTHING! It begins after the main character loses his job due to artificial intelligence. Following this incident, a stranger delivers a parcel with glasses called DateViators. This accessory revives inanimate things in the dwelling of the protagonist, endowing them with his own character. The project contains a list of 100 potential partners, from bed to fire alarm, each of which is completely voiced. Through dialogues, the player studies the background and motives of these household objects that have now become his companions.</description></item><item><title>Nitro Gen Omega</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nitro-gen-omega/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nitro-gen-omega/</guid><description>Game Description Nitro Gen Omega represents the world where cars dominate the landscape after the lost war of mankind. Survivor people are huddled in cities erected on giant supports, so the mercenaries teams are forced to travel to dangerous wastelands. The player originates under his beginning to one of these detachments, based on a flying ship to complete tasks for the supply of resources and technologies. The task is to study this world, the leadership of a detachment and control of combat fur.</description></item><item><title>Covenant of Solitude</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</guid><description>Game Description Covenant of Solitude introduces the story of a young man named Fort, who secretly owns the gift to command monsters in a secluded settlement of the leaves. The carriers of such a force are called ginns - their fate is full of persecution, fear and exploitation from others. The familiar way of life of the hero breaks off when the war breaks into his house, flooding the streets with blood and forcing the fort to accept his essence.</description></item><item><title>Fearbonding</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fearbonding/</guid><description>Game Description Fearbonding represents Hinata, a demon for whom fear has a tangible quality, like sweet, viscous honey. The lack of genuine horror makes his meeting with the Kosuke, a personality with obvious instability, determining the moment. This meeting encourages Hinata, focusing his demonic existence on the goal: to subordinate this person and cultivate his fear. He seeks to make Kosuke with his new instrument for the extraction of this resource so necessary for food.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Island: Missing Amy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</guid><description>Game Description Mystery Island: Missing Amy tells about the hell, the researcher, looking for sister, mysteriously missing months ago. The plot unfolds when hell receives a selfie from a loved one; The picture captures the missing girl on a remote island, where sea water has a bloody red color. This frame encourages hell to take a sea trip to search for a relative and study the location from a mysterious message.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>It</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</guid><description>Game Description IT&amp;rsquo;s on the Mouse combines a cafe management with a 3D platformer, providing players with control over the main characters of Holly. Being a tiny maid, she is forced to use a special navigation method in the working environment due to her growth. The gamer has to jump and run around the tables and racks to get to customers and submit orders to them. This movement system is central mechanics for receiving applications and delivery of the desired dishes.</description></item><item><title>Promise Mascot Agency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</guid><description>Game Description Promise Mascot Agency offers the gamer to plunge into the life of Kaso-Machi, a damned Japanese town. The main character, Michi, is in exile and must establish the work of the agency of urban masks. Key tasks include hiring these creatures, resolving the problems that arise due to their actions, and clarifying the causes of the protagonist link. Communication with a kick, a living finger with a complex character, is also part of the gameplay while you are trying to make your agency the best in the region through the study of the world and plot events.</description></item><item><title>Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-the-grand-master-4-absolute-eye/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tetris-the-grand-master-4-absolute-eye/</guid><description>Game Description Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye - marks the continuation of the TGM series, originating in the arcade halls. This fourth part goes after a 20-year break between the main parts of the series, representing new elements in the established formula. The project contains content designed both for beginners unfamiliar with the specific style of the series, and for gamers with extensive experience.
Tetris The Grand Master 4 -Absolute Eye offers several passage options, including recently introduced ASUKA and Shiranui options.</description></item><item><title>AI Limit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-limit/</guid><description>Game Description AI Limit throws into the world standing on the edge of the abyss, where humanity clings to survival in the ruins of civilization. Hivensvell, the last city, keeps a whisper about the lost hope, and Arris, the immortal Blaider, goes to his destroying streets in search of answers. The artificial ecosystem crashed, leaving behind chaos, wars and creeping, mysterious substance called mud. Monsters roam freely, and scattered survivors are trying to understand the meaning of the crash of the world.</description></item><item><title>Inayh - Life after Gods</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inayah-life-after-gods/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inayah-life-after-gods/</guid><description>Game Description Inayh - Life after Gods describes the journey of a lone warrior on split setting. The remnants of the once prosperous civilization now serve as a battlefield for warring groups, each of which fights for dominance over the ruins. Inaya, an orphaned exile, is looking for her lost tribe, faced with inexorable opponents and revealing forgotten truths. Its path runs through hostile landscapes, abandoned buildings and hidden shelters, where dangers and opportunities exist nearby.</description></item><item><title>Atelier Yumia: The Alchemist of Memories &amp; The Envisioned Land</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atelier-yumia-the-alchemist-of-memories-the-envisioned-land/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atelier-yumia-the-alchemist-of-memories-the-envisioned-land/</guid><description>Game Description Atelier yumia: the alchemist of memorials &amp;amp; the envisioned Land offers users to plunge into the world formed by the remnants of the lost empire. In the center of the plot is Yumi Lissfeldt, a young alchemist who goes in search of secrets of the cataclysm, who once destroyed a powerful civilization. During a trip to the unknown continent, gamers will engage in various types of activities, such as collecting materials, the synthesis of objects and battle with enemies.</description></item><item><title>Bleach Rebirth of Souls</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bleach-rebirth-of-souls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bleach-rebirth-of-souls/</guid><description>Game Description Bleach Rebirth of Souls invites users to a world where fate can be rewritten by one blow of the blade. In this game, the characters of the popular anime series come to life, each of which is armed with the unique abilities of the sword offering various styles. Regardless of whether you are familiar with the franchise or for the first time plunge into the world of Soul Reapers, the title offers a dynamic combat system that allows you to control the course of the battle.</description></item><item><title>Dead Dragons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Dragons launches history 100 years after the victory of people over the dragons - the events that allegedly brought the world. Now rumors about the return of these creatures encourage the protagonist to investigate the case of a mysterious girl associated with the dragon race. This task develops into a conflict that decides the fate of the whole world and raises the main question of the survival of one of the species in the upcoming confrontation.</description></item><item><title>Star Knightess aura</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</guid><description>Game Description Star Knightess aura - Anime -Nella, the main character of which is a girl with an unusual name of the aura. She falls into a fantastic world called Roya. The heroine is cursed by the king of demons. Its task is to deal with otherworldly monsters every night. At the same time, it is very important not to lose yourself. The girl has insanity and she begins to consider herself a completely different person.</description></item><item><title>Endless Alice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-alice/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-alice/</guid><description>Game Description endless alice - this is an adventure from a third person with an intriguing combination of elements of the Rowlaik and visual design, inspired by anime. Title invites gamers to explore a huge, constantly changing world, where each solution can determine their path. Six characters to choose from, each of which offers its own set of abilities and styles of battle, allow users to combine them in accordance with their style.</description></item><item><title>Threefold Recital</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</guid><description>Game Description Threefold Recital invites gamers to move to bright eastern fantasy, where the overgrown city of Bluscles stands on the threshold of a new era. Once the city was warmed in the rays of the Golden Age, and now it is mired in political instability and tension. Title draws a picture of the world where ancient magic and modern technologies are intertwined, creating a unique mixture that drives the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Bat to the Heavens</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bat-to-the-heavens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bat-to-the-heavens/</guid><description>Game Description Bat to the Heavens offers gamers to accept a unique set of calls. At first glance, it may seem that this is just another platformer, but his mechanic quickly emits him among other games of the genre. Instead of relying on running or jumping, gamers must use the bat as the main tool to move in confusing levels full of obstacles. This is not a typical game where you simply move from point A to point B.</description></item><item><title>Retrowave 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</guid><description>Game Description Retrowave 2 places a player under the control of the supercar of the 1980s, moving along an endless highway surrounded by neon lights and palm trees. The project draws inspiration in an idealized, futuristic interpretation of that era, causing a sense of nostalgia for a period that never existed. This atmosphere provides a complete immersion in the world of Syntveyva. The main lesson is the piloting of transport along the road system on a retro -futuristic background, where aesthetics are built around synthesizer music.</description></item><item><title>Midori no Kaori</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</guid><description>Game Description Midori no Kaori is an adventure game based on the art of peaceful store management. In this relaxed environment, gamers will create and manage their own establishment, drawing on elements of Japanese culture to shape their vision. The title doesn&amp;rsquo;t focus on fast-paced action or intense competition, but rather encourages players to create a space that reflects their personal taste. There are no strict goals or deadlines, making it a refreshing alternative to many other games that prioritize speed or performance.</description></item><item><title>Take Me</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/take-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/take-me/</guid><description>Game Description Take Me is a title that is a distinct fusion of stealth, horror and dark humor. The story centers on Maria, a young woman who finds herself in an unexpected and somewhat strange situation. After attending a masquerade, Maria loses consciousness and wakes up in a strange situation - in the house of a mysterious man named Vitaly. From the very beginning, the gamer finds himself in the role of Maria, trying to get out of a place that seems both mysterious and dangerous.</description></item><item><title>Skufs against lizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skufy-protiv-jascherov/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/skufy-protiv-jascherov/</guid><description>Game Description Skufs against lizards immerse gamers into the life of Skuf Cicetus, an ordinary guy whose world turns upside down as a result of an unexpected invasion of reptiles. History begins with the fact that one night the Skuf hears a strange sound and discovers that his city, Olycnishchensk, is captured by lizards. These are not ordinary garden creatures, but evil, aggressive invaders who came from nowhere. Armed only with his ingenuity and by the fact that he can capture along the road, Skuf takes responsibility to fight off the scaly horde.</description></item><item><title>PSYCHOPOPP GOLD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psychopomp-gold/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/psychopomp-gold/</guid><description>Game Description Psychopomp Gold - This is a remasted version of the popular horror game that sends gamers on a trip along terrible catacombs filled with strange creatures and hidden secrets. In the remaster there are new levels and modes that expand the concept of the original. Adding a third-person species changes the perspective, allowing users to navigate the environment differently. Each corner is fraught with a new test, because gamers must maintain vigilance, making their way through the dark depths.</description></item><item><title>Hidden in My Paradise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hidden-in-my-paradise/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hidden-in-my-paradise/</guid><description>Game Description Hidden in My Paradise is an adventure game with hidden objects that offers fascinating experience for players looking for a combination of research and creativity. The main character, Lali, goes on a journey with Fairy Crown, creating a bizarre atmosphere from the very beginning. The purpose of the duet is to find hidden objects scattered in various zones, each of which has its own unique taste. Such an environment encourages gamers to plunge into various conditions, to look for objects, solving small stories that accompany each mission.</description></item><item><title>Sword Art Online FRACTURED DAYDream</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sword-art-online-fractured-daydream/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sword-art-online-fractured-daydream/</guid><description>Game Description Sword Art Online FRACTURED DAYDREAM gives gamers an unexpected call. This new part of the popular franchise is not a standard VR adventure. Here, familiar landscapes are spinning and turning, temporary lines collide, and past glory is mixed with new problems. Fasten the belts because the system failure in the main game program, Galaxia, throws characters from different stories together. In this project there is no mentality of a lone wolf.</description></item><item><title>Halluci-Sabbath of Koishi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halluci-sabbat-of-koishi/</guid><description>Game Description Halluci-Sabbat of Koishi immerses users in a fantasy setting where they will have to take control of the monster Satori Komeiji Koishi, who is an adventurer and a trained soldier. During the adventure, the hero meets a human witch who is looking for rare ingredients to create potions. Traveling together, the protagonists stumble upon a dangerous mushroom family and undead that they have to fight. Players will explore the forest with miasma and encounter many opponents.</description></item><item><title>Class of '09: The Flip Side</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</guid><description>Game Description Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side is the final chapter of the visual novel series that follows the characters&amp;rsquo; lives as they navigate their post-high school struggles. This installment puts the spotlight on Jack, a character who was previously seen in a supporting role. The adventure focuses on her experiences and the emotional difficulties she faces, which contrasts with the more light-hearted approach of the previous protagonist, Nicole. The narrative structure of Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side allows gamers to make choices that affect the storyline and offers multiple endings depending on the decisions made.</description></item><item><title>TOUHOU GENSOU MAHJONG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-gensou-mahjong/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-gensou-mahjong/</guid><description>Game Description TOUHOU GENSOU MAHJONG is not an ordinary mahjong game. Of course, the core mechanics remain the same - matching tiles, building chalks, challenging Riichi - but here&amp;rsquo;s the kicker: Touhou Project throws its huge cast of characters into the game. Over 120 familiar faces spanning two decades of history bring a new layer of strategy to the classic four-player format. Do you think you have everything figured out with Riichi?</description></item><item><title>LOLLIPOP CHAINSAW RePOP</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lollipop-chainsaw-repop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lollipop-chainsaw-repop/</guid><description>Game Description Lollipop Chainsaw RePOP is a fast-paced hack-and-slash that follows the adventures of Juliet Starling, a high school cheerleader turned zombie hunter. Juliet will face a new wave of the undead and a mysterious outbreak that threatens her hometown. Armed with her trusty chainsaw, Juliet must fight her way through hordes of zombies, from classic Shamblers to more grotesque and dangerous creatures. The combat system is smooth and enjoyable, with a variety of combos and attacks to keep gamers on their toes.</description></item><item><title>Towerborne</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/towerborne/</guid><description>Game Description Towerborne is an action-adventure game set in a world where humanity&amp;rsquo;s cities have been destroyed by a mysterious evil. The only refuge is the Bell Tower, a tower that holds secrets and dangers. Gamers take on the role of Ace, a hero tasked with protecting the inhabitants of the Belfry and uncovering the truth about the evil threatening humanity. Here gamers explore a huge world filled with various creatures and challenges.</description></item><item><title>Yars Rising</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yars-rising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yars-rising/</guid><description>Game Description Yars Rising is an exciting adventure game that will take gamers on an exciting journey through a dystopian future. In the role of Emi Kimura, an experienced hacker, you have to infiltrate the mysterious QoTech corporation. This shadowy organization holds secrets that could potentially change the world. The gameplay is a delightful mixture of 2D platforming, stealth and hacking. As Amy, you&amp;rsquo;ll navigate intricate levels, dodging laser bars, outsmarting security drones, and solving challenging puzzles.</description></item><item><title>Arcane Blast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</guid><description>Game Description InArcane Blast you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself wearing the fur boots of Adrian, a cat mage on a mission. This roguelike adventure throws you into a chaotic world filled with spells, enemies, and the constant threat of a cat&amp;rsquo;s life. Do you think you can handle it? This isn&amp;rsquo;t your average walk in the park, unless that park is filled with evil goblins and fire-breathing lizards. It&amp;rsquo;s all about reflexes here.</description></item><item><title>Ace Attorney Investigations Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Ace Attorney Investigations Collection, a collection of two games featuring the famous prosecutor Miles Edgeworth, invites users to step into his shoes and go on an exciting investigation. Unlike the courtroom drama of the original series, this collection focuses on the detective work that precedes the trial. Gamers will have to collect evidence, interview witnesses and solve intricate mysteries using logical deduction. The collection includes various quality of life improvements to make gameplay more enjoyable.</description></item><item><title>BAKERU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bakeru/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bakeru/</guid><description>Game Description The adventure ofBAKERU, set in fantasy Japan, revolves around a tanuki boy named Bakeru. His mission is to restore order after the chaos unleashed by Oracle Saitaro and his Festival Army. Armed with a mystical drum, Buckaroo sets out on a journey to free Japan from evil spirits. BAKERU takes place across 50 scenes inspired by Japanese prefectures. This vibrant world combines modern Japan with echoes of period dramas to create a captivating backdrop.</description></item><item><title>Kamikaze Lasplanes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</guid><description>Game Description Kamikaze Lassplanes is a visual novel that combines the plot of a novel with the action of a shoot-&amp;lsquo;em-up game. Set in a steampunk world, the dramatic storyline involves two powerful weapons, Lassplanes, and two girls who become them. Gamers navigate a war-torn kingdom and make choices that affect not only the fate of the kingdom, but also their own hearts.
The project introduces Alba Trosset and Hannah Brandenburg, two girls who transform into deadly warplanes.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</guid><description>Game Description Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way is a story about two young women. Studio SPRITE created this cinematic romance. Mina, a loner, withdraws from the world. School becomes a battlefield for her. Her hideout? A room filled with dried flowers. Captive of her thoughts, she wanders through endless days. Meanwhile, Ran, born into wealth, discovers the emptiness beneath the gilded cage. Her perfect life is falling apart.</description></item><item><title>Gundam Breaker 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gundam-breaker-4/</guid><description>Game Description GUNDAM BREAKER 4 hits the gaming scene with a bang as part of the heist gaming franchise. It&amp;rsquo;s all about building and fighting with a set of Gundam models, a concept fans are very familiar with. However, adventure games breathe new life into this formula, offering a deeper and more expansive experience. Customization is the cornerstone of the game. An extensive library of over 250 base sets provides the foundation for creating the Gunpla of your dreams.</description></item><item><title>Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/umamusume-pretty-derby-party-dash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/umamusume-pretty-derby-party-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash is a colorful spin-off that departs from the traditional racing focus. The title is evolving into a playful, party-oriented title. Gamers are immersed in a pixelated world teeming with familiar Umamusume. The Slapdash Grand Prix, the centerpiece, unfolds like a chaotic school festival. Four different events promise laughter, competition and unexpected twists. The pixel relay will spark the fun.
Time plays a crucial role in Umamusume: Pretty Derby - Party Dash.</description></item><item><title>Kamitsubaki City Ensemble</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamitsubaki-city-ensemble/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamitsubaki-city-ensemble/</guid><description>Game Description Kamitsubaki City Ensemble represents a post -apocalyptic world in which music is the key to revival. Girls of artificial intelligence, awakened after the cataclysm, use the magic of songs to restore the destroyed reality. However, their existence is still shrouded in secret. Advencura musical library boasts a variety of compositions from Kamitsubaki Studio and the Musical Isotope series. More than 48 compositions in the basic version of the game and many additional tracks in seasonal pass allow users to explore an extensive musical landscape.</description></item><item><title>Finding Mosey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/finding-mosey/</guid><description>Game Description InFinding Mosey, your feline companion Mosey has mysteriously disappeared. You go in search of him, and your path will depend on the choice you make. Developed by youpiepoopie, this single-player third-person RPG offers a refreshing blend of exploration, storytelling, and whimsical interactions. The search begins. Imagine waking up during a peaceful hike to find Mosey nowhere to be found.
This seemingly simple premise turns into an exciting adventure. The landscape is rife with secrets, and whether your character&amp;rsquo;s path is destructive or peaceful will determine how the quest unfolds.</description></item><item><title>Depersonalization</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</guid><description>Game Description Depersonalization may interest amateurs of anime, Howard Lovecraft and Tactical Japanese Role Games. This is a mixture of TRPG, horror and visual novel. When creating their project, Chinese developers were inspired by the world of space horrors created by an eminent writer. Their creation boasts a detailed and designed pixel 2D graphic in anime style. The project is divided into several modules. Each of them has various finals and branches.</description></item><item><title>Fields of Mistria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fields-of-mistria/</guid><description>Game Description Fields of Mistria invites users to exchange the hustle and bustle for a charming life in the village of Mistria. Here the fields lie between a whispering forest and a sparkling sea. But in Mystria, not everything is so rosy and sunny. The recent earthquake has left its mark, and now there is a strange magic in the air. This is where you come to the rescue. In Mystria you inherit an overgrown estate - a diamond in the bowels of the earth.</description></item><item><title>8th Heaven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/8th-heaven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/8th-heaven/</guid><description>Game Description 8th Heaven immerses gamers in the bright atmosphere of the island, filled with opportunities for social interaction and research. Title is a simulation of life, offering users to navigate in everyday matters and build relationships with a variety of characters. Against the background of fantastic elements, players can interact with the environment in various ways. Whether it is craft, farming or participation in public events, users will always find something to do.</description></item><item><title>Tavern Talk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</guid><description>Game Description Tavern Talk throws you into the very heart of the fantasy kingdom, but not as a powerful warrior or clever robber. Here you will take into your hands the reins of the reign of a cozy tavern Wayfarer&amp;rsquo;s Inn. But this is not an ordinary bartender simulator. The “Traveler” tavern is filled with a whisper and secrets of adventure seekers - your regulars. This is not just thirsty souls who want to drink a mug of ale.</description></item><item><title>Shin Megami Tensei V: Vengeance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shin-megami-tensei-v-vengeance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shin-megami-tensei-v-vengeance/</guid><description>Game Description Shin Megami Tensei V: Vengeance throws you headlong into a deserted Tokyo. Remember that school life? Gone. It was replaced by Daath - a nightmare kingdom infested with demons. You, an ordinary teenager, in one minute turn into Nakhobino - non-human and non-demon. With a mysterious savior at your side, you navigate the treacherous landscape of Da&amp;rsquo;ath, caught between warring gods and demonic tyrants vying for dominance.
This expanded re-release offers a buffet of options.</description></item><item><title>Rabbit and Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rabbit-and-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Rabbit and Steel is a co-op action roguelike that will take you into epic battles. Choose your class, gather your bunny friends and fight to the top of Moon Peak. Months ago, all ties with the Moonlight Kingdom were severed. It is reported that the city&amp;rsquo;s residents are attacking all newcomers. Exploratory expeditions are repulsed or go missing. Every night, a huge white tower appears in the center of the city, reaching towards the stars.</description></item><item><title>Chrono Ark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</guid><description>Game Description Chrono Ark is a classic Japanese-style RPG adventure that supports high-resolution textures, but uses similar camera views and turn-based dialogue and battle system rendering. The story campaign is available for completion only in single-player mode; multiplayer is not provided in this project.
The gameplay is based on gathering a team, which includes 4 characters, for further leveling up and creating an invincible squad, ready to fight on equal terms with all opponents presented in the locations of the bizarre Distorted World.</description></item><item><title>The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty is a visual novel set in China during the turbulent reign of the Chongzhen Emperor. Players take on the role of Liang, a former merchant turned bandit tasked with escorting four girls to the prosperous city of Luoyang. The journey is fraught with danger and moral problems. Liang struggles with the truth behind his mission when one of the girls, Sui, reveals a terrifying secret: their goal is not a luxurious life, but an encounter with a monstrous pig demon.</description></item><item><title>Altushka for skufa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</guid><description>Game Description In the gameAltushka for skufa the state provides a tart for skufa through a special service using personal data. For men who have reached forty years of age, do not have a wife and have a stable outlook on life, the project provides the opportunity to receive a legal altushka through the online service Skufuslugi, using the password from your account.
The game is an immersive first-person scoof simulator created by comic artist Vitaly Terletsky and the author of viral anime videos RIKANI in a short time.</description></item><item><title>Spirit City: Lofi Sessions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spirit-city-lofi-sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spirit-city-lofi-sessions/</guid><description>Game Description Spirit City: Lofi Sessions is not an ordinary adventure game. It combines game elements and practical tools to improve focus and reduce stress. You will find yourself in a virtual world filled with a variety of activities, the essence of which comes down to collecting and interacting with spirits. These aren&amp;rsquo;t just pretty additions to your virtual homes - they play an important role in achieving the goal of making you more productive.</description></item><item><title>Quit Today</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quit-today/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quit-today/</guid><description>Game Description QUIT TODAY is a 2D sid-screen in the action genre with a setting of a corporate workplace. The plot starts on ordinary morning, when the central character enters the office and finds out that all colleagues are confident in his imminent dismissal. Employees perceive this as a betrayal and communicate with him. First, the hero fights off his portfolio, trying to figure out what is happening. Upon learning of the dark affairs in the company, he decides to break through all departments with a battle in order to submit an application for care.</description></item><item><title>Macross -shooting Insight-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/macross-shooting-insight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/macross-shooting-insight/</guid><description>Game Description Macross -shooting Insight - This is a title in which the rapid action of the sword fighting is embodied in a fascinating form. The control of the transformable Veritech fighters, immersing gamers into high -tied missions with lateral scrolling, is based. Target? To fight the formidable forces of Zentradi is a task that requires accuracy, quick reflexes and confident ownership of various mechanics that the game offers. Are you a fan of the Mecha genre or just like good Sidskrollers, this adventure will not leave a place for boredom.</description></item><item><title>Momo and the Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</guid><description>Game Description Momo and the Mine sends a mole-protagonist to a dangerous, abandoned network of dungeons for collecting matches. The player will have to conduct a character through a series of difficult jumping tests, where accuracy is the key to survival. The gameplay requires accurate movement through the hostile surroundings filled with ghosts of tunnels. Success directly depends on mastering responsive controls to overcome each obstacle in the dilapidated structure of the mine, which creates a constant test of skill.</description></item><item><title>Secrets of Grindea</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/secrets-of-grindea/</guid><description>Game Description Secrets of Grindea is an interesting adventure game in which you will need to take control of a hero and go on a long journey through a huge fantasy world in search of new adventures. The game begins with character generation. You will have to create it, change its appearance using an advanced editor, and then decide on the basic skills. After this, you can begin to explore the world around you.</description></item><item><title>Blaz Blue Entropy Effect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazblue-entropy-effect/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blazblue-entropy-effect/</guid><description>Game Description BlazBlue Entropy Effect is a 2D adventure game set in the BlazBlue universe, but with a different genre and style than previous fighting games. It features roguelite elements such as procedurally generated maps, permadeath, and character customization. There is also a rich plot with several endings, depending on the choice of the gamer.
In the game you can choose one of seven unique characters, each of which has its own abilities and character.</description></item><item><title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/granblue-fantasy-relink/</guid><description>Game Description Granblue Fantasy: Relink - an adventure in the vastness of the Heavenly Kingdom, where islands soar among the vast azure expanses. As the captain of a skyship, you&amp;rsquo;ll embark on a journey full of mystery, magic and camaraderie. Together with your faithful companions, such as the energetic dragon Virn and the mysterious Lyria, you will go to Estalucia - a mythical island shrouded in legends.
You have to assemble a team of four people, which will include a variety of sky wanderers who own unique weapons and fighting styles.</description></item><item><title>GU LONG FENGYUN LU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</guid><description>Game Description GU LONG FENGYUN LU is a massive martial arts RPG based on the classic works of Gu Long, the famous Chinese writer. The plot tells about the turbulent times of the end of the Ming Dynasty, when various heroes and factions fought for power and glory. The main character is Feng Yun, a young martial artist traveling across the country, encountering friends, enemies, love, hate, loyalty and betrayal.</description></item><item><title>Tekken 8</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</guid><description>Game Description Tekken 8 is a continuation of the cult fighting game, directly continuing the story of the previous part. In the sequel, many beloved heroes return, and new fighters are introduced. A full-fledged story campaign is presented, telling the dramatic story of Jin Kazama&amp;rsquo;s family. In addition, you will find many different modes, including multiplayer battles, various tests, local co-op, the ability to customize fighters, etc.
The gameplay of Tekken 8 is based on a complex combat system based on memorizing combinations and timings of opponents.</description></item><item><title>Under Night In-Birth II Sys: Celes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-night-in-birth-ii-sysceles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-night-in-birth-ii-sysceles/</guid><description>Game Description Under Night In-Birth II Sys: Celes, the last part of the favorite fighting range, bursts on stage. This is not just a fresh layer of paint, it is a full -fledged evolution, promising a deeper and more dramatic experience of both veterans and beginners. Get ready to join the battle with 24 unique fighters, each of whom can boast of their own style of battle and a background. Three new fighters occupy a central place: Kaguya, elegant, but deadly dancer, owning two blades; Tsurugi, an unshakable wall of a warrior; And Kuon, a creature, challenging the borders of existence to the very borders.</description></item><item><title>Palworld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</guid><description>Game Description Palworld offers you to find and use friends as helpers in a huge and dangerous world. The multiplayer survival game has elements of crafting, and the creatures themselves, discovered by the user in the process, become his pet friends, which help him at all stages of the passage, including the ability to move on them, construct buildings, engage in farming, production, and explore dungeons.
The user finds himself in a virtual universe inhabited by bizarre animal creatures, which in this world are simply called Friends.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</guid><description>Game Description Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout - an adventure action in which a group of people falls on a tropical island equipped with high -tech objects. The territory is governed by AI, which produces a huge number of combat robots and artificially nurtures of dinosaurs. The game is made in the Cyberpanus setting and contains elements of metroid.
Once on the island, it must be examined by opening the results of a monstrous experiment.</description></item><item><title>Noctuary</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</guid><description>Game Description Noctuary - an alloy of visual novel and adventure action, which immerses abortor in the bright world, following the intertwined travels of Fanny and Alina. Being novice arbarars, the duet passes through the rich tapestry of characters, quests and enemies in this colorful kingdom. Distinguished by the inventive mechanics of the battle, the game allows you to smoothly switch the characters between fanchia and Alina, each of which is endowed with various skills and styles of battle.</description></item><item><title>Higurashi whether They Cry Hou+</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</guid><description>Game Description Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ is the final part of its franchise, representing 4 new chapters for playing players. The people who were in the grip of Hinamidzava are now exempted from fate, which riveted them to the repeating events of June 1983. Despite this permission, the story of the region is not completed, and this project proposes to explore many previously hidden worlds.
The narrative Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ departs from the established secret, representing alternative scenarios full of both psychological stress and unexpected humor.</description></item><item><title>Concealed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</guid><description>Game Description Concealed begins with the fact that Maine Jiannan returns to the secondary school of Diinlin after the student exchange program. Her return to school life is interrupted when classmates begin to disappear without explanation. These events are correlated with old, unsolved matters and city legends circulating in the territory of the educational institution for years. Maine Jiannan has to face incidents and find a way to reveal the secrets hidden behind the facade of the school.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Tavern</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-tavern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-tavern/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon Tavern fantasy world allows players to try out the unique adventurer skills, which will participate in erotic adventures. Users will take under the control of different heroes who will have to make their way into the mysterious tavern and face lustful girls and guys. Users will encounter NSFW content throughout the passage, which is designed for an adult audience. The game contains many shots with sexual entertainment between the characters.</description></item><item><title>Bomb Rush Cyberfunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bomb-rush-cyberfunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bomb-rush-cyberfunk/</guid><description>Game Description Bomb Rush Cyberfunk is a dynamic 3D platformer that invites you to explore the world of the near future. Cyberfunk has a huge number of techniques, including high speed movement, parkour, dancing, tags, stunts and much more. This is funkstyle! Find your unique handwriting and font. Fight against law enforcement officers and claim your rights to compete in a huge dystopian metropolis.
The game is distinguished by a cartoon style, made to look like a comic book.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>Hi-Fi RUSH</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hi-fi-rush/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hi-fi-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Hi-Fi RUSH tells the story of the adventures of a guy named Chai. This music lover without one arm decided to take part in the Armstrong project. Vandeley Technologies provides implants to people with physical disabilities, but in return requires them to work for themselves. The hero was supposed to become a scavenger after receiving a mechanical prosthesis. However, during the operation, a music player is accidentally implanted into his chest and gives him new powers.</description></item><item><title>Persona 5 Royal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 5 Royal is the official expansion for the fifth part of the Japanese role-playing video game of the same name, which contains even more unique personas, as well as a lot of interesting quests and items. The plot centers on a seemingly ordinary high school student who goes with his family to Tokyo, where he enrolls in a new school. Soon the main character begins to see inexplicable dreams, in which someone tells the guy that a monstrous catastrophe will befall him in the near future.</description></item><item><title>Mars Base</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</guid><description>Game Description Mars Base will appreciate all fans of science fiction, as Gamer goes to the world of the future, in which travels between planets became possible. Humanity makes a desperate attempt to colonize Mars, but the first settlers will be in a serious danger. The protagonist is one of those who fell into the very first expedition and is obliged to build a huge complex on the surface of the Red Planet, which will make a person’s life away from the ground.</description></item><item><title>RPG Developer Bakin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rpg-developer-bakin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rpg-developer-bakin/</guid><description>Game Description RPG Developer Bakin is a tool for creating games that opens up the ability to create their own role -playing adventures without any encoding experience. Regardless of whether someone creates his first game or wants to finalize the concept, Bakin provides a convenient interface and a set of tools that simplify the game development process. Thanks to an intuitive design, users can immediately begin designing cards, creating characters and storylines.</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Squishcraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squishcraft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squishcraft/</guid><description>Game Description Squishcraft is a series of logical tasks focused on manipulating blocks in a closed space. The fundamental action is the movement of cubes, however, the main feature is the ability to squeeze them together under certain conditions. Such compression can combine several elements into one or change their properties, irrevocably transforming the current state of the riddle. Players have to carefully think through each movement, since one wrong step is able to change the location of the objects and make a dead end.</description></item><item><title>Like Dreamer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/like-dreamer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/like-dreamer/</guid><description>Game Description Like Dreamer acts in a virtual space that operates as a social network in the Bullethell genre-a concept called Bullet-Shell SNS. Players control the character, passing through the streams of shells launched by other users on many digital locations. The main goal is to accumulate a larger number of likes and subscribers from the intra -game audience awarded for performance during the gameplay.
This mechanics allows gamers to build a reputation and increase their recognition on the internal social platform.</description></item><item><title>Neon White</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</guid><description>Game Description Neon White is a first-person adventure platformer with card game elements. The gameplay stands out for its incredible dynamics and speed. It is necessary to quickly react to situations and the environment, because enemies, traps, obstacles and other dangers await you at every turn. Events develop behind the pearly gates of Paradise.
The task in the game is simple and trivial - you need to destroy all the demons in Heaven.</description></item><item><title>Mirror 2: Project X</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror 2: Project X follows the adventures of Dinkudin Naoto, who collaborates with the FBI (Federal Bureau of Research and Conservation). The hero searches for mystical manifestations and otherworldly creatures that sometimes appear in the world. The plot begins with a story with a Demon that infects the body of one of the victims. During the proceedings and investigation of the case, the protagonist will find out the motivations and goals of the creatures in order to make a choice to support or destroy the monster.</description></item><item><title>Idle Calibur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</guid><description>Game Description Idle Calibur combines a study of the open world with tactical RPG tactical and real -time mechanics in real time. The gameplay is focused on the construction of a city, which serves to recruit heroes with special abilities. Battles can be automatically due to IDLE function, or you can take direct manual control of your detachments during the fight. Key tasks include the collection of forces to attack other settlements on the world map and participate in structured tests with bosses for development.</description></item><item><title>Monster Hunter Rise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-hunter-rise/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Hunter Rise is a role-playing adventure set in the fictional village of Kamura. The territory is presented in the form of a vast mountainous area with studied hunting equipment and the original culture of the inhabitants. Players will play the role of hunters, and before starting the game they will have to choose one of several types of weapons, armor or special abilities.
The world is filled with ancient ruins, shrines, dungeons and other locations.</description></item><item><title>Milk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of milk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description The narrative adventureMilk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of mil continues the story of the previous part. The player finds himself in a crazy and mysterious world filled with different combinations of unusual colors and surreal events. On a new journey, you will again have to help the young girl become a little happier. Initially she will be terrified, but as she progresses she will meet new people and realize her own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Sands of Salzaar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</guid><description>Game Description Sands of Salzaar is a strategic game whose actions unfold in the Salzaara desert. Fight with numerous hostile factions, gathering your own army and developing your city. Choose your character, profession and faction, on whose side your army will have to fight. The eastern land is filled with various secrets and you have to solve them all.
Sands of Salzaar events talk about an exotic old empire that once ruled the desert.</description></item><item><title>Honkai Impact 3RD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/honkai-impact-3rd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/honkai-impact-3rd/</guid><description>Game Description Honkai Impact 3RD is a role-playing game with Hak-N-Slash elements, in which players manage three heroes called Valkyrie at once. The fighting is realized in real time. You can move freely across the battle of the battle, switching on the go between the characters. Each protagonist has its own unique features and skills. Combining their capabilities, it is necessary to look for effective tactics against enemies. The project is closely related to Genshin Impact.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Mystia's Izakaya</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-mystias-izakaya/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Mystia&amp;rsquo;s Izakaya takes gamers to a fictional Japanese town called Gensoke, where the young and very charming owner of the local night izakaya lives. This term usually refers to a night drinking establishment where people gather, usually after a night shift, and drink alcoholic beverages. The protagonist is the beautiful Mistia Lorelei, who has a dream to make the entire establishment the most popular in the city.</description></item><item><title>Doki Doki Literature Club Plus!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</guid><description>Game Description Doki Doki Literature Club Plus! is a visual novel, the plot tells the story of a student who joins a literature club. Most of the passage is focused on interactions with the girls who are part of the team. The gameplay is similar to other projects in this genre. The player gets few interactive moments. Only occasionally do elections appear that significantly affect the further passage.
The scenes in Doki Doki consist of static 2D images with drawn anime characters.</description></item><item><title>Kakatte Koi Yo!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</guid><description>Game Description kakatte koi yo! - This is a two -dimensional action platform with the possibility of local multiplayer. This is a real cat’s battle, in which you have to take control of powerful cats and master even more powerful fish to defeat your opponents in a fierce 2D platform battle. This game with charming aesthetics in the Japanese style and irresistibly cute characters is an obligatory game for any cat lover.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Bunny</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</guid><description>Game Description Tiny Bunny is a black and white visual novel containing a considerable amount of horror and sappress. Get lost in the forest, in no case can you hear his voice, otherwise death will follow. The events of the game occur in winter. Something follows you and constantly walks between the trees. There are rumors about constant screams from the forest, and the board with the losses of children is replenished each time.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm Doctor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</guid><description>Game Description Rhythm Doctor is an indie game in which you need to treat patients to the rhythm of music. The music in the game has healing properties. Each patient has unusual problems based on music theory: polyrhythms, hemiols, atonality, syncopation, etc. Rhythm Doctor helps you learn music theory through gameplay. The game contains: more than 20 levels with their own stories; each chapter is a rhythmic concept; many doctors and unique patients; single and cooperative mode; about 50 different visual effects and backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>OMORI</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/omori/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/omori/</guid><description>Game Description Two realities and only one is true in the gameOMORI. A psychological history of surrealism with elements of thriller and horror. The protagonist will have to travel between two dimensions. They are similar, and at the same time radically different. Each reality has its own mysteries and secrets. Explore the new (old) world, make acquaintances with friendly characters who, in another reality, will immediately attack you. Explore the memories of your own path, and finally determine which world is the real reality for you, and which is the other world.</description></item><item><title>Endless Furry Killer 2020</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</guid><description>Game Description The conflict in Endless Furry Killer 2020 puts a player against the endless waves of anthropomorphic opponents. The gamer has to move through two -dimensional arenas with a view of the top intended for continuous battles. The key lesson lies in the shooting of goals in a tense struggle for life with a constant stream of enemies. Such a gameplay requires constant movement and aiming to defeat non -aloscorizing resistance.</description></item><item><title>Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk is a short visual novel with a deep message and unusual execution, made by the efforts of one developer, one of the indie creators. The visual design of the single-player campaign, which is the only game mode, is made using only two colors - purple and black. For completing a short story, which will take about 15 minutes, the developer has prepared three rewards, implementing a small list of achievements.</description></item><item><title>ATRI -My Dear Moments-</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</guid><description>Game Description ATRI -My Dear Moments- is a visual novel with a well-developed plot that leaves food for thought after completing the single-player campaign. Casual control is carried out using the keys on the mouse, allowing you to enjoy reading a work with anime-style slides even for people who are not familiar with games. Recognized masters of this genre worked on the story, which allowed the project to receive many prestigious awards and the love of an audience that loves visual novels.</description></item><item><title>Persona 4 Golden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 4 Golden is a role-playing game about a group of friends who are able to summon demons from the other world. To do this, it is enough to shoot yourself in the temple. The events take place in the small Japanese town of Inaba. The children in Persona 4 are teenagers going through puberty. The heroes are investigating a mysterious series of murders.
The gameplay of Persona 4 Golden contains elements of a visual novel.</description></item><item><title>Senren＊Banka</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</guid><description>Game Description Senren＊Banka is primarily aimed at anime fans. The project uses the appropriate style (including chibi art) and Japanese voice acting. The plot combines romantic, tragic, mystical and humorous elements. The story revolves around supernatural incidents. A group of young people are trying to hide them from ordinary people.
The premise in Senren＊Banka: A Thousand Colors of Love is as follows. A guy named Arichi Masaomi comes to the provincial town of Hoori in the summer.</description></item><item><title>Muse Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Muse Dash is a dynamic rhythm game in anime style, where you will visit many colorful locations, dance to the rhythm of fiery songs and send enemies into outer space. At the center of the story are three charismatic beauties. Having chosen one of the heroines, you need to fight with various creatures in the rhythm of the dance. The action will take place on a colorful background accompanied by dynamic dance music.</description></item><item><title>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</guid><description>Game Description Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy is a re-release of three parts of lawyer simulators combined with adventure. Here the player will not only defend a person in court, but will also begin to investigate the circumstances of the crime, exploring the place, finding evidence, interrogating witnesses. At the trial, the user will listen to both sides, question, look for contradictions in their words, using found objects. The lawyer will be able to defend himself, even if there is only one piece of evidence proving the innocence of the accused, and will also delay time to collect more information.</description></item><item><title>Devil May Cry 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/devil-may-cry-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/devil-may-cry-5/</guid><description>Game Description Devil May Cry 5 is a new third-person slasher for fans of the series. Dante and Nero return to the game universe to defeat all the demons, but will they have a different task? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look. The developers did not touch the game mechanics; they only significantly changed the speed of the battle. If shooters have a subgenre - FPS - then this slasher is an analogue.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Luna Nights</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-luna-nights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-luna-nights/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Luna Nights is a platformer that immerses you in the atmosphere of gothic mysticism. The main character is Sakuya Izaei, who works as a senior maid for the vampire Remilia Scarlet. The girl was calmly doing housework when the mistress deprived her of her powers and sent her to the “Magical Space.” Sakuya is looking for her way home and is eager to find out what her treacherous boss is up to.</description></item><item><title>A Dance of Fire and Ice</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-dance-of-fire-and-ice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-dance-of-fire-and-ice/</guid><description>Game Description A Dance of Fire and Ice-a rhythm explosion created by a small indie company, which has used a minimalistic style of graphic design for its brainchild so that nothing distracts from a study of exciting levels of different complexity. The player needs to constantly be on the alert and not relax for a second, because the game throws difficulties at every turn. Two planets, united by an invisible connection, fall under the control of a gamer (using a keyboard or a gamepad).</description></item><item><title>GRIS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gris/</guid><description>Game Description GRIS is a standard platformer, made entirely in bed colors and a constant atmosphere of suffering of the human soul, capturing the reality of pain and the entire oppressive existence. The personification of everything bad lies in the perception of the girl Gris. She is naive, so she suffered a lot in her life.
The heroine&amp;rsquo;s power lies in her dress, which gives her unique abilities. One element of a woman’s wardrobe can replace the protagonist’s entire world in the forge of pain.</description></item><item><title>Mirror</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror is a visual novel that perfectly combines erotic content, an RPG component, an interactive plot and battles in which you take a direct part. The whole game is built on the “three in a row” principle. In the casual combination of characters, you will only take part in the battle on the Match 3 battlefield. That is, you will win if you can score more points. The game features three heroines who will oppose you throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Shalnor Legends: Sacred Lands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shalnor-legends-sacred-lands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shalnor-legends-sacred-lands/</guid><description>Game Description In Shalnor Legends: Sacred Lands, the player follows the trip of the Elf of the Rinna, which goes to the title territory. Its main goal is to complete the complex task created by the goddess Illeria, in order to ultimately become the chosen champion of this deity. The sacred lands obey one special rule: the entrance to this territory is voluntary, but the exit is given only after the complete passage of the test from the goddess.</description></item><item><title>NEKO Navy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neko-navy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neko-navy/</guid><description>Game Description In Neko Navy, gamers are taken under the management of flying cats, opposing a whole army of various opponents. The main conflict of this scroll-player is unfolding at seven dynamic levels with horizontal scrolling, filled with continuous air battles. Six unique cat pilots are available to choose from, each of which acts as an avatar of the player and has its own characteristics.
The storyline consistently leads to a special final event designed to resolve the main intrigue and complete the main story.</description></item><item><title>TEKKEN 7</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</guid><description>Game Description TEKKEN 7 is a side-scrolling 3D fighting game that tells the true story of the Mishima clan&amp;rsquo;s feud. In the storyline we learn why Heitachi killed his wife, for what reasons Kazuya Mishima survived. The basis of the game&amp;rsquo;s action is a fighting game based on love, family relationships with friendly fights.
Each battle in Tekken 7 is a separate branch in the plot, so after the end of the battle (victory in it), we see a small interactive video of the creation of the entire universe, Kazuya growing up, and the formation of the Mishima clan.</description></item><item><title>NieR: Automata</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nier-automata/</guid><description>Game Description An open-world action-adventure game,NieR: Automata tells the story of androids 2B, 9S and A2 as they battle a dystopia created by powerful machines. All of humanity was evicted from their planet by mechanical creatures that arrived from another world.
In an attempt to retake the Earth from aliens, people send combat robots to somehow resist the invaders. This must be the final attempt, the last hope to get your home back.</description></item><item><title>A magical High School Girl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-magical-high-school-girl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-magical-high-school-girl/</guid><description>Game Description A Magical High School Girl puts a student in a magical dimension, where her only means of protection is the magic that she creates personally. This role -playing game is based on a mechanic that allows the player to come up with the names for his own spells. Based on the words introduced into the interface, the system automatically generates the spontaneous properties and combat effects of the spell.</description></item><item><title>STEINS;GATE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</guid><description>Game Description STEINS;GATE is a visual novel made in an anime style, which is reflected in the appearance of the characters in the single-player campaign. The game received a lot of positive reviews due to its deep dramatic plot, which is not often found in the video game entertainment industry. The narrative is filled with sad moments that touch the soul and make you empathize with the main characters, who are trying to save all of humanity, while paying a terrible price.</description></item><item><title>VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</guid><description>Game Description VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action is an adventure simulator of a bartender in the setting of a dystopian future, where humanity finds itself under the control of huge corporations dictating the rules of life, and nanorobots controlling every area of ​​human activity and the implementation of laws and regulations adopted new world government. Stylistically, this project refers to Japanese games of the last century. The gameplay consists of communicating with bar visitors and providing them with high-quality service in order to build warm, friendly relationships with them.</description></item><item><title>NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-4/</guid><description>Game Description Familiar to many fans of the Naruto series,NARUTO SHIPPUDEN: Ultimate Ninja STORM 4 transcends the fighting game genre, taking the game to the next level. In the final part, we will find out who will win in the confrontation between Naruto and Sasuke. We will learn a lot of details about the 4th Shinobi War, and also go over some aspects of the anime that were missed in previous parts.</description></item><item><title>Touhou kanjuden ~ legacy of lunatic kingdom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-kanjuden-legacy-of-lunatic-kingdom/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Kanjuden ~ Legacy of lunatic Kingdom opens as city legends become tangible events throughout Gansko. The rumor that the Apollo program never reached the moon is gaining strength against the backdrop of the appearance of an enemy army from the lunar capital. At the same time, metal spiders begin to cross the mountains, moving with an even, leisurely step. These machines have a functional, non -biological form, and the earth under them loses vitality: the fog is dissipated, and the vegetation fades.</description></item><item><title>Touhou shinreibyou ~ ten desires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-shinreibyou-ten-desires/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-shinreibyou-ten-desires/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou shinreibyou ~ ten desires begins when strange divine perfumes begin to come from people, Yokaev and fairies. In response to this event, female protagonists of the game go to the other world, suggesting that it is the key to unraveling the phenomenon. The gameplay offers to lead the chosen heroine through a series of levels filled with flitches of shells from opponents. The task is to survive these attacks and destroy the entire opposition, completing the passage of the stage with the boss.</description></item><item><title>Touhou Searensen ~ undefined fantastic object</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-seirensen-undefined-fantastic-object/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touhou-seirensen-undefined-fantastic-object/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Searensen ~ Undefined Fantastic Object is a scroll-player in which the player controls the human character and uses shells to win the antagonists. Any contact with enemy bullets, lasers or opponents themselves leads to a loss of life. When the player’s reserve runs out, the game ends. All items on the screen are collected when moving the controlled character to the upper boundary of the location.
Activation of the function of the slow movement attracts the nearest objects directly to the protagonist, helping in their collection during the battle.</description></item><item><title>CLANNAD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clannad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clannad/</guid><description>Game Description CLANNAD is a visual novel in anime style. The story follows a second grade student who begins a new school year at Hikarizaka School. On his way to school, he meets a girl, Nagisa. It turns out that she is constantly alone and has no friends at all. Depending on the actions you take, the course of the story changes. By helping a girl make friends, you build good relationships with some characters, but at the same time spoil them with others.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description Salvus: aries throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item><item><title>Solitaire Battle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</guid><description>Game Description Solitaire Battle combines the mechanics of the card game with the progression of the Autobatler&amp;rsquo;s Horned. Players are faced with opponents where key interaction is a party in the solitaire of three peaks. Each card taken from the field or from the deck is converted into an offensive or defensive action, creating automated combat sequences. The main task is to strategically disassemble the layout to win enemies, while forming a set of random pool of tools that contribute to powerful synergies and encouraging new combinations in each passage.</description></item><item><title>Zenless Zone Zero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zenless-zone-zero/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zenless-zone-zero/</guid><description>Game Description Zenless Zone Zero is a role -playing game whose action takes place in a world standing on the edge of the abyss, where players take on the role of proxy, a conductor according to alternative dimensions, known as hollows. Players choose one of the two main characters, the wise or Belle, each of which leads the expedition to these dangerous areas. Target? Fight with creatures called Eterials, and go through various tests in these dimensions.</description></item><item><title>Nihongo Quest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nihongo-quest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nihongo-quest/</guid><description>Game Description The fantasy world in** nihongo quest** shows the Gakush universe, where users will be able to create and customize their character to go on adventure. The game is made in the form of Japanese role adventura, where you have to move on a pixel isometric map with a view of the top. Players will participate in step -by -step battles with opponents, pump a hero and face a variety of puzzles, which are based on the creation of more than 1000 words and hieroglyphs.</description></item><item><title>OneShot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oneshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oneshot/</guid><description>Game Description OneShot is an adventure puzzle game with Metroidvania elements. As Niko, you interact with both the character and the world. The gameplay invites you to go through an inventive quest in which you need to find a variety of objects, combining them with each other and using them on the environment, which will allow you to advance through the plot. Stylistically, OneShot is a 2D game from a top-down perspective.</description></item><item><title>Sunrider Legends Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Sunrider Legends Tactics will put a player at the head of the Navy leading his ships along the seas of the fantasy world in the era of sails. You have to command the courts in step -by -step battles, making tactical decisions on maneuvers, positioning and the use of weapons against enemy armades. The adventure will require solving strategic problems in the open sea and participation in special plot events.</description></item><item><title>Zero Escape: The Nonary Games</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Escape: The Nonary Games is a collection of high -resolution visual novels developed by Spike Chunsoft. The mysterious plot involves us in the role of one of the nine abducted people and play the game on the stake of which life is standing.
The game has undergone updates and is now equipped with high graphics, more modern intuitive controls, as well as many new functions, including Japanese and English voice acting!</description></item></channel></rss>