<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Survival on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/survival/</link><description>Recent content in Survival on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/survival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aztecs The Last Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aztecs-the-last-sun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aztecs-the-last-sun/</guid><description>Game Description In Aztecs The Last Sun, the player becomes the ruler of Tenochtitlan, a great state that can win the whole world. The user relies on many tasks, as the head of his own power. He has to develop a city, increase military power and improve the quality of life of citizens. Having taken the control over the Aztecs, you will need to go through the three great centuries, to dominate in the nearest territories and write new pages in world history.</description></item><item><title>Celestial Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celestial-empire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celestial-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Celestial Empire offers to go to the Han dynasty when the Chinese empire was one of the most powerful in the world. Here, the user is given the role of the Governor of the province, who was personally chosen by the emperor. Now, everything must be done in order to make this place better and provide a high standard of living for people. And given that there are a lot of ways for the development of the structure, you can not limit yourself to a single strategy, but try different options.</description></item><item><title>Megabonk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megabonk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megabonk/</guid><description>Game Description In Megabonk, the gamer opposes the endless waves of creatures on randomly generated maps. The main task is to withstand the onslaught for as long as possible, using the mechanics of the slasher and a third -person shooter. With the strengthening of the Horde, survival depends on the destruction of opponents and maneuvering in space. The purpose of each stage is to find and defeat the location boss, opening access to a new, more difficult zone.</description></item><item><title>Arctic Awakening</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arctic-awakening/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arctic-awakening/</guid><description>Game Description Arctic Awakening is an adventure first -person game, the plot of which is served episodically. Once in the vastness of the harsh Arctic, surviving after air flipping. Traveling to travel in the company of a protagonist and drone with pumped artificial intelligence. Together, the heroes need to go on a journey in which they need to find the second pilot in order to get out of snowy lands.</description></item><item><title>Superhero Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/superhero-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/superhero-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description The Superhero Simulator has to protect Goldpine - a city faced with an increase in crime. The player’s main task is to patrol streets, suppress robberies, save civilians and enter into an open battle with villains. Each successful act reveals new abilities, gradually increasing the power of the character. This gameplay cycle is combined with the need to lead an ordinary life, forcing to constantly look for a balance between two different roles.</description></item><item><title>Voyages of Nera</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voyagers-of-nera/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voyagers-of-nera/</guid><description>Game Description Voyages of Nera offers gamers the role of Echo, a descendant of the long -disappeared defenders of the world. The main task is to cross the magical ocean to confront monstrous creatures and the awakening of scattered spirits. This world, negligently, is filled with ancient ruins and original biomes located on its islands. Players can combine up to 10 people for joint swimming around the seas or go on a trip alone.</description></item><item><title>Fata Deum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fata-deum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fata-deum/</guid><description>Game Description Fata Deum is a strategy game with simulation elements, inspired by old-school games about gods who rule a settlement. Shape the city and its inhabitants by terraforming, building houses and increasing the population of people by creating them in your image. What will your society be like? Majestic and highly moral, or will you be able to persuade them to debauchery and demonic essence?
All your whims are reflected in the game world.</description></item><item><title>Misty Judgment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</guid><description>Game Description Misty Judgment begins with the awakening of the protagonist, qi and, from a nightmare in a strange reality without clear memories. Unable to confirm his own personality, he investigates a series of murders filed in the video format with real actors. The main task is the search and analysis of evidence, the comparison of facts and the calculation of the criminal. Any solution affects further events, and the future of the protagonist depends on the deductive abilities of the player.</description></item><item><title>It</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-time-your-majesty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-time-your-majesty/</guid><description>Game Description It&amp;rsquo;s Time Your Majesty is a strategy in which the fate of the whole dynasty falls on the shoulders of the ruler, where each decision is made through the choice of cards. In the role of the monarch, it is necessary to rule the state, trying to achieve prosperity and protect subjects from numerous threats. On the way to greatness, both external enemies and internal problems that require a balanced approach will stand.</description></item><item><title>Metal Gear Solid Δ: Snake Eater</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-snake-eater/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-snake-eater/</guid><description>Game Description Metal Gear Solid δ: Snake Eater is a remake of a classic stealth explosion, telling the story of the origin of the legendary soldier Big Boss. The action unfolds in 1964, during the Cold War, and the main character Naked Snape penetrates the Soviet Union to stop the nuclear threat and resist his former mentor Boss, who went over to the side of the enemy. There is a rich storyline with memorable characters, such as Ozelot, Eve and The End, which throw various challenges.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Map</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond The Map begins with a shipwreck on the outskirts of the known seas, setting the player an immediate task of survival in a mysterious territory. The development of the character is complete without a class system: increasing the level of skills opens up new basic abilities. The search for rare folios with spells around the world provides access to incredible forces, additionally determining the capabilities of the hero.</description></item><item><title>Cleanfall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cleanfall/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cleanfall/</guid><description>Game Description Cleanfall puts a player at the head of the harvesting robot, the only function of which is to maintain cleanliness in the house. This simple task becomes a planetary mission after one techie brought the world closer to his sun. The cataclysm that happened covered the surface with a whirlwind of dust and death, making a restraint of order impossible. In order to bring cleanliness in his house again, the mechanism must first correct the whole world, going down to the underground layers of the planet to start his work.</description></item><item><title>GuntouChables</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guntouchables/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/guntouchables/</guid><description>Game Description GuntouChables sets from 1 to 4 players in the role of prepared survivors in the conditions of post -apocalypse. The main task is to conquer ground territories at hordes of hostile, continuously evolving mutants. These creatures constantly invent new methods of eliminating heroes, bringing fresh threats with every battle. The gameplay is tied to the confrontation of this dynamically changing enemy force.
Promotion in the plot is tied to the execution of missions for which Upcrates are issued with currency and perks to increase the chances of survival.</description></item><item><title>Heartworm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heartworm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heartworm/</guid><description>Game Description Heartworm is a classic Survival Horror with elements of a psychological thriller. A girl named Sam with cut legs leads a closed lifestyle and does not want to leave her home. From the very beginning, the game hints that due to difficult childhood a young woman began to have problems with the psyche. Once she receives a video cassette with strange contents. Having looked at the record, the heroine suddenly comes to his senses in a completely different place.</description></item><item><title>Prospector</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</guid><description>Game Description Prospector begins with arrival at someone else&amp;rsquo;s world, having only a set of tools at its disposal. The primary task is to collect the planet’s resources for the construction of the basis for the base. Players build structures, explore the environment, and then establish automated production lines. For construction, everything is used, from primitive materials to unknown alien substances found on the landscape.
Gradually, a simple avantopost turns into a complex object with an optimized working process.</description></item><item><title>Grounded 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grounded-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grounded-2/</guid><description>Game Description Grounded 2 returns players to a reduced state in a much larger world. The new environment was the playground, now representing a spacious area from man -made structures and overgrown nature. Survival makes it necessary to create weapons and armor, as well as the construction of defensive bases to confront local threats. This title allows you to explore the open territory alone or in cooperative online mode. The main goal is to search for hidden secret secrets in the struggle for existence in this environment.</description></item><item><title>Dinosaurs Dominion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dinosaurs-dominion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dinosaurs-dominion/</guid><description>Game Description Dinosaurs Dominion is a single -user adventure focused on territorial conquest. The player has to control the dinosaur for battles, evolution and gradual seizure of control over the environment. Progress in each passage is earned through the study of the world and victory in battle. The defeat returns the creature by the beginning of his journey, which is a key feature of Roguelite design. The choice of 14 accessible species, from agile scouts to massive predators, provides different approaches to this survival cycle.</description></item><item><title>Grimshire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimshire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimshire/</guid><description>Game Description Grimshire represents a script with a spreading plague that threatens an isolated mountain settlement. The player arrives here after the absorption of his hometown with chaos, getting a chance for a new beginning on the local farm. Its role consists in managing the economy, collecting forest gifts and ensuring a permanent reserve in the cellar. The main task is to prevent bloating of food in preparation for the arrival of the disease, which requires competent supplies to maintain everyone&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Ascension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Ascension puts the player in the lord position with the task of creating his own possession in an empty plot of land. The initial stage includes a systematic collection of provisions and materials - basic elements for any settlement. These assets then go to the construction of the first buildings to create a stronghold in the world. Subsequently, the focus shifts the recruitment of military detachments that form an army to protect native lands and spread the influence of the outside.</description></item><item><title>The Wandering Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wandering-village/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wandering-village/</guid><description>Game Description Once in The Wandering Village on an infected planet, people have no choice but to poison the back of a giant creature that can move in the process. The urban planning simulator is made in a post -apocalyptic setting and offers to lead a small society that saved, settling on the essence and gradually rebuild the new world.
Having moved to the virtual universe, the user observes as some toxic substances that appeared due to mysterious plants, quickly spread on the ground by giving out toxic disputes.</description></item><item><title>Nelumbra</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nelumbra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nelumbra/</guid><description>Game Description Nelumbra puts the player in the role of the bearer of light, character who fell into a temporary loop without memories of the past. The main task is to fight for the truth of one’s own existence, and the price of this is unknown. Survival is built on the use of rhythmic car autocat and jerks as the surrounding light is extinct, which steadily pumps stress with each action.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fairy Tale: Dreamland Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-fairy-tale-dreamland-survivors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-fairy-tale-dreamland-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Dark Fairy Tale: Dreamland Survivors puts a player under the control of Pinocchio, a puppet who has trapped in a hostile and distorted space of nightmares. The character moves around this world by controlling one hand, while the system is automatically introduced to creatures from rethought fairy tales. The promotion depends on the collection and absorption of more than 100 different forbidden dreams of dreams, each of which modifies offensive and defensive capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Chinese Frontiers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chinese-frontiers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chinese-frontiers/</guid><description>Game Description Chinese Frontiers is an atmospheric immersion in the time of ancient China, where users will be able to feel the life of a simple resident of the village. The game is a simulator of life where you have to take under the management of the employee, which is working on the construction of a great Chinese wall. Gamers will be able to test various types of crafts of that time, and will also monitor the character indicators, giving him food, water and rest in time.</description></item><item><title>Len's Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lens-island/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lens-island/</guid><description>Game Description Len&amp;rsquo;s Island is an open world adventure, which is the construction of a base with the possibility of a pharmacy, craft, research and battles. Each player is able to build his own house of dreams, care for crops and simply explore the secrets of the island. If you manage to find a sword, then you can go to more dangerous adventures, fighting with numerous enemies guarding the treasures.</description></item><item><title>Thrive: Heavy Lies the Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Thrive: Heavy Lies The Crown is an exciting medieval fantasy urban planning strategy that will check your leadership qualities and make you make a difficult choice to ensure the survival and prosperity of your kingdom. In this game, the fate of your people largely depends on the decisions you have taken, and the path you have chosen - favor or tyranny - will determine your heritage. The will is your weapon, you must build and strengthen your city, form the land and develop your kingdom with the help of a deep technological tree.</description></item><item><title>The Alters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-alters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-alters/</guid><description>Game Description The Alters is a science fiction adventure that immerses in the world of choice and consequences. Imagine yourself stuck on an unfriendly planet, where there is no one to rely on, except for your own ingenuity. This is the intriguing plan of this innovative game, which immerses in the world of parallel lives and alternative realities. Going on this journey, you take on the role of Jan Dolsky, a worker who made an emergency landing on a foreign world and is now facing the problem of survival and salvation.</description></item><item><title>Neuroshima Hex</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuroshima-hex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuroshima-hex/</guid><description>Game Description Neuroshima Hex is a post -apocalyptic tactical competition adapted from the board game system. The course of events is built on strategic solutions on the hexagonal field. Opponents use various detachments, technologies and their special skills for the implementation of military plans. Mechanics implies the arrangement of chips and determine the moment of their action.
In Neuroshima Hex, players fall into the world, surviving the decline of nature, where there is a struggle for resources.</description></item><item><title>Elden Ring Nightreign</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring-nightreign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elden-ring-nightreign/</guid><description>Game Description Elden Ring Nightreign is a separate part of the Universe, where the action takes place in Limgrava, the very first district with the open world, presented in the original series. However, this is not the usual version of Limgrave. The world here is procedurally generated, which means that each passage offers unique experience. Users fall into the game with their team of two people, each of whom has their own abilities.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Survive the Fall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survive-the-fall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survive-the-fall/</guid><description>Game Description The disaster in Survive The Fall occurred in 2023, when a huge asteroid crashed into the ground. Most of the population died, and those who were in distant places in the world survived. The player moves to the post -apocalyptic environment, where it is necessary to engage in the construction of settlements, using tactical and strategic elements. An extensive and open world includes many good lands, forests or destroyed cities.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-call-of-prypiat-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-call-of-prypiat-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition puts the player in the role of Major Degtyarev, an intelligence officer sent to the cover under the cover. Its task is to find out the causes of the failure of the military operation and the disappearance of the detachment. Events unfold in the Pripyat region, where everything is permeated with dangers: anomalies, radiation, hostile groups and an unstable situation.
In Stalker: Call of Prypiat - Enhanced Edition, each action has consequences.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-clear-sky-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-clear-sky-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky - Enhanced Edition transfers a gamer to the role of a mercenary named Scar, forced to survive among warring groups, unstable abnormalities and deadly emissions. The action takes place to the events of the previous title of the series, demonstrating the origins of the territorial split in the zone. The basis of the mechanics is the system of wars of fractions - with its help, the user is able to change the alignment of forces between armed formations.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chornobyl - Enhanced Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-shadow-of-chornobyl-enhanced-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-shadow-of-chornobyl-enhanced-edition/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chornobyl - Enhanced Edition transferred gamers to the alienation zone around the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, where anomalies, armed groups and mutants act outside the law framework. Movement in this territory depends on food supplies, the level of radiation, the number of cartridges and relations with other characters. Plot tasks can be performed in different ways using research, shootings and dialogs. The environment is a constant danger, which requires attention to details, and not following the finished routes.</description></item><item><title>Blacksmith Master</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</guid><description>Game Description Blacksmith Master is an exciting simulator in which you can control your own blacksmiths, starting with mining and precious stones to the design and sale of finished products. Your task will be tortured everything - from weapons and armor to instruments and kitchen utensils - to earn on your craft and become a real master of blacksmithing.
Here you can lead your own medieval blacksmith and you will control the entire process: the extraction of resources, their processing and production and sale of finished products.</description></item><item><title>Cubic Odyssey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cubic-odyssey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cubic-odyssey/</guid><description>Game Description Cubic Odyssey is a large -scale project with an open setting that combines the elements of research, survival and creativity. Users move according to procedured planets, interact with a variety of ecosystems and fight with the upcoming force known as red darkness. In the universe there are planets with a changing environment, ancient ruins and settlements inhabited by NPC fraction. Each place is complex tasks and opportunities that require strategic resource management and adaptation.</description></item><item><title>Dino Path Trail</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-path-trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-path-trail/</guid><description>Game Description Dino Path Trail shows the world where dinosaurs survived to the era, similar to the wild West, setting a person to survive in this altered land. The main goal includes the search and salvation of a stolen sister through the intersection of various lands full of dangers. The chances of surviving are strongly dependent on the solutions and actions of the player as part of the structure of this action-rowlaine, where it is necessary to repulse predators, hostile people and elements.</description></item><item><title>Revenge of the Savage Planet</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revenge-of-the-savage-planet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revenge-of-the-savage-planet/</guid><description>Game Description Revenge of the Savage Planet throws the player into alien locations. The character turns out to be thrown on the edge of the space by the former corporate employer. The central task is to move around alien territories, collecting resources and finding improvements to organize home and revenge the corporation, guilty of its position. The study of the area includes the detection of hidden objects and the interaction with the environment.</description></item><item><title>Knights of the Crusades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</guid><description>Game Description Knights of the Crusades sends a player during the first crusades, where a lone knight will come to begin. It is ahead to go to the foundation and management of the holy order, choosing the Templars or creating their own fraction. The process combines real -time elements with the construction of settlements and management within the sandbox. You have to solve problems related to war, religious influence, diplomacy and strategic planning.</description></item><item><title>Ratopia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratopia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratopia/</guid><description>Game Description Ratopia is an original strategy that challenges genres thanks to a unique combination of survival, sandbox and a city construction simulator. Get ready to plunge into a huge and exciting world that will captivate you with its endless possibilities. Here you have to create your ideal city and manage it, but be careful, because every resident has its own characteristics and wealth that you must take into account. No one said that it would be easy, but with the right selection of jobs and services, you can make your residents happy, and your economy is prosperous.</description></item><item><title>Survivalist: Invisible Strain</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</guid><description>Game Description Survivalist: Invisible Strain - continuation of the game Survivalist. Events take place near Vancouver in Canada. The zombivirus epidemic has been going on for 10 years. People managed to erect settlements, well -guarded from revived dead. However, the defense of the shelters fell for unknown reasons. The survivors go to the hill, hoping to build new outposts.
In the game, the survivor: an invisible strain can create your own community.</description></item><item><title>Darkwater</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkwater/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkwater/</guid><description>Game Description Darkwater gives gamers to command a submarine, which ended up in an ice trap on a foreign planet. This is a cooperative horror, designed to work from 1 to 4 people. Survival implies navigation in a hostile environment, clashes with enemy courts and underwater life forms, as well as an active search for resources necessary for further work of submarine. Success depends on the implementation of the necessary actions for existence in underland conditions.</description></item><item><title>Escape the Mad Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Escape the Mad Empire is a Roguelike Dungeon Crawler, promising a mixture of tactical battles and base control. Players collect a detachment of heroes whose survival depends on strategy and resourcefulness. The combat system requires an attentive approach. Each move, each action has weight. Using the area, shelters and objects becomes the second nature, when users move around the battlefield with high rates. The Title is not amenable to simple classification, combining the elements of Roguelike, RPG and Base-Building into unique experience.</description></item><item><title>Laser Tag Massacre</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/laser-tag-massacre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/laser-tag-massacre/</guid><description>Game Description Laser Tag Massacre puts the player in the script in the spirit of slasers of the 1980s. Events unfold on the night of Halloween, when a group of 5 friends is going to celebrate a holiday in a large abandoned gym. This dilapidated structure is located in the remote part of the Campinas, Brazil, which isolates the characters from any external assistance. Their plan for the usual match in the laser tag is sharply interrupted by the appearance of a hostile presence, shifting the focus from resting for self -preservation.</description></item><item><title>Forever skies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forever-skies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forever-skies/</guid><description>Game Description Forever skies is an atypical survival in the world of post -apocalypse, where the player will become the captain of the airship. Unfortunately, the protagonist is the only crew member, but even this does not reduce the number of his problems. After all, he still needs food, which is practically no in the air with the exception of rare birds. And the technique tends to break, and it requires constantly replacing old details.</description></item><item><title>Crashlands 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crashlands-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crashlands-2/</guid><description>Game Description Crashlands 2 Returns you to the crazy world of Wuanop. Flux Deibs, all the beloved intergalactic trucker, was again in a difficult position. This time forget about the transportation of goods. It is about reunite with old friends and getting new, eccentric. But these are not only calls to the old cosmic friends. We are talking about the connections that you create. Friendship with Voanop’s colorful character opens the door, and literally.</description></item><item><title>Hollow Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollow-survivors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollow-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hollow Survivors is Rogue -Like Dungeon Crawler, in which gamers take on the role of one of the last rational Hollow in the world captured by terrible monsters. Then the users have to fight with the endless waves of enemies, rising to the tower, which is under the control of the ominous cult. Along the way, you will find a variety of weapons, improvements and synergistic effects that will help you survive and survive.</description></item><item><title>Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</guid><description>Game Description Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days transfer the player to Walton City, Texas, 1980 sample, covered by a zombie epidemic. The gamer has to lead a detachment of surviving through the dying metropolis. The key task of the gameplay is to move the wards between temporary shelters, taking care of their condition. It is necessary to find provisions, make objects and repulse constant danger from the dead who filled the streets.</description></item><item><title>Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</guid><description>Game Description Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder can be attributed to the simulators of the colony and real -time strategies. There are also survival elements in the indie project. He has high reigree due to the random generation of cards. The gamer here is offered to establish a settlement and help it develop to a full -fledged city. At the same time, it is necessary to monitor the needs and mood of the townspeople.</description></item><item><title>The Last of US Part 2 Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-of-us-part-2-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-of-us-part-2-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description The Last of US Part II Remastered goes to the PC and transfers the narrative experience of the Naughty Dog to a new platform. Players fall into a world where survival intersects with personal revenge, following the main characters of Ellie and Abby along the interconnected plot lines. The game takes place in the post -pandemic landscape and transfers participants in territories, transformed infection and human conflicts.
Jackson, Wyming, serves as an initial background on which the characters are in the framework of the survivor community.</description></item><item><title>Emissary Zero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emissary-zero/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/emissary-zero/</guid><description>Game Description Emissary Zero is a title in which a group of people under cover of darkness enters an unfamiliar building. With minimal tips from a remote manager, they are looking for something called the moon, hoping to leave him intact. The structure is unpredictable, it shifts as they move, forcing them to navigate in space, which refuses to be understandable. Each sound alone becomes a potential threat; Together, coordination becomes both a tool and a risk.</description></item><item><title>Voids Vigil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voids-vigil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voids-vigil/</guid><description>Game Description Voids Vigil is an arena with an Autoboy in the Rogue -Lite style, where the action never stops. Gamers will have to clean the one who flooded the arena of the hordes of robots armed only with automatic weapons, drones and many special abilities. Title maintains interest, offering a variety of modes and complexity settings, which allows you to always find new tests. As you advanced, users should competently dispose of their koga - the key resource, which is used in stores that appear throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Card Survival: Fantasy Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Card Survival: Fantasy Forest is a survival simulator that immerses in the very heart of the ancient forest. Title takes users to a world where nature is not only living, but also has its own mind. Here, gamers build a house, overcome daily difficulties and interact with a rich ecosystem full of wild animals, magical creatures and unpredictable forces. Every day brings new difficulties associated with survival: from hunger and health management to solving problems with the weather and seasons.</description></item><item><title>R.E.P.O.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/repo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/repo/</guid><description>Game Description **R.E.P.O. **- this is a online cooperative in the genre of Horror, in which gamers are united to collect valuable objects surrounded by terrible dangers. In this intense adventure, up to six gamers can immerse it, each of which is equipped with a tool based on physics, designed to capture and transport objects. What is the difficulty? Take care of the cargo, moving through the enchanted spaces, and not allow something to break along the way.</description></item><item><title>Dawnfolk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</guid><description>Game Description In Dawnfolk, the action of which takes place in a world covered by darkness. As a ruler of the kingdom lost to the shadows, you must restore and protect your people. With the help of a mystical creature, Luer, you must navigate in the darkness and work on the restoration of light on Earth. In the center - research, resource management and decision -making when you restore your kingdom from scratch.</description></item><item><title>Mind Over Magic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mind-over-magic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mind-over-magic/</guid><description>Game Description The Mind Over Magic offers the player to become the master of the magic school located over a dangerous underground maze. You have to design, build and manage all aspects of your school, from classes to dormitories, from gardens to laboratories. You also have to train your students with various magical skills, such as lost lasso, production of potions, growing plants and necromancy.
But your school is not a safe refuge.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</guid><description>Game Description The urban planning simulator-Foundation-will allow you to plunge in the medieval era, build a whole settlement, make people happy at the expense of unique structures, as well as understand the history of the construction of houses and churches, on which there was a lot of emphasis due to constant rivalry of religious directions.
We will build houses and other structures with smart brushes. They will allow us not to exceed authority and put only those buildings that will meet environmental norms and criteria.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Diddy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</guid><description>Game Description Diddy begins with a mission to destroy a dark party held in a private estate. Players in the Company of Eminam and 51 Centers must stop the owner’s atrocities and stop the meeting. The main task is the salvation of Justin B, who is in the territory after the accumulation of a state fraud. The detachment confronts the army of Selebri, acting as a guards, ready to defend the estate and its owner.</description></item><item><title>My Summer Car</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</guid><description>Game Description My Summer Car is a life simulator of a Finnish, a 19-year-old boy who lives in a dacha in picturesque forests. His relatives on vacation in Tenerife, the whole house, and most importantly, garage, at his disposal. Created on Unity, thanks to the flexibility of this engine, and it became possible to add so much mechanic, which are below.
Your main occupation will be the restoration of the ancient Satsuma AMP car made on the basis of a real car - Datsun 100a.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Swordhaven: Iron Conspiracy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swordhaven-iron-conspiracy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swordhaven-iron-conspiracy/</guid><description>Game Description Swordhaven: Iron Conspiracy will dips you with your head in full intrigue of the new dragon. Forget about hard classes - here you pave your own path. Each decision by you determines your journey on this richly detailed kingdom. Imagine that you have to reveal a secret conspiracy that can destroy the fragile world of the new dragon. That is what awaits you. Each of your quest is a thread in a grand tapestry, and the choice you make can rewrite history.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of QUD-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>The Thing: Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-thing-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-thing-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description The Thing: Remastered returns to Antarctica, continuing the story of the 1982 film. Nightdive Studios resurrects the 2002 horror third-person shooter with a sequel to Outpost 31. Players play as Captain J.F. Blake, commander of a US Special Forces rescue team sent to investigate the aftermath of a scientific expedition.
Gameplay centers on facing off against shape-shifting alien creatures in a challenging environment. Team management becomes one of the core mechanics in which players must navigate complex interpersonal dynamics and potential contagion among team members.</description></item><item><title>Unknown Tapes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unknown-tapes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unknown-tapes/</guid><description>Game Description Unknown Tapes immerses you in a primitive nightmare. Developed by Traviteam Games, this horror game uses found personnel to place you in the very center of the modern world in which dinosaurs occurred. Remember the &amp;ldquo;Jurassic Park&amp;rdquo;, where all safety measures were torn and replaced by rusty nails, and the heart freezes in tension. Here you are not a hero with a flamethrower, but prey. Each rustle of foliage, every creak of floorboards is a potential death.</description></item><item><title>Space Architect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</guid><description>Game Description Space Architect is a simulator where gamers have to become in place of the manager of the space station. The main goal is to build, maintain and expand the space station, simultaneously coping with the difficulties of resource management and interstellar trade. In the beginning, users are faced with a serious financial burden - a huge debt to a powerful megarporace, which forces them to make complex decisions on how to get income and stay afloat in endless cosmic voids.</description></item><item><title>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stalker-2-heart-of-chornobyl/</guid><description>Game Description S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl is a first-person shooter in a post-apocalyptic world. The events of the game will develop in the exclusion zone formed as a result of the disaster at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. In 2006, a new catastrophe occurred, which led to various physical, chemical and biological processes, creating many anomalies, artifacts and generating a large number of mutants.
The gameplay is a classic FPS with elements of a role-playing game, immersive sim and horror.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Command is a strategy with elements of a bagel and a card game. You need to collect resources, form a unique deck of cards and fight against robots. When gathering an army, you need to study the enemy&amp;rsquo;s tactics in order to deal a crushing blow to him. While exploring locations, you need to obtain resources to build buildings and hire units. There are factories, auxiliary buildings, turrets and special weapons of mass destruction.</description></item><item><title>Space Trash Scavenger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</guid><description>Game Description Space Trash Scavenger takes place in a future where humanity has reached for the stars and survival means using what others have left behind. Here, gamers take on the role of scavengers operating in a galaxy littered with the rubble of an ancient conflict. The journey begins with a space drill - a multi-purpose node floating among the remains of abandoned ships, forgotten outposts and asteroid fields. This is not just a shelter, but a factory, equipped with critical systems for agriculture, defense and waste processing - all necessary to turn interstellar waste into something valuable.</description></item><item><title>Bullet Runner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</guid><description>Game Description The dynamic shootouts inBullet Runner show the adventures of a pixelated man who is forced to resist against a crowd of evil opponents. The game is a top-down action shooter where you have to fight with various opponents. The project is filled with fast and active gameplay, where users can test the speed of their reaction to current events. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to move around the map and shoot enemies using a wide arsenal of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Mirthwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirthwood/</guid><description>Game Description Mirthwood is a fun medieval fantasy sandbox game that combines the charm of a life simulation with the thrill of an RPG. It offers gamers the opportunity to create their own adventure in a new country, escaping their war-torn homeland. The game offers two main paths: settle down and build a farm, trade with other cities and start a family; or explore a huge open world and fight bandits, monsters and other dangers.</description></item><item><title>Sofie: The Echoes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sofie-the-echoes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sofie-the-echoes/</guid><description>Game Description Sofie: The Echoes is an adventure game that immerses gamers in an exciting storyline. The main character, Sophie, goes on a quest, guided by personal interests. In search of her husband and son, she goes through a world full of difficulties and trials. In this world, the boundaries between reality and echoes of the past are blurred. Every moment in the adventure feels weighty as users follow Sophie’s path through treacherous landscapes and emotional turmoil.</description></item><item><title>Sulfur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sulfur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sulfur/</guid><description>Game Description Sulfur is an adventure adventure, in which the elements of the first -person shooter are combined with traditional role -playing games and mob. Gamers take on the role of a character, moving around a complex world, filled with problems and capabilities. The gameplay is focused on battles and research, forcing users to think strategically, faced with various enemies. Each collision requires a different approach, which makes the adaptation key.</description></item><item><title>Dark Hours</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-hours/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dark-hours/</guid><description>Game Description Dark Hours is a cooperative horror game for survival created by Piece of Cake. Here users are sent to a robbery, which sharply turns into the unknown. Locked in an auction house, they face a demonic being, which violates their plans. What began as a mission to theft of valuable things quickly turns into a battle for survival. The atmosphere changes when gamers understand that now their goal is to get out alive.</description></item><item><title>The Dead Await</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</guid><description>Game Description The Dead Await immerses users in gloomy adventures, where it is necessary to survive during the zombie apocalypse. The users will have to participate in cruel step-by-step battles with walking dead, gradually gathering their own deck with cards-abilities. It will be possible to configure and pump the characters in the detachment, engage in the study of the open world, to extract resources, trade with secondary NPS and manage its own caravan for survival.</description></item><item><title>Eden Crafters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</guid><description>Game Description Eden Crafters throws glove in the hands of survival and automation lovers. In this cooperative adventure with the open world, players will turn to turn a hostile planet into a hospitable refuge for humanity. Think about this as a space project of reconstruction - harsh conditions, fluids of the house of dreams. Task? Overcome the unpleasant habits of the planet and build a new house for humanity. Imagine radioactive zones and insidious landscapes are not the best real estate.</description></item><item><title>Diplomacy is Not an Option</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</guid><description>Game Description InDiplomacy is Not an Option the player becomes a feudal lord in the Middle Ages. The main character is going through a midlife crisis. Every day the protagonist comes up with hundreds of ways to improve his own economy, how to properly lead his subjects and competently develop the city. He lived like this for a long time. He was tired of monotonous and meaningless intellectual stress.
New adventures in the life of the central character begin when hordes of monsters began to attack settlements, and the townspeople rebelled together.</description></item><item><title>The Last Plague: Blight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-plague-blight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-plague-blight/</guid><description>Game Description The Last Plague: Blight is a survival simulator in the open world, which is generated randomly. The user controls one character and watches what is happening from above. The camera is tied to the hero. It is allowed to rotate. Indi-project uses medieval setting with a light fantasy raid.
The events of the Blight game occur in a world where there is a filth. This is the name of a mysterious disease.</description></item><item><title>Start Over</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/start-over/</guid><description>Game Description Start Over is a multiplayer survival simulator set on a desert island, providing an immersive experience. You have to build a base, make the necessary equipment and defend against waves of enemies. The game features a realistic and dynamic environment where you need to adapt to constantly changing weather conditions, hunt animals, collect resources for survival and engage in trading items to earn money. As you explore the island, you can discover hidden secrets such as secret caves, ancient ruins, and even military camps.</description></item><item><title>DreadHaunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadhaunt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadhaunt/</guid><description>Game Description DreadHaunt is a 4v1 multiplayer horror and deception game in co-op and PVP. Here one of the users becomes possessed and turns into a ghost, and the rest must survive. The action takes place in a country plunged into chaos as a result of mass demonic possession. Gamers take on the role of an E-Class field agent tasked with securing, containing and protecting the source of evil to investigate and save the country.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk 2 is a continuation of the survival game, which is based on management and construction. The events of the game take place 30 years after the catastrophe that covered the Earth. Now the planet has experienced severe cooling and people are suffering from constant frosts. In the urban planning simulator, you are asked to try on the role of a hero who, in the process, must lead an entire metropolis and take care of the well-being of local residents.</description></item><item><title>Bloody Hills</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloody-hills/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloody-hills/</guid><description>Game Description Bloody Hills invites gamers into a gripping survival horror scenario set within the walls of a remote forest camp. Here, calm gave way to horror, turning the camp area into a chilling place where danger lurks at every step. At the center of the story is a relentless killer, known only by the nickname Hiker, who wanders through the forest with sinister intentions. As night falls, the atmosphere changes, creating an oppressive heaviness that seems to tighten around users, intensifying the fear that grips them to the core.</description></item><item><title>Seed of Heroes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seed-of-heroes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seed-of-heroes/</guid><description>Game Description Seed of Heroes is a game where the player controls a detachment of warriors, moving through numerous worlds with a view of the top. The goal is to defeat opponents and earn the right to enter the halls of Valhalla. During this trip, it is necessary to participate in the battles of the Bullet Heaven genre, to resist many enemies and collect treasures to strengthen their power. Progress is built on Roguelite elements, discovering after several attempts to access new heroes, objects and other game capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Trail of Ayash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trail-of-ayash/</guid><description>Game Description The world ofTrail of Ayash is based on the myths and legends of the inhabitants. An open game location allows you to freely explore the area and learn more about the life of Native Americans. The player will encounter various tribes competing with each other, participating in diplomacy, organizing wars and expansion. The main character is Ayash, a respected man in his own faction. One day, a close person frames Ayash, and after that he is expelled from the tribe.</description></item><item><title>Panic In The Woods</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panic-in-the-woods/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panic-in-the-woods/</guid><description>Game Description Panic In The Woods is a survival and loot horror game that immerses gamers in a chilling woodland environment. The game can be played solo or in co-op with up to four gamers, playing as boy scouts lost in a haunted forest. The goal is simple: survive the relentless pursuit of the monstrous creature. Communication and strategy are of utmost importance. Users use walkie-talkies to coordinate their movements and exchange important information.</description></item><item><title>Hive Jump 2: Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hive-jump-2-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Hive Jump 2: Survivors is a sci-fi role-playing adventure game with action elements. In this adrenaline-pumping sequel to the acclaimed action-platformer, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself the only survivor of your squad, stranded on an alien planet. Armed with only your guns and your trusty jetpack, you set out on a mission of revenge. Here you have to fight relentless waves of killer insects. What is your goal? Destroy these swarms of aliens and collect their valuable entrails.</description></item><item><title>Satisfactory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</guid><description>Game Description Satisfactory is an open-world first-person adventure where you build industrial buildings, explore, and fight. Explore a new planet alone or with other users. Build huge structures and do whatever you want in assembly line paradise. You are an employee of FICSIT Corporation.
Players can build wherever they want. Expand production in all directions, install factories in the mountains, forests or plains. Mine natural resources found all around you. Build complex networks and transport routes, automate all mechanics, without forgetting about safety.</description></item><item><title>Hit of Chernobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</guid><description>Game Description Hit of Chernobyl immerses users in a post-apocalyptic environment where survival is of paramount importance. Finding themselves in an area contaminated by an unspecified disaster, gamers take on the role of an adventurer. He must navigate a landscape full of dangers, not only from the environment, but also from other characters. The world is populated by marauders, journalists and thrill seekers, each with their own motives. Finding unique artifacts becomes the main task, requiring users to overcome a landscape replete with difficulties.</description></item><item><title>Don't Stare</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-stare/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-stare/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Stare is a stealth platformer that weaves together gameplay and storytelling in a thoughtful and engaging way. You enter the world as an introvert, navigating an environment filled with extroverts who want to make small talk, invite you to a party, or just chat about their day. However, the introvert has his own mission, much more personal than just making new acquaintances. You are not here to join the crowd, but to reunite with old friends who, for unspoken reasons, have grown apart.</description></item><item><title>Star Trucker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-trucker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-trucker/</guid><description>Game Description InStar Trucker imagine yourself speeding through space, a lone trucker in a galaxy of endless possibilities. Welcome to a game that combines the spirit of the open road of American trucking with the vastness of space. You are not just a driver, you are the captain of your destiny in a space suit. What is your mission? Transport cargo, search for salvaged items and communicate with other truckers across the galaxy.</description></item><item><title>Unstoppable: Breakout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unstoppable-breakout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unstoppable-breakout/</guid><description>Game Description Unstoppable: Breakout is an adventure game in which gamers find themselves in a chilling complex, leaving them alone and confused. Guided by the voice of a colleague, the protagonist, a researcher, must navigate dark and mysterious corridors, battling inhuman experiments and uncovering hidden secrets. The game is an intense mix of strategy and combat, requiring careful resource management and precision in every strike. The gameplay of Unstoppable: Breakout is an exciting roller coaster ride with challenging combat and boss battles.</description></item><item><title>DEATH IN UNISON</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-in-unison/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-in-unison/</guid><description>Game Description DEATH IN UNISON is a co-op survival adventure game set in an isolated rehabilitation institute on Corton Island. Here gamers will have to survive in the fight against some of the most dangerous criminals in the world, many of whom have supernatural powers. Users must perform their prison duties alone or with a partner, relying primarily on radio communications to navigate the treacherous environment.
Gameplay in DEATH IN UNISON revolves around completing administrative tasks and protecting yourself from hostile prisoners.</description></item><item><title>ENDLESS DAYS Z</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-days-z/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-days-z/</guid><description>Game Description ENDLESS DAYS Z immerses gamers in a desolate, post-apocalyptic world devastated by DeltaVirus-7. As the leader of a group of survivors, you must overcome treacherous obstacles, collect vital samples, and confront hordes of the undead as you desperately search for a cure. The gripping narrative and intense gameplay make the game appealing to fans of survival horror and action games. The gameplay of ENDLESS DAYS Z is based on exploration, combat and resource management.</description></item><item><title>The Lord of the Rings: Return to Moria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lord-of-the-rings-return-to-moria/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lord-of-the-rings-return-to-moria/</guid><description>Game Description The Lord of the Rings: Return to Moria is an adventure game in the Lord of the Rings universe, the events of which develop in the world of Middle-earth during the Fourth Age. In the game you can meet characters from the original work. For example, Gimli appears at the beginning of the story. He leads a company of dwarves, leading them to Durin&amp;rsquo;s Doors. The plot centers on the dwarves, whose task is to reclaim Moria and restore the entire kingdom of Khazad-dum under their rule.</description></item><item><title>Core Keeper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/core-keeper/</guid><description>Game Description Going on an adventure inCore Keeper, you are immersed in an atmosphere of the unknown, requiring exploration on behalf of an archaeologist who wants to discover as many new relics and ancient artifacts as possible. Waking up in an unfamiliar area that resembles a cave, the protagonist will have to fight through a variety of monsters and obstacles that impede progress in order to achieve his goals.
Taking control of the main character, who finds himself in a pixel world filled with the spirit of adventure and precious treasures, you have to survive and explore the dangerous environment.</description></item><item><title>Endzone 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</guid><description>Game Description Endzone 2 throws you into the thick of the post -apocalyptic world. Humanity died, and you remained to collect fragments - literally. Each decision that you make as if you can send your scattered colony by the line. Lack of resources? Eat. Danger to the environment? Do not hesitate. Ruthless raiders eager to steal your lunch? Undoubtedly. This is not a simple walk. This is the management of your nascent civilization.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Dynasty takes place in 1800s America. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to build his own ranch, providing himself with wealth and food. Over time, other settlers, workers and friends will join the main character. Each minor character has their own qualities, characteristics and mannerisms. Many of them will turn out to be bandits, and only the gamer can decide who is sent to the gallows.
Having become determined, the central character set out to build a Wild West dynasty, moving further across the Pacific region of America.</description></item><item><title>Terminus: Zombie Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terminus-zombie-survivors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terminus-zombie-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Terminus: Zombie Survivors is a gloomy journey that takes gamers to the setting of the zombie apocalypse. It is ahead to survive among dangerous mutants, making their way through a variety of locations. The main task for the hero will be the search for the place of terminus, the last stronghold of mankind. In the game there are elements of Rowlaik that create random situations on the map. It will come out to compete with starvation, cold temperature and aggressive opponents.</description></item><item><title>ODD Realm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</guid><description>Game Description ODD Realm is a game that combines both the strategy and the survival simulator. The player will have to take on the role of the leader of a small settlement and provide residents with the necessary resources, houses, as well as protect their subjects from bloodthirsty enemies and dishonest bandits from a high road. The variability of the development of the plot provides the gamer with wide opportunities for the construction of the city of his own dreams.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>7 Days to Die</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</guid><description>Game Description In7 Days to Die you will need the ability to loot, kill other players, take loot, build buildings, craft items, shoot accurately and keep track of time, because in the open world there is a night in which zombies and other undead sharpen their attention . A horror first-person shooter that combines city building, multiplayer, survival, tower defense and character leveling in an RPG style. Despite the fact that a severe epidemic has struck the world, you will be able to kill animals to take their meat and skin.</description></item><item><title>Pigromance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pigromance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pigromance/</guid><description>Game Description Pigromance tells about the efforts of one pig to avoid turning into a food product, this is a story about the escape contrary to the established expectations. The action starts on a farm, where the piglets were previously behind the fence, in the usual environment. Over time, this design of the content succumbed, initiating the mass departure of animals from the agricultural limits in search of an alternative to their prepared role.</description></item><item><title>Acre Crisis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/acre-crisis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/acre-crisis/</guid><description>Game Description Acre CRISIS transfers players in 1992, placing them in the AKR area in the jungle of the Amazon. The Brazilian Military Police Brigade is going to this area to investigate a series of deaths caused by wild animals, as well as reports of a meeting with cryptids. Upon arrival, the soldiers were in direct confrontation with a group of hungry dinosaurs, which was very different from their initial task.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>The Crust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</guid><description>Game Description The Crust is a survival with elements of the economy, where the player will build a whole small town with highly limited resources almost without the possibility of replenishing them. In order to grow at least something on such a surface and provide your people with the proper amount of food, you will have to try hard. However, with proper management, this is still quite possible.
The main character is the head of the space company, which was decided by the first to colonize the moon.</description></item><item><title>Workers and Resources: Soviet Republic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</guid><description>Game Description InWorkers and Resources: Soviet Republic you have to lead a fallen country and turn it into the strongest republic, making it a superpower with the happiest inhabitants who have built world progress. The urban planning strategy will show you a country that is very similar to the Soviet Union. You accept it broken, plundered, ruined. There is absolutely no money in the treasury, and people have no opportunity to raise territories, plant crops, go to work, simply because there is no money even for food, but you understand that all this can be corrected.</description></item><item><title>Bodycam</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</guid><description>Game Description Bodycam throws you headlong into a hyper-realistic multiplayer battlefield. Powered by Unreal Engine 5, this all-new shooter promises a next-gen experience that will redefine your expectations. Teamwork is key here. Every bullet counts, and the victory or defeat of your squad depends on your every decision.
Forget playing Rambo. Bodycam requires strategic thinking and coordinated attacks. Team up with your teammates, map out a plan of action, and use your arsenal to outmaneuver your opponents.</description></item><item><title>Empires of the Undergrowth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</guid><description>Game Description Empires of the Undergrowth is a simulation and real-time strategy game with unique mechanics. In the game you will have to manage a colony of ants. Starting to play as one ant, you will hunt, manage builders, and create a unique hive. The design of your hive will determine whether your colony can survive in this harsh world. Why harsh?
Throughout the game you will face various obstacles. First of all, these are your enemies!</description></item><item><title>Genome Guardian</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/genome-guardian/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/genome-guardian/</guid><description>Game Description Genome Guardian transfers gamers to the environment, where a microscopic becomes a scene for a high -octane action. This is a game where the usual meets the unusual, offering the world filled with microscopic organisms, some of which are harmless, while others are far from the case. A distinctive feature is that it is based on the mixing and selection of DNA nucleotides to create bio -weapons, which serves you the main protection from the hostile environment.</description></item><item><title>V Rising</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rising/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rising/</guid><description>Game Description Waking up inV Rising, the hero as a vampire must hunt for blood, while simultaneously avoiding direct sunlight. The survival slasher film puts you in the shoes of a bloodsucker who wakes up in his own castle and must regain his possession and authority while operating in a vast open world full of secrets. Here you have to conquer the lands of the living, unite with allies to complete the task.</description></item><item><title>Manor Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Manor Lords is a strategy game set in the Middle Ages. The game mechanics center on the realistic process of constructing buildings and intense fights with the enemy army. The building element is based on historical data about cities and villages. All buildings presented in Manor Lords are as authentic as possible. Landscapes and types of terrain influence the process of settlement formation.
Create trade routes, establish market relations with neighboring cities and promote the economic prosperity of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Bellwright</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</guid><description>Game Description Bellwright throws you into a world of rebellion and intrigue. Finding yourself in prison for a heinous crime, you must not only clear your name, but also organize a revolution against a tyrannical ruler. Build and manage settlements, collect resources and recruit villagers into your ranks. Each new adept brings valuable skills, strengthening your rebellion and unlocking new technologies for your cities.
Combat is based on skill and focus.</description></item><item><title>The Planet Crafter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-planet-crafter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-planet-crafter/</guid><description>Game Description The main character ofThe Planet Crafter was sent to a hostile planet to make it suitable for human life. Alone, he will have to extract resources, use existing technologies, found a small settlement and develop technologies. In the future, it will be able to heat the planet and create an atmosphere with a normal amount of oxygen. This will help redirect a large part of the population to the new world.</description></item><item><title>From Glory to Goo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</guid><description>Game Description From Glory to Goo is a cosmic adventure. Forget about the conquest of the new worlds - here the survival depends on how to cling to the fragment of the rock among the inexorable stream of mucus. You play for the captain, the last hope of mankind, who is instructed to establish a fragile colony on a hostile foreign world. Your enemies are not rival empires and not robots with lasers, but the ubiquitous mucus, a reasonable, changing form, the threat that oozes, drips and crawls to your colony from all sides.</description></item><item><title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</guid><description>Game Description Outpost: Infinity Siege is a fun sci-fi first-person shooter with elements of base building and tower defense. You command the Mobile Outpost and go with the Protoslug Cannon to deeply explore the forbidden zone of Cygnet, where many dangers await you. Collect unique weapon units and strengthen the firepower of the outpost that is fighting with you. This game combines elements of TD, FPS and RTS at the same time, making the gameplay incredibly exciting.</description></item><item><title>Machick</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machick/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machick/</guid><description>Game Description Machick puts a player against the organized force of anti -magic toads aimed at destroying the forest. The main task is to stop this army and regain control of the territory. The gameplay is built on the cycle: Gamer creates personal magic sticks, crushes enemies and gets experience from them. The experience gained is to buy improvements that allow each attempt to move further deep into the conflict. The whole trip is a process of collecting resources to approach the ultimate goal.</description></item><item><title>The Outlast Trials</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-outlast-trials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-outlast-trials/</guid><description>Game Description The Outlast Trials - first-person horror game in the Outlast universe. The difference from the main series is that you can play both alone and in a company. At the center of the story is the Murkoff company, which is engaged in inhumane and sadistic experiments. You will play as one of these crazy organizations. You can join forces with up to 4 people and try to survive this nightmare together.</description></item><item><title>Spiritfall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spiritfall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spiritfall/</guid><description>Game Description Spiritfall - an action -platformer with elements of a sling, which is based on the gameplay of which is a worked out combat system. It will be necessary to beat enemies, chop everything in their path and throw enemies into the wall. The gameplay is released by speed and concentrated dynamics. Opponents attack every second. At the end of the stage, a fight with a unique boss is waiting.</description></item><item><title>Sons of the Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sons-of-the-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Sons of The Forest is a first-person multiplayer horror game with survival elements. The game is a sequel to the acclaimed hit The Forest. As in the previous part, you need to explore a mysterious forest inhabited by bloodthirsty monsters. Survive by hiding from enemies and carefully study the surrounding areas. Arm yourself with powerful weapons to face numerous opponents.
The story centers on a special forces soldier with a Fight Demons tattoo.</description></item><item><title>Myth of Empires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</guid><description>Game Description The goal ofMyth of Empires is to teach the user to fight for their own place in a huge world. The game is positioned as a multiplayer sandbox in which the user creates an Empire, forming troops that participate in massive battles and sieges of cities, and also builds their own fortresses for defense.
The action takes place in the East during the era of antiquity, when many states constantly fought among themselves, which led to chaos, famine and destruction.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>Nightingale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nightingale/</guid><description>Game Description Nightingale takes you on a dangerous journey through the fantastical kingdoms of the fairies. As a Realmwalker, you&amp;rsquo;ll explore, craft, build, and fight across a variety of environments, alone or with friends. This open world survival game takes you through a labyrinth of beautiful but treacherous kingdoms. Stranded after the destruction of a network of portals, you must reach Nightingale, the last human bastion. Open portals and travel through wild forests, treacherous swamps and shimmering deserts.</description></item><item><title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smalland-survive-the-wilds/</guid><description>Game Description InSmalland: Survive the Wilds the player takes on the role of a hero who has been diminished under unexplained circumstances. The protagonist woke up in the forest, not knowing whether other people had the same fate. With a head full of questions, he begins a struggle whose goal is not only to find out the truth, but, above all, to survive in a new inhospitable world.
The player watches what is happening from the first person.</description></item><item><title>Enshrouded</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enshrouded/</guid><description>Game Description Enshrouded is an exciting game set in the kingdom of Embervale, taking players on an exciting journey through a land once devastated by a devastating magical plague. The user will have to explore the remnants of the lost kingdom, fight mutated creatures and unravel the mysterious secrets of the ancient Flame. One of the distinctive features of the project is the emphasis on the independence of the hero.</description></item><item><title>The Universim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city construction, the development of an entire planet and a ward civilization -The Universim is a short sand strategy in which you have to try on the role of God. The game begins with the fact that you settle several people on one of the planets, give them food, indicate what needs to be done - set priorities. And then watch how people develop on their own, without your help.</description></item><item><title>Palworld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/palworld/</guid><description>Game Description Palworld offers you to find and use friends as helpers in a huge and dangerous world. The multiplayer survival game has elements of crafting, and the creatures themselves, discovered by the user in the process, become his pet friends, which help him at all stages of the passage, including the ability to move on them, construct buildings, engage in farming, production, and explore dungeons.
The user finds himself in a virtual universe inhabited by bizarre animal creatures, which in this world are simply called Friends.</description></item><item><title>Lost Hope: Backrooms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Hope: BackRooms offers a single first -person adventure in the alarming locations of backstage. Key classes include navigation for these confusing, interconnected places and active interaction with the environment for solving logical puzzles, which contributes to the development of the main plot. The area often demonstrates strange and inexplicable phenomena, which are difficult to immediately comprehend. Gamers have to carefully study these elements in order to reveal the secrets hidden in this tense journey.</description></item><item><title>Out of Orbit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-orbit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-orbit/</guid><description>Game Description Out of Orbit offers space experience, focused on the liberty of the player in accidentally created universes. Gamers design, build and command their own starships, or can attack, disassemble or capture the vessels of others. People base planetary bases to expand the influence and extraction of materials. The actions of the gamer affect the game world and have long -term consequences. Any ship met can be taken on boarding and destroyed.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>The Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</guid><description>Game Description In The Front, your task, as a resistance fighter, boils down to go into the past in order to prevent the formation of a tyrannical empire that threatens the very existence of mankind. The game is a craft shooter with an open world, immersing a player in a post -apocalyptic sandbox, teeming with mutants and hostile groups.
In this terrain destroyed by the war, you have to fight with tyrannical imperial forces, exiles, bandits and rebels in an epic battle, which will determine the future of mankind.</description></item><item><title>Dotage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dotage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dotage/</guid><description>Game Description Dotage offers a unique game experience. Michele was feasted and others developed the concept of this digital kingdom. Players move around the world devoid of clear goals. The gameplay rotates around simple mechanics: pressing one button moves the protagonist forward. This seemingly simple action becomes the basis for a trip, rich in interpretation. The visual language of the game consists of abstract landscapes and mysterious symbols. The narrative unfolds through these elements, inviting to introspection, and not giving obvious explanations.</description></item><item><title>Saleblazers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saleblazers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saleblazers/</guid><description>Game Description Saleblazers offers to enjoy the exciting experience of survival in the multiplayer action, in which you have to create a store and survive in a dangerous world filled with various dangers. On this dangerous island you will have to build cozy cafes or huge shopping centers in the company with other players. The whole world of the game is a reactive sandbox, where each buyer has his own character, tastes and preferences.</description></item><item><title>El Paso, Elsewhere</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/el-paso-elsewhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/el-paso-elsewhere/</guid><description>Game Description El Paso, Elsewhere immerses players in dynamic shootings with werewolves, vampires and other evil spirits that make his way to the surface of the planet. Events transfer to the territory of a small Texas settlement under the name El Passes, where he will have to fight terrible opponents. The main character finds himself in a small three -story hotel hiding the secret deep underground. Players will have to go down to dark basements to go through 46 combat missions and destroy hellish creatures.</description></item><item><title>The Matchless KungFu</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</guid><description>Game Description The Matchless KungFu immerses users in a world where martial arts are at the forefront. The gamer can choose the path of any warrior he likes and go on a journey through these lands. Be a loner or join a group of like-minded people - you can choose any convenient way. Only the decisions made will shape the character’s story, throwing him into different circumstances, giving him complete freedom of action in certain aspects.</description></item><item><title>Desynced</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</guid><description>Game Description Desynced is a three -dimensional real -time strategy. The indie project also has elements of survival and a colony control simulator. The Title is made in a science fiction setting. It has support for user modifications. According to the plot, the hero travels along with artificial intelligence and colonizers between distant planets. The protagonist plants bots to the surface, and he remains in orbit and leads mechanical creatures from there.</description></item><item><title>Sengoku Dynasty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sengoku-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Sengoku Dynasty tells the story of difficult life in feudal Japan. To convey everything with maximum accuracy, the developers consulted with a historical group, which provided valuable advice and confirmed records with information about the life of that period. The player will have to become the leader of one of the villages and lead it to prosperity and expansion in one of the ways.
The player will have one, almost abandoned settlement at his disposal, which he will have to restore and provide the inhabitants with everything they need.</description></item><item><title>My Friendly Neighborhood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-friendly-neighborhood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-friendly-neighborhood/</guid><description>Game Description My Friendly Neighborhood immerses users for the role of a simple repairman Gordon, which is forced to cope with gloomy and revived puppets attacking the hero during the play &amp;ldquo;Our friendly neighborhood.&amp;rdquo; The protagonist is forced to survive and cope with various puzzles to find a way out of the trap. The MFN game is an action horror where you have to cope with dynamic levels, using a variety of weapons for self -defense.</description></item><item><title>Yet Another Zombie Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yet-another-zombie-survivors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yet-another-zombie-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Yet Another Zombie Survivors is an action roginal for those who are ready to fight with the horde of undead! Humanity can be on the verge of extinction, but this does not mean that you will fall without a fight. This is not a typical game with long scenes and complex management - here you need to immediately join the battle and see how sparks fly! Regardless of what your level of game experience you have, you will enjoy this game.</description></item><item><title>Survival and Horror: Mortanis Prisoners 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survival-and-horror-mortanis-prisoners-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survival-and-horror-mortanis-prisoners-1/</guid><description>Game Description Survival and Horror: Mortanis Prisoners #1 occurs in the Nazi concentration camp, where the main characters are prisoners who are going to execute for participation in the conspiracy of the rebels. However, they soon find out that death is not the worst thing that can happen to them, because they will find an even more terrible fate. They must find a way to escape from the nightmare that awaits them in the camp.</description></item><item><title>Brotato</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brotato/</guid><description>Game Description In the shooterBratato you have to take control of a potato using a variety of guns while fighting alien creatures. The gameplay includes roguelite genre elements. Locations are procedurally generated, and each run can take up to 30 minutes of real time. There are dozens of types of weapons and additional items of equipment to choose from, allowing you to progress at your own pace and combine the effects of items.</description></item><item><title>Keeper's Toll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</guid><description>Game Description Keeper&amp;rsquo;s Toll is a fun and challenging game that will test the skills of any gamer who enjoys the classic retro time survival genre. Featuring unique dark fantasy elements, the game boasts a carefully crafted blend of skill-based gameplay, roguelike elements, and unique mechanics that set it apart from others in the genre.
Gamers will be able to choose from six different heroes, each with their own defining mechanics, abilities, and meta progression.</description></item><item><title>Stranded: Alien Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description Stranded: Alien Dawn is an open world survival simulator. In this case, an alien. According to the plot, a group of people on a rescue shuttle is evacuated from a burning starship and landed on the first planet that fall. The player controls the team of surviving crew members of the space ship. He needs to take care of his wards, providing them with warmth, light, food, medicines, weapons, entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 4 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-4-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-4-remake/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil 4 Remake is a full-fledged remake of the cult fourth part, which is rightfully considered one of the best in the series. The developers took into account the criticism of fans after the release of the remake of the third game and did not stray far from their roots, adhering to the course taken with Resident Evil 2. The plot has not undergone drastic changes, however, some storylines have been added that were not in the original, the arcs of minor characters have expanded and, Of course, the controls have been improved and the graphics have been significantly updated.</description></item><item><title>Barotrauma</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/barotrauma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/barotrauma/</guid><description>Game Description Barotrauma is a two -dimensional simulator decorated in the style of the platformer. According to the plot, your courageous shoulders are entrusted to enter the captain of the real submarine, but you will not control it on the ground, but on one of the satellites of Jupiter called Europe, in the bowels of which the underground ocean spreads. The surface of the satellite is shrouded in an impassable radiation layer, due to which the colony of people are forced to hide under the thickness of the ice that protect the local waters.</description></item><item><title>Terraformers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraformers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraformers/</guid><description>Game Description Terraformers - 3x game with Roguelite elements, in which you are heading the terraforming of Mars. Get on the Red Planet, where there are no buildings of humanity. Use the resources of the environment and gradually expand your base, based on new cities, settlements and industrial territories. Start the process of terraforming by warming the planet, editing oceans and spreading life thanks to bacteria and brought creatures.
Control the leaders and send them to mysterious places to open huge places rich in resources.</description></item><item><title>Contraband Police</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</guid><description>Game Description Contraband Police - The simulator of the border guard in the first person. The player in the role of the commander of the border post makes an inspection of transport for the presence of smuggling on the border of the third world countries. The inspection tasks include: checking documents: inspection and permit for entry criminals &amp;hellip; or take a bribe. What? Nobody heard this! To carry out reports on the successful completion of tasks through the mail; the accumulated experience can be spent on pumping the department, buying new equipment or training dogs;</description></item><item><title>Fargone</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fargone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fargone/</guid><description>Game Description Fargone is a role shooter with survival elements in which gamers fall into the world after a mysterious nuclear disaster, known as the Wasteland. Here you will have to survive by any means, whether it is alone or entering into alliances with various fractions. Explore the gloomy and atmospheric lands of the wasteland, where life continues, despite the terrible catastrophe. Here you will find not only other surviving, but also stray corpses affected by infection caused by disaster.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging intoZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip - a continuation of the popular series of satirical adventure, the actions of which unfold in a fabulous universe. Instead of people, it is inhabited by various very cute monsters of all possible species and appearance. Unlike previous parts, here the developers do not focus on the simulation of dates, but on road travel and survival. Juzer needs to get to a certain epic place in order to end the campaign successfully.</description></item><item><title>After the Collapse</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</guid><description>Game Description AFTER The COLLAPSE is a 2D strategy, a management and management simulator of its own settlement. A camera that is above above the surface at right angles is used. The surrounding world survived the apocalypse, which is why it turned into radioactive wastelands and became very dangerous for living people without means of protection against monsters and aggressive bandits. The task of the gamer is to develop existing buildings and build new ones to increase population growth and create a powerful army that is ready to fight off external threats.</description></item><item><title>Farthest Frontier</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</guid><description>Game Description Farthest Frontier is a strategic game with the simulator elements. The game is made by all canons of 4x-mechanics. You have to develop your settlement and defend it from an attack by the enemy. Guide your people and try not only to survive, but also to develop. The world of wildlife is fraught with many dangers with which you have to face face every day.
Collect resources, go hunting, do fishing or farming - do everything possible to survive in harsh and wild conditions.</description></item><item><title>Surroundead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surroundead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surroundead/</guid><description>Game Description Surroundead is a survival simulator in the open world where the apocalypse happened. In the indie project, you can switch between the view from the first and third-party. Its three -dimensional graphics are made in Low Poly style. According to the plot, a zombie virus appeared on Earth. For 5 years, people fought to him unsuccessfully. As a result, the planet has changed forever. Along the devastated streets, living dead began to roam, and civilization in its level of development rolled back to dark times.</description></item><item><title>Raft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</guid><description>Game Description Raft is a first-person survival sandbox in which the player will have to survive on a small raft and explore new lands. The main character will begin his journey by waking up hungry and dehydrated on a small wreck of a ship. Get food and drink by catching garbage floating past the hero on the waves. To catch the item, you can use the hook. Find useful items and materials to craft a mug, light a fire, and filter sea water.</description></item><item><title>Postal: Brain Damage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-brain-damaged/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-brain-damaged/</guid><description>Game Description Postal: Brain Damageed - Spin -Off series of a series of old -time jumper in the first person. Here, a classic dynamic gameplay for the same name is implemented, as well as the mass of black humor, satire, rudeness and recklessness. The game proposes the most crazy arsenal of weapons, there are many bonuses and a twisted plot, which is based on violence. To this end, the ability to strike the head, carry out a real massacre and even damage the brain to the opponent.</description></item><item><title>Keplerth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the futuristic Indo-video trigger Keplerth unfold in the distant future-on the previously unknown planet Kepler. According to the genre, the project can be attributed to the simulator of survival with the possibility of construction and RPG elements. According to the plot, people built a large spaceship, which was supposed to transport the colonists on board to the nearest planet suitable for life. But there is a disaster, as a result of which the ship crashes on an unknown planet.</description></item><item><title>Stacklands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</guid><description>Game Description InStacklands you have to build a village, completing various levels in the style of a deck-building battler. Users will collect food, build buildings and fight monsters on a special field using ability cards. It will be possible to use combinations of cards. For example, when you move a “village dweller” to a “berry bush”, “berries” will appear, which the city dweller will consume as food and get a chance to survive.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light 2: Stay Human</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-2-stay-human/</guid><description>Game Description Dying Light 2: Stay Human starts 15 years after humanity became infected with a terrible virus. Many have turned into zombies who scour in search of living flesh, and the few survivors wage a daily struggle for existence. People are divided into several warring factions, which during the day make forays from shelters to find resources, and at night they hide from bloodthirsty monsters. The world has returned to its primitive state, where everyone fights only for their own lives.</description></item><item><title>Breakwaters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/breakwaters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/breakwaters/</guid><description>Game Description In Breakwaters, the player will reconnolate the procedurally generated world with monstrous ocean depths and huge titans that change the method of interaction with water. Water is replaced by powerful crystals obtained in the mine. The user is able to delve into its bowels to collect rare objects, build obstacles to restrain the ocean or block waves, and help people after destruction.
Titans, creatures of an extinct submarine race, wander around the world, causing cataclysms.</description></item><item><title>Icarus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</guid><description>Game Description Icarus is a first -person survival that will send you to explore the secrets of one distant planet. You wake up from cryosn after your shuttle made a forced landing on the surface of a mysterious planet. Now you need to stay alive, surviving in unusual conditions. Collect resources, craft items and play both alone and along with other players. The gameplay Ikarus can be described as cooperative action with survival elements.</description></item><item><title>Dysmantle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dysmantle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dysmantle/</guid><description>Game Description Dysmantle offers gamers to survive on the island and find a way to get out of this place. The local post -apocalyptic world is not gloomy. There is no atmosphere of hopelessness here either. The game has a bright cartoon graphics with juicy colors. During the end of the world, the protagonist hides in an underground bunker. Once the hero crawls out and discovers that people and animals have turned into evil creatures similar to zombies.</description></item><item><title>Scrapnaut</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrapnaut/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrapnaut/</guid><description>Game Description Scrapnaut stands out against the background of other sandboxes with elements of survival with its concept. The hero has to fight for life in an open world using the surroundings of steampunk. He periodically fights steam robots and is engaged in the study of the surroundings. On the back, the protagonist wears an oxygen cylinder, so it is important to monitor the level of air. The appearance of the adventurer can be changed due to the change of clothing.</description></item><item><title>TimberBorn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/timberborn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/timberborn/</guid><description>Game Description TimberBorn allows you to develop a beaver colony. The game does not claim realism, because rodents behave and move like people. This is a full -fledged urban planning simulator. The settlement has to rebuild in the world where humanity has disappeared, leaving behind the exhausted land. In an alternative future, the planet suffers from drought.
To control the water resource in TimberBorn, you can build dams and dig channels.</description></item><item><title>Residual</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/residual/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/residual/</guid><description>Game Description Residual is a platformer with elements of the survival simulator. The game can boast of the worked out pixel graphics and procedural generation of the world. It is made in a science fiction setting. According to the plot, the hero crashes on one of the planets in the forgotten part of the galaxy. Its task is to study alien technologies and find a way to fix a starship.</description></item><item><title>The Doors of Trithius</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</guid><description>Game Description The Doors of Trithius is a RPG -Rogalik in the fantasy world with procedurally generated content. Here you have to fight monsters, avoid traps, collect prey and much more, traveling along the mysterious world of Enalia. Every time you start the game, you have to explore the new generated city, dungeon and map of the world. Movement and battle use a unique time system, returning the priority of the player based on the speed of weapons or action, maintaining tactical decisions, as well as knowledge about your enemies.</description></item><item><title>Clone Drone in the Danger Zone</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clone-drone-in-the-danger-zone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clone-drone-in-the-danger-zone/</guid><description>Game Description Clone Drone in the Danger Zone is an exciting arcade game in which the player will play as a person whose mind has been transferred into an iron robot! The player enters the arena with the only task - to survive. It is worth considering that each opponent is endowed with individual characteristics and skills, so winning will not be easy. Each blow is under the close attention of a robot commentator, who will cover the course of the battle and your actions throughout it.</description></item><item><title>Tunguska: The Visim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tunguska-the-visitation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tunguska-the-visitation/</guid><description>Game Description After the fall of the meteorite, in Tunguska: The Visitation begins the invasion of mutants. Having fallen to the ground in the Tunguska area, the alien body caused the transformation of all local residents. As a result, a special zone is formed here, the main goal in which is to survive and survive against enemies. The game often has to make a difficult choice, on the result of which its own existence depends.</description></item><item><title>Going Medieval</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</guid><description>Game Description Going Medieval is a simulator in which you need to build a fortress on the ruins of an old castle and equip it to protect your settlement. Any event can affect the mood of your people, so you need to satisfy all their needs and be a good king. Events unfold in the era of the dark Middle Ages of the late XIV century.
Only five percent of the population survived after a heavy plague epidemic.</description></item><item><title>Days Gone</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/days-gone-pc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/days-gone-pc/</guid><description>Game Description Days gone tells the story of Deikon Saint-Jones. The former member of the Mad Dog Motokoksluba suffers from the loss of the spouse and wanders through an almost destroyed epidemic to the open world. He is inhabited by the remaining groups of peaceful people, looters, crazy cultists, wild animals and freezers. The latter are like zombies. However, these are not revived dead, but live creatures. And these monsters move much faster than any undead.</description></item><item><title>Subnautica: Below Zero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica-below-zero/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica-below-zero/</guid><description>Game Description A game about the underwater world, which became a continuation of the original game, completely borrowing the engine. The world ofSubnautica: Below Zero is inhabited not by simple creatures similar to those in the previous part, but by aliens who are more interesting to fight, and their world is much more beautiful than our reality. Adventures will be with you at every step, but do not forget that the world of the game was recognized as a real horror setting, where it is light and bright only in the first hundreds of meters of immersion in depth.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-village/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-village/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil Village continues the adventures of Ethan from the Seven. The Roman numeral hidden in the title on the posters hints that this is not a spin-off, but the eighth part of the series. This is already the tenth project in the main line. Winters was able to escape from the cannibal mansion and save his wife Mia. They got away from the American outback and decided to live an ordinary life.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Prepper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-prepper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-prepper/</guid><description>Game Description Mr. Prepper is a construction simulator where you have to build a bunker under a residential building. Mr. The survivor of those who believe in the theory of conspiracies and understands that a serious threat of nuclear war hung over the world. He does not care about his neighbors and those who do not believe him, so he alone begins to build his own bomb shelter. The nuclear war is close and you must be ready!</description></item><item><title>Valheim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/valheim/</guid><description>Game Description Valheim is a survival in the open world where you will build your own base and fight with the mythical creatures of Scandinavian folklore. The events of the game take place in Valheim - the tenth world of the Vikings. The goal of the hero is to get to the gate of Walgalla. Killing various monsters and monsters, you earn the blessing of the gods.
The hero will visit the most diverse corners of the world: thick forests, snowy mountains and much more.</description></item><item><title>Kingdoms Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-reborn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdoms Reborn is a urban planning simulator with a full multipleor and card game elements. The project was primarily created under the online, but there is also a single in it. The world is randomly generated. It is divided into 7 biomes that do not gameplay. In the Arctic zone and tropics, it will be more difficult to grow food on ordinary fields than in the territory with a temperate climate.</description></item><item><title>Endless Furry Killer 2020</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</guid><description>Game Description The conflict in Endless Furry Killer 2020 puts a player against the endless waves of anthropomorphic opponents. The gamer has to move through two -dimensional arenas with a view of the top intended for continuous battles. The key lesson lies in the shooting of goals in a tense struggle for life with a constant stream of enemies. Such a gameplay requires constant movement and aiming to defeat non -aloscorizing resistance.</description></item><item><title>Ostranauts</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostranauts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostranauts/</guid><description>Game Description Ostranauts-a role-playing lifetime in a zero gravity in a noir ship, which is located in outer space. The game supports only a single -user study of the universe, and has no voice acting, the information is submitted in the form of text in subtitles or notes. The main character is a character that is created and customized personally by a gamer in order to achieve uniqueness. Also, before the start of the passage, the initial ship is also set up, which is subject to further improvement after collecting the necessary resources.</description></item><item><title>Factorio</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</guid><description>Game Description The new planet should have everything to provide people with a comfortable, peaceful existence. Factorio is a sandbox in 2D graphics, where a new planet should be fully equipped for the future life of people. As soon as we arrive in a new place, we need to extract resources, assemble elements from them, and build structures so that people in the future can settle in and exist peacefully. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that the planet reacts aggressively to colonizers.</description></item><item><title>Risk of Rain 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</guid><description>Game Description Risk of Rain 2 is a continuation of the classic online game, which has become better and more complex than the original. The player will challenge the cruel world alone or team up with friends to defeat hordes of monsters, collect the necessary relics and escape from the terrifying planet. With each new attempt, you will be able to better understand the behavior of your opponents and defeat them outright with your skills, even when they are outnumbered.</description></item><item><title>Empyrion - Galactic Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Empyrion - Galactic Survival shows the world of the future. In the 24th century, in the ice of Antarctica, they find a spacecraft of aliens. Scientists investigated the object and discovered the technology of the hyperdrod. Earthlings send an expedition to the planet Empirion, which is in the Andromeda nebula. The crew gets to the destination, but tolerates the crash and cannot return home.
In survival mode, the player leaves the rescue capsule and is alone against the hostile world.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic is a co-op shooter with fast-paced gameplay in which you will fight with other users against alien monsters. The game is made in a sci-fi style and has procedurally generated levels in which you will fight. The mission can be completed by 1 to 4 players. Act as one. Dig, explore the area and shoot with enemies waiting for you in huge numbers around every corner.</description></item><item><title>Fallout 76</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-76/</guid><description>Game Description According to the plot ofFallout 76, the first people came out of shelters after a nuclear war. They set off to explore the Wasteland, where mutants are already lying in wait. The player will be able to visit 6 regions, each of which has its own types of dangerous animals and landscape. Among the scorched desert there are also wooded areas with red trees. What is most surprising is that quite recently the desert territories were inhabited by those who were able to survive the apocalypse on the surface.</description></item><item><title>Zompiercer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zompiercer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zompiercer/</guid><description>Game Description Conceptively Zompiercer is a sandbox with an open detailed world, but the whole thing is played as a first-person shooter about survival during the zombie apocalypse. The planet is covered by a virus. People mutated in bloodthirsty walking corpses. Not many managed to survive, but you are lucky more than the rest. Or not? Survival is just beginning!
The game from an independent developer under the nickname DDDIMANN is not a comprehension not by the setting, but by the scale and the implementation of ideas.</description></item><item><title>Ostriv</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</guid><description>Game Description OSTRIV, this is a city -building simulator that makes you the ruler of the monarch of the 18th century. The player will have to work hard and show his ability to the manager, as well as creative abilities. The goal of the game to transfer the gameplay of simulators of this kind to a new level, by means of adding a huge number of opportunities and abandoning the usual restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Stoneshard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</guid><description>Game Description Come in the role of a harsh mercenary in a harsh, ruined war, kingdom. Take part in step -by -step battles and examine the RPG elements of Stoneshard, available in the gameplay. You can perform contracts, secondary and plot missions. Heal the wounds, purchase equipment and improve the protagonist as soon as you wish.
Freely move around the big and seamless world. Explore the villages lying in the ruins, go down to the dungeons or look into abandoned tracts.</description></item><item><title>The Sapling</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-sapling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-sapling/</guid><description>Game Description The Sapling is a simulator in which you will be selected by growing new plant species or crossing animals. Build your own world inhabited by unusual animals and a phantasmagoric fauna. The Sapling allows you to choose a random mutation mode to be a third -party observer, providing nature to conduct evolution itself and create its own ecosystems. At any time, you can take the development of the environment into your own hands.</description></item><item><title>Oxygen Not Included</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</guid><description>Game Description The player&amp;rsquo;s task inOxygen Not Included is to obtain food, water, oxygen, valuable resources and happiness for the duplicates - the inhabitants of his colony. The world settled into different parts, because of this, half of the people went to other planets, and the second part called themselves duplicates and decided to travel through space, flying between asteroids.
The idea of ​​the most hardcore survival simulator in a strategic shell - Oxygen Not Included - shows that maintaining your own base and several people on it is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Pixark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pixark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pixark/</guid><description>Game Description Pixark is made in the style of the famous Maycraft, but the game has a good plot, which is revealed in different ways for each player. The world of wildlife includes more than 100 different creatures that we can clone, tame and use for our own purposes. Among them will be friendly inhabitants of the jungle, as well as aggressive representatives of the game world.
The mysterious lands made in the form of cubes are destroyed and built every minute.</description></item><item><title>MORDHAU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mordhau/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mordhau/</guid><description>Game Description MORDHAU is a hack and slash game. Fights take place online on the company’s servers; offline you can train your skills in fights against artificial intelligence. A training session is also available, in which you will learn the basic mechanics and get your initial gold capital.
The name refers to a special German grip on the weapon, which, by the way, is available for selection. The main, but not the only feature is a fencing system that is as close to reality as possible, created through consultations with experts.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay ofSpace Engineers is that you will build space stations, ships, and begin to study neighboring planets and passing asteroids, where you will find many useful resources. Control is carried out from the perspective of a person, a ship, a base, a flying station, and you can change the camera view from both the third and first person.
When you create a world, the game automatically generates a random sequence of planets on which you can find valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Metro Exodus: Gold Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-exodus-gold-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The events ofMetro Exodus - a first-person shooter with elements of stealth and horror - take place in the same areas as the previous parts. The Russian Federation and the Republic of Kazakhstan are still waging a fierce war for life inside, in underground territories, with representatives of hostile clans, factions and monsters who devour, rather than kill, their prey. Artyom leaves the Order after the battle for D6.</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 2 Remake</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-2-remake/</guid><description>Game Description RESIDENT EVIL 2 / BIOHAZARD RE:2 - a complete rework, allowing players to enjoy modern graphics, a new engine, enemies, weapons and a much more advanced game story. Follow the story of police officer Leon S. Kennedy and student Claire Redfield.
Due to an unknown outbreak of a virus, the entire city of Raccoon City was enveloped in monsters, people began to turn into strange creatures, and then kill the survivors.</description></item><item><title>Bloons TD 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</guid><description>Game Description Bloons TD 6 (Bloons Tower Defense 6) is a 2018 action strategy game where the player will have to defend a fortress with the help of monkeys. The goal of the game is to destroy a stream of fast-moving balloons. The fewer goals missed, the greater the chances of winning. The balls differ in appearance and characteristics - new ones have been added in this part: purple, reinforced and impenetrable.</description></item><item><title>DayZ</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dayz/</guid><description>Game Description The multiplayer sandboxDayZ is a reworked version of the mod of the same name for Arma 2. The game is distinguished by its extremely realistic setting and hardcore survival in a post-apocalyptic environment. The game takes place in the fictional post-Soviet country of Chernarus. After the outbreak of an unknown virus, most of the population has turned into zombies, and the survivors are forced to fight for their lives and valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Two Crows</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Two Crowns is a cooperative microstrategy that tells about the brave, who has become a king and now he needs to gather his army. Having saddled the right horse, he goes on a long journey to expand the kingdom. He will be opposed by the army of greed, trying to take everything from him that he has set up with his own labor. The game offers to rush not only in European medieval landscapes, but also to see many radically new ones.</description></item><item><title>Kenshi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</guid><description>Game Description Kenshi forces you to survive from the very first minutes of the game. An impressive RPG with an open world and the ability to create your own squad, the remaining player privileges are gradually revealed to us. For example, you can build your own buildings in any location, conquer them from other factions, create your own business, sell goods in peaceful settlements, craft whatever you want, explore the environment and do whatever you want.</description></item><item><title>Among Us</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/among-us/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/among-us/</guid><description>Game Description Among Us (Among As) is a multiplayer game designed for 4 to 10 people on the server at the same time for exciting gameplay with a variety of scenarios. The setting of the project is boundless outer space, in which maps with different structures of surrounding objects are located. Casual controls and the ability to play on a local network in cross-platform mode make it possible to invite a noisy group to spend time together on the Among Us project.</description></item><item><title>The Colonists</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</guid><description>Game Description The Colonists are a urban planning sandbox in which you control a team of robots that create themselves. In the game you do not have to fight or kill enemies. The plot side of the project is meditative. You are landing on the planet, begin to carry out non -difficult tasks in which you need to build a settlement, and then improve your town depending on the preferences. Also in the game there is a “free mode” - here you make an island yourself, plant robots, begin to build a city from the resources obtained.</description></item><item><title>RimWorld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city planning and strategic base development on a planet unknown to the player. The player inRimWorld must build a base where the last forces of people are concentrated. To survive, get food, study the technology tree and understand what the planet wants from you is the main task of the player. The project itself is characterized by the enormous depth of built mechanics that you can apply to your buildings and the base as a whole.</description></item><item><title>SCUM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scum/</guid><description>Game Description SCUM is another survival game set in a completely open world. The developers tried to make the gameplay and the story of the characters so absurd that the very fact of some actions causes disgust. The plot reveals to us a modern society that wants nothing more than to “watch the spectacle.” The well-known producer TEC1 organized a show with the name - Scam - where people are thrown out in an open location, forced to survive without everything, and after that they are gradually introduced to a series of difficulties: a zombie epidemic, robots, dangerous animals, or money with the promise that once they get out , players will be able to spend them to buy freedom in the new society.</description></item><item><title>Mist Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mist-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mist-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Another survival game among zombies is Mist Survival. A completely open world, a unique system of characteristics, new types of weapons, shelters and the ability to create their own gang, attracted new players to fight on an open map against the crowd of enraged people absorbed in the epidemic. The main character, like all real players, will be protected from the epidemic, because in their body there is a special hormone that needs to be nourished every day.</description></item><item><title>Conan Exiles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</guid><description>Game Description Conan Exiles is an amazing multiplayer survival game with RPG and action elements. Employees of the Norwegian company Funcom worked on the project. The project was released at the end of spring 2018. Stunning graphics are a rare quality that developers of various MMORPG games pay attention to. But this time everything happened exactly the opposite. Funcom, 10 years before Conan Exiles, had already released a similar game called Age Of Conan.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk is an economic strategy game, a simulator of city construction in extremely harsh climatic conditions, where there are no wars, but there is a main enemy in the form of global cooling. The employees of the main office of 11 bit studios worked on the creation of this project. The official release of the game took place in April 2018.
In technical terms, we have a three-dimensional strategy game, with a top-down view, a simulator of the leader of a surviving human population in the Arctic cold.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</guid><description>Game Description Finally, the plot ofFar Cry 5 has reached America. Crazed fanatics unleashed their might on the state of Montana. A first-person shooter with action elements brings us to a reality in which even the movements of dogs will be more than real. The modernization of the shooter took several years, so the development studio warns us in advance that the game is based on religious motives. Age limit: 18+.</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rust/</guid><description>Game Description Rust (Rust) An ideal first-person survival simulator is not a simple escape from a city or civilization, but a necessary measure based on the conditions of our player. In Rust we will have to kill people, animals, build houses, dwellings, try to make fire out of nothing and survive in a world where everything is trying to kill us. The gameplay begins with the fact that we find ourselves on an island.</description></item><item><title>Subnautica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subnautica/</guid><description>Game Description In the world ofSubnautica, your ship has crashed in an oceanic area, and there is only one straight line - down to the bottom. The landscapes around you are illuminated by the sun, the coral reefs shimmer beautifully under the sun as you slowly sink towards the endless darkness of space. Exploring a huge open world allows you not only to plunge under the water and look at the inhabitants of this ocean, but also to build your own underwater base there and build a research center on it.</description></item><item><title>StationEers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stationeers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stationeers/</guid><description>Game Description Stationeers will transfer the player to outer space, in which it is necessary to control the space station alone or with other participants. You will follow all aspects of the station. Manage and deal with complex atmospheric, electric, production, medical and other equally important technologies inside a large room.
You will need to correctly build mechanisms and other objects to create a beautiful architecture, and also not to die due to a lack of oxygen or an excess of electricity.</description></item><item><title>Escape from Tarkov</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-from-tarkov/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-from-tarkov/</guid><description>Game Description Escape from Tarkov, a first -ized shooter with the first person with RPG and MMO elements, is one of the few games in which the plot is transmitted on the basis of a fictional conflict, but real interests. On the territory of Tarkov, in the Norvinsky region, there is a war between the soldiers of the USEC and Bear. Our hero is a simple soldier who is trying to get out of Tarkov at all costs, but for this he has to get acquainted with the same survivors after the conflict, try to survive and grab something valuable with him.</description></item><item><title>ARK: Survival Evolved</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ark-survival-evolved/</guid><description>Game Description The world ofARK: Survival Evolved is a setting full of dangers, in which not only dinosaurs, but also other creatures will try to kill you. People become especially dangerous. The game does not have any interesting plot, but there is a huge open world in which you have to build your base, hunt with a group of people (your friends), attack, defend, make weapons and explore the area. This is a full-fledged survival simulator from the first person (possibly from the 3rd person), where survival is limited to a base with a fire.</description></item><item><title>The Long Dark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</guid><description>Game Description A game about survival in a world without electricity. The Long Dark is eternal darkness in locations, gorgeous graphics from developers who love the sky and stars as their second home. Players were pleased that the entire gameplay is divided into two modes. The first is a story-based passage of 5 episodes, the total duration of which is 60-70 hours, depending on how the plot is followed. The second mode is survival in an excellent open world, where you will have to keep an eye on the contents of your backpack, check for items, collect skins, fry meat, take refuge in shelters, furnish your own house or a small corner in a house for survivors, where the owner of this establishment will shelter you.</description></item><item><title>Brigand: Oaxaca</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</guid><description>Game Description Brigand: Oaxaca is a first -person shooter hybrid, immersive simulator and role -playing game. The project has three -dimensional low -polygonal graphics. Due to her, the title resembles computer action of the late 90s and early 2000s. The action takes place in a world where nuclear apocalypse happened. Events unfold on the territory of the Mexican state of Ohak. Indi-game combines elements of different settings. In it, the gunshot weapons are adjacent to Voodoo magic, and not only mutters, but also demons roam the wastelands.</description></item><item><title>Unturned</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unturned/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unturned/</guid><description>Game Description Unturned combines a zombie-player and a sandbox with survival elements. In the single, the user studies locations, destroys the undead, looking for a useful lutus. In the multiplayer, the user is engaged in about the same, but also fights with living opponents. There is also a separate regime of the royal battle.
Players who kill other gamers for no reason become bandits. You can become a hero, having taken up the shooting of criminals.</description></item><item><title>Friday the 13th: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/friday-the-13th-the-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/friday-the-13th-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Friday The 13th: The Game is a horror with a third -person view, where the player will test the role of the victim or become a maniac. 7 people try to survive and escape from Jason Wurchis. The game takes place in a small town near the forest. You can hide in houses, hide in the foliage, but the inexorable killer will still overtake you. The main goal is to get out of the damned place by leading the engine of the car or calling the police.</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Wildlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the new part -Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands - truly inspires what the developers tried to convict all players of. It must be said, but there is no plot in a third-person shooter. You independently write the story of your team, which is initially aimed at destroying the cartel that trades and produces drugs. But more on that later.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s worth discussing the inner world of Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands.</description></item><item><title>theHunter: Call of the Wild</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</guid><description>Game Description The Hunter&amp;rsquo;s Open World is now available intheHunter: Call of the Wild. This is not a simple hunter simulator, where we will have to climb trees and hide in the grass to kill the next deer, but a full-fledged world with smells, changing wind and weather; with the individual behavior of each animal that must be killed to complete the task. This is not a simple hunt, but a real one!</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 7: Biohazard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil 7: Biohazard is a survival horror game that continues the famous series of games, one of the founders of the genre. The release is timed to coincide with the twentieth anniversary of the universe. An option is available to play using a virtual reality helmet and control of special complete controllers from VR glasses.
The seventh part was a return to the roots of the first games in the series, because, unlike parts 5 and 6, which were focused on action, shooting and the plot taking place in different parts of the world, this project has the main location in the form of a small estate of the Baker family, which gives the atmosphere is claustrophobic and increases the degree of fear.</description></item><item><title>ASTRONER</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astroneer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astroneer/</guid><description>Game Description New resources inASTRONEER are presented in the form of any discovery on other planets, and everything that a person could bring with him after a galactic expedition was bought up at a clean price. There was an explosion in the world. Humanity is again hunting for “gold”, sending its compatriots into space. However, in the 25th century, when humanity has fully explored space, they send people to distant planets, where all that is known is that the planets are just as round.</description></item><item><title>Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</guid><description>Game Description Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun is a tactical stealth action game set in the Japanese Edo era (1603-1868). A conspiracy led by Kage-sama is carried out against the new shogun, after he was able to unite the lands of Japan. In order not to destroy the world, the ruler instructs his henchman samurai named Mugen to track down Kage-sama and his organization. For these purposes, the hero enlists the support of four companions - masters of secrecy and penetration.</description></item><item><title>Killing Floor 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</guid><description>Game Description A cooperative first-person shooter in which there are only two modes - survival and battle in the territory. Killing Floor 2 does not have a plot, but there is sharp FPS on several maps, where each player chooses the desired role for himself - a zombie or a department fighting an epidemic. In addition to the fact that the gameplay differs on both sides of the barricades, players can buy additional weapons, make skins and show who can stand up best on the map.</description></item><item><title>No Man's Sky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/no-mans-sky/</guid><description>Game Description Travel on an intergalactic level has become too simple and ordinary. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly difficult to create a game that captivates with its graphics, but the developers ofNo Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky, an indie adventure game with an open world and a wonderful RPG base, were able to recreate the image of space. Distant, limitless, completely open and so human.
We play as a character, but then our gameplay switches to an entire space station or ship.</description></item><item><title>Starbound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starbound/</guid><description>Game Description Starbound is a 2D side-scrolling indie RPG adventure with graphics that reference the classic 8-bit titles of the last century. The project has become widespread thanks to the ability to play with a friend in co-op mode on different platforms, as well as a well-developed system of achievements and rewards that motivate you to improve your own skills and collect all kinds of items for crafting and collecting. The surrounding world is presented in the form of open territories, where there are no prohibitions on colonizing unknown planets or performing secondary tasks; you can even not touch the story campaign at all.</description></item><item><title>Dead by Daylight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</guid><description>Game Description Dead by Daylight is an asymmetrical cooperative horror game inspired by youth slashers. The story centers on four survivors facing off against a fifth player who controls a bloodthirsty maniac. The defending team&amp;rsquo;s job is to do everything possible to ensure they aren&amp;rsquo;t dead by dawn. Finding yourself in the same location with the killer, you need to use the environment and interact with your partners, trying to resist the monster.</description></item><item><title>Wayward</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</guid><description>Game Description Survive in the wild in Wayward, traveling around the open world. The protagonist has no basic specialization, as he passes, he pumps skills and becomes capable of everything. To get new characteristics, you have to interact with objects and the world around you. You have the opportunity to play as you want.
The world is endless and generated randomly. Objects, chests, opponents, dangers, dungeons and tasks are also created by chance.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve Together is a survival simulator in an unknown world, where our character, pre-selected in the editor, wakes up and immediately goes to look for firewood, because Maxwell said so. The game is cooperative, since the story passage is divided into 2 parts. The first is survival. It is built on three phases of the day: day, evening and night.
During the day, your character calmly survives, collects items, crafts new ones, eats and carries out orders for Maxwell.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light: The Following</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-the-following/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light-the-following/</guid><description>Game Description Dying Light: The Following provides the players with an extensive game world, a large arsenal of weapons, modifications, secondary and plot tasks, as well as dozens of gameplay hours. Visit in the post-apocalyptic world, teeming zombies and other bloodthirsty creatures in the action of the first person.
Pour blood in epic battles! Use dozens of ways to kill zombies, as well as interact with surrounding objects that allow the enemies to eliminate opponents.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Our task inRise of the Tomb Raider is to get ahead of your enemies, go on your first expedition and watch interactive videos, of which there are at least 1.5 hours of gameplay in the game. Lara Croft goes to the unknown world of the city of Kitezh. A secret organization called “Trinity” is also heading there. The principle of the game about Lara is an adventure game mixed with the adventure romance of the first journey, in which we kill with a bow, collect important items, and sometimes survive in the wild.</description></item><item><title>Scrap Mechanic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scrap-mechanic/</guid><description>Game Description Scrap Mechanic is a multiplayer engineering sandbox that offers you to design various mechanisms and compete with friends. The game world revolves around a mechanic who maintains robots on an agricultural planet. He makes sure that they are working properly: that they are cultivating the land on time, sowing, collecting raw materials, which the hero then sends to the central planets, where people live ordinary lives. But one day the spaceship crashed, and the robots around went crazy.</description></item><item><title>The Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</guid><description>Game Description The island on whichThe Isle takes place has a rich and varied environment that is randomly generated. All artifacts, items and events will be located in different places with each new launch. Players must team up to effectively explore the area, which contains many secrets, including various quest items that further advance the plot. The map contains an area of ​​16x16 square kilometers. Multiplayer survival game The Isle allows you to play with three different factions in three different modes:</description></item><item><title>Fallout 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fallout-4/</guid><description>Game Description Fallout 4 is a sequel to the famous role-playing game series in a post-apocalyptic setting. The player wakes up from cryosleep and discovers that he is the only survivor of Vault 111. Having made it to the surface, he finds himself in the Wasteland - a world destroyed by nuclear war. The gameplay includes: a free open world with hundreds of locations to explore, a huge number of NPCs, companions and quests, as well as interaction with many factions, including the Institute, the Brotherhood of Steel, the Minutemen and agents of the Underground; S.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Army Trilogy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-army-trilogy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-army-trilogy/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Army Trilogy - this game is a collectible gaming collection created in the style of a three -dimensional bloody shooter, which are narrated from a third -person.
The plot of the game tells us about the resurrection of Hitler, who was aroused with the help of a deal with Satan. He begins to create an entire army of a zombie-soldier, which, after his death, are full of aggression, thirst for blood and revenge.</description></item><item><title>Forsaken Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forsaken-isle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forsaken-isle/</guid><description>Game Description Forsaken Isle is an adventure survival with a view of the top. You find yourself on a uninhabited island where you have to explore the surrounding territories, collect resources, build refuge and fight with a huge number of enemies. The main thing is to survive at all costs in the hostile environment of the forgotten island. Once alone with nature, you have to use all the skills to survive.</description></item><item><title>Dying Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dying-light/</guid><description>Game Description A terrible virus grows into a global problem inDying Light. Starting from the city of Harran in Latin America, the infection is decimating the entire world, turning those infected into the walking dead. The hero must survive in such circumstances and try to correct the situation. As an undercover operative, Kyle Crane receives his most important assignment. He needs to find a guy named Suleiman in order to take away from him an important file that he stole.</description></item><item><title>Rising World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-world/</guid><description>Game Description Rising World - a game in the “sandbox” genre. Your main goal is to survive in a world that you can create yourself. Explore caves, forests, mountains and dungeons. Develop new tools to solve problems and invent your powerful technologies. You can unite with other players to create civilization, trade and fight. This world is in your hands!
Peculiarities:
The modified world - everything you see can be changed.</description></item><item><title>Craft the World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</guid><description>Game Description Craft the World is an adventure 2D game that combines multiple elements. You can explore the procedurally generated worlds, build locks and fortresses, fight with hostile creatures and get materials necessary for numerous crafts.
Manage the dwarf tribe and lead them the way you want. The player can send his wards to extract resources, build structures or fight with opponents. But, not everything is so simple. You have to put them on, help in battles and feed them in time.</description></item><item><title>This War of Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</guid><description>Game Description This War of Mine is a cross-platform platformer game with elements of survival for an entire group of people. At the beginning of the game, you are given several characters to control the group, and you develop them depending on the time of day. During the day, the characters live in a house located in a city besieged by rebels. They arrange their everyday life, help each other, perform joint tasks and craft the necessary items.</description></item><item><title>Metro 2033 Redux</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</guid><description>Game Description Metro 2033 Redux is a first-person shooter with a deep story and horror elements. The developers questioned not the simple existence of people underground, but the relationships between them. Has the main threat always been with us, in people? In the world of the post-apocalypse, we play as a character named Artem. He grew up underground, in the Moscow metro. In 2013, the world was hit by the terrible consequences of the latest epidemic.</description></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: Season 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-2/</guid><description>Game Description The Walking Dead: The Game. Season 2 – the continuation of the “Walking Dead” franchise does not lag behind the first part and begins its story 2 years after the previous events. Now in The Walking Dead: Season Two, the user plays as a 10-year-old girl, Clementine, who is once again trying to find shelter and survive in a mortal world filled with living corpses. Having lost all his old friends, a brave child begins a journey on his own.</description></item><item><title>Project Zomboid</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/project-zomboid/</guid><description>Game Description Project Zomboid is a cross-platform game in which we will have to find a house, equip it, and start surviving in a world where a zombie apocalypse has recently occurred. We are located in Knox County. The latest epidemic infected more than 90% of the district&amp;rsquo;s residents, and they all became zombies. Difficult conditions will force us to survive, stock up on food, water, weapons and all available supplies in order to simply survive.</description></item><item><title>Contagion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contagion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contagion/</guid><description>Game Description Contagion - a fascinating zombie at the first person, created in the best traditions of action with a completely open world. The plot tells us about the world into which the virus penetrates and absorbs everyone without a trace. Everyone who fell under his actions turned into half -dead carcasses that crave blood. We take the role of the character, for the large -scale cleansing of human lands from the zombie.</description></item><item><title>Outlast (+Whistleblower)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outlast-whistleblower/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outlast-whistleblower/</guid><description>Game Description Outlast (+Whistleblower) - DLC for the game of the same name, which added more content and a new storyline. The addition contains a backstory of the events that happened in the original, where Miles Upshur played the game. The journalist went to the Mount Massive mental hospital, where, for information received, there were many violations. Here he encountered a crowd of terrible psychos - monsters who had taken over the hospital.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve is an adventure arcade game in the action strategy genre with crafting elements. This game is an interesting survival simulator with a complete open game world. The plot tells us about the main character who was sailing on a ship and was shipwrecked. He woke up on an abandoned island. You will travel a lot through beautiful locations that were drawn by hand. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin to explore previously unknown living creatures and the remains of bygone times.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter -Far Cry 3 - will teach you how to survive in the wild conditions of the open world, more or less value relationships with good people, and show you what real madness is. The series rewarded us with enough action, showing that a huge arsenal of weapons is just part of what can be given to players in return for their desire to enjoy a completely open world and a good story.</description></item><item><title>FTL: Faster Than Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</guid><description>Game Description FTL: Faster Than Light - this project is a two-dimensional simulator of a space combat ship. The creation and publication of this media product was carried out by the Subset Games studio. The official release took place in the first half of autumn 2012. The gameplay is based on the interaction between the player and the crew of the combat starship.
The success of this space tactical strategy will depend on how successful this cooperation is.</description></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: Season One</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-walking-dead-season-one/</guid><description>Game Description The Walking Dead: Season One is an interactive story divided into 6 episodes with elements of a point-n-click adventure and with QTEs in action scenes, telling the story of Lee Everett, a prisoner who was being transported in a police station when the zombie apocalypse began. car to another place of serving his sentence, but due to an attack on the vehicle by the dead, he managed to escape.</description></item><item><title>Terraria</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraria/</guid><description>Game Description Terraria is a simulator of construction, life, survival, an interesting storyline and everything that could be combined into a game with the Sand Box style. Simple 8-bit graphics take us into a randomly generated world generated by the game itself. The open map is almost endless if you dig deep into the world, but you will be stopped by armies of monsters or underground knights. Terraria is not as simple as it seems.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</guid><description>Game Description InLeft 4 Dead 2 we have a choice between 4 characters. The coach is a massive African American; Nick is an avid gambler, a trickster and a master of theft; Rochelle is a black 29-year-old Depeche Mode fan and journalist; Ellis is a racing fan and car enthusiast. The cooperative first-person shooter captivated many players for several years, providing ample ground for exterminating zombies in 5 game campaigns, which take place in swamps, cities, caves and closed locations.</description></item><item><title>Plants vs. Zombies GOTY Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-goty-edition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-goty-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Plants vs. Zombies became the game of the year, winning in many categories. The developers invite us to once again plunge into battles in a small location in order to free ourselves from the shackles of various zombies, hold back all the ardor of the monsters and save the city by using the latest technologies in the agricultural industry. Among the primary weapons in strategy, we have a pea shooter, a cherry bomb and sunflowers, which we use to earn money to purchase new strategic weapons.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</guid><description>Game Description The first part ofLeft 4 Dead has 6 campaigns, several levels in each. The history and chronology of the chapters are interconnected, which will prevent the gamer from getting confused in the plot. At the beginning of each area, characters will appear at a checkpoint, where they can pick up weapons and ammunition and set off on their further journey.
The United States of America has been gripped by an unknown virus that turns people into terrible monsters with bouts of aggression and rage.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment,Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</guid><description>Game Description Counter-strike is a legendary multiplayer shooter, the founder of one of the most popular series in the history of the gaming industry.
The concept is simple but ingenious. Two teams - terrorists and special forces - are trying to destroy each other on the map. Terrorists have the ability to plant a bomb at one of the key points. and the counterterrorism department tries to predict which point the opponents will attack.</description></item><item><title>International Vending Machine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/interdimensional-vending-machine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:46 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/interdimensional-vending-machine/</guid><description>Game Description The International Vending Machine tells about a homeless girl who has found a strange apparatus. The device, located in a tight and buzzing space at the junction of the worlds, accepts Japanese yen, giving out objects from unknown times and realities in return. The exhausted heroine is forced to use it for the extraction of food. Any item obtained contradicts the laws of biology and logic, creating an oppressive atmosphere of mystery in its attempts to survive another night.</description></item><item><title>Blades of Fire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blades-of-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blades-of-fire/</guid><description>Game Description Blades of Fire offers to gamers to take on the role of Aran de Lira, who begins his way to find a true purpose. The Queen of Nereya turned steel into stone throughout the kingdom with her witchcraft. Only her army, consisting of abominations and undead, has a divine metal that can effectively resist any other armament. This mission leads Aran and his ADSO companion through the vast world, filled with dangers, deep secrets and various locations, such as huge castles and labyrinths of palaces.</description></item><item><title>Machine Mind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</guid><description>Game Description Machine Mind places the player in the role of consciousness transferred to a mechanical shell after the crash of a spaceship. The existence of a gamer is limited by the world, a changed planetary virus and subsequent nuclear conflict - the cataclysm, which forced the remnants of civilization to hide at the orbital station. Managing a series of rovers, it is necessary to provide its survival on the surface of the planet, now inhabited by aggressive raiders.</description></item><item><title>Minecraft for Windows - Bedrock Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/minecraft-for-windows-bedrock-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:35 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/minecraft-for-windows-bedrock-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Minecraft for Windows - Bedrock Edition - a procedurally generated sandbox, in which players are able to create unique cubic worlds. The card is divided into biomers. All areas are represented by an individual environment and climatic conditions. Deserts, mountains, plains, forests, ponds, etc. are available. In Minecraft for Windows - Brap of Edisen, you can switch between the first and third parties. The whole world consists of blocks.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Cits</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</guid><description>Game Description Ancient Cits - a strategic game based on survival and construction mechanics. The game transfers in ancient times when people lived in tribes and built the first settlements. Plunge in prehistoric times and find the primitive life of our ancestors and their ancient cities. Events develop in the era of mesolithic.
Draw your settlers through a whole generation, improving technologies, mastering new tools, engaged in resources, developing the population and fighting external threats.</description></item><item><title>Dustland Delivery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</guid><description>Game Description Dustland Delivery puts users in the post -apocalyptic world, where they have to build an empire of delivery. The center of the game is profit, survival and strategic decisions. Gamers start with a truck and gain a team, each of which has unique skills. The purpose of the game? Build cities by successful delivery of goods, competing with rivals and overcoming dangers. The world is inexorable. Users move in an insidious area, control resources and make a critical choice.</description></item><item><title>Ells Tales: Chairbound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ells-tales-chairbound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ells-tales-chairbound/</guid><description>Game Description Ells Tales: Chairbound begins with the awakening of a character tied to an office chair in an empty room. A strange device with a 10-minute timer is attached to it, steadily counting time. The player’s main task is a desperate search for a way out of a closed corporate building. Movement is achieved by repulsion from surfaces - a method dictated by the physics of finding furniture with wheels, and the main difficulty is to maintain equilibrium.</description></item><item><title>From the Depths</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</guid><description>Game Description From the Depths allows you to accept command of battleships, aircraft, submarines, space ships, balloons and many other modes of transport. The story campaign will visit more than a hundred lands and fight against 8 fractions. Misses consist in planning competent tactics and protecting your own fleet in a series of difficult tests. In addition to the main campaign, there is an adventure mode where it will be proposed to start the game alone on a small ship and grow to a whole fleet, furrows the expanses of the universe.</description></item><item><title>Good Heavens!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/good-heavens/</guid><description>Game Description Good HEAVENS! It takes place in the Severe Kingdom of Xant-Rar, a bizarre afterlife, where souls live on floating islands. This songwriter with the open world allows gamers to pave their own path in the world, crowded with bizarre capabilities. Imagine: you have lived a good life, have left the earthly path and got into Xant -Rar - a place intended for the fulfillment of all your desires throughout eternity.</description></item><item><title>Ifsunsets</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ifsunsets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ifsunsets/</guid><description>Game Description IFSUnsets is an adventure role -playing adventure for survival in which gamers fall into a complex situation. The game begins with the fact that users find themselves on the island after a shipwreck. This initial scenario lays the basis for research and survival. During the day, users can collect supplies and resources scattered across the island. This stage of collecting resources is very important for preparing for dangers that are hidden after sunset.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Nomad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-nomad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-nomad/</guid><description>Game Description Mr. Nomad immerses in a world, where survival depends on the only camp, serving as a mobile refuge. The main task is to build a fortified base around this van to reflect constant raids of the horde of zombies. The basis of gameplay is a two -level construction system that allows you to place ground fortifications and at the same time dig a safe bunker under them. This underground space serves as a protected area for growing a crop and storing valuable supplies far from external threats.</description></item><item><title>Soulmask</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulmask/</guid><description>Game Description Soulmask is a mystical twist on the survival genre. Gamers eschew the usual &amp;ldquo;rags&amp;rdquo; and instead awaken clutching an ancient mask after a near-death experience. This relic is more than just a creepy wall decoration, it&amp;rsquo;s a game changer. Angry weather and wild animals won&amp;rsquo;t be your only problem. Soulmask features a vast open world that you must navigate in order to survive. Gathering resources is a must, but you can&amp;rsquo;t do it alone.</description></item><item><title>Terratech Worlds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terratech-worlds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terratech-worlds/</guid><description>Game Description In TerRatech Worlds, you will plunge with your head in a PVE survival with the open world on the mysterious planet of aliens. Put your way as a free prospector, exploring an extensive environment with an area of ​​300 km² with a variety of bioms, dynamic weather and a day/night cycle. To confront the hostile flora and fauna, rival fractions and insidious areas - and at the same time use the power of the planet in their interests.</description></item><item><title>Under a New Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Under a New Sun begins after a catastrophic failure of the ship, who left the player on an unknown planet. Awakening from cryosn occurs among fragments, completely solitude under a stranger sky. The mission to search for a new house for humanity failed, and the fate of the crew remains a mystery. The path begins in the middle of the wreckage of the vessel, in a world where the earthly flora has taken roots next to local views.</description></item></channel></rss>