<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>strategies on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/</link><description>Recent content in strategies on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BellFortis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</guid><description>Game Description In BellFortis, the action takes place in the early Middle Ages, where users seek to expand their kingdoms and influence the course of history. Title combines step -by -step strategic planning and real -time battles, which gives you the opportunity to control the army and make decisions that affect the world. Would you like to build a strong empire with the help of diplomacy or strength - the choice is yours.</description></item><item><title>Rugby League Team Manager 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</guid><description>Game Description Rugby League Team Manager 4 puts you at the head of the regional club. The circle of your tasks is covered by financial management, negotiations with sponsors and the selection of the state of assistants, mentors and medical staff. You have to improve infrastructure, including the stadium, gym and training fields. This project covers 226 teams from the Northern and Southern Hems, and over 7,000 adult players are available for choice.</description></item><item><title>Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</guid><description>Game Description Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil! - This is an exciting strategy in real time, in which you will go to study the distant world called Grimstar, where you will find a new type of natural energy resources. But not everything is so rosy and sunny - because of your brother’s sudden death, you have to fulfill his contract with the corporation for which he worked, and you must take his place on an alien planet.</description></item><item><title>IDLE WATERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</guid><description>Game Description IDLE WATERS is a game in the IDLE-Rybank genre that works from the window at the bottom of the screen and is designed to simultaneously work with other computer operations. The game window has flexibility: it can be scale, change the layout, change the size and move to any part of the desktop or completely hide. This system allows the simulator to function without requiring constant attention from the gamer.</description></item><item><title>Fuga: Melodies of Steel 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</guid><description>Game Description fuga: Melodies of Steel 3 unfolds the story of desperate efforts. The inexplicable disappearance of Malta forces the group of children to head to the forbidden cave, where they are leaded by a mysterious voice to Taranis - a powerful armored vehicle, which was considered lost. The determination to find Malta returns them aboard this combat vehicle, starting a direct attack on the central regions of the Berman Empire.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>9 kings</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</guid><description>Game Description 9 Kings throws users into the very heart of the medieval kingdom, where the strategy, tactics and resource management dictates the need for survival. This urban planning Roguelike combines a lot of a mechanic, offering unpredictable experience with each launch. The expansion of the kingdom requires careful planning, because the power of the empire depends on each decision. Using a deck of various cards, rulers form their possessions, adapting to unexpected challenges.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Monster Train 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-train-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-train-2/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Train 2 offers a dynamic and strategic approach to creating decks in Roguelike. Users control powerful clans on board the train, laying their way through a chaotic setting filled with demons, angels and threats of titans. As the plot develops, the gamer has several levels of composition, each of which provides unique tasks and opportunities to improve their collection.
The gameplay emphasizes the importance of tactical choice, requiring thorough planning and quick thinking to defeat more and more complex enemies.</description></item><item><title>Monster Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Battles is a tactical auto-batler with equipment control. In this project, participants collect, unite and strategically place a group of creatures for upcoming fights. These creatures are purchased in a special store and then are placed on a certain battlefield before the start of an automatic fight. An effective selection and location of a variety of combat units forms the basis of the game cycle.
In Monster Battles, building a successful detachment requires thoroughly accounting for the features and belonging of the collected creatures.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Mogul 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Mogul 4 — это текстовый бизнес-симулятор, ставящий человека во главе киностудии. Система позволяет создавать кинофильмы и мини-сериалы на основе библиотеки из более чем 14 000 исходных материалов или собственных идей. Ready -made paintings can be planned for global film distribution or for distribution through streaming service. The process includes the formation of accurate budgets, the conclusion of agreements on rental in 19 foreign territories and the management of advertising expenses.</description></item><item><title>Synergy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</guid><description>Game Description synergy dedicated to survival on a hostile planet. In this urban planning strategy, players have to develop their city, face natural cataclysms and make the right decisions that will certainly have consequences. Explore this constantly changing world, preserving the happiness of the townspeople in extreme weather conditions.
Gamers will control the weather, seasons, extreme conditions and natural disasters. The main goal is to build a city where residents will be happy and satisfied, respecting the natural needs of the inhabitants and living in harmony with the local fauna and flora.</description></item><item><title>Pocket City 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket City 2 makes it possible for players to build cities, and then study their first -person creations. The process starts from the laying of roads, the markings of sections for residential, commercial or industrial needs and the construction of the necessary objects on the map. Control over the economy implies monitoring of stocks, profit and a thoughtful placement of special structures, access to which opens as they move.</description></item><item><title>Learning Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</guid><description>Game Description learning factory - a simulator that is designed to create an automated process of processes and, most importantly, understand one simple truth: what do cats want? The gameplay allows you to head the Kotovod factory. It was once closed, but now it has been possible to renew the process and create your own cat store. Learning factory gameplay largely gives an idea of ​​how machine learning works.
Your factory is analyzing a huge database, trying to study the behavior of pets.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of QUD-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Zephon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in Zephon have to take control of the remnants of mankind in order to survive on the territory of the Earth. On the planet, there are few areas that are not suitable for life, and most of the cities were destroyed. In wild territories are mutating creatures that they gather in small groups and begin to hunt for surviving people. Alien robots with damaged systems roam on the surface, and the aliens themselves are hidden and try to secure survival.</description></item><item><title>Citadelum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</guid><description>Game Description Citadelum throws its hat to the ring of strategic games, offering the experience of building cities with an admixture of mythology and strategic conquests. Ancient Rome serves as a background for the game: gamers take control of a nascent settlement and should turn it into a lively metropolis. Resource management is a paramount task for any novice urban planner. But Citadelum is not only overgrown suburbs and towering monuments.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>Tendryll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tendryll/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tendryll/</guid><description>Game Description Tendryll uses tactical battles on the grid as part of a horny structure, where players go through a series of enemies. You have to command a detachment of heroes, which requires careful coordination of their unique skills to survive in every clash. The battlefield itself poses a threat due to a distorting map of the area, which directly affects the characters&amp;rsquo; hands, imposing a curse on their ability.</description></item><item><title>Nordic ashes: Survivors of Ragnarok</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</guid><description>Game Description Nordic ashes: survivors of ragnarok - Dynamic adventure with elements of action and simplified cuckle. The plot is inspired by Scandinavian legends and motives. The main character finds himself in a dangerous environment in which he will face hordes of enemy and deadly creatures. He needs to stay alive among hundreds of opponents and traps, gradually pumping his abilities and finding more powerful equipment.
The central character will move between worlds, fight with powerful bosses, overcome traps and find objects of equipment.</description></item><item><title>Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</guid><description>Game Description Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout - an adventure action in which a group of people falls on a tropical island equipped with high -tech objects. The territory is governed by AI, which produces a huge number of combat robots and artificially nurtures of dinosaurs. The game is made in the Cyberpanus setting and contains elements of metroid.
Once on the island, it must be examined by opening the results of a monstrous experiment.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the White Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of the White Sun transfers to the chaos of China of the 1920s, the period of riots and fragmented leadership. In this grandiose strategic game, you have to pave the way through a fragmented nation controlled by military leaders, rebels and political groups. The action unfolds at a time when various groups dispute control of vast territories and armies, each of which has its own goals, objectives and motives.</description></item><item><title>Darkest Dungeon 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</guid><description>Game Description Darkest Dungeon II, exciting and tense Roguelike-game, immerses players in the nightmare world, standing on the verge of an apocalypse. In the game, you have to become a brave leader, assemble a detachment, equip your faithful diligyans and go on a difficult journey through a destroying landscape. Plunging into the abyss, you will soon find that the most terrible threat may come from your detachment.
The combat system, known for its innovations in the original Darkest Dungeon, triumphantly returns to the sequel.</description></item><item><title>Caves of Lore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of lore-role-playing game with two-dimensional pixel art style graphics and from above. Moving by locations occurs in real time. During the study of the area, you can neutralize traps, look for secrets and hack chests with loot. Equipment can be of different colors. Coloring depends on the rarity of the object. There are hundreds of things here. Battles with monsters are held in step -by -step mode. In battle, heroes can move around the cells.</description></item><item><title>Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</guid><description>Game Description Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga tells about the events that erupted after the conflict between the Empire of Veridia and Tanra. They fought for a long time, and in the end all these events led to the fact that the first empire remained in losses. However, thanks to the young ruler of Florin, a shaky, but peace finally formed. Everyone began to gradually recover until something terrible happened.</description></item><item><title>Polimines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</guid><description>Game Description Thanks to** Polimines** you can try to swing your own intelligence, as well as strangle to strain your brains. Yes, this is a head-headed game in which the levels will need to go through the locations. But it will not be at all as easy as it might seem at first glance. Therefore, it will be necessary to make all your efforts, as well as understand the basic principle.</description></item><item><title>Kakatte Koi Yo!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</guid><description>Game Description kakatte koi yo! - This is a two -dimensional action platform with the possibility of local multiplayer. This is a real cat’s battle, in which you have to take control of powerful cats and master even more powerful fish to defeat your opponents in a fierce 2D platform battle. This game with charming aesthetics in the Japanese style and irresistibly cute characters is an obligatory game for any cat lover.</description></item><item><title>Hex of Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Players in Hex of Steel have to go during the Second World War, where you will have to control the troops on land, water and in the air. The project is a full -scale Vargam, where you have to perform step -by -step actions on the global map of the world, which includes Europe, Africa and the Pacific regions. Users will be able to fight against AI in a single campaign or special historical scenarios, as well as in the cross -platform mode of PBEM and multiplayer skirmishes against other users (there is the possibility of cooperative passage).</description></item><item><title>On the Western Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</guid><description>Game Description On the Western Front - this is a tactical strategy, the action of which unfolds against the background of the First World War, namely on the infamous Western Front. Users take on the role of the division commander, who are instructed to manage various aspects of military operations in one of the most exhausting and complex periods in history. The Title emphasizes the harsh realities of the trench war, where the soldiers are faced with many problems, from the constant threat of enemy fire to the constant need to manage resources.</description></item><item><title>Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth abandoned long walks and romantic novels with stars that are found in other farm sigas. It’s enough just to click a cursor. The Title with a strategic farm bias with your head immerses you in the creation, construction, collection and management of a prosperous farm. Starting from a modest site, do not allow the initial sizes to deceive you. Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth is all about potential.</description></item><item><title>Let's Build a Zoo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</guid><description>Game Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Zoo - A bright sandbox with a simulator elements, which provides players with the opportunity to build their own zoo. It is required to install enclosures, buy rare animals, hire employees for service and much more. It is allowed to cross animal DNA, producing more than 300,000 unique rocks into the world.
In order for the reserve to function, it will be necessary to hire veterinarians, trainers, cleaners, repairmen and other performers who support their lives in the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item></channel></rss>