<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>strategies on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/</link><description>Recent content in strategies on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IDLE BOSS Rush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-boss-rush/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-boss-rush/</guid><description>Game Description In IDLE BOSS Rush, the starting point for creating a powerful kingdom is a lifeless wasteland. The main task is to turn a modest camp into a prosperous city, gathering an army to defeat giant bosses. Each battle with the enemy is a serious test that requires either time or competent tactics. Further development depends on the management of the population and resources. The economic foundation is important for the maintenance of an army that can reflect the onslaught of huge monsters and expand the boundaries of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Rose of Wind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rose-of-wind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rose-of-wind/</guid><description>Game Description Rose of Wind offers to take care of an old tavern inherited from his grandfather. This once flourished institution now needs a caring hand to restore its reputation and again make the center of attraction for travelers. A variety of guests will knock on the door, from tired merchants to brave adventurers, each with his own fate. The atmosphere depends on the decisions of the manager: you can feed them added to them, provide an overnight stay or support the conversation at the hearth.</description></item><item><title>Cloverpit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cloverpit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cloverpit/</guid><description>Game Description Cloverpit puts the protagonist in a rusty camera equipped only with a slot machine and an ATM. Each round sets a clear goal: to accumulate enough coins to pay a constantly growing debt to an invisible kidnapper. This cycle of risky bets works as a debt simulator, in which non -payment leads to an immediate loss. A closed, surreal environment creates an atmosphere of a psychological horror, turning a solitary passage into a desperate attempt to escape from the hellish Western.</description></item><item><title>Buggos 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buggos-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buggos-2/</guid><description>Game Description In Buggos 2, the key goal is to conquer planets under the control of a reasonable hive. In the role of this collective intelligence, the player directs the beetle waves to human settlements. The task is to crush the defense of a pure biomass and completely exterminate humanity on all six worlds of the solar system. The destruction campaign consists in sending successive swarms to destroy fortified positions until the target world goes under the control of the swarm.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Magnate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotel-magnate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotel-magnate/</guid><description>Game Description Hotel Magnate is a hotel manager simulator. You need to manage the whole process: from building a building and choosing the color of the walls - to the hire of workers and the fight against emergency situations. You can manage a luxurious hotel in the center of the metropolis, a small motel by the road or a sunny resort with a pool.
In the Hotel Magnate, everything will begin with the construction of the building: the foundation, walls, rooms and stairs.</description></item><item><title>Forsaker: Dingding and Blade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forsaker-dingding-and-blade/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forsaker-dingding-and-blade/</guid><description>Game Description Forsaker: Dingding and Blade begins with a regular mission for two young men, which develops into a Cannibal Odyssey on the Hel continent. The local world is divided into three fractions: people, the Church of the Divine Body and the devouring flesh of the outcasts. Players explore this society, constantly faced with the main choice: to eat another or become prey. The plot reveals deep conspiracies and casts doubt on the established order and the very nature of survival.</description></item><item><title>Aethermancer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aethermancer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aethermancer/</guid><description>Game Description Aethermancer - an adventure in which the player in the role of a powerful Ethermant will have to explore the constantly changing world of the Terast. The main task is to create an indestructible connection with mythical creatures that fell into an endless cycle of death and rebirth. The protagonist needs to assemble a detachment of three monsters and conduct them through dangerous procedurally generated locations of destroyed ruins.</description></item><item><title>Aztecs The Last Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aztecs-the-last-sun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aztecs-the-last-sun/</guid><description>Game Description In Aztecs The Last Sun, the player becomes the ruler of Tenochtitlan, a great state that can win the whole world. The user relies on many tasks, as the head of his own power. He has to develop a city, increase military power and improve the quality of life of citizens. Having taken the control over the Aztecs, you will need to go through the three great centuries, to dominate in the nearest territories and write new pages in world history.</description></item><item><title>Celestial Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celestial-empire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/celestial-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Celestial Empire offers to go to the Han dynasty when the Chinese empire was one of the most powerful in the world. Here, the user is given the role of the Governor of the province, who was personally chosen by the emperor. Now, everything must be done in order to make this place better and provide a high standard of living for people. And given that there are a lot of ways for the development of the structure, you can not limit yourself to a single strategy, but try different options.</description></item><item><title>Crypt Crawler</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crypt-crawler/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crypt-crawler/</guid><description>Game Description The plot of Crypt Crawler starts after the fall of the heroes of the kingdom under the onslaught of the hordes of undead, poured from the open gates of the underworld. The mission to seal the fault is assigned to a lonely mechanic goblin. The character will have a 16-level descent into the dungeon in a dungeon in a monsters to achieve and close the portal. Each stage offers a new tactical task, forcing the goblin to climb deeper into the enemy territory for the sake of fulfilling the mission.</description></item><item><title>Global Magnates: Shipping Tycoon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/global-magnates-shipping-tycoon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/global-magnates-shipping-tycoon/</guid><description>Game Description Global Magnates: Shipping Tycoon sets the gamers the task of creating a marine empire built around a new technology for its time - a sea container. The main goal is to turn a small enterprise into a dominant logistics corporation. The process includes competition with rivals under the control of AI, using hostile absorptions, buying assets and price wars to capture the market share.
Success requires the acquisition of key ports, expand the flotilla and investment in a shipyard to maintain superiority in a changeable economic situation, where each solution affects the situation.</description></item><item><title>Pompeii: The Legacy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pompeii-the-legacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pompeii-the-legacy/</guid><description>Game Description Pompeii: The Legacy sets the gamers the task of leading the Roman family and restore the city 20 years after the eruption of Vesuvius. The project requires to take into account the different needs of the patricians, plebeians and slaves, since each group has its own goals. Players from scratch lay streets, erects forums and build aqueducts. Any infrastructure or social decision affects the position of the family and determines its legacy for centuries, generating the consequences for future generations.</description></item><item><title>The House of Tesla</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-tesla/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-house-of-tesla/</guid><description>Game Description The House of Tesla offers Gamer the role of Nikola Tesla, who was stuck alone on the territory of his most ambitious project - the abandoned complex of Wardencliffe. The main task is to study idle industrial equipment and reveal a secret that has entailed the current desolation. History is presented on behalf of the inventor exploring the key points that led to the construction and subsequent fall of the famous tower.</description></item><item><title>Endless Legend 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-legend-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-legend-2/</guid><description>Game Description In Endless Legend 2, the factions fight in the variable ocean world on the verge of collapse. The task of the gamer is to conduct its civilization through expansion, policy and military clashes, revealing secrets hidden in the bowels of the planet. The world itself is transformed: cataclysms force the oceans to retreat, exposing new lands for conquest. It is necessary to base cities, develop economic infrastructure and command troops in step -by -step tactical battles to conquer opponents and consolidate on a changing map.</description></item><item><title>Northwind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/northwind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/northwind/</guid><description>Game Description The mercenary in Northwind chooses a specific hunt, after which it plans the route through a dangerous, frozen territory. The main task is to travel around these lands in order to find and defeat formidable monsters. In the breaks between the signs, the avant -navpost serves as a central base for preparation and improvements. The gameplay is built on the implementation of such tasks, overcoming powerful bosses and collecting resources to strengthen subsequent attempts.</description></item><item><title>A Gentlemen's Dispute</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-gentlemens-dispute/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-gentlemens-dispute/</guid><description>Game Description In A Gentlemen&amp;rsquo;s Dispute, up to 8 fighters fight in multiplaying competitions for the title of the last survivor. They use various weapons, including bits, bazuki, guns and placed traps to eliminate opponents. The action takes place on closed arenas for a simple purpose - to eliminate all other opponents. Each match is a dynamic battle with a third -person view, focusing on a direct collision and tactical placement for victory.</description></item><item><title>Ale Abbey</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-abbey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ale-abbey/</guid><description>Game Description Ale Abbey is a unique world where users will be able to build, manage and expand the monastery specializing in the cooking of the Holy Elya. Title does not make it possible to use ready -made recipes, forcing to experiment and create your own varieties of beer from scratch. The users will have to comprehend the art of brewing, adjusting the temperature of the grout, the quality and amount of beer in order to achieve the perfect result.</description></item><item><title>Flick Shot Rogues</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flick-shot-rogues/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flick-shot-rogues/</guid><description>Game Description Flick Shot Rogues places heroes on a desktop field, where the outcome of each course depends on the laws of physics. Players plan, aim and start their characters, like balls in billiards or pinball. The task is to clean the location from opponents, causing chain reactions and thoughtful clashes. Success requires a combination of tactical insight with an understanding of inertia to conquer various biomes of the island, including the full trap of the jungle.</description></item><item><title>Lord Ambermase</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lord-ambermaze/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lord-ambermaze/</guid><description>Game Description The Universe in Lord Ambermaze succumbed to a terrible curse that stopped the normal course of time. The main character is a guy named Zin, who owns an ancient magic relic under the name &amp;ldquo;sword of movement.&amp;rdquo; Thanks to the enchanted weapon, the protagonist gets the opportunity to move freely around the world and resist the dangers that the Lord Ambermase prepares. Users will have to save the kingdom and the princess, which is in the imprisonment of the criminal.</description></item><item><title>Shapehero Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapehero-factory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapehero-factory/</guid><description>Game Description Shapehero Factory combines the elements of the simulator of the factory, rogelitis and Tower Defense. Players build huts for the mass production of heroes who automatically fight with the waves of enemies. The goal is to defeat the great disaster sealed in the book of magic. With the help of minions, collect a variety of characters from basic figures found on a magic scroll. Circles and triangles form soldiers, and circles and squares - sprites.</description></item><item><title>Rana Card</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rana-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rana-card/</guid><description>Game Description The player plays the role of a farm manager working on the TimeTech corporation. Its task is to achieve planned indicators established by management. The whole process is built on the formation of the deck and the competent use of cards, each of which has its own time in time. Each move has to decide whether it is worth taking another card, risking the exhausted time limit. This element of excitement and balanced risk is the central part of the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Pinata Go Boom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinata-go-boom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinata-go-boom/</guid><description>Game Description Pinata Go Boom throws a player in the role of an employee armed with bat and corporate ambitions. The main task is to break the Pignata in a series of industrial premises. To go to the next zone, it is necessary to destroy all containers. Broken Pignata releases a variety of toys and prey to be collected. The accumulated catch becomes the basis for career growth and development of skills in the hierarchy.</description></item><item><title>Misty Judgment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</guid><description>Game Description Misty Judgment begins with the awakening of the protagonist, qi and, from a nightmare in a strange reality without clear memories. Unable to confirm his own personality, he investigates a series of murders filed in the video format with real actors. The main task is the search and analysis of evidence, the comparison of facts and the calculation of the criminal. Any solution affects further events, and the future of the protagonist depends on the deductive abilities of the player.</description></item><item><title>Coal LLC</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coal-llc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coal-llc/</guid><description>Game Description In Coal LLC, the player is engaged in the extraction of constantly growing coal volumes to perform a daily quota, and the failure leads to the end of the passage. The activity begins with one Old Kirki, forcing to descend deep underground to achieve production goals before dark. The underground world is updated daily, offering a new location of resources requiring quick development. As the company&amp;rsquo;s industrial activity expands, the environment begins to demonstrate signs of decline.</description></item><item><title>It</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-time-your-majesty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-time-your-majesty/</guid><description>Game Description It&amp;rsquo;s Time Your Majesty is a strategy in which the fate of the whole dynasty falls on the shoulders of the ruler, where each decision is made through the choice of cards. In the role of the monarch, it is necessary to rule the state, trying to achieve prosperity and protect subjects from numerous threats. On the way to greatness, both external enemies and internal problems that require a balanced approach will stand.</description></item><item><title>Mage and Monsters 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mage-and-monsters-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mage-and-monsters-2/</guid><description>Game Description Mage and Monsters 2 opens the battlefield on which the hired hero leads the army to an automatic battle. During these battles, the player actively supports his forces, using spells with a view of the top. Further development is determined by the strategic elections accepted between the battles and focused on the strengthening of the hero’s personal power, strengthen the troops or increase the potential of magic. The decisions made directly affect the effectiveness of autonomously acting units and determine the course of fantasy war.</description></item><item><title>Trainatic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trainatic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trainatic/</guid><description>Game Description Trainatic offers the player to pump wagons to collect materials when driving along a railway canvas. The key task is the constant expansion of the locomotive, starting with one engine. The accession of new components increases its length and capabilities, facilitating the promotion of the procedurally generated path. This process allows you to accumulate raw materials for subsequent construction. Over time, the composition is transformed from the initial form into a massive structure that occupies a significant part of the screen.</description></item><item><title>Star Fire: Eternal Cycle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-fire-eternal-cycle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-fire-eternal-cycle/</guid><description>Game Description Star Fire: Eternal Cycle triggers a race in which the main character makes jerks and combo against alien enemies in futuristic 2.5D-gallocations. The gameplay is built on a combination of sid-scrolling battles in the spirit of Beat &amp;lsquo;Em Up and progression systems characteristic of Roguelite. Each attempt to clean the level is distinguished by a unique arrangement of enemies and procedurally generated branches of tracks. The player’s movement and attacks are designed for direct control, requiring evasions and accurate calculation of the time to win the cyberpanic opponents in the destroyed environment.</description></item><item><title>Overlooting</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/overlooting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/overlooting/</guid><description>Game Description Overlooting combines the alliance of three characters against the decaying dark power. The group includes Maximilian, a hero from a noble family, Liz, a thief wanted in many countries, and a shadow is a mysterious creature that was previously considered a source of damage. Their main task is the extraction of equipment controlled through the system of inventory within the framework of the crog. Such a structure guarantees that each attempt to complete the mission sets different conditions before the detachment, changing the path to victory in every new game.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Warfare 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-warfare-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-warfare-3/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Warfare 3 offers the player to construct a deadly obstacle strip, laying out the landscape tiles and cutting out dangerous paths for the advancing adventurers. The main activity is the deployment of an expanded arsenal of traps and cunning mechanisms intended for inflicting injuries, wounds and disorientation of enemy detachments. You can directly form a battlefield, erecting walls or swarms and thereby directing opponents to strategically arranged protective structures.</description></item><item><title>PLAN B: TerRaform</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plan-b-terraform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plan-b-terraform/</guid><description>Game Description In PLAN B: TerraForm, it is necessary to take up the colonization of the planet. To do this, it is necessary to collect resources on the surface of the continent and debug a system for supplying production to cities for further production. The most important resource is settlers. It is required to do everything you need to make the planet suitable for people to live. For example, you need to heat the atmosphere to the correct temperature, create water bodies, plant trees and much more.</description></item><item><title>Chip N Clawz vs. The Brainioids</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chip-n-clawz-vs-the-brainioids/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chip-n-clawz-vs-the-brainioids/</guid><description>Game Description In Chip N Clawz vs. The Brainioids will have to collect a resource called Brainum, build bases and manage the army of bots against alien invaders. The gamer takes under the direct control of the inventor of the chip or robocot Clause with a third -person view, leading the assault in order to return the abducted crystals. The main conflict is tied to the Braynioids who took resources into their engraving spheres.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Map</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond The Map begins with a shipwreck on the outskirts of the known seas, setting the player an immediate task of survival in a mysterious territory. The development of the character is complete without a class system: increasing the level of skills opens up new basic abilities. The search for rare folios with spells around the world provides access to incredible forces, additionally determining the capabilities of the hero.</description></item><item><title>Knightica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knightica/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knightica/</guid><description>Game Description Knightica instructs commanders to gather a detachment and strategically arrange its fighters to use combat synergies. Units have unique abilities activated by accurate arrangement and turning on the battlefield. The player forms these forces from various fractions, such as the legions of undead or adherents of the guild of magicians, before their entry into automated battles. The assembled army then goes on a hike through a series of trials in order to free the kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Worldwide rush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/worldwide-rush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/worldwide-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Worldwide Rush is immersed in the management of the global passenger corporation. The start of the career begins with the construction of the main office and the selection of equipment from an extensive park in 120 models, including cars, trains, planes and ships. The main goal of this gaming project is to connect thousands of settlements with profitable routes, based on dynamic demand. To increase profits, you can invest in the hotel business and advertising campaigns, while the entire logistics system requires constant improvement.</description></item><item><title>Planetary Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/planetary-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/planetary-life/</guid><description>Game Description In Planetary Life, you will find yourself in the role of a planetary architect. In this Simulator, you get divine control over the barren world. Create mountains and cut the valleys, erupt volcanic rage or create gentle slopes. Create the perfect environment: adjust the heat of the nuclei, work with gases in the atmosphere and control precipitation.
Planetary life is not only the formation of land. You will also become a shepherd of life itself.</description></item><item><title>A FISTFUL of YANKEES</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-fistful-of-yankees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-fistful-of-yankees/</guid><description>Game Description A FISTFUL of Yankes offers the player to lead a detachment of government soldiers sent to the American West in 1865 to combat desperate criminals and robber barons. On this post -war frontier, life and death solve weapons. The key task of the unit is to establish order by tracking the robbers attacking the settlers. However, this mission draws the fighters into a much larger conflict with serious consequences, going beyond initial orders.</description></item><item><title>Dice Gambit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</guid><description>Game Description Step -by -step battles in Dice Gambit allow us to plunge into tactical competitions, where the victory determines the cubes that affect the management of the characters. The game is designed for strategic miscalculations where a variety and excitement makes a bone throw. Each result on dits permits to obtain a limited number of actions for heroes fighting on combat arenas. The characters will be able to move, perform interactions with the environment or inflict damage to the opponents on the field.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Dawn of War - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-dawn-of-war-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-dawn-of-war-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Dawn of War - Definitive Edition - this is a single package uniting the original project and all its additions. Players have to accept the command of one of the 9 factions, from the technological tau and the mysterious Eldar to the ruthless forces of Chaos, and lead them in cruel conflicts on more than 100 cards. This publication contains four full -fledged campaigns offering both linear plots and nonlinear conquests of entire planetary systems.</description></item><item><title>Cleanfall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cleanfall/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cleanfall/</guid><description>Game Description Cleanfall puts a player at the head of the harvesting robot, the only function of which is to maintain cleanliness in the house. This simple task becomes a planetary mission after one techie brought the world closer to his sun. The cataclysm that happened covered the surface with a whirlwind of dust and death, making a restraint of order impossible. In order to bring cleanliness in his house again, the mechanism must first correct the whole world, going down to the underground layers of the planet to start his work.</description></item><item><title>Era One</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/era-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/era-one/</guid><description>Game Description Era One puts the player into the future with the destroyed political system of mankind. After a catastrophic gravitational event that paralyzed mass migration, societies on board the giant space cities enter the war for stinging resources. The mutated bioshahters pose a constant threat to the entire solar system. In these conditions, a woman named Alya de Chars is trying to get a source of energy for a secret ship, striving for a new beginning.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Supermarket Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-supermarket-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-supermarket-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Supermarket Simulator immerses the player at the head of the universal store in 1850. The action takes place in a ghost town, empty after the end of the gold fever and the majority of their inhabitants. The gamer arrives to lead a business, which is only a shadow of former greatness. The main task is to restore the enterprise from scratch, laying out goods on shelves and managing supplies to revive an abandoned location.</description></item><item><title>Demigoddess!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demigoddess/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demigoddess/</guid><description>Game Description Demigoddess! - A step -by -step strategic game, with sessions calculated for completion for 1 hour. The procedural generation each time creates a unique world, changing the continents, the deployment of the enemy and the distribution of resources. The world consists of 64 regions, and to win the player needs to win over 32 of these territories. You can command armies of 20 different fractions, including over 450 species of soldiers and monsters.</description></item><item><title>Frosthaven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frosthaven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frosthaven/</guid><description>Game Description Frosthaven is a digital adaptation of a board game that puts players at the head of a detachment of mercenaries in the northern settlement. This tactical role strategy uses step -by -step battles on a hexagonal map. You can go through the campaign missions alone or in an online cooperative with three other gamers. The action is unfolding on a border known by harsh conditions and dangerous inhabitants, constantly challenging the survival of the group.</description></item><item><title>Game of Grass</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/game-of-grass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/game-of-grass/</guid><description>Game Description Game of Grass begins with a call from a neighbor who offended the player’s lawn. The main task is to demonstrate superiority through the cultivation of the remarkable courtyard. The process includes methodical mowing of vegetation using a variety of tools. Gamers acquire upgrades to increase the efficiency of their equipment, which allows you to quickly clear the territory.
The goal is to achieve the status of the legend of haircuts of grass by methodically improving the site, and advance in this simulator is linearly and focused on tangible results.</description></item><item><title>Mashina</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashina/</guid><description>Game Description Mashina immerses the player in a solitary adventure, where under his control is a robot with a mission to restore his native world. The basis of this project is the methodical study of the subsoil to collect valuable materials necessary for the survival of the whole settlement. All fossils found are used to help the community of other mechanisms, contributing to the gradual revival of their destroyed house.</description></item><item><title>Prospector</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</guid><description>Game Description Prospector begins with arrival at someone else&amp;rsquo;s world, having only a set of tools at its disposal. The primary task is to collect the planet’s resources for the construction of the basis for the base. Players build structures, explore the environment, and then establish automated production lines. For construction, everything is used, from primitive materials to unknown alien substances found on the landscape.
Gradually, a simple avantopost turns into a complex object with an optimized working process.</description></item><item><title>Reflex Unit: Strike Ops</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reflex-unit-strike-ops/</guid><description>Game Description Reflex Unit: Strike Ops immerses in the future, destroyed by cataclysm and captured by powerful corporations. The player is headed by an elite detachment opposing the despotistical corporation Neotech, operating the remnants of civilization. The key gameplay consists in managing specialized equipment during various tactical operations. The tasks include daring rescue sorties, collecting key resources and direct attacks on enemy bases to undermine the power of the regime and struggle for freedom of the population.</description></item><item><title>Inkborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inkborn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inkborn/</guid><description>Game Description Inkborn represents a card combat system based on the consistent use of glyphs for a tactical effect. Gamers have cards according to special symbols, activating chain results during step -by -step clashes with otherworldly creatures. Such a gameplay is the basis for promotion. The scene is a world created from ink, folded paper and metal containing a hidden story for disclosure.
The narrative unfolds as the expeditions are completed and the tasks set.</description></item><item><title>Village Tale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/village-tale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/village-tale/</guid><description>Game Description Village Tale represents the construction simulator designed for continuous work on the user desktop. The gamer will have to build structures, create goods and engage in commerce to expand its village from the very foundation. The task is to open new industries and increase the number of community. The gameplay proceeds in real time, allowing the village to function even when you are busy with other matters. The activity of residents and the development of resources go continuously, creating a permanent world for management.</description></item><item><title>The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</guid><description>Game Description The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily is a step -by -step tactical game about the Duchess of Scarlet, faced with accusation of regicide. Accused of the murder of the emperor, she concludes an alliance with Lily, the captain of the aircraft, a stream. Together they declare the war of the empire, becoming the first military streamers on the continent. The conflict grows due to a clash of impulsiveness and cold pragmatism.</description></item><item><title>Slidemagi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slidemagi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slidemagi/</guid><description>Game Description Slidemagi is a duel between the two magicians on the 10x10 board, where units move by shifting the entire grid lines. In one move, the player performs one action: moves a row or applies a spell. This solution is central to the tactical pattern of battle. Following this, all controlled fighters on the field simultaneously attack in four main directions in the presence of goals.
This tactical game offers several modes for single and multiplayer competitions.</description></item><item><title>Monument Valley 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monument-valley-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monument-valley-3/</guid><description>Game Description In the Monument Valley 3, players will go on a new journey, leading a student of Nur through a world built from optical illusions and mobile architecture. The main goal is to comprehend the meaning of sacred light, moving along locations with changeable gravity. For advance, it is necessary to directly manipulate buildings, rotate entire levels and change the perspective, paving routes through impossible geometry.
Features of the surrealist adventure Nur:</description></item><item><title>The King Is Watching</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-king-is-watching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-king-is-watching/</guid><description>Game Description The King Is Watching is a unique combination of strategy, Roguelike and controls. In this Title, users take on the role of the ruler, whose presence affects the productivity of the kingdom. The central mechanics revolves around the strength of the gamer&amp;rsquo;s gaze, which dictates the effectiveness of various tasks, including resources, military training and much more.
At any moment in time, the ruler must choose what to focus on, balancing between agriculture, mining and protection from external threats.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Ascension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-ascension/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Ascension puts the player in the lord position with the task of creating his own possession in an empty plot of land. The initial stage includes a systematic collection of provisions and materials - basic elements for any settlement. These assets then go to the construction of the first buildings to create a stronghold in the world. Subsequently, the focus shifts the recruitment of military detachments that form an army to protect native lands and spread the influence of the outside.</description></item><item><title>DUST RADERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</guid><description>Game Description Dust Raiders puts the player in the role of the manager on the lawless, post -apocalyptic wasteland, where control over resources is the main task. The plot originates after the Sawblade attack, which led to the loss of the oil refinery, the death of the Viktor’s ally and the dissolution of the original team. Left without fuel and equipment, it is necessary to collect a functional machine from scrap metal to start recovery.</description></item><item><title>Fill up the Hole</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fill-up-the-hole/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fill-up-the-hole/</guid><description>Game Description Fill up the Hole puts the player in the role of the overseer of the anti -utopian settlement, built around the only economic activity: transformation of waste into profit. The population of the peons independently collects garbage for discharge into the central pit - this process generates resources for growth. The main task is to build and expand the village, as well as strategic placement of structures to increase the volume of garbage production and its subsequent disposal.</description></item><item><title>Forest Heroes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forest-heroes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forest-heroes/</guid><description>Game Description Forest Heroes combines Tower Defense elements with Roguelike Deckbuilding. The place of action is the Nokflufol, the forest that flourished under the auspices of the elves who own mushroom magic. However, the offended oak imposed a curse on the ground, distorting it. In the role of an elf-guardian, the player’s task is to rally the allies-living ones for rebuke. The main mission is to defend the operating base and clean the surrounding area from the influence of the curse in order to restore the area to its original state.</description></item><item><title>He is coming</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/he-is-coming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/he-is-coming/</guid><description>Game Description He is coming is a world where forgotten evil awakens. The king of demons is rebelled, carrying the promise of death with him. The users have to find powerful artifacts and weapons to resist this formidable enemy. In the afternoon you are exploring the kingdom, collecting resources and honing your skills, and at night you fight off its minions and prepare for the next monstrous test. The clock is constantly ticking, and each solution can mean the difference between survival and destruction.</description></item><item><title>The Necromincer's Tale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-necromancers-tale/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-necromancers-tale/</guid><description>Game Description The Necromincer&amp;rsquo;s Tale is a role -playing game in the setting of dark fantasy. The adventure is presented by a top-distance. It is a nobleman to manage a nobleman living in the world of an alternative of the 18th century. The tale of the necromancer is a mystical story full of political conspiracies, dark knowledge and thirst for revenge. Exploring surrounding, everything may not be at all the same as it seems initially.</description></item><item><title>The Wandering Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wandering-village/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-wandering-village/</guid><description>Game Description Once in The Wandering Village on an infected planet, people have no choice but to poison the back of a giant creature that can move in the process. The urban planning simulator is made in a post -apocalyptic setting and offers to lead a small society that saved, settling on the essence and gradually rebuild the new world.
Having moved to the virtual universe, the user observes as some toxic substances that appeared due to mysterious plants, quickly spread on the ground by giving out toxic disputes.</description></item><item><title>Demonic Mahjong</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demonic-mahjong/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demonic-mahjong/</guid><description>Game Description Demonic Mahjong races Majong bones with a horn structure. Players have to use chips from their hands to collect combinations that meet the established rules for counting glasses. However, the main task is beyond the scope of simple accumulation of points. The final goal is to build a hand and strategies that allow you to defeat the main boss, which turns every entry into preparation for the final battle.</description></item><item><title>Everstrife</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everstrife/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everstrife/</guid><description>Game Description Everstrife combines a battle with a look from the top and strategy for building a deck, placing players in locations filled with shells. Development depends on the system of skills based on Roguelike maps and elements. The central place in the gameplay is occupied by a synthesis mechanic that allows you to combine basic abilities. With 30 fundamental spells, gamers can generate more than 2000 of their options, so that each race offers new tactical solutions.</description></item><item><title>Stronghold Crusader: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Stronghold Crusader: Definitive Edition puts the player in the historical context of the Crusades, where the armies in the desert lands will have to be commanded. The gameplay is focused on building a castle economy, managing production and creating troops for siege battles. The plot campaigns illuminate conflicts from the point of view of Richard the Lion Heart and Saladin, the ruler of the Ayubid dynasty. Gamers have to withstand 20 and lords, each of which uses unique fortresses and tactical approaches for warfare.</description></item><item><title>Motemancer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motemancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motemancer/</guid><description>Game Description Motemancer is a game about automation in which players act on 6 intersecting elemental plans, procedurally generated and affordable in real time. The action takes place on a hexagonal network that serves as the basis for the construction of alchemical structures and the design of logistics systems for resource management. Gamers saturate the ingredients and combine various components, which directly changes the world around him.
The art of managing elements and matter in Motemacer:</description></item><item><title>Seacret 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seacret-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seacret-1/</guid><description>Game Description Seacret 1 is a sandbox in the 17th century Caribbean, where players are engaged in trade, battles or management. The economy here functions in real time, and the prices and volumes of goods in each individual city are constantly fluctuating. The journey begins with one modest tartan, but over time you can expand your flotilla to three vessels, including fast slices or more impressive galleons.
Strategic planning of commercial routes is becoming a key basis for the accumulation of wealth, vital for conducting operations in an extensive open world.</description></item><item><title>Aurora Defense</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aurora-defense/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aurora-defense/</guid><description>Game Description Aurora Defense combines Roguelike Deckbuilding with Tower-Defense gameplay with the construction of the base. The player’s task is to build defensive structures in the last stronghold of light, restraining the onslaught of the advancing darkness. The protection of the last goddess is the main goal of the mission throughout the passage. The tool for all actions is maps that allow you to place new buildings, modernize existing buildings and use spells.</description></item><item><title>Crisis in the Kremlin: The Cold War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crisis-in-the-kremlin-the-cold-war/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crisis-in-the-kremlin-the-cold-war/</guid><description>Game Description Crisis in the Kremlin: The Cold War is a political strategic simulation that has put you at the head of the Soviet Union in its last decade. The project demonstrates a country encountered with pressure from the internal fractions and external forces requiring changes. As the head of state, you lead the economy, external relations and determine the internal course of the Union. The gameplay includes interaction with other nations, the use of diplomatic channels, or the outbreak of proxy conflicts to expand influence.</description></item><item><title>OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/our-war-firepower-suppression/</guid><description>Game Description OUR WAR: FirePower Suppression is a flight shooter in which players use continuous fire to neutralize enemy forces. The story of the Title is submitted after 30 plot chapters, describing the war between the human faction and the essence of the fat bird from the parallel world. Combat operations take place on various three -dimensional locations, each with a unique relief that affects the tactical approach to clashes.</description></item><item><title>Power The Future</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/power-the-future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/power-the-future/</guid><description>Game Description Power The Future throws the player under the control of one of 7 nations, including the USA, Germany and China. The game is developing step by step from 2025 to 2038, where the main task is to provide the state’s energy needs. Players achieve this, developing technologies and creating a power grid that extends through national and international territories. This system requires the provision of consumption units located in its own and surrounding territories.</description></item><item><title>Wildrise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wildrise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wildrise/</guid><description>Game Description Wildrise represents the world where concrete has captured natural soil, leaving the silent space. A forest keeper named Floof is awakening from a dream that lasted for centuries and sees this altered landscape. The main task of the player is to help this keeper systematically revive nature, destroying artificial coatings. This is achieved through step -by -step mechanics of arranging and combining mushrooms, flowers and animals on the field, while each combination helps to restore land and fauna.</description></item><item><title>EVERY DAY WE FIGHT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/every-day-we-fight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/every-day-we-fight/</guid><description>Game Description EVERY DAY WE FIGHT places a group of resistance fighters in a temporary anomaly during an alien invasion. The world and its population were frozen in one moment, and a small detachment remains active, falling into a cycle, where death is not the end. Each time the team dies, time is unwinded back, but the acquired skills and knowledge are preserved with every new round. Players have to lead these people in urban locations in real time, turning into a step -by -step regime for tactical skirmishes with aliens forces.</description></item><item><title>Chosen War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chosen-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chosen-war/</guid><description>Game Description Chosen War puts the player in the role of the chosen one who is instructed to gather and novels the army in the archipelago. It is necessary to move around the fogs covered in fog and enter into battle with enemy forces using the tactical placement of detachments. Each adventure is built around the study of the world and provisions. The ultimate goal is a collision with the supreme priest on the final location.</description></item><item><title>Frog Jump</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</guid><description>Game Description Frog Jump puts players under the control of amphibians with the aim of vertical climbing through the three -dimensional world. They have to move according to a complex design, using jumps and climbing to go from one site to another. The entire level is designed around this movement up, representing a continuous navigation task. The first princess’s kiss receives a victory that reached the top.
This platformer can be held alone or in a multi -user competition for 8 competitors over the network.</description></item><item><title>Click and Conquer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</guid><description>Game Description Click and Conquer represents a resource management system through military operations. The main gameplay is based on the discharge of bombs on the grid to detect disguised enemy detachments. Each opened unit brings currency that serves as a central resource for further development. The received funds are distributed to increase passive income and an increase in the destructive force of each ammunition. The cycle of expenses and savings determines the promotion of the player at affordable stages.</description></item><item><title>Wordatro!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wordatro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wordatro/</guid><description>Game Description Wordatro! Combines the compilation of words with step -by -step mechanics Roguelite. The players are given a set of letters, each of which has point value, and they form expressions from them to achieve a target. The creation of words with a high cost activates the combo-abdominal, increasing points for subsequent moves. The strategic selection of lexemes and the use of symbols are of key importance for the completion of each stage.</description></item><item><title>BellFortis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</guid><description>Game Description In BellFortis, the action takes place in the early Middle Ages, where users seek to expand their kingdoms and influence the course of history. Title combines step -by -step strategic planning and real -time battles, which gives you the opportunity to control the army and make decisions that affect the world. Would you like to build a strong empire with the help of diplomacy or strength - the choice is yours.</description></item><item><title>Merge Maestro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</guid><description>Game Description Merge Maestro suggests placing an emoji chip on a mesh field. These elements are combined with others of the same type to create stronger and more high -level units. The main task is to overcome the advancing waves of opponents using these improved tokens. After each round, Gamer chooses a new element for its set, expanding tactical opportunities for future clashes. Such a cycle of placement and fusion forms a key game process that requires step -by -step solutions to clean the field and survival.</description></item><item><title>Rugby League Team Manager 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</guid><description>Game Description Rugby League Team Manager 4 puts you at the head of the regional club. The circle of your tasks is covered by financial management, negotiations with sponsors and the selection of the state of assistants, mentors and medical staff. You have to improve infrastructure, including the stadium, gym and training fields. This project covers 226 teams from the Northern and Southern Hems, and over 7,000 adult players are available for choice.</description></item><item><title>Thrive: Heavy Lies the Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Thrive: Heavy Lies The Crown is an exciting medieval fantasy urban planning strategy that will check your leadership qualities and make you make a difficult choice to ensure the survival and prosperity of your kingdom. In this game, the fate of your people largely depends on the decisions you have taken, and the path you have chosen - favor or tyranny - will determine your heritage. The will is your weapon, you must build and strengthen your city, form the land and develop your kingdom with the help of a deep technological tree.</description></item><item><title>Loot of Baal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/loot-of-baal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/loot-of-baal/</guid><description>Game Description Loot of Baal works from the side panel of the screen, allowing you to play at the same time with other computer tasks. Players collect and send a detachment of mercenaries for battles with demons and obtaining treasures on randomly generated combat locations. The project offers hundreds of fighters, each with unique skills, and a collection of more than 1000 different things for the search. This concept of gameplay facilitates the promotion, because the key adventure occurs in a separate area of the display and does not require constant attention.</description></item><item><title>Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</guid><description>Game Description Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil! - This is an exciting strategy in real time, in which you will go to study the distant world called Grimstar, where you will find a new type of natural energy resources. But not everything is so rosy and sunny - because of your brother’s sudden death, you have to fulfill his contract with the corporation for which he worked, and you must take his place on an alien planet.</description></item><item><title>IDLE WATERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</guid><description>Game Description IDLE WATERS is a game in the IDLE-Rybank genre that works from the window at the bottom of the screen and is designed to simultaneously work with other computer operations. The game window has flexibility: it can be scale, change the layout, change the size and move to any part of the desktop or completely hide. This system allows the simulator to function without requiring constant attention from the gamer.</description></item><item><title>Covenant of Solitude</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</guid><description>Game Description Covenant of Solitude introduces the story of a young man named Fort, who secretly owns the gift to command monsters in a secluded settlement of the leaves. The carriers of such a force are called ginns - their fate is full of persecution, fear and exploitation from others. The familiar way of life of the hero breaks off when the war breaks into his house, flooding the streets with blood and forcing the fort to accept his essence.</description></item><item><title>Rise of Industry 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-industry-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-industry-2/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of Industry 2 is a setting in which production magnates form the economy, factories produce goods at a frantic speed, and transactions are concluded according to stationary phones with a rotating dial. Success depends on smart investments, effective production and happiness of the right people. Each solution has weight, whether it is the conclusion of profitable trading transactions or the choice of the industry in which it should be dominated.</description></item><item><title>VOID War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</guid><description>Game Description Void War puts a player at the head of an ancient starship, sending him on a journey to the heart of a dying empire. This ship is described as a powerful and formidable gun filled with secret technologies. The tasks include the reflection of the attacks of crazy cultists, cowardly cosmopirates and xenophobic imperial soldiers. The detection of powerful artifacts allows you to turn a starship into a frightening combat vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Knights: Flashpoint</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyber-knights-flashpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cyber-knights-flashpoint/</guid><description>Game Description Cyber Knights: Flashpoint is an anti -utopic world in which a modern cyberpunk and a gloomy atmosphere of despair and disobey have intertwined. Since the colonization of the solar system on Earth and in other places, complete anarchy began with illegal trade and hired killers. The player will be in the very center of this new world, exploring his shadow side.
Actions take place in 2223 as a result of the environmental disaster and negligence of mankind, the ozone ball was completely destroyed and people were forced to create colonies on more distant planets, the benefit of technology allow.</description></item><item><title>Neuroshima Hex</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuroshima-hex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuroshima-hex/</guid><description>Game Description Neuroshima Hex is a post -apocalyptic tactical competition adapted from the board game system. The course of events is built on strategic solutions on the hexagonal field. Opponents use various detachments, technologies and their special skills for the implementation of military plans. Mechanics implies the arrangement of chips and determine the moment of their action.
In Neuroshima Hex, players fall into the world, surviving the decline of nature, where there is a struggle for resources.</description></item><item><title>Ricave</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ricave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ricave/</guid><description>Game Description Ricave sends a player to an escape from a changeable dungeon, where the movement occurs step by step around the cells. The battles suggest the use of the environment: you can encounter opponents in poisonous water or lure them to barrels with explosives. The state of the character monitors specific ailments, including diseases, bleeding and fractures. The damage here is local: the loss of the leg slows down, the eye injury leads to blindness, and the lack of hands limits the interaction with objects for all creatures.</description></item><item><title>Voidsayer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voidsayer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voidsayer/</guid><description>Game Description Voidsayer takes users to the world, captured by the abyss - all -consuming power, which leaves nothing behind. As one of the few survivors, you must accept this gloomy challenge, armed with a team of monsters. However, unlike others, you can repulse not with simple weapons, but taming and developing creatures. These are not just pets - they will become an integral part of your survival. However, there is one catch.</description></item><item><title>Fuga: Melodies of Steel 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</guid><description>Game Description fuga: Melodies of Steel 3 unfolds the story of desperate efforts. The inexplicable disappearance of Malta forces the group of children to head to the forbidden cave, where they are leaded by a mysterious voice to Taranis - a powerful armored vehicle, which was considered lost. The determination to find Malta returns them aboard this combat vehicle, starting a direct attack on the central regions of the Berman Empire.</description></item><item><title>As We Descend</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</guid><description>Game Description AS We Descend combines Roguelike debiting with strategic gameplay. Gamers command forces in card battles against enemies in the post -apocalyptic city. The fate of mankind is determined by the tactical decisions made on the battlefield and in the political structure of the city. The project includes the creation and development of detachments using the found technologies. Each group has a special set of cards that can be expanded and modified.</description></item><item><title>ODDSPARKS: An Automation Adventure</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oddsparks-an-automation-adventure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oddsparks-an-automation-adventure/</guid><description>Game Description ODDSPARKS: An Automation Adventure combines the elements of automation and real -time strategy, focusing on both veterans and beginners in the automation genre. Players explore the strange fantasy world, solve ancient secrets, build automated workshops and go to adventure with their charming sparks. The main gameplay rotates around the design and automation of workshops.
Forget about conveyor ribbons - you have to control the movement of sparks in order to optimize the work of your creations.</description></item><item><title>SOL CESTO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sol-cesto/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sol-cesto/</guid><description>Game Description SOL CESTO is a swift route that encounter a strategy and accident. Gamers fall into the world shrouded in secrets, and seek to get to the depths of the dungeon in search of a long -lost sun. The dungeon is generated randomly, which means that there are no two identical travels. Each floor is divided into four rooms, and you have to decide which one to enter, never knowing what awaits the door.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>9 kings</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</guid><description>Game Description 9 Kings throws users into the very heart of the medieval kingdom, where the strategy, tactics and resource management dictates the need for survival. This urban planning Roguelike combines a lot of a mechanic, offering unpredictable experience with each launch. The expansion of the kingdom requires careful planning, because the power of the empire depends on each decision. Using a deck of various cards, rulers form their possessions, adapting to unexpected challenges.</description></item><item><title>Coin Push RPG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coin-push-rpg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coin-push-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Coin Push RPG combines the mechanics of an arcade machine with elements of pumping characters. In the center of the process is a full-fledged simulator of a classic coin-pusher, where actions directly affect resources. Good luck drums, bonus towers and jackpotes form the rhythm of sessions and provide an influx of coins. It is these coins that launch the actions of fighters subordinates to the player.
In the Coin Push RPG project, characters do not enter the battle for free.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Survive the Fall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survive-the-fall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survive-the-fall/</guid><description>Game Description The disaster in Survive The Fall occurred in 2023, when a huge asteroid crashed into the ground. Most of the population died, and those who were in distant places in the world survived. The player moves to the post -apocalyptic environment, where it is necessary to engage in the construction of settlements, using tactical and strategic elements. An extensive and open world includes many good lands, forests or destroyed cities.</description></item><item><title>Cauldron</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</guid><description>Game Description Cauldron is a role project with an emphasis on a system of improvement and the implementation of mini-stories. In the role of NIX, a character who finds himself in a world immersed in darkness will have to explore the environment and look for allies. The structure implies the cycle: the commission of actions leads to strengthening the party, which opens the way to the study of new areas and obtaining content.</description></item><item><title>Monster Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Battles is a tactical auto-batler with equipment control. In this project, participants collect, unite and strategically place a group of creatures for upcoming fights. These creatures are purchased in a special store and then are placed on a certain battlefield before the start of an automatic fight. An effective selection and location of a variety of combat units forms the basis of the game cycle.
In Monster Battles, building a successful detachment requires thoroughly accounting for the features and belonging of the collected creatures.</description></item><item><title>Blacksmith Master</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</guid><description>Game Description Blacksmith Master is an exciting simulator in which you can control your own blacksmiths, starting with mining and precious stones to the design and sale of finished products. Your task will be tortured everything - from weapons and armor to instruments and kitchen utensils - to earn on your craft and become a real master of blacksmithing.
Here you can lead your own medieval blacksmith and you will control the entire process: the extraction of resources, their processing and production and sale of finished products.</description></item><item><title>House of Legacy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/house-of-legacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/house-of-legacy/</guid><description>Game Description House of Legacy starts at the moment when the rebels overcome the city defense, which forces the player to lead the remaining relatives in wanderings, promising many difficulties. They find a shelter in the county center, the last uninhabited corner, which is not affected by the embarrassment, where the foundations of the new dynasty are laid. This journey becomes a starting point for the formation of a weighty dynastic influence that can resist the world transformed by straightforwardness.</description></item><item><title>Ascension</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ascension/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ascension/</guid><description>Game Description Ascension invites the gamer to try on the role of a young follower, the last chance for a community that has been in a distress. Once on the other side of the portal, this character takes on the reins of government. The paramount goal is the revival of the order, honing alchemical skills and moving along the path to the highest form of being; This path is associated with the need for a competent disposal of stocks and balanced tactical moves.</description></item><item><title>Dice with Death</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-with-death/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-with-death/</guid><description>Game Description Dice with Death provides a script where the protagonist has already died. Instead of an immediate transition to another world, the essence known as death offers a competition. This competition forms the basis of activity presented in the Roguelike format with cube collection mechanics. The gameplay requires a direct confrontation with death in step -by -step strategic meetings. The goal lies in successful rivalry with this mythical opponent through thoughtful bones of bones.</description></item><item><title>Tower Dominion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-dominion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-dominion/</guid><description>Game Description Tower Dominion proposes to combine the construction of the landscape with the protection of the citadel from alien forces as part of Roguelike strategy. The commander (this gamer) must protect the territory from constant raids of arthronids. The gameplay implies the creation of fortifications and control over the battlefield itself during skirmishes. Each confrontation poses new tasks due to procedural generation that affects the arising difficulties. Success depends on changes in the protective orders and competent use of available funds against the advancing enemy detachments.</description></item><item><title>Yes, Your Grace 2: Snowfall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yes-your-grace-2-snowfall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yes-your-grace-2-snowfall/</guid><description>Game Description Yes, Your Grace 2: Snowfall puts players in the role of the monarch of the crumbling kingdom. They have to manage this cinematic game in the management of possessions. The key task is to find the balance between the needs of the subjects and the resources of the state. Well -being or collapse depends on the decisions made.
The throne room becomes a place for a series of petitioners who bring trouble, help or entertainment in the world of Slavic folklore.</description></item><item><title>Drop Duchy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drop-duchy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drop-duchy/</guid><description>Game Description Drop Duchy combines the mechanics of geometric puzzles with the construction of the territory and the management of resources. Gamers use falling figures not only to clean the lines, but also for the phased construction of possessions. The task is to collect materials and the formation of troops to confront enemy armies, while each installed block contributes to the development of the kingdom on the path to the triumph.</description></item><item><title>Knights of the Crusades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</guid><description>Game Description Knights of the Crusades sends a player during the first crusades, where a lone knight will come to begin. It is ahead to go to the foundation and management of the holy order, choosing the Templars or creating their own fraction. The process combines real -time elements with the construction of settlements and management within the sandbox. You have to solve problems related to war, religious influence, diplomacy and strategic planning.</description></item><item><title>Ratopia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratopia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ratopia/</guid><description>Game Description Ratopia is an original strategy that challenges genres thanks to a unique combination of survival, sandbox and a city construction simulator. Get ready to plunge into a huge and exciting world that will captivate you with its endless possibilities. Here you have to create your ideal city and manage it, but be careful, because every resident has its own characteristics and wealth that you must take into account. No one said that it would be easy, but with the right selection of jobs and services, you can make your residents happy, and your economy is prosperous.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>Age of Reforming: The Frelands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</guid><description>Game Description Age of reforging: The Frelands is a cruel world of the Middle Ages in an alternative world where magic exists, and the gods are quite real and if they are enough to pray and make generous gifts, they can even bless the asking person. There reigns tyranny and lawlessness, and survival is being built in trade. The more successful the seller, the easier he lives, the rest was terribly unlucky.</description></item><item><title>Badlands Crew</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/badlands-crew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/badlands-crew/</guid><description>Game Description Badlands Crew transfers to the gamer control over a combat vehicle in the world of lawlessness that arose after a global catastrophe. Key tasks include the construction of transport, its modification and use against hostile groups for the search and salvation of the survivors. You collect your mobile fortress from individual components, selecting elements such as flamethrowers, sniper turrets, rate of fire machine guns, observation tower and medical points.</description></item><item><title>Survivalist: Invisible Strain</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</guid><description>Game Description Survivalist: Invisible Strain - continuation of the game Survivalist. Events take place near Vancouver in Canada. The zombivirus epidemic has been going on for 10 years. People managed to erect settlements, well -guarded from revived dead. However, the defense of the shelters fell for unknown reasons. The survivors go to the hill, hoping to build new outposts.
In the game, the survivor: an invisible strain can create your own community.</description></item><item><title>SpellroGue</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spellrogue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spellrogue/</guid><description>Game Description SpellroGue immerses players in a world captured by corrupted hollowers. You pick up weapons, but not blades and bows, but powerful spells, fed by unpredictable mana cubes. In this step -by -step game, based on the construction of the decks, spells are pronouncing the manipulation of these cubes. The desired combination will fall out, and you will release fire balls, earthen walls or ark explosions. But the bones are unstable.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Mogul 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Mogul 4 — это текстовый бизнес-симулятор, ставящий человека во главе киностудии. Система позволяет создавать кинофильмы и мини-сериалы на основе библиотеки из более чем 14 000 исходных материалов или собственных идей. Ready -made paintings can be planned for global film distribution or for distribution through streaming service. The process includes the formation of accurate budgets, the conclusion of agreements on rental in 19 foreign territories and the management of advertising expenses.</description></item><item><title>Sunderfolk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunderfolk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunderfolk/</guid><description>Game Description Sunderfolk is a cooperative role -playing adventure designed for joint passage on one screen. This tactical adventure is designed for a team of up to 4 people traveling together around the Sunderlands world. Title uses personal gadgets as the main interface for gamer commands and information management, instead of familiar controllers. A special program provides this connection by collecting all functions on the display of each smartphone. The company is going to overcome trials in the general virtual world.</description></item><item><title>Darkwater</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkwater/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkwater/</guid><description>Game Description Darkwater gives gamers to command a submarine, which ended up in an ice trap on a foreign planet. This is a cooperative horror, designed to work from 1 to 4 people. Survival implies navigation in a hostile environment, clashes with enemy courts and underwater life forms, as well as an active search for resources necessary for further work of submarine. Success depends on the implementation of the necessary actions for existence in underland conditions.</description></item><item><title>Escape the Mad Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Escape the Mad Empire is a Roguelike Dungeon Crawler, promising a mixture of tactical battles and base control. Players collect a detachment of heroes whose survival depends on strategy and resourcefulness. The combat system requires an attentive approach. Each move, each action has weight. Using the area, shelters and objects becomes the second nature, when users move around the battlefield with high rates. The Title is not amenable to simple classification, combining the elements of Roguelike, RPG and Base-Building into unique experience.</description></item><item><title>Farm Manager World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-world/</guid><description>Game Description Farm Manager World puts you in the place of the world agricultural magnate. Build your farm from scratch in a variety of corners of Europe, Central America, and soon Asia. Grow a variety of exotic crops, each of which has special needs for the soil. Study and use fertilizers to improve soil quality and increase productivity. Use crop rotation to achieve optimal results.
Grow livestock from birth or buy it directly.</description></item><item><title>It</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/its-on-the-mouse/</guid><description>Game Description IT&amp;rsquo;s on the Mouse combines a cafe management with a 3D platformer, providing players with control over the main characters of Holly. Being a tiny maid, she is forced to use a special navigation method in the working environment due to her growth. The gamer has to jump and run around the tables and racks to get to customers and submit orders to them. This movement system is central mechanics for receiving applications and delivery of the desired dishes.</description></item><item><title>Synergy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</guid><description>Game Description synergy dedicated to survival on a hostile planet. In this urban planning strategy, players have to develop their city, face natural cataclysms and make the right decisions that will certainly have consequences. Explore this constantly changing world, preserving the happiness of the townspeople in extreme weather conditions.
Gamers will control the weather, seasons, extreme conditions and natural disasters. The main goal is to build a city where residents will be happy and satisfied, respecting the natural needs of the inhabitants and living in harmony with the local fauna and flora.</description></item><item><title>Milord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/milord/</guid><description>Game Description Milord is a role -playing game about the management of medieval ownership, combined with elements of urban development. You take under direct control of the Earth, where your specific instructions determine the fate of the inhabitants and general prosperity. Preservation of reserves is a constant factor affecting all aspects of management and requiring careful planning. Through a petition system, subjects directly turn to the ruler for help, intervention or solving various local issues.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Animal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-animal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-animal/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Animal is not an ordinary strategic game. Forget about the conquest of empires or the construction of huge cities. Here you are in the roaring twenties - the time when the silent movie gave way to the &amp;ldquo;talkers&amp;rdquo;, and the film studios tried to keep up. You are in the director’s chair, but not for the camera. This time you are a studio boss, solving all issues, starting from who will play in the film, and ending when the last blockbuster is released.</description></item><item><title>Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</guid><description>Game Description Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days transfer the player to Walton City, Texas, 1980 sample, covered by a zombie epidemic. The gamer has to lead a detachment of surviving through the dying metropolis. The key task of the gameplay is to move the wards between temporary shelters, taking care of their condition. It is necessary to find provisions, make objects and repulse constant danger from the dead who filled the streets.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/burden-of-command/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/burden-of-command/</guid><description>Game Description Burden of Command gives players a completely different idea of what projects can be in the theme of World War II. The local scale is considered here, and the focus is a small group of fighters. The gamer is given the opportunity to become the commander of this group, making important decisions in key situations. The guys have to visit hot spots around the world, from Western Europe and ending with Morocco, where the remnants of enemy forces were still based at that moment.</description></item><item><title>Commandos: Origins</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/commandos-origins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/commandos-origins/</guid><description>Game Description Commandos: Origins depicts the origin of a specialized military group of the Second World War. This part of the series returns gamers to the origins of tactics in real time. The narrative covers the period when Jack O’Hara, Green Beres, met his five comrades, forming a detachment, which was entrusted with tasks that were considered too dangerous for ordinary forces.
Players have to lead this detachment in the Title Commandos: Origins, coordinating the actions of the green beret, sapper, sniper, driver, marine and spy.</description></item><item><title>Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</guid><description>Game Description Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers calls the gamarines into a world filled with more than 180 creatures who need to collect, fight and develop. The Title combines the elements of autoboeviks, rogeliks and card battles, allowing users to develop unique strategies. The purpose of the game is to assemble the KDOMON team, each of which has various abilities and types in order to pass more and more difficult tests. As you pass, you will encounter powerful bosses and open rare monsters with special abilities.</description></item><item><title>Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</guid><description>Game Description Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder can be attributed to the simulators of the colony and real -time strategies. There are also survival elements in the indie project. He has high reigree due to the random generation of cards. The gamer here is offered to establish a settlement and help it develop to a full -fledged city. At the same time, it is necessary to monitor the needs and mood of the townspeople.</description></item><item><title>Pocket City 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket City 2 makes it possible for players to build cities, and then study their first -person creations. The process starts from the laying of roads, the markings of sections for residential, commercial or industrial needs and the construction of the necessary objects on the map. Control over the economy implies monitoring of stocks, profit and a thoughtful placement of special structures, access to which opens as they move.</description></item><item><title>Kaiserpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Kaiserpunk throws you headlong into an alternative XX century, instructing to build an empire from scratch. This is not Grandfather&amp;rsquo;s Urban planner - Title offers a grandiose strategy, demanding from you to win a vast card, while preserving the residents happy, and the factory - working. Does it sound like a high task? This is true. Forget that you can just put at home and finish it on this.</description></item><item><title>Card Survival: Fantasy Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Card Survival: Fantasy Forest is a survival simulator that immerses in the very heart of the ancient forest. Title takes users to a world where nature is not only living, but also has its own mind. Here, gamers build a house, overcome daily difficulties and interact with a rich ecosystem full of wild animals, magical creatures and unpredictable forces. Every day brings new difficulties associated with survival: from hunger and health management to solving problems with the weather and seasons.</description></item><item><title>FACEMINER</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/faceminer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/faceminer/</guid><description>Game Description FaceMiner offers a deep immersion in the world of collecting biometric data. Here gamers fall into the chaotic world before the beginning of the new millennium, where the main task is to collect and classifying data on faces on a mass scale. As a user, you start small, gradually building an empire from biometric data. On this path, you have to expand the scale: to update software, develop infrastructure and maximize profits, overcoming the sea of ​​corporate problems.</description></item><item><title>Die in the dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/die-in-the-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/die-in-the-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Die in the Dungeon throws another set of cubes in the Roguelike genre. Forget about the meticulously compiled deck of cards. Instead, you collect your arsenal from a set of cubes, each of which indicates the action: attack enemies, treat wounds or control yourself a throw of fate. Each meeting becomes a gambling game, an exciting test of luck, where one throw can turn the course of the battle.</description></item><item><title>Dead Dragons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Dragons launches history 100 years after the victory of people over the dragons - the events that allegedly brought the world. Now rumors about the return of these creatures encourage the protagonist to investigate the case of a mysterious girl associated with the dragon race. This task develops into a conflict that decides the fate of the whole world and raises the main question of the survival of one of the species in the upcoming confrontation.</description></item><item><title>Dawnfolk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</guid><description>Game Description In Dawnfolk, the action of which takes place in a world covered by darkness. As a ruler of the kingdom lost to the shadows, you must restore and protect your people. With the help of a mystical creature, Luer, you must navigate in the darkness and work on the restoration of light on Earth. In the center - research, resource management and decision -making when you restore your kingdom from scratch.</description></item><item><title>Astronomics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</guid><description>Game Description In Astronomics, gamers are sent to study the space and the production of asteroids. You have to move through randomly generated asteroids, extract resources and manage a developing enterprise. At first, the whole thing is assembling materials on asteroids flying past, but as it moves forward, automation becomes a key factor. With workers and command bots, at your disposal, the tasks for which the clock used to go, can be completed much faster.</description></item><item><title>Novus orbis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/novus-orbis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/novus-orbis/</guid><description>Game Description Novus orbis is a Roguelike designer of decks, inviting gamers to the world, where selected cards and how you play them determine your path. The essence is to master the combo. Each card has its value, and their effect depends on how you arrange them - play the cards in the correct order to maximize their strength, or mix them to get a potentially different result. This emphasis on the strategy gives Tita depth, forcing you to be on the alert while you are guided in complex mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Last outpost</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-outpost/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/last-outpost/</guid><description>Game Description Last Outpost is a strategy with elements of basic construction, the action of which takes place in the post -apocalyptic world, teeming with zombies. Gamers have to build and strengthen their outpost in order to survive in chaos conditions. As the days stretch, the threat poses not only the undead - the other survivors, the same desperate, will try to capture what you built. Resource management, modernization of defensive structures and ensuring the safety of outpost require constant attention.</description></item><item><title>Stray Path</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray-path/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stray-path/</guid><description>Game Description Stray Path combines Freecell mechanics and strategic adventure gameplay. Gamers begin with the choice of one of several characters and plunge into the world, which is different each time. The Title offers a random set of enemies, tests and awards, all this is regulated by the cards that you pull. Each card is a new decision, whether it is a battle, avoiding a meeting or choosing equipment. The choice you make affects the outcome of your trip.</description></item><item><title>Blood Bar Tycoon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blood-bar-tycoon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blood-bar-tycoon/</guid><description>Game Description In Blood Bar Tycoon, users are in the place of the manager of the Vampire Bar. The goal is to create and manage a series of blood bars so that people and vampire customers are satisfied. Along the way, gamers build blood factories, collect blood and encounter problems such as hunters and vampire-competing. Due to the possibility of micro -study or assignment automation, users can accurately configure the work to develop their dark empire.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</guid><description>Game Description The urban planning simulator-Foundation-will allow you to plunge in the medieval era, build a whole settlement, make people happy at the expense of unique structures, as well as understand the history of the construction of houses and churches, on which there was a lot of emphasis due to constant rivalry of religious directions.
We will build houses and other structures with smart brushes. They will allow us not to exceed authority and put only those buildings that will meet environmental norms and criteria.</description></item><item><title>Heart of the Machine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</guid><description>Game Description Heart of the Machine outwardly resembles a town -planning Taikun. But in fact, the project is something like a god of God with elements of tactics and strategy in real time. Only here the Juzer is assigned the role of not a divine being, which owns magic, but artificial intelligence. This video game has a science fiction setting. Its action takes place in a distant and gloomy future in the territory of the metropolis-colonies.</description></item><item><title>Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/orcs-must-die-deathtrap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/orcs-must-die-deathtrap/</guid><description>Game Description Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap is a third -person action player and trap protection, which used the main elements of its predecessors and added several new opportunities designed to diversify the gameplay. The action takes place in the same universe as in the previous parts of Orcs Must Die!, And gamers will have to join chaotic battles with the waves of orcs and other monstrous creatures, using all kinds of weapons, traps and strategic solutions.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</guid><description>Game Description Space Engineers 2 returns to the world of space development with updated experience. In this continuation, you will have a new adventure in the Almagest system, where engineering tasks and spaces of space are combined in the most unexpected way. This is a sandbox with an open world in which you can build from scratch - or, rather, from stars - from starships to entire space stations. The goal is simple: to raise your creative potential to a new height, while managing the difficulties of survival in the cold, inexorable spaces of space.</description></item><item><title>Learning Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</guid><description>Game Description learning factory - a simulator that is designed to create an automated process of processes and, most importantly, understand one simple truth: what do cats want? The gameplay allows you to head the Kotovod factory. It was once closed, but now it has been possible to renew the process and create your own cat store. Learning factory gameplay largely gives an idea of ​​how machine learning works.
Your factory is analyzing a huge database, trying to study the behavior of pets.</description></item><item><title>Those Who Rule</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/those-who-rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/those-who-rule/</guid><description>Game Description In Those Who Rule, users find themselves in the place of recruits who fell into a whirlwind of deception and war. Title begins with the team of characters that should be guided in a complex world where decisions have weight, and unions change from the wind. Users gain allies, each of which has special abilities and personal history, and spend them through more and more complex battles. The main goal is to reveal the true forces standing behind the current conflict, while trying to be one step ahead of enemies and changing loyalty.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Harvest Hills</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/harvest-hills/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/harvest-hills/</guid><description>Game Description Harvest Hills immerses the player in plant cultivation and animal care in order to obtain agricultural products. The initial actions allow you to create products such as eggs, milk, honey and wool. The sale of these products in the local market provides income to modernize the economy and introduce automation systems. According to the plot, the protagonist leaves the city bustle for the founding of an agrarian enterprise, gradually turning the empty plot of land into a flourishing ranch.</description></item><item><title>Builders of Egypt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/builders-of-egypt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/builders-of-egypt/</guid><description>Game Description Builders of Egypt is a urban planning simulator in which the player acts as a manager of a great country located in the Nile River Valley. The huge rate is made on the economic development of the state, for this a large number of mechanics have been added, complicating the process of state development. The gamer will see the history of the origin of the Egyptian state in the proto -the -stage period, the golden age, ending with the death of Cleopatra Seventh.</description></item><item><title>Deathless. Tales of Old Rus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deathless-tales-of-old-rus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deathless-tales-of-old-rus/</guid><description>Game Description Deathless. Tales of Old Rus immerses gamers in a role -playing game with a deck created against the backdrop of Slavic myths and legends. Explore the vivid world of the Belosweres along with the legendary heroes and terrible creatures from children&amp;rsquo;s fairy tales at night. Currently, you can take on the role of brave barbarian beautiful, and soon wise Vasilisa will join you. Together you will withstand the growing bestiaria from more than 40 monsters and 8 bosses.</description></item><item><title>Defensurvivor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/defensurvivor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/defensurvivor/</guid><description>Game Description Defensurvivor puts a player at the head of the protection of asylum in the world captured by zombies. The main goal is to hold out for 15 minutes against the continuous waves of attackers, managing defense and staff. Gamers erect and modernize the walls through the construction menu, creating barriers to the direction of movement of the approaching horde. Success requires adaptation to the fighters accidentally issued for each session.</description></item><item><title>Fernageddon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fernageddon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fernageddon/</guid><description>Game Description Fernageddon begins the global burning campaign, during which the player acts as a champion of the great god of fire. The main task is to incinerate the world in accordance with the will of the deity about complete destruction. A novice novice goes on this journey, accumulating skills, studying spells and finding followers to help in total annihilation. Successful conquests bring the favor of a capricious idol, opening access to increasing power and legendary weapons.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of QUD-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Space Architect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</guid><description>Game Description Space Architect is a simulator where gamers have to become in place of the manager of the space station. The main goal is to build, maintain and expand the space station, simultaneously coping with the difficulties of resource management and interstellar trade. In the beginning, users are faced with a serious financial burden - a huge debt to a powerful megarporace, which forces them to make complex decisions on how to get income and stay afloat in endless cosmic voids.</description></item><item><title>Industry Giant 4.0</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/industry-giant-40/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/industry-giant-40/</guid><description>Game Description Industry Giant 4.0 immerses gamers in the landscape determined by industrial management and strategy. Since the 1950s, users are moving through the fourth industrial revolution, where digitalization and interconnected chains of creating cost play the most important role. The goal is to create and manage the industrial empire. This includes not only the production of goods, but also the creation of complex transport networks and monitoring financial transactions.</description></item><item><title>Zephon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in Zephon have to take control of the remnants of mankind in order to survive on the territory of the Earth. On the planet, there are few areas that are not suitable for life, and most of the cities were destroyed. In wild territories are mutating creatures that they gather in small groups and begin to hunt for surviving people. Alien robots with damaged systems roam on the surface, and the aliens themselves are hidden and try to secure survival.</description></item><item><title>One Socket</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-socket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/one-socket/</guid><description>Game Description One Socket puts the player before the need to charge the generator to power vital devices, which is complicated by the presence of only one working outlet. This critical restriction makes us make constant strategic decisions about which equipment to use, while the monster is hiding in the surrounding darkness. To get out of imprisonment, you need to dispose of meager resources, solve the secrets of the location and survive a constant threat.</description></item><item><title>Elin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elin/</guid><description>Game Description Elin is a two -dimensional role morned in which you can completely immerse yourself in an exciting world, where each solution matters. Choose your hero and go on a dangerous trip to Ylva’s lands, exploring mysterious places, meeting unique characters and fighting various dangers. You will find unforgettable adventures, where you will create your own story, influence the world and leave your mark on Ylva Earth. You have to fight for survival, find and create resources, build houses and manage your city.</description></item><item><title>Widget Inc.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/widget-inc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/widget-inc/</guid><description>Game Description Widget Inc. - This is a hybrid of the designer of factories and an incremental clicker, who invites users to the kingdom of crafts and production. Starting with basic resources, people go on a trip to master various craft processes. Target? Build a huge factory capable of producing advanced technologies, known as widgets. These widgets serve as a key element of the revival of civilization after the apocalypse. Users perform many tasks, each of which helps to build an empire extending to the stars.</description></item><item><title>The Dead Await</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</guid><description>Game Description The Dead Await immerses users in gloomy adventures, where it is necessary to survive during the zombie apocalypse. The users will have to participate in cruel step-by-step battles with walking dead, gradually gathering their own deck with cards-abilities. It will be possible to configure and pump the characters in the detachment, engage in the study of the open world, to extract resources, trade with secondary NPS and manage its own caravan for survival.</description></item><item><title>Citadelum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</guid><description>Game Description Citadelum throws its hat to the ring of strategic games, offering the experience of building cities with an admixture of mythology and strategic conquests. Ancient Rome serves as a background for the game: gamers take control of a nascent settlement and should turn it into a lively metropolis. Resource management is a paramount task for any novice urban planner. But Citadelum is not only overgrown suburbs and towering monuments.</description></item><item><title>Eden Crafters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</guid><description>Game Description Eden Crafters throws glove in the hands of survival and automation lovers. In this cooperative adventure with the open world, players will turn to turn a hostile planet into a hospitable refuge for humanity. Think about this as a space project of reconstruction - harsh conditions, fluids of the house of dreams. Task? Overcome the unpleasant habits of the planet and build a new house for humanity. Imagine radioactive zones and insidious landscapes are not the best real estate.</description></item><item><title>Heavy Cargo - The Truck Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heavy-cargo-the-truck-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heavy-cargo-the-truck-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Heavy Cargo - The Truck Simulator is an opportunity to feel like a real trucker who is forced to transport goods through the huge open world. It is necessary to search for orders, loading, unloading and accompanying a variety of cars in convoys. It will be possible to test several types of trailers that can transport the tractor. Juzerov is waiting for the gameplay of the classic driver’s simulator, which controls a big truck.</description></item><item><title>Liar's bar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</guid><description>Game Description Liar&amp;rsquo;s Bar is a multi -user online game, whose action takes place in a bar, where deception and strategy play a key role. Users are united at tables of four people to take part in games such as Liar&amp;rsquo;s Dice and Liar&amp;rsquo;s Deck. The goal is to outwit rivals using bliff and strategic moves. Each session is filled with stress, as gamers are trying to unravel each other&amp;rsquo;s intentions and make the right moves to win.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Zombie Defense 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-zombie-defense-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-zombie-defense-2/</guid><description>Game Description Ultimate Zombie Defense 2 throws you headlong into the tireless struggle for survival. Strengthen your positions against the wave waves with the help of a reliable base construction system. Classes from chains, sandbags and concrete barriers - it is time to show ingenuity and build an impenetrable fortress. But defense is only one side of the coin. The main thing here is the strategy. To restrain the inexorable hordes, you will have to cunningly arrange turrets, mines and even fog lights.</description></item><item><title>Rats in a Cage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rats-in-a-cage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rats-in-a-cage/</guid><description>Game Description Rats in a Cage proposes to solve puzzles in the form of a corporate certification. The player will manipulate colleagues, strategically placing coffee or spreading gossip, changing their routes and assigning other people&amp;rsquo;s merits to himself. The whole process oversees artificial intelligence, actively interfering with passage and sometimes interacting with elements outside the game window.
Such a gameplay constantly experiences the willingness to sacrifice others for the sake of personal benefits and career growth.</description></item><item><title>Endzone 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</guid><description>Game Description Endzone 2 throws you into the thick of the post -apocalyptic world. Humanity died, and you remained to collect fragments - literally. Each decision that you make as if you can send your scattered colony by the line. Lack of resources? Eat. Danger to the environment? Do not hesitate. Ruthless raiders eager to steal your lunch? Undoubtedly. This is not a simple walk. This is the management of your nascent civilization.</description></item><item><title>Toy Shire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-shire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-shire/</guid><description>Game Description Toy Shire revives a children&amp;rsquo;s room in a strategic battle. Bluespy Studios came up with this curious name by putting the player in the role of a defender. No pistols or grenades. Instead, plastic warriors and cardboard fortresses dominate the battlefield. The territory of the child is becoming a zone of hostilities. Tables, corners and floor of the bedroom turn into strategic landscapes. Gamers erect toy towers, these bizarre structures built from childhood residues.</description></item><item><title>Terminus: Zombie Survivors</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terminus-zombie-survivors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terminus-zombie-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Terminus: Zombie Survivors is a gloomy journey that takes gamers to the setting of the zombie apocalypse. It is ahead to survive among dangerous mutants, making their way through a variety of locations. The main task for the hero will be the search for the place of terminus, the last stronghold of mankind. In the game there are elements of Rowlaik that create random situations on the map. It will come out to compete with starvation, cold temperature and aggressive opponents.</description></item><item><title>Intravenous 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</guid><description>Game Description Intravenous 2 immerses you in the world of cruel intrigues and intense action. Play for Sean, desperately trying to save his abducted father, and Steve, a grumbling former military with a dark past. Their unlikely union is based on a common goal: to pass the labyrinth of the underworld, complete secrets, lies and mortal danger.
But how you can handle this insidious Odyssey depends only on you. Will you be a ghost, fluttering in shadows and manipulating environment in your interests?</description></item><item><title>ODD Realm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</guid><description>Game Description ODD Realm is a game that combines both the strategy and the survival simulator. The player will have to take on the role of the leader of a small settlement and provide residents with the necessary resources, houses, as well as protect their subjects from bloodthirsty enemies and dishonest bandits from a high road. The variability of the development of the plot provides the gamer with wide opportunities for the construction of the city of his own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Sins of A Solar Empire 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sins-of-a-solar-empire-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sins-of-a-solar-empire-2/</guid><description>Game Description Sins of A Solar Empire 2 is a space strategy in which players have to take one of three races under their control in order to fight for dominance over the whole galaxy. It will be necessary to engage in the study of space, expand the sphere of influence, extract resources and fight with representatives of the warring faction. The game presents a lot of diverse mechanics, including military operations, diplomacy, trade, etc.</description></item><item><title>Depersonalization</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/depersonalization/</guid><description>Game Description Depersonalization may interest amateurs of anime, Howard Lovecraft and Tactical Japanese Role Games. This is a mixture of TRPG, horror and visual novel. When creating their project, Chinese developers were inspired by the world of space horrors created by an eminent writer. Their creation boasts a detailed and designed pixel 2D graphic in anime style. The project is divided into several modules. Each of them has various finals and branches.</description></item><item><title>Dungeons &amp; Degenerate Gamblers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-degenerate-gamblers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-degenerate-gamblers/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeons &amp;amp; Degenerate Gamblers throws a crooked ball into traditional card games. Forget about the ink, peaks and trefches. Here the king is a blackjack, but with a highlight - a Roguelike -inventor, that is. Imagine yourself in a dull lighted tavern, smoke falls from your tube while you evaluate your opponent at a shabby table. But instead of swords and witchcraft, your weapons are cards. Unique cards that can improve your hand, ruin the enemy’s deck or even affect the course of history.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>Strategic Command Wwii: War in the Pacific</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/strategic-command-wwii-war-in-the-pacific/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/strategic-command-wwii-war-in-the-pacific/</guid><description>Game Description Strategic Command Wwii: War in the Pacific, heads you into the chaos of the Pacific Theater during the Second World War. This step -by -step strategic game boasts a huge map of 36,000 hexes, allowing you to develop a strategy in a vast territory - from the jungle of Burma to the shores of California. Fasten the belts, because on December 7, 1941 you will encounter a full-scale Japanese offensive, which will pass throughout Southeast Asia and the Pacific Ocean.</description></item><item><title>Terrascape</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrascape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrascape/</guid><description>Game Description Terrascape allows gamers to fulfill their dream - build their own city! Thanks to the wide selection of decks, offering unique buildings and the possibilities of expansion, you can strategically place your cards on the game field to earn points and open new awards. You will need to carefully consider the influence of each building on your city, including its influence on other buildings, natural resources and terrain. Collect positive factors of influence to get bonus glasses, but beware of negative factors that may interfere with your progress.</description></item><item><title>The Crust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</guid><description>Game Description The Crust is a survival with elements of the economy, where the player will build a whole small town with highly limited resources almost without the possibility of replenishing them. In order to grow at least something on such a surface and provide your people with the proper amount of food, you will have to try hard. However, with proper management, this is still quite possible.
The main character is the head of the space company, which was decided by the first to colonize the moon.</description></item><item><title>The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS is a step-by-step game where survival depends on spatial thinking. Each enemy and type of weapons act according to a unique scheme on the battlefield, forming a tactical environment from intersecting zones of defeat. Success is maneuvering for the operation of enemy vulnerability, while trying to cover the maximum area with his own arsenal. Any movement, the use of an object or attack completes the move, giving opponents the opportunity to deliver a response.</description></item><item><title>Dystopika</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dystopika/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dystopika/</guid><description>Game Description Dystopika is not an ordinary Advent. This is a digital sandbox, a neon platform for builders without drawings. Forget about resource management, population growth or economic balance. These things do not exist here. Instead, you are a digital architect, free to create a metropolis from scratch. No grandiose plans, no ultimate goal. This is a trip, not a destination. You build buildings, observe their growth and allow the city to develop organically.</description></item><item><title>Field of Glory: Kingdoms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/field-of-glory-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/field-of-glory-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Field of Glory: Kingdoms is an unusual strategy that allows you to lead various nations and create formidable kingdoms from them, which makes it one of the most exciting games in the genre. The action takes place in 1054, shortly after the great split, and immerses players in the more than two -century history of Europe, Africa and the Middle East. The project has a stunning set of capabilities: 375 fractions, 325 detachments, 600 buildings, 14 religions and 90 cultural characteristics, all of which are new for this publication.</description></item><item><title>Thriving City: Song</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thriving-city-song/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thriving-city-song/</guid><description>Game Description Thriving City: Song offers to be transferred to the past, in 960 of our era, and take on the role of the mayor in the recently formed Zhao Song dynasty. This gaming -symbol of the city’s construction in ancient China is a rich historical adventure with elements of strategy and plot. Your task as a mayor is to help the townspeople settle down, cultivate the land and expand the city.</description></item><item><title>Reus 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reus-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reus-2/</guid><description>Game Description Reus 2 stands out with its uniqueness and fascination. In this game, you have the power of the gods, controlling powerful giants that form the world for the prosperity or death of human civilizations. From the very beginning, everything is extremely clear: in Reus 2 you have to decide the fate of mankind, making your choice and committing actions.
You will get the opportunity to choose giants for yourself, each of which has its own abilities and characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Isles of Sea and Sky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/isles-of-sea-and-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/isles-of-sea-and-sky/</guid><description>Game Description Isles of Sea and Sky - a strategic adventure with a huge number of puzzles for logic, attentiveness and ingenuity. The project, developed by two programmers, uses pixel graphics and a camera located on top, which refers to some classic games with a similar theme and visual side. There is support for gamepads without additional configuration.
The casual management will make life easier for beginners, but the complex tasks posed to the user will gradually become increasingly confusing and incomprehensible at first glance.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Voltage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-voltage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-voltage/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Voltage immerses you in the world of crazy science and monstrous chaos. This indie game combines Roguelike elements and automation mechanics, in which you have to create your own combat abilities. Forget about pressing the buttons - the strategy dominates here. Each move you have to manage resources. To release a powerful explosion, heal yourself with a potion or accumulate energy for the future offensive? The choice is yours, and each solution can persuade the scales in the battle.</description></item><item><title>Nordic ashes: Survivors of Ragnarok</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</guid><description>Game Description Nordic ashes: survivors of ragnarok - Dynamic adventure with elements of action and simplified cuckle. The plot is inspired by Scandinavian legends and motives. The main character finds himself in a dangerous environment in which he will face hordes of enemy and deadly creatures. He needs to stay alive among hundreds of opponents and traps, gradually pumping his abilities and finding more powerful equipment.
The central character will move between worlds, fight with powerful bosses, overcome traps and find objects of equipment.</description></item><item><title>Headquarters: World War II</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/headquarters-world-war-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/headquarters-world-war-ii/</guid><description>Game Description Headquarters: World War 2, a fascinating step -by -step strategy, immerses users into an exciting battle for Normandy through three campaigns and numerous skirmishes. This project allows gamers to accept command on both sides of the conflict, heading the United States, Great Britain or Germany. The combat system is simultaneously accessible and complex, providing players with many strategic capabilities.
In this dynamic game, combat units have anterior, side, rear and upper armor, which makes their location on the battlefield by a decisive factor.</description></item><item><title>From Glory to Goo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</guid><description>Game Description From Glory to Goo is a cosmic adventure. Forget about the conquest of the new worlds - here the survival depends on how to cling to the fragment of the rock among the inexorable stream of mucus. You play for the captain, the last hope of mankind, who is instructed to establish a fragile colony on a hostile foreign world. Your enemies are not rival empires and not robots with lasers, but the ubiquitous mucus, a reasonable, changing form, the threat that oozes, drips and crawls to your colony from all sides.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Glory 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-glory-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-glory-2/</guid><description>Game Description Mortal Glory 2 is a fantasy RPG in the Roguelike genre, which combines a step -by -step tactical battle and team management. It is proposed to be in the role of the leader of the team of wandering gladiators, and your ultimate goal is to take part in the tournament, the victory in which guarantees glory and wealth. One of the main features of the game is the variety of available races, each of which has its own unique advantages and disadvantages.</description></item><item><title>Primitive Society Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/primitive-society-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/primitive-society-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Primitive Society Simulator will transfer you to the inexorable cradle of civilization. In the role of the leader of the ancient tribe, you will lead your people through the torment of the prehistoric period, controlling the subtle dance between survival and progress. Guided by Chinese legends, Primitive Society Simulator echoes Rimworld and Dawn of Man. You will move to those days when every sunrise was like victory, and every hunt is the risk of extinction.</description></item><item><title>Craftomation 101: Programming and Craft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftomation-101-programming-and-craft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftomation-101-programming-and-craft/</guid><description>Game Description CraftMATION 101: Programming and Craft offers to gamers to be on an unknown planet, in the company of the right robot and many mechanisms that will help you make it viable. You will find endless opportunities for the extraction and combination of resources, programming robots, creating tools and terraforming the planet. You can create your own army of robots that will work for you, collect resources, perform tasks and even create new robots.</description></item><item><title>Arms Trade Tycoon: Tanks</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arms-trade-tycoon-tanks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arms-trade-tycoon-tanks/</guid><description>Game Description ARMS TRADE TYCOON: Tanks is a full -fledged simulation of the life of a magnate, managing the beginner company in trade and distribution of weapons. The company specializes in the creation and sale of tanks, on the technical characteristics of which the user will work. The game allows you to create unique engineering solutions by exploring new technologies and production methods. It is necessary to engage in the formation of the history of tank wars, where the created cars will be involved.</description></item><item><title>Hellcard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellcard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hellcard/</guid><description>Game Description Hellcard is made in the same style as the original book of demons. Their universe is also common. The first game was a simplified diabloid and narrated about the fight against evil awakened in the catacombs under the city. The spin-off changed the genre, turning from Hack and Slash into a step-by-step card RPG. One of the chips in the form of cardboard graphics has not gone away. The elements of the sideline remained.</description></item><item><title>Rising Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Rising Lords presents a mixture of a strategy with a card game in medieval setting. Fights are implemented using step -by -step mechanics. The player collects slaves and uses them for his personal purposes. As in any economic strategy, the gameplay is based on the collection of resources and taxes. The player is free to set the amount of duties depending on the solvency of units. It is required to set tasks and work to the peasants for the whole day.</description></item><item><title>Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</guid><description>Game Description Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout - an adventure action in which a group of people falls on a tropical island equipped with high -tech objects. The territory is governed by AI, which produces a huge number of combat robots and artificially nurtures of dinosaurs. The game is made in the Cyberpanus setting and contains elements of metroid.
Once on the island, it must be examined by opening the results of a monstrous experiment.</description></item><item><title>World Warfare and Economics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-warfare-and-economics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-warfare-and-economics/</guid><description>Game Description World Warfare and Economics is a fascinating and large -scale strategy that offers to take control of any country on Earth, finding himself at the helm of world history. Having the opportunity to manage politics, economics and the armed forces of the country, players go through many trials, including the impending ghost of the Third World War, the inexorable procession of global pandemia and even scenarios created at their own discretion.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-rogue-trader/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-rogue-trader/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader is an isometric role -playing game made based on the cult universe of a fighting hammer. In her setting, the Grimard is mixed with science fiction. This product offers to travel through space on a huge ship, visit different places, chat with colorful non -pains, pump, perform quests, participate in battles. All the battles here are step -by -step and tactical.
They are divided into 2 types.</description></item><item><title>Ticket to Ride</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ticket-to-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ticket-to-ride/</guid><description>Game Description Ticket to Ride is a digital adaptation of a popular board game that invites gamers to go to a global railway adventure. Here, participants will have to build the most branched railway network, connecting the cities and completing the routes. Users play the cards to capture sections of the railway, building a strategy to go around rivals and achieve their goals. Title has both a single -user and multi -user regimes, which allows you to diversify the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Dungeons 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-4/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeons 4 is a real -time fantasy strategy with a bias in urban development, in which gamers will take the side of darkness and help the absolute evil and his faithful waist of the waist to win over the forces of good. You will fall into a fascinating world where peace and harmony once reigned, but now other times have come. You have to build your dungeon and direct your creatures into the outside world in order to envelop it with darkness and bring victory to the absolute evil.</description></item><item><title>Lost Hope: Backrooms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Hope: BackRooms offers a single first -person adventure in the alarming locations of backstage. Key classes include navigation for these confusing, interconnected places and active interaction with the environment for solving logical puzzles, which contributes to the development of the main plot. The area often demonstrates strange and inexplicable phenomena, which are difficult to immediately comprehend. Gamers have to carefully study these elements in order to reveal the secrets hidden in this tense journey.</description></item><item><title>Back to the Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description The prison atmosphere in Back to the Dawn shows the life of an anthropomorphic animal that is forced to fight for the right to exist in a zone. Gamers will explore prison laws, rules and locations in which a protagonist finds himself. The main character will pump and make new acquaintances, relying on his own social skills. It will be possible to use cunning and intelligence to solve many problems, where the main task is an attempt to escape from imprisonment.</description></item><item><title>For the king 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/for-the-king-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/for-the-king-2/</guid><description>Game Description For The King 2 is a continuation of an unforgettable adventure RPG with elements of the board game and Roguelike, where you can defeat the formidable queen alone or together with three comrades. You have to explore the world and increase your level in order to reveal the secrets of the past and overthrow the despotistical queen. Try to avoid the queen fanatical guards who control everything around, and combine their forces with their apostates to conquer this world.</description></item><item><title>CITIES: SkyLines 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines-ii/</guid><description>Game Description CITIES: Skylines II, which allows you to truly prove yourself as an urban plan and mayor, allows you to get an incomparable experience in urban planning. This is a world where your creative abilities and the ability to solve problems are subjected to a fierce test, and there are no limits to what you can achieve. The game begins with the creation of the main elements of the city - roads, infrastructure and systems that ensure its life.</description></item><item><title>Galactic Civilizations IV: Supernova</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galactic-civilizations-iv-supernova/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galactic-civilizations-iv-supernova/</guid><description>Game Description Galactic Civilizations IV: Supernova is a fascinating global strategy in science fiction setting. You are the leader of the cosmic civilization, which is ready to conquer the universe. You have many abilities to achieve this goal: from conquering planets to creating cultural domination and political alliances. You have to explore the galaxy, colonize new worlds and manage your home planet. You will be engaged in trade, diplomacy, intrigue and war with other aliens.</description></item><item><title>Railgrade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</guid><description>Game Description Railgrade gameplay combines elements of strategy and construction. The plot covers the times of the great construction of railways around the world in order to connect fast transportation between foreign cities with valuable industry. The main character will save the future of mankind, since he is the last employee of the earth colony. Megacorporations asked him to fulfill a difficult mission and save everything that remained on the planet after the disaster that occurred due to errors in the calculations of management.</description></item><item><title>Dotage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dotage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dotage/</guid><description>Game Description Dotage offers a unique game experience. Michele was feasted and others developed the concept of this digital kingdom. Players move around the world devoid of clear goals. The gameplay rotates around simple mechanics: pressing one button moves the protagonist forward. This seemingly simple action becomes the basis for a trip, rich in interpretation. The visual language of the game consists of abstract landscapes and mysterious symbols. The narrative unfolds through these elements, inviting to introspection, and not giving obvious explanations.</description></item><item><title>AFTERWAR</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/afterwar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/afterwar/</guid><description>Game Description AFTERWAR represents a global scenario unfolding in 2028, after a centuries of conflicts. The alternative version of the future left behind historical wars, laying the foundation for universal interaction. In the role of the national leader, the player will have to unite the states and dispose of resources to build a new society. Any step, from the distribution of the budget and the introduction of advanced technologies to the conclusion of international agreements, directly affects the balance between stability and chaos.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the White Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of the White Sun transfers to the chaos of China of the 1920s, the period of riots and fragmented leadership. In this grandiose strategic game, you have to pave the way through a fragmented nation controlled by military leaders, rebels and political groups. The action unfolds at a time when various groups dispute control of vast territories and armies, each of which has its own goals, objectives and motives.</description></item><item><title>High Sea Saga DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</guid><description>Game Description High Sea Saga DX immerses players in the marine environment, focused on the accumulation of wealth and global research. In this Title, gamers control the pirate team crossing the oceans in search of hidden treasures scattered through a variety of geographical zones. Each such journey entails a clash with various wild creatures and battles with warring pirate fractions that pursue similar goals. Success requires the collection of an effective detachment and the construction of a swimming agent, ready for long -term crossings by open waters.</description></item><item><title>Bee Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-island/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-island/</guid><description>Game Description In Bee Island, you will become the head of a prosperous hive, taking on the role of a defender from impending threats. The main attention in the game is paid to defense and strategic construction. Enemies make sporadic attacks, and your task is to protect the hive. They are armed with bombs, poisonous aerosols and missiles, their strength is constantly growing. To reflect their attack, you have to build a whole complex of protective structures - ballists, machine guns, anti -aircraft missile systems and much more.</description></item><item><title>Golf it!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/golf-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/golf-it/</guid><description>Game Description The simulator of a real golf - Golf it! - It is a sports, but ridiculous brainchild of the studio of developers who want to turn American sport into a kind of fantastic game. The player’s career begins with simple levels, where to calculate the trajectory and the impact of the impact is easier, but gradually we will approach the complex levels at which even pushing the ball will be difficult.</description></item><item><title>Desynced</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</guid><description>Game Description Desynced is a three -dimensional real -time strategy. The indie project also has elements of survival and a colony control simulator. The Title is made in a science fiction setting. It has support for user modifications. According to the plot, the hero travels along with artificial intelligence and colonizers between distant planets. The protagonist plants bots to the surface, and he remains in orbit and leads mechanical creatures from there.</description></item><item><title>Railway Empire 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</guid><description>Game Description Railway Empire 2 is a transport strategy that offers to go into the past, at the beginning of the 19th century, and lead a small railway company, which will become the leader of the economy thanks to steam cars. Here you have to compete with competitors and build a network of railways, which will connect cities and companies throughout the continent. At your disposal 60 famous steam machines that pull freight and passenger cars, opening the historically significant era of the time of the industrial revolution.</description></item><item><title>Fly Corp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fly-corp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fly-corp/</guid><description>Game Description The development of routes in Fly Corp allows you to feel the work of real airports located throughout the globe. Players get the opportunity to create transport routes in the airspace, setting up the uninterrupted transportation of passengers who want to fly from one city to another. The task of the user will be to establish the right nodes and the implementation of flights that can most profitably and effectively transport the inhabitants of the planet to the necessary destination.</description></item><item><title>Silica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</guid><description>Game Description Silica is a dynamic alloy of action and a science fiction strategy that revolves around a fierce struggle for power over a Baltarus, a planet who is replete with quartz crystals, desired for all fractions. Players can manage their armies as commanders from orbit or plunge into battle with their heads as an infantry, vehicles or various insect -like aliens.
Silica allows gamers to choose their game style without limiting them to specific rules.</description></item><item><title>Stranded: Alien Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description Stranded: Alien Dawn is an open world survival simulator. In this case, an alien. According to the plot, a group of people on a rescue shuttle is evacuated from a burning starship and landed on the first planet that fall. The player controls the team of surviving crew members of the space ship. He needs to take care of his wards, providing them with warmth, light, food, medicines, weapons, entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Total Conflict: Resistance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</guid><description>Game Description Total Conflict: Resistance is an incredible mixture of global strategy, tactics and an action in the first person that provides incredible battles, many types of armored vehicles, weapons and armor, as well as unique mechanics to immerse you in exciting gameplay. You have to take part in events, manage units, create your army and produce or purchase armored vehicles and weapons. You can also build fortifications, outposts and settlements, manage military operations in the first person, as well as in tactical mode.</description></item><item><title>Swirl Watch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swirl-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swirl-watch/</guid><description>Game Description Swirl Watch is a stealth scene of a horn, unfolding on a gas giant undergoing excessive operation. Players have to penetrate industrial complexes, bypass or neutralize protection vessels, committing corporate sabotage to create a resistance movement. In the dense atmosphere of the planet Cloud 2, ships find each other only in laser light, noise of engines and echolocation.
This situation creates specific conditions for bypassing patrols and dismantling cloud processing stations.</description></item><item><title>Endgame of Devil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endgame-of-devil/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endgame-of-devil/</guid><description>Game Description Endgame of Devil will put a player in the role of a devil who is entrusted with protecting the castle. The task is to stop the adventurers' units trying to take possession of treasures in your possessions. To do this, it is necessary to call on and command the servants to reflect the onslaught of the invaders. Combat clashes are automatic, moving the gameplay towards the strategic formation of the detachment before the battle.</description></item><item><title>Terra Nil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-nil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-nil/</guid><description>Game Description Terra Nil is a urban planning simulator, which uses pixel graphics with a large number of parts of the area. A feature of the project is that the player needs to build a settlement from scratch, without using factories and other buildings, that they can pollute the air, water spaces and the ground, having achieved the title of environmental place for residence for his creation. Starting with a randomly generated area, the gamer receives initial capital for the construction of the first residential buildings and various production, to provide residents with work.</description></item><item><title>Nucleares</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nucleares/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nucleares/</guid><description>Game Description Nucleares may be of interest to lovers of original projects and unusual indie-symptures. This is a simulator of an employee of a nuclear power plant with a first -person view. The character has arms, legs and torso. They can be seen if you lower the camera. The hero turns out to be the only employee at an experimental nuclear power plant for which large staff does not need. This object requires only one person, because artificial intelligence is responsible for everything else.</description></item><item><title>Barotrauma</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/barotrauma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/barotrauma/</guid><description>Game Description Barotrauma is a two -dimensional simulator decorated in the style of the platformer. According to the plot, your courageous shoulders are entrusted to enter the captain of the real submarine, but you will not control it on the ground, but on one of the satellites of Jupiter called Europe, in the bowels of which the underground ocean spreads. The surface of the satellite is shrouded in an impassable radiation layer, due to which the colony of people are forced to hide under the thickness of the ice that protect the local waters.</description></item><item><title>Terraformers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraformers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraformers/</guid><description>Game Description Terraformers - 3x game with Roguelite elements, in which you are heading the terraforming of Mars. Get on the Red Planet, where there are no buildings of humanity. Use the resources of the environment and gradually expand your base, based on new cities, settlements and industrial territories. Start the process of terraforming by warming the planet, editing oceans and spreading life thanks to bacteria and brought creatures.
Control the leaders and send them to mysterious places to open huge places rich in resources.</description></item><item><title>DREADFUL River</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadful-river/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadful-river/</guid><description>Game Description DREADFUL River is an arcade rafting simulator on the river on a raft with elements of role -playing play, action and tactics. The project was carried out in medieval setting. The plot tie begins with the attack of enemies on the kingdom. While the enemies are storming the castle, the king with a small group of the most faithful guards goes in search of an eternal crown, about which different legends go.</description></item><item><title>Caves of Lore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of lore-role-playing game with two-dimensional pixel art style graphics and from above. Moving by locations occurs in real time. During the study of the area, you can neutralize traps, look for secrets and hack chests with loot. Equipment can be of different colors. Coloring depends on the rarity of the object. There are hundreds of things here. Battles with monsters are held in step -by -step mode. In battle, heroes can move around the cells.</description></item><item><title>Winter Falling: Battle Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Falling: Battle Tactics invites gamers to lead the troops and lead them to victory in the most stressful and tactical battles. And only your mind can save the dying world from devastation. You control a detachment of mercenaries, collect supplies and troops, perform tasks and even you can burn villages if you decide that you need it. But do not forget that all your actions have consequences.</description></item><item><title>Victoria 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victoria-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victoria-3/</guid><description>Game Description Victoria 3 is a direct sequel to the game of the same name, where the gamer will act in a time period from 1836 to 1936. In the manager’s simulator, Juzer is invited to choose one of the available countries, and manage it for the specified time. It will have to be controlled by political, demographic, economic processes, as well as try to pacify the layers of the population in order to build an ideal society.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip - a continuation of the popular series of satirical adventure, the actions of which unfold in a fabulous universe. Instead of people, it is inhabited by various very cute monsters of all possible species and appearance. Unlike previous parts, here the developers do not focus on the simulation of dates, but on road travel and survival. Juzer needs to get to a certain epic place in order to end the campaign successfully.</description></item><item><title>Terra Invicta</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-invicta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-invicta/</guid><description>Game Description Terra Invicta is a cosmic 4x strategy, the events of which develop in the distant future. Once, alien forces invaded our galaxy, dividing humanity into 7 factions. Each union saw its development of the future. You have to lead one of the seven ideologies to impose it to the whole world. Explore the solar system, expand the territories and fight enemies in tactical fights.
The aliens invaded the far corner of the Kuiper ice belt.</description></item><item><title>After the Collapse</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</guid><description>Game Description AFTER The COLLAPSE is a 2D strategy, a management and management simulator of its own settlement. A camera that is above above the surface at right angles is used. The surrounding world survived the apocalypse, which is why it turned into radioactive wastelands and became very dangerous for living people without means of protection against monsters and aggressive bandits. The task of the gamer is to develop existing buildings and build new ones to increase population growth and create a powerful army that is ready to fight off external threats.</description></item><item><title>Lost Branch of Legend</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-branch-of-legend/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-branch-of-legend/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou: Lost Branch of Legend will transfer you to the fantastic world of Genskoo. Create your deck using mana of different colors, and then fight with famous characters from the Touhou universe. In this Roguelike builder, there is a constant increase in mana from scattered exhibits, which makes each passage of the game unique.
The game can boast of more than 500 unique bullet rains, which accurately recreate the frantic charm of Gennosoko.</description></item><item><title>Farthest Frontier</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</guid><description>Game Description Farthest Frontier is a strategic game with the simulator elements. The game is made by all canons of 4x-mechanics. You have to develop your settlement and defend it from an attack by the enemy. Guide your people and try not only to survive, but also to develop. The world of wildlife is fraught with many dangers with which you have to face face every day.
Collect resources, go hunting, do fishing or farming - do everything possible to survive in harsh and wild conditions.</description></item><item><title>Plateup!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plateup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plateup/</guid><description>Game Description Plateup! -This is an arcade simulator of cooking and restaurant control with elements of time management. This arcade is designed for cooperative passage. Multiplayer is available through a local network (LAN) and the Internet. There is also the opportunity to play together at the same computer. Single mode is also available. In this video game, users own a whole franchise. Each institution is a separate level. It randomly generates the conditions, climate and visitors.</description></item><item><title>Alchemia: Creatio ex nihilo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemia-creatio-ex-nihilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemia-creatio-ex-nihilo/</guid><description>Game Description Alchemia: Creatio Ex Nihilo combines several genres. This is a head-headed game, a step-by-step strategy and a simplified corgorate. The action takes place in the fantasy world, where magic is adjacent to alchemy. The hero travels through the forgotten kingdom, finds artifacts (available 30 species), collects materials, opens recipes (there are 40 varieties here), crafts weapons from them and fights with its help with different monsters. The user can choose a route for his ward on a fork.</description></item><item><title>Strategic Command: American Civil War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/strategic-command-american-civil-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/strategic-command-american-civil-war/</guid><description>Game Description Strategic Command: American Civil War is a new part of a small series of step -by -step strategies. The engine was improved in it. As the name implies, the continuation is dedicated to the civil war in America. The game transfers users to the 19th century. The developers created the largest card in the history of the franchise. It consists of 66,000 hexes and covers the entire North America from the Caribbean to Canada (and New Mexico).</description></item><item><title>Starship Troopers - Terran Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starship-troopers-terran-command/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starship-troopers-terran-command/</guid><description>Game Description Starship Troopers - Terran Command is a real -time strategy developed based on the Feature Film Star landing. Engage in the construction of the base, get resources and create an army to fight with giant insects living on a foreign planet. You need to colonize the hostile planet, which was suitable for the human race, but a huge number of hostile alien creatures live on its surface.
Take the role of the leader of the Terran army.</description></item><item><title>Frozenheim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frozenheim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frozenheim/</guid><description>Game Description Frozenheim - a saga about the Vikings, in which the main character is expelled from his native lands, since blood feud tears his last name. He goes in search of a new home for himself and his loyal subjects. The harsh winter is approaching, and the clan needs to get to the shelter as quickly as possible. The construction of the settlement is a prolonged matter and the central character does not fit.</description></item><item><title>Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</guid><description>Game Description Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga tells about the events that erupted after the conflict between the Empire of Veridia and Tanra. They fought for a long time, and in the end all these events led to the fact that the first empire remained in losses. However, thanks to the young ruler of Florin, a shaky, but peace finally formed. Everyone began to gradually recover until something terrible happened.</description></item><item><title>Venture Towns</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</guid><description>Game Description Venture Towns allows players to build a city landscape. This project transfers to the gamers the corporation forming a settlement. From the initial structures to vast skyscrapers, the player leads the development, striving for economic superiority. The game emphasizes the deliberate arrangement of various architectural elements, contributing to a systematic approach to urbanistic growth and current economic activity.
In Venture Towns, the processes of the construction of objects open the ways for development.</description></item><item><title>Old World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/old-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/old-world/</guid><description>Game Description Old World in the past was also known as 10 Crowns. The game is a step -by -step global strategy in the antique setting. The gameplay is strikingly different from the games of this genre: it is allowed to give several orders to Unit in one move. Such a resource as &amp;ldquo;orders&amp;rdquo; is responsible for additional moves. The more recognition points, the more moves can be made. The resource &amp;ldquo;Order&amp;rdquo; can be used in different ways: in battle, in construction, in events or diplomacy.</description></item><item><title>Coromon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coromon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coromon/</guid><description>Game Description Coromon is a role-playing indie adventure about taming animals for their further fights among themselves, according to the type of Pokemon. This project uses a rare pixel visual design as a tribute to the game industry of the last century. The camera is at an angle to create an isometric view of the world around the world, which is much more examined in this position. The single -user campaign of this game will take a gamer not for one day, and a thorough study will require even more free time.</description></item><item><title>Polimines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</guid><description>Game Description Thanks to** Polimines** you can try to swing your own intelligence, as well as strangle to strain your brains. Yes, this is a head-headed game in which the levels will need to go through the locations. But it will not be at all as easy as it might seem at first glance. Therefore, it will be necessary to make all your efforts, as well as understand the basic principle.</description></item><item><title>SCP: 5k</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scp-5k/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scp-5k/</guid><description>Game Description SCP: 5k - cooperative shooter in the first person with the elements of the horror. Play both alone and unite with friends. The game is represented by hardcore complexity. Particular attention is paid to the detailed environment and plot. The team can have up to four people. Go to a complex and saturated adventure!
The story of SCP: 5k talks about how a foreign creature was discovered in the human psyche, which is responsible for all negative features: pain, cruelty, etc.</description></item><item><title>Idle Calibur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</guid><description>Game Description Idle Calibur combines a study of the open world with tactical RPG tactical and real -time mechanics in real time. The gameplay is focused on the construction of a city, which serves to recruit heroes with special abilities. Battles can be automatically due to IDLE function, or you can take direct manual control of your detachments during the fight. Key tasks include the collection of forces to attack other settlements on the world map and participate in structured tests with bosses for development.</description></item><item><title>Sands of Salzaar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sands-of-salzaar/</guid><description>Game Description Sands of Salzaar is a strategic game whose actions unfold in the Salzaara desert. Fight with numerous hostile factions, gathering your own army and developing your city. Choose your character, profession and faction, on whose side your army will have to fight. The eastern land is filled with various secrets and you have to solve them all.
Sands of Salzaar events talk about an exotic old empire that once ruled the desert.</description></item><item><title>Fights in Tight Spaces</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fights-in-tight-spaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fights-in-tight-spaces/</guid><description>Game Description Fights in Tight Spaces - a mixture of a card game with a step -by -step strategy and animated battles made in classical setting. Here, a gamer will learn to build his own tactics in any conditions, knocking out the right cards and their location in order to win in battles. To create a deck in the game, there are 150 cards compiled taking into account the abilities of the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Mud and Blood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mud-and-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mud-and-blood/</guid><description>Game Description The rethought project MUD and Blood is a shootout between the two sides of the conflict, where the user has to observe the events. The setting transfers during the Second World War, where soldiers converge in battles. The updated engine and improved artificial intelligence allows you to try out the old classic flash game, filled with innovations in terms of functions and a graphic component that immerses gameplay into the process.</description></item><item><title>TimberBorn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/timberborn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/timberborn/</guid><description>Game Description TimberBorn allows you to develop a beaver colony. The game does not claim realism, because rodents behave and move like people. This is a full -fledged urban planning simulator. The settlement has to rebuild in the world where humanity has disappeared, leaving behind the exhausted land. In an alternative future, the planet suffers from drought.
To control the water resource in TimberBorn, you can build dams and dig channels.</description></item><item><title>City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</guid><description>Game Description City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV is a strategic simulator in which it is important not only to chase the demand of players, but also be able to reduce expenses and vice versa, be able to spend money where they are actually needed. Games developers presented a simulator in which you will have to develop a company that develops games. A small studio creating video games decided to expand, so you must make every effort to create a whole headquarters of developers who can satisfy the needs of modern gamers.</description></item><item><title>The Doors of Trithius</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</guid><description>Game Description The Doors of Trithius is a RPG -Rogalik in the fantasy world with procedurally generated content. Here you have to fight monsters, avoid traps, collect prey and much more, traveling along the mysterious world of Enalia. Every time you start the game, you have to explore the new generated city, dungeon and map of the world. Movement and battle use a unique time system, returning the priority of the player based on the speed of weapons or action, maintaining tactical decisions, as well as knowledge about your enemies.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Battlesctor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-battlesector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-battlesector/</guid><description>Game Description The step-by-step strategy Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector transfers to the world of the future of the 41st millennium. It is required to collect their military units, build up strength, develop leaders' abilities and enter into a stressful confrontation, controlling destructive weapons. It is necessary to go through a rich plot campaign of 20 unique tasks. History is devoted to the devastation of the Vaal continent. It is required, together with Sergeant Carleon and his allies, cleanse Baal for a second of the influence of tyranids.</description></item><item><title>Mini MotorWays</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mini-motorways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mini-motorways/</guid><description>Game Description Mini MotorWays - Top -Daw Simulator, which allows you to develop the city, building buildings, infrastructure, roads, etc. It is necessary to build a huge metropolis, filling it with highways, highways, in various ways, etc. It is important to create the best option to avoid traffic jams and accidents. The problem of urban traffic is the most important question for any mayor.
The Mini MotorWays game process is a real puzzle in which it is necessary to solve the problem with the movement of transport.</description></item><item><title>The Fermi Paradox</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-fermi-paradox/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-fermi-paradox/</guid><description>Game Description The Fermi Paradox is a fantastic setting strategy. The gameplay is focused on choosing a plot, which will affect the player’s decisions, the place of travel and presented civilizations. It is necessary to conduct races and types of creatures through tens of centuries, helping them to study the expanses of the universe, establish contacts with other living organisms and create harmony.
Being the ruler of an alien civilization, you will need to direct them to prosperity, help survive, collect radio signals from long stars and make contact with new races.</description></item><item><title>Going Medieval</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</guid><description>Game Description Going Medieval is a simulator in which you need to build a fortress on the ruins of an old castle and equip it to protect your settlement. Any event can affect the mood of your people, so you need to satisfy all their needs and be a good king. Events unfold in the era of the dark Middle Ages of the late XIV century.
Only five percent of the population survived after a heavy plague epidemic.</description></item><item><title>Across the Obelisk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/across-the-obelisk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/across-the-obelisk/</guid><description>Game Description Across the Obelisk is a cooperative game with role -playing elements and collecting its own deck. The gameplay presents a single and multi -user regime. Participants choose a variety of heroes, open access to new items and cards, creating a set of characters. After that, you have to fight monsters and bosses in deep tactical contractions.
Features of Across the Obelisk:
Dynamic assembly of decks in the Roguelite style, where each card improves by different items, increased level or other methods.</description></item><item><title>Element TD 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/element-td-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/element-td-2/</guid><description>Game Description Element TD 2 is a strategy in the style of &amp;ldquo;protection of a tower&amp;rdquo; with competitive elements. Events unfold in a fantastic world, where the player will use six main elements: nature, earth, fire, light, darkness and water. Before passing, you will need to choose several elements that determine the type of towers and abilities. At the start of the match, a certain amount of funds for which buildings are installed is issued.</description></item><item><title>Eximius: Seize the Frontline</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eximius-seize-the-frontline/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eximius-seize-the-frontline/</guid><description>Game Description EXIMIUS: Seize the Frontline is a first -person shooter with real -time strategy elements. The multiplayer game consists in battles of 5 by 5, where 4 people act as officers on the front line and one commander acting as a support and giving orders.
Cards for battles are represented by various cities in the world of post -apocalypse. When playing for the commander, you need to build a base, train your fighters and help allied organizations.</description></item><item><title>Empire of Sin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empire-of-sin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empire-of-sin/</guid><description>Game Description Empire of Sin is a strategy whose actions unfold in Chicago of the 1920s. A dry law has been introduced, which means that the time is for the heyday of crime and smuggling. Being a boss of the criminal world, take the Office of one of the 14 groups. Many characters are based on real prototypes of gangsters such as Al Capone, Stefani Saint-Claire or Goldi Garno.
Your tasks include building a whole criminal empire.</description></item><item><title>Easy Red 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</guid><description>Game Description Easy Red 2 is a first -person shooter with elements of a strategy that immerses in an authentic atmosphere of World War II. The gameplay can plunge into tense and cruel battles, where the main thing is planning and tactics. The gameplay relies on realism. Take a break through the tanks and the enemy’s huge army. Do not fall into the explosion zone and look for ways to survive on the battlefield with your partners.</description></item><item><title>Kingdoms Reborn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-reborn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-reborn/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdoms Reborn is a urban planning simulator with a full multipleor and card game elements. The project was primarily created under the online, but there is also a single in it. The world is randomly generated. It is divided into 7 biomes that do not gameplay. In the Arctic zone and tropics, it will be more difficult to grow food on ordinary fields than in the territory with a temperate climate.</description></item><item><title>Endless Furry Killer 2020</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-furry-killer-2020/</guid><description>Game Description The conflict in Endless Furry Killer 2020 puts a player against the endless waves of anthropomorphic opponents. The gamer has to move through two -dimensional arenas with a view of the top intended for continuous battles. The key lesson lies in the shooting of goals in a tense struggle for life with a constant stream of enemies. Such a gameplay requires constant movement and aiming to defeat non -aloscorizing resistance.</description></item><item><title>Wingspan (Wings)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wingspan-krylja/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wingspan-krylja/</guid><description>Game Description Wingspan (wings) - a collectible card game based on the same tough. The version for personal computers is designed for a session of one to five people. Players are assigned the role of ornithologists involved in studying new species of birds and trying to collect and bring as many rare individuals as possible to the natural reserve.
Gathering in the world of various birds, more points go to those who will be able to get a unique and dying look.</description></item><item><title>Empyrion - Galactic Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Empyrion - Galactic Survival shows the world of the future. In the 24th century, in the ice of Antarctica, they find a spacecraft of aliens. Scientists investigated the object and discovered the technology of the hyperdrod. Earthlings send an expedition to the planet Empirion, which is in the Andromeda nebula. The crew gets to the destination, but tolerates the crash and cannot return home.
In survival mode, the player leaves the rescue capsule and is alone against the hostile world.</description></item><item><title>Baldi's Basics Plus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldis-basics-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldis-basics-plus/</guid><description>Game Description Baldi&amp;rsquo;s Basics Plus - a parody of the first -person horror and educational games of the 90s. All levels are randomly generated, and mini-games are made in bright colors and allow you to go to nature. Baldi&amp;rsquo;s Basics Plus is an extended version of the original game containing more objects and characters.
The game contains a huge number of strange characters and useful objects necessary for passing. Exploring the confusing corridors of Baldie’s school, the hero will come across many random and hilarious events.</description></item><item><title>Ostriv</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</guid><description>Game Description OSTRIV, this is a city -building simulator that makes you the ruler of the monarch of the 18th century. The player will have to work hard and show his ability to the manager, as well as creative abilities. The goal of the game to transfer the gameplay of simulators of this kind to a new level, by means of adding a huge number of opportunities and abandoning the usual restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Panzer Corps 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panzer-corps-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panzer-corps-2/</guid><description>Game Description Plunge into a new type of step -by -step strategies in Panzer Corps 2. The game tells about terrible events during the Second World War. You have to play a key role, taking a large army under command. This is easy to master the gameplay, and the outcome of the battles will depend only on the correct moves, not the reaction.
Players can take control of any European country and create their own army of thousands of various units.</description></item><item><title>Hex of Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Players in Hex of Steel have to go during the Second World War, where you will have to control the troops on land, water and in the air. The project is a full -scale Vargam, where you have to perform step -by -step actions on the global map of the world, which includes Europe, Africa and the Pacific regions. Users will be able to fight against AI in a single campaign or special historical scenarios, as well as in the cross -platform mode of PBEM and multiplayer skirmishes against other users (there is the possibility of cooperative passage).</description></item><item><title>Stoneshard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stoneshard/</guid><description>Game Description Come in the role of a harsh mercenary in a harsh, ruined war, kingdom. Take part in step -by -step battles and examine the RPG elements of Stoneshard, available in the gameplay. You can perform contracts, secondary and plot missions. Heal the wounds, purchase equipment and improve the protagonist as soon as you wish.
Freely move around the big and seamless world. Explore the villages lying in the ruins, go down to the dungeons or look into abandoned tracts.</description></item><item><title>Ai War 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-war-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-war-2/</guid><description>Game Description In AI WAR 2, an even more advanced version of AI captured the entire galaxy, and left only a tiny planet to the player. It&amp;rsquo;s time to strike and outwit the enemy. This will come in handy new capabilities, large flotillas and hacking skills. Or you can get involved in a much more confusing galactic struggle. On the agenda - macrophages, Dyson spheres, nanocosts and much more. Each faction has its own goal, its own rules, units and a completely unique economy.</description></item><item><title>Police Stories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/police-stories/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/police-stories/</guid><description>Game Description John Reims and Rick Jones are two brave cops trying to put the streets of his hometown in order. Police Stories is a story full of intrigues and conspiracies. Having learned the motives of some heroes, a terrible truth will open. But on the way to the answers, many hostages have to be saved, kill the pack of bandits and neutralize a huge number of bombs.
Police Stories implemented mechanics:</description></item><item><title>Microtown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microtown/</guid><description>Game Description Microtown is a urban planning simulator in which you will control your own settlement. Build the village of your dreams, lead it inhabitants and try to expand your possessions in order to become the most prosperous settlement on all land. Microtown&amp;rsquo;s gameplay is emphasized on production chains.
You begin your way as a small village, gradually expanding to a huge city. Explore the surrounding territories, collect and process resources to not only improve the city, but also provide a happy life for your settlers.</description></item><item><title>Steel Division 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steel-division-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steel-division-2/</guid><description>Game Description Steel Division 2 is a real -time strategy, during which you will visit the role of Army General during the Bagration Operation. The plot was established during the Second World War on the Eastern Front, and there are thousands of fighters under your command. Thanks to an extensive list of opportunities, the gameplay can take you tens of hours. Pass the plot missions or participate in free mode in a multi -user or single game.</description></item><item><title>Pixark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pixark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pixark/</guid><description>Game Description Pixark is made in the style of the famous Maycraft, but the game has a good plot, which is revealed in different ways for each player. The world of wildlife includes more than 100 different creatures that we can clone, tame and use for our own purposes. Among them will be friendly inhabitants of the jungle, as well as aggressive representatives of the game world.
The mysterious lands made in the form of cubes are destroyed and built every minute.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Truckker: Extended Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-trucker-extended-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/galaxy-trucker-extended-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Galaxy Truckker: Extended Edition - a strategy about truckers from distant space. The gameplay was based on the same tough. You will build cosmic shuttles, evade asteroids and enter into battle with a huge number of enemies. The main task is to earn as many cosmicredites as possible.
The life of a cosmic trucker is not easy. The Galaxy Truckker game process: Extended Edition offers a branch scenario, the events of which depend on your moral elections.</description></item><item><title>Parkitect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parkitect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parkitect/</guid><description>Game Description The game is a simulator where the construction of the amusement park will be the main task. Parkitect surpasses the rest of the games of this genre due to tactical management, the economic component and entertainment, which the player can only dream of. Initially, you are given a small plot of land and a few resources. Your task, as a manager of this park, invite as many people as possible.</description></item><item><title>X4: Foundations</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x4-foundations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x4-foundations/</guid><description>Game Description In X4: Foundations you can create any spaceship, and then sit down for its helm and start to smash the enemies right and left. The first -person shooter with RPG and sandboxes combines several temporary eras enclosed in a couple of hours of game, but it is impossible to enjoy the gameplay of this project even in a week.
You can construct ships of different sizes and goals. It can be small scouts and large ships, wearing several hundred combat birds on their huge backs.</description></item><item><title>The Colonists</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</guid><description>Game Description The Colonists are a urban planning sandbox in which you control a team of robots that create themselves. In the game you do not have to fight or kill enemies. The plot side of the project is meditative. You are landing on the planet, begin to carry out non -difficult tasks in which you need to build a settlement, and then improve your town depending on the preferences. Also in the game there is a “free mode” - here you make an island yourself, plant robots, begin to build a city from the resources obtained.</description></item><item><title>Terraforming Mars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraforming-mars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terraforming-mars/</guid><description>Game Description Terraforming Mars is an official adaptation of the board game popular behind the ocean about the colonization of Mars and the transformation of this planet into suitable humanity habitat. The video game is presented in the form of a step -by -step strategy, where a sufficient amount of time is provided to think about further actions in order to extract maximum benefits. Game options are available both against artificial intelligence with several levels of complexity, and against people using the Internet, local network or one personal computer at a personal meeting of players.</description></item><item><title>Mashinky</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashinky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashinky/</guid><description>Game Description The strategic simulator - Mashinky - about how to create your own network of trains and cars that will bring you money, and in return you can modernize or send them to rest when buying new equipment. Around you are beautiful landscapes of the Czech Republic, Poland, Germany and England. The sun sits down, and floods the evening light of the forest and fields, granting nightlife to residents. In the game, a system of day, night and time in general is thought out.</description></item><item><title>On the Western Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</guid><description>Game Description On the Western Front - this is a tactical strategy, the action of which unfolds against the background of the First World War, namely on the infamous Western Front. Users take on the role of the division commander, who are instructed to manage various aspects of military operations in one of the most exhausting and complex periods in history. The Title emphasizes the harsh realities of the trench war, where the soldiers are faced with many problems, from the constant threat of enemy fire to the constant need to manage resources.</description></item><item><title>Mad Restaurant People</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</guid><description>Game Description Mad Restaurant People makes it possible to feel all the difficulty of working as a waiter. The game is presented with a top distance, which makes it possible to observe the entire hall at once. Take orders, serve customers, serve dishes in time, count the guests and much more. Mad Restaurant People is a full -fledged waiter’s simulator who will not let you relax for a second.
The gameplay requires attentiveness, reaction speed, good memory and many other important qualities.</description></item><item><title>Zero-K</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-k/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-k/</guid><description>Game Description Zero-K is a real-time strategy. The indie project allows for large-scale battles on land, water and in the air. This RTS has worked out physics and ballistics. During the battles, the landscape changes. You can even level the soil to your tactical needs. The game allows you to create funnels for enemy tanks, digging ditches and erecting embankments, hiding fighters behind the hills so that they are not taken by enemy shells, dig water channels for the passage of their fleet through land, put a soldier on a hill for better visibility and increase the range of shooting.</description></item><item><title>Tower of Time</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-time/</guid><description>Game Description At sunset, artara gradually open up new horizons of another world. Thousands of pages of books, manuscripts and video stations tell us the plot of Tower of Time through the prism of distant views on the plot from the game character. The new system in the RPG game is revealed from the first minutes of gameplay. We create a unique character who does not know what is happening in his world.</description></item><item><title>Farm Manager 2018</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-2018/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-2018/</guid><description>Game Description Farm Manager 2018 is a simulator for building your own farm, where the territory of your competitors will slowly go into your possessions. A change of day and nights was added to the game. Also, such cultures as cucumbers, apples, strawberries and other varieties were added to the new part. If you are tired of growing simple wheat or oats, then you can definitely change the direction, but do not forget to monitor the economy.</description></item><item><title>Through The Ages</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/through-the-ages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/through-the-ages/</guid><description>Game Description Through The Ages is a port of a cult board game adapted to personal computers. Compared to the original party in the digital version, they take much less time. Instead of 4-8 hours, a maximum of 1 hour takes the game session, since the computer is engaged in all calculations.
According to its concept, Through The Ages resembles the Titles of the Civilization series. Only here development occurs using various cards.</description></item><item><title>Bio Inc. Redemption</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bio-inc-redemption/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bio-inc-redemption/</guid><description>Game Description Bio Inc. Redemption is a biomedical simulator where a player has to choose life or death. These are 2 main regimes where you need to perform a variety of tasks. You are able to create deadly diseases, mocking a person presented on the screen. Or put on the medic&amp;rsquo;s mask and find the virus, look for the vaccine and save the infected ones.
The gameplay provides more than 600 diseases existing in the real world, accurate symptoms, diagnostic tests and various ways of treatment for each virus.</description></item><item><title>Northgard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/northgard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/northgard/</guid><description>Game Description The Scandinavian strategy of Northgard with a deepening into the ancient mythology of the Vikings, which found Nordgard - a city full of wealth, myths and ancient legends. The game combines the peaceful graphics and the gradual development of your settlement. However, the Vikings quickly cooled their ardor when they met with the first danger of Northgard - a brutal cold enveloping all the shores and heart of the island.</description></item><item><title>Grey Hack</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grey-hack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grey-hack/</guid><description>Game Description The multi -user game Grey Hack makes it possible to feel like a professional hacker. The player is accessible to complete freedom of action as a procedurally generated world web network. At the beginning of the game, only a few programs are available, including File Explorer, Text Editor and Terminal. As a hacker skill grows, many new utilities will appear and a wide range of opportunities will open.</description></item><item><title>Brigand: Oaxaca</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</guid><description>Game Description Brigand: Oaxaca is a first -person shooter hybrid, immersive simulator and role -playing game. The project has three -dimensional low -polygonal graphics. Due to her, the title resembles computer action of the late 90s and early 2000s. The action takes place in a world where nuclear apocalypse happened. Events unfold on the territory of the Mexican state of Ohak. Indi-game combines elements of different settings. In it, the gunshot weapons are adjacent to Voodoo magic, and not only mutters, but also demons roam the wastelands.</description></item><item><title>Revhead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revhead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revhead/</guid><description>Game Description In the REVHEAD car racing simulator, the user will have to design his own car. The protagonist has a friend named Charlie who is well versed in creating cars. He invites the central character to Australia to help him with something. It will be necessary to win the competition and get recognition from Charlie, then it will create improved transport.
There is an opportunity to sell and buy cars, as well as trade in various details and customization items.</description></item><item><title>Software Inc.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/software-inc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/software-inc/</guid><description>Game Description Software Inc. - An economic simulator that allows the development of a company engaged in the development of software. Initially, it is required to build an office building, buy inexpensive equipment and hire several employees, distributing tasks between them. To get funding, at first the newly made team will take on third -party projects and various simple tasks.
As the budget becomes more, the staff will be more experienced and new faces will come, it will also be possible to engage in the external design of the facade, build beautiful paths and decor items to give the office a presentable look.</description></item><item><title>Automation - The Car Company Tycoon Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automation-the-car-company-tycoon-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/automation-the-car-company-tycoon-game/</guid><description>Game Description Automation - The Car Company Tycoon Game is the simulator of the owner of the car concerns. A good product if you like to disassemble and redo cars in your own way. To design a car starting from the engine and ending with the suspension, body, as well as other parts. In this game there is a company where we will be the head of the campaign for the production of machines and will be part of the market from the end of World War II and now on our days.</description></item><item><title>Dynasty Warriors 8 Empires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dynasty-warriors-8-empires/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dynasty-warriors-8-empires/</guid><description>Game Description Alone, fighting thousands of enemies, and using the strategy and tactics of battles, the Dynasty Warriors 8 Empires player will be able to win all ancient China. There is no specific plot, but only scenarios, during which you can play in a certain period of time. In each of the episodes there is a separate distribution of territories, a set of heroes, which is at the start of the battle on the unification of the lands of China.</description></item><item><title>Dungeonmans</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeonmans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeonmans/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeonmans The Heroic Adventure Roguelike - a traditional horned in which you explore the dungeons, fight with a variety of monsters and collect lutus. You have to develop your academy in order to open new opportunities and skills. Go to the adventure and take part in step -by -step battles. A fascinating fantasy story awaits you, telling about the confrontation of good and evil.
Gameplay Dungeonmans The Heroic Adventure Roguelike:</description></item><item><title>Craft the World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</guid><description>Game Description Craft the World is an adventure 2D game that combines multiple elements. You can explore the procedurally generated worlds, build locks and fortresses, fight with hostile creatures and get materials necessary for numerous crafts.
Manage the dwarf tribe and lead them the way you want. The player can send his wards to extract resources, build structures or fight with opponents. But, not everything is so simple. You have to put them on, help in battles and feed them in time.</description></item><item><title>Gems of War - Puzzle RPG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-puzzle-rpg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-puzzle-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Gems of War - Puzzle RPG is a mixture of role -playing game and casual puzzle in the spirit of &amp;ldquo;three in a row&amp;rdquo; with KKI elements. Title came to a PC from mobile devices. The project has a single and multiplayer content. There is a PVP with a rating system, online tournaments, contractions with mobs, weekly events, quests, guilds, events for several players, mini-games, a story campaign where history is given through dialogue inserts.</description></item><item><title>Calyx</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/calyx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/calyx/</guid><description>Game Description Calyx is a real -time strategy that puts a player at the head of a remote space operation to mining. The main enemy is a group of alien organisms of plant origin, evolving and exciting the territory on the map in the absence of deterrence. The protagonist, the last acting member of the crew of the Avaris Corporation, after a centenary cryosn, must establish the current base on the surface of the planet.</description></item><item><title>Heroes of Might and Magic: Olden Era</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heroes-of-might-and-magic-olden-era/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heroes-of-might-and-magic-olden-era/</guid><description>Game Description Heroes of Might and Magic: Olden Era returns to the world of Enrot, inviting both veterans and new gamers to the strategic campaign on the continent of Jadam. This prequel returns to the origins of the determining genre and the recognition of critics of a series of step -by -step strategic games. Here, the rival factions should unite against the hive - the swarm of the insectoids, led by the master of the demons of Inferno.</description></item><item><title>Machine Mind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</guid><description>Game Description Machine Mind places the player in the role of consciousness transferred to a mechanical shell after the crash of a spaceship. The existence of a gamer is limited by the world, a changed planetary virus and subsequent nuclear conflict - the cataclysm, which forced the remnants of civilization to hide at the orbital station. Managing a series of rovers, it is necessary to provide its survival on the surface of the planet, now inhabited by aggressive raiders.</description></item><item><title>Solitaire Battle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</guid><description>Game Description Solitaire Battle combines the mechanics of the card game with the progression of the Autobatler&amp;rsquo;s Horned. Players are faced with opponents where key interaction is a party in the solitaire of three peaks. Each card taken from the field or from the deck is converted into an offensive or defensive action, creating automated combat sequences. The main task is to strategically disassemble the layout to win enemies, while forming a set of random pool of tools that contribute to powerful synergies and encouraging new combinations in each passage.</description></item><item><title>Space Spum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-scum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-scum/</guid><description>Game Description The squad in Space Scum is fighting for survival in a harsh, procedurally generated universe that allows any options. Each journey offers unique locations, hostile fractions and various missions formed by the background set by the player, and his subsequent actions. Any solution entails consequences, directly affecting the path of the company as part of the structure of the open world. Moving between different planets, the team will face the events and goals that organically arise from the choice made and determining its own history.</description></item><item><title>The X-Com Files</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-x-com-files/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:42 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-x-com-files/</guid><description>Game Description The X -Com Files is a global modification for the same step -by -step strategy that allows you to see how all the events of the franchise began. The game transfers in 1996. The organization of x-hk is only born. The tasks of employees include an investigation of abnormal incidents. Stylistics is inspired by the series secret materials. It will be necessary to manage two special agents, moving in regular transport.</description></item><item><title>Openrct2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/openrct2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/openrct2/</guid><description>Game Description Openrct2 brings an interesting turn to the world of creating entertainment parks. Being a rethinking of Rollercoaster Tycoon 2, it goes beyond the original, offering a wider range of opportunities and corrections. Open source code means that gamers can plunge into the game and study all the tools for free, without any conditions. Thanks to the open community of developers, it is constantly developing, which means that new ideas and improvements will always be at hand.</description></item><item><title>Command &amp; Conquer: Dawn of the Tiberium Age</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/command-amp-conquer-dawn-of-the-tiberium-age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:27 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/command-amp-conquer-dawn-of-the-tiberium-age/</guid><description>Game Description Dawn of the Tiberium Age can be attributed to atypical mods for the game Command &amp;amp; Conquer: Tiberian Sun. The purpose of this project is to combine two universes together. In one of them, Albert Enstein changes the course of time, which affects history and leads to an open confrontation between Russians and West. In another, the organization created by the UN and the secret ancient society fight, while an alien substance that destroys the biosphere spreads on the Earth.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Cits</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</guid><description>Game Description Ancient Cits - a strategic game based on survival and construction mechanics. The game transfers in ancient times when people lived in tribes and built the first settlements. Plunge in prehistoric times and find the primitive life of our ancestors and their ancient cities. Events develop in the era of mesolithic.
Draw your settlers through a whole generation, improving technologies, mastering new tools, engaged in resources, developing the population and fighting external threats.</description></item><item><title>Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth abandoned long walks and romantic novels with stars that are found in other farm sigas. It’s enough just to click a cursor. The Title with a strategic farm bias with your head immerses you in the creation, construction, collection and management of a prosperous farm. Starting from a modest site, do not allow the initial sizes to deceive you. Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth is all about potential.</description></item><item><title>Coral Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coral-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/coral-island/</guid><description>Game Description Coral Island is a classic farm simulator that transports you to a tropical island where you will grow crops, care for living creatures and communicate with secondary characters. Your task is to create your own farm, to gradually expand the territory, to acquire new seedlings and animals. There are 16 characters with which you are able to build relationships and even create a couple.
It all starts with how you leave Pokier, after which you go to the coral island to build a farm in a paradise.</description></item><item><title>Dustland Delivery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</guid><description>Game Description Dustland Delivery puts users in the post -apocalyptic world, where they have to build an empire of delivery. The center of the game is profit, survival and strategic decisions. Gamers start with a truck and gain a team, each of which has unique skills. The purpose of the game? Build cities by successful delivery of goods, competing with rivals and overcoming dangers. The world is inexorable. Users move in an insidious area, control resources and make a critical choice.</description></item><item><title>Empire of the Ants</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empire-of-the-ants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empire-of-the-ants/</guid><description>Game Description Empire of the Ants is an amazing strategy that will transfer gamers to the exciting world of infinitely small creatures. You have to lead your ants and lead to prosperity, protecting it from numerous dangers and winning new territories. You will explore various areas and get acquainted with amazing representatives of the local fauna. However, be careful: other ants and residents of the forest that can become enemies will meet on your way.</description></item><item><title>From the Depths</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</guid><description>Game Description From the Depths allows you to accept command of battleships, aircraft, submarines, space ships, balloons and many other modes of transport. The story campaign will visit more than a hundred lands and fight against 8 fractions. Misses consist in planning competent tactics and protecting your own fleet in a series of difficult tests. In addition to the main campaign, there is an adventure mode where it will be proposed to start the game alone on a small ship and grow to a whole fleet, furrows the expanses of the universe.</description></item><item><title>Let's Build a Zoo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</guid><description>Game Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Zoo - A bright sandbox with a simulator elements, which provides players with the opportunity to build their own zoo. It is required to install enclosures, buy rare animals, hire employees for service and much more. It is allowed to cross animal DNA, producing more than 300,000 unique rocks into the world.
In order for the reserve to function, it will be necessary to hire veterinarians, trainers, cleaners, repairmen and other performers who support their lives in the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Maze: Path of Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maze-path-of-light/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maze-path-of-light/</guid><description>Game Description Maze: Path of Light offers thousands of separate labyrinths for passing. The puzzles are placed on geometric fields of various shapes, including square, round, triangular and hexagonal. Players will face unique contours of structures resembling the outlines of fish, guitars and trees. This single title uses the view from the top to move along the cell card. The essence of the gameplay is to solve such logical riddles at numerous levels.</description></item><item><title>Microcivilization</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microcivilization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/microcivilization/</guid><description>Game Description Microcivilization - a hybrid of the genres of an incremental clker and a strategy - offers players a dynamic gameplay. A unique combination of expansion, construction, research, battles and gathering heroes allows you to solve multifaceted problems. The narrative unfolds in a campaign mode, during which players pass various historical scenarios - from ancient times to a futuristic setting. A distinctive feature of the game is the ascension mechanism that allows players to lose their progress and start everything from the clean sheet.</description></item><item><title>Operator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</guid><description>Game Description Operator is an exciting game where you become a secret operative performing dangerous tasks around the world. A realistic experience of tactical battle awaits you, where your every decision matters. The game contains a unique system of physical interaction, which allows you to manipulate objects and weapons naturally. This adds a feeling of presence and realism, without the need to use VR-Schles.
A special emphasis in the operator is placed on a multi -user cooperative regime.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item><item><title>Soul Apocalypto</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-apocalypto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-apocalypto/</guid><description>Game Description Soul Apocalypto is a role -playing game that includes systems of several strategic sucks. The gameplay combines team battles with the collecting of creatures and some mechanics of collecting decks, with a view of both from above and from a third party. The main lesson is the call of various companions for creating a personalized combat detachment. Progress directly depends on the choice of these fighters and their layout in a group that can explore the open world.</description></item><item><title>Soul of the Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-of-the-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soul-of-the-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Soul of the Dungeon is an action with a view of the top, which makes the opponents resist the hordes in a hostile location. The gameplay is tied to survival in a series of attacks, collecting gold from defeated enemies and investing resources in pumping skills. Such progress is necessary, because each next wave is complicated, introducing more formidable rivals. The key task is built on constant adaptation and honing of combat techniques for the confrontation of the growing threat.</description></item><item><title>Sunrider Legends Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Sunrider Legends Tactics will put a player at the head of the Navy leading his ships along the seas of the fantasy world in the era of sails. You have to command the courts in step -by -step battles, making tactical decisions on maneuvers, positioning and the use of weapons against enemy armades. The adventure will require solving strategic problems in the open sea and participation in special plot events.</description></item><item><title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Splintered Fate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-splintered-fate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-splintered-fate/</guid><description>Game Description Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Splintered Fate immerses players in a Roguelike adventure, in the center of which are your favorite ninja turtles. Here, gamers take on the roles of Leonardo, Michelangelo, Donatello and Raphael, each of which is endowed with certain abilities. The narrative begins with the abduction of their mentor, Splinter, an evil Shredder. This laid the foundation for the study of various areas of New York, full of difficulties and enemies hiding behind each angle.</description></item><item><title>Terratech Worlds</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terratech-worlds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terratech-worlds/</guid><description>Game Description In TerRatech Worlds, you will plunge with your head in a PVE survival with the open world on the mysterious planet of aliens. Put your way as a free prospector, exploring an extensive environment with an area of ​​300 km² with a variety of bioms, dynamic weather and a day/night cycle. To confront the hostile flora and fauna, rival fractions and insidious areas - and at the same time use the power of the planet in their interests.</description></item><item><title>Train Sim World 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-sim-world-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/train-sim-world-6/</guid><description>Game Description Train Sim World 6 proposes to master three unique international railway networks. Players have to work on an electrified American line NJ Transit Morristown, driving the ARROW III EMU electric trains and Alp-46 locomotives. The route of the English Riviera includes the GWR coasts on the coasts of the Internet on the Intercity Class 802 trains. The German section of Bahnstrecke Leipzig - Dresden allows passenger and freight transportation according to the oldest long -distance highway in modern equipment, such as ICE -T and BR 442.</description></item><item><title>Vault of the void</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vault-of-the-void/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vault-of-the-void/</guid><description>Game Description Vault of the Void is a well -planning contractions, where users need to collect abyss stones and make their way through the fantasy worlds of emptiness. We&amp;rsquo;ll have to fight against various monsters and aggressive creatures that penetrate the universe of people. The game is an atmospheric map of the Rowlaik project, where the users will be able to influence the storyline and the events taking place with their actions and decisions during the passage.</description></item></channel></rss>