<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>strategies on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/</link><description>Recent content in strategies on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chosen War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chosen-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chosen-war/</guid><description>Game Description Chosen War puts the player in the role of the chosen one who is instructed to gather and novels the army in the archipelago. It is necessary to move around the fogs covered in fog and enter into battle with enemy forces using the tactical placement of detachments. Each adventure is built around the study of the world and provisions. The ultimate goal is a collision with the supreme priest on the final location.</description></item><item><title>Frog Jump</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frog-jump/</guid><description>Game Description Frog Jump puts players under the control of amphibians with the aim of vertical climbing through the three -dimensional world. They have to move according to a complex design, using jumps and climbing to go from one site to another. The entire level is designed around this movement up, representing a continuous navigation task. The first princess’s kiss receives a victory that reached the top.
This platformer can be held alone or in a multi -user competition for 8 competitors over the network.</description></item><item><title>Click and Conquer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</guid><description>Game Description Click and Conquer represents a resource management system through military operations. The main gameplay is based on the discharge of bombs on the grid to detect disguised enemy detachments. Each opened unit brings currency that serves as a central resource for further development. The received funds are distributed to increase passive income and an increase in the destructive force of each ammunition. The cycle of expenses and savings determines the promotion of the player at affordable stages.</description></item><item><title>BellFortis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</guid><description>Game Description In BellFortis, the action takes place in the early Middle Ages, where users seek to expand their kingdoms and influence the course of history. Title combines step -by -step strategic planning and real -time battles, which gives you the opportunity to control the army and make decisions that affect the world. Would you like to build a strong empire with the help of diplomacy or strength - the choice is yours.</description></item><item><title>Rugby League Team Manager 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</guid><description>Game Description Rugby League Team Manager 4 puts you at the head of the regional club. The circle of your tasks is covered by financial management, negotiations with sponsors and the selection of the state of assistants, mentors and medical staff. You have to improve infrastructure, including the stadium, gym and training fields. This project covers 226 teams from the Northern and Southern Hems, and over 7,000 adult players are available for choice.</description></item><item><title>Nitro Gen Omega</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nitro-gen-omega/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nitro-gen-omega/</guid><description>Game Description Nitro Gen Omega represents the world where cars dominate the landscape after the lost war of mankind. Survivor people are huddled in cities erected on giant supports, so the mercenaries teams are forced to travel to dangerous wastelands. The player originates under his beginning to one of these detachments, based on a flying ship to complete tasks for the supply of resources and technologies. The task is to study this world, the leadership of a detachment and control of combat fur.</description></item><item><title>Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimstar-crystals-are-the-new-oil/</guid><description>Game Description Grimstar: Crystals Are the New Oil! - This is an exciting strategy in real time, in which you will go to study the distant world called Grimstar, where you will find a new type of natural energy resources. But not everything is so rosy and sunny - because of your brother’s sudden death, you have to fulfill his contract with the corporation for which he worked, and you must take his place on an alien planet.</description></item><item><title>IDLE WATERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</guid><description>Game Description IDLE WATERS is a game in the IDLE-Rybank genre that works from the window at the bottom of the screen and is designed to simultaneously work with other computer operations. The game window has flexibility: it can be scale, change the layout, change the size and move to any part of the desktop or completely hide. This system allows the simulator to function without requiring constant attention from the gamer.</description></item><item><title>VOID War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</guid><description>Game Description Void War puts a player at the head of an ancient starship, sending him on a journey to the heart of a dying empire. This ship is described as a powerful and formidable gun filled with secret technologies. The tasks include the reflection of the attacks of crazy cultists, cowardly cosmopirates and xenophobic imperial soldiers. The detection of powerful artifacts allows you to turn a starship into a frightening combat vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Fuga: Melodies of Steel 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</guid><description>Game Description fuga: Melodies of Steel 3 unfolds the story of desperate efforts. The inexplicable disappearance of Malta forces the group of children to head to the forbidden cave, where they are leaded by a mysterious voice to Taranis - a powerful armored vehicle, which was considered lost. The determination to find Malta returns them aboard this combat vehicle, starting a direct attack on the central regions of the Berman Empire.</description></item><item><title>SOL CESTO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sol-cesto/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sol-cesto/</guid><description>Game Description SOL CESTO is a swift route that encounter a strategy and accident. Gamers fall into the world shrouded in secrets, and seek to get to the depths of the dungeon in search of a long -lost sun. The dungeon is generated randomly, which means that there are no two identical travels. Each floor is divided into four rooms, and you have to decide which one to enter, never knowing what awaits the door.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>9 kings</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-kings/</guid><description>Game Description 9 Kings throws users into the very heart of the medieval kingdom, where the strategy, tactics and resource management dictates the need for survival. This urban planning Roguelike combines a lot of a mechanic, offering unpredictable experience with each launch. The expansion of the kingdom requires careful planning, because the power of the empire depends on each decision. Using a deck of various cards, rulers form their possessions, adapting to unexpected challenges.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Monster Train 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-train-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-train-2/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Train 2 offers a dynamic and strategic approach to creating decks in Roguelike. Users control powerful clans on board the train, laying their way through a chaotic setting filled with demons, angels and threats of titans. As the plot develops, the gamer has several levels of composition, each of which provides unique tasks and opportunities to improve their collection.
The gameplay emphasizes the importance of tactical choice, requiring thorough planning and quick thinking to defeat more and more complex enemies.</description></item><item><title>Monster Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Battles is a tactical auto-batler with equipment control. In this project, participants collect, unite and strategically place a group of creatures for upcoming fights. These creatures are purchased in a special store and then are placed on a certain battlefield before the start of an automatic fight. An effective selection and location of a variety of combat units forms the basis of the game cycle.
In Monster Battles, building a successful detachment requires thoroughly accounting for the features and belonging of the collected creatures.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>Age of Reforming: The Frelands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-reforging-the-freelands/</guid><description>Game Description Age of reforging: The Frelands is a cruel world of the Middle Ages in an alternative world where magic exists, and the gods are quite real and if they are enough to pray and make generous gifts, they can even bless the asking person. There reigns tyranny and lawlessness, and survival is being built in trade. The more successful the seller, the easier he lives, the rest was terribly unlucky.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Mogul 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Mogul 4 — это текстовый бизнес-симулятор, ставящий человека во главе киностудии. Система позволяет создавать кинофильмы и мини-сериалы на основе библиотеки из более чем 14 000 исходных материалов или собственных идей. Ready -made paintings can be planned for global film distribution or for distribution through streaming service. The process includes the formation of accurate budgets, the conclusion of agreements on rental in 19 foreign territories and the management of advertising expenses.</description></item><item><title>Synergy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</guid><description>Game Description synergy dedicated to survival on a hostile planet. In this urban planning strategy, players have to develop their city, face natural cataclysms and make the right decisions that will certainly have consequences. Explore this constantly changing world, preserving the happiness of the townspeople in extreme weather conditions.
Gamers will control the weather, seasons, extreme conditions and natural disasters. The main goal is to build a city where residents will be happy and satisfied, respecting the natural needs of the inhabitants and living in harmony with the local fauna and flora.</description></item><item><title>Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</guid><description>Game Description Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers calls the gamarines into a world filled with more than 180 creatures who need to collect, fight and develop. The Title combines the elements of autoboeviks, rogeliks and card battles, allowing users to develop unique strategies. The purpose of the game is to assemble the KDOMON team, each of which has various abilities and types in order to pass more and more difficult tests. As you pass, you will encounter powerful bosses and open rare monsters with special abilities.</description></item><item><title>Pocket City 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket City 2 makes it possible for players to build cities, and then study their first -person creations. The process starts from the laying of roads, the markings of sections for residential, commercial or industrial needs and the construction of the necessary objects on the map. Control over the economy implies monitoring of stocks, profit and a thoughtful placement of special structures, access to which opens as they move.</description></item><item><title>Kaiserpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Kaiserpunk throws you headlong into an alternative XX century, instructing to build an empire from scratch. This is not Grandfather&amp;rsquo;s Urban planner - Title offers a grandiose strategy, demanding from you to win a vast card, while preserving the residents happy, and the factory - working. Does it sound like a high task? This is true. Forget that you can just put at home and finish it on this.</description></item><item><title>Astronomics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</guid><description>Game Description In Astronomics, gamers are sent to study the space and the production of asteroids. You have to move through randomly generated asteroids, extract resources and manage a developing enterprise. At first, the whole thing is assembling materials on asteroids flying past, but as it moves forward, automation becomes a key factor. With workers and command bots, at your disposal, the tasks for which the clock used to go, can be completed much faster.</description></item><item><title>Heart of the Machine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</guid><description>Game Description Heart of the Machine outwardly resembles a town -planning Taikun. But in fact, the project is something like a god of God with elements of tactics and strategy in real time. Only here the Juzer is assigned the role of not a divine being, which owns magic, but artificial intelligence. This video game has a science fiction setting. Its action takes place in a distant and gloomy future in the territory of the metropolis-colonies.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</guid><description>Game Description Space Engineers 2 returns to the world of space development with updated experience. In this continuation, you will have a new adventure in the Almagest system, where engineering tasks and spaces of space are combined in the most unexpected way. This is a sandbox with an open world in which you can build from scratch - or, rather, from stars - from starships to entire space stations. The goal is simple: to raise your creative potential to a new height, while managing the difficulties of survival in the cold, inexorable spaces of space.</description></item><item><title>Learning Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</guid><description>Game Description learning factory - a simulator that is designed to create an automated process of processes and, most importantly, understand one simple truth: what do cats want? The gameplay allows you to head the Kotovod factory. It was once closed, but now it has been possible to renew the process and create your own cat store. Learning factory gameplay largely gives an idea of ​​how machine learning works.
Your factory is analyzing a huge database, trying to study the behavior of pets.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Age of Darkness: Final Stand</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-darkness-final-stand/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-darkness-final-stand/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Darkness: Final Stand is a real -time strategy focused on survival among the preemptive number of opponents. The player will take control over the last bastion of mankind to fight with the hordes of nightmares. The monsters crawl out from the mysterious poisonous fog. The rivals have already destroyed all large cities and are ready to take control of the planet. The user decides where to act and how to apply the remnants of mankind.</description></item><item><title>Urban Strife</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-strife/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-strife/</guid><description>Game Description Urban Strife actions take place in the post-apocalyptic world, and the gameplay is presented in the style of the old-school TBS. The main character lives in a dangerous environment, where every resident does everything, for his own benefit. The resources are running out, there is no work, and the majority kills and robs to survive. The player can enter into alliances, choosing 1 of several fractions, automatically becoming an enemy for other groups.</description></item><item><title>Caves of QUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-qud/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of QUD-A game in the sling genre with an unusual mixture of styles, such as: fantasy (ordinary swords and bows as a weapon of murders, are combined with magic and marvelous creatures), post-apocalypse and science fiction. A feature will be the choice of a protagonist before the start of each new preservation with his bonuses. The mutant receives unlimited scope for various modifications, by obtaining changes in his DNA, in other words, mutations, among which there is a second heart, second head, wings, claws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Zephon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in Zephon have to take control of the remnants of mankind in order to survive on the territory of the Earth. On the planet, there are few areas that are not suitable for life, and most of the cities were destroyed. In wild territories are mutating creatures that they gather in small groups and begin to hunt for surviving people. Alien robots with damaged systems roam on the surface, and the aliens themselves are hidden and try to secure survival.</description></item><item><title>Citadelum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</guid><description>Game Description Citadelum throws its hat to the ring of strategic games, offering the experience of building cities with an admixture of mythology and strategic conquests. Ancient Rome serves as a background for the game: gamers take control of a nascent settlement and should turn it into a lively metropolis. Resource management is a paramount task for any novice urban planner. But Citadelum is not only overgrown suburbs and towering monuments.</description></item><item><title>Eden Crafters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</guid><description>Game Description Eden Crafters throws glove in the hands of survival and automation lovers. In this cooperative adventure with the open world, players will turn to turn a hostile planet into a hospitable refuge for humanity. Think about this as a space project of reconstruction - harsh conditions, fluids of the house of dreams. Task? Overcome the unpleasant habits of the planet and build a new house for humanity. Imagine radioactive zones and insidious landscapes are not the best real estate.</description></item><item><title>Liar's bar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</guid><description>Game Description Liar&amp;rsquo;s Bar is a multi -user online game, whose action takes place in a bar, where deception and strategy play a key role. Users are united at tables of four people to take part in games such as Liar&amp;rsquo;s Dice and Liar&amp;rsquo;s Deck. The goal is to outwit rivals using bliff and strategic moves. Each session is filled with stress, as gamers are trying to unravel each other&amp;rsquo;s intentions and make the right moves to win.</description></item><item><title>Endzone 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</guid><description>Game Description Endzone 2 throws you into the thick of the post -apocalyptic world. Humanity died, and you remained to collect fragments - literally. Each decision that you make as if you can send your scattered colony by the line. Lack of resources? Eat. Danger to the environment? Do not hesitate. Ruthless raiders eager to steal your lunch? Undoubtedly. This is not a simple walk. This is the management of your nascent civilization.</description></item><item><title>Toy Shire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-shire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-shire/</guid><description>Game Description Toy Shire revives a children&amp;rsquo;s room in a strategic battle. Bluespy Studios came up with this curious name by putting the player in the role of a defender. No pistols or grenades. Instead, plastic warriors and cardboard fortresses dominate the battlefield. The territory of the child is becoming a zone of hostilities. Tables, corners and floor of the bedroom turn into strategic landscapes. Gamers erect toy towers, these bizarre structures built from childhood residues.</description></item><item><title>ODD Realm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</guid><description>Game Description ODD Realm is a game that combines both the strategy and the survival simulator. The player will have to take on the role of the leader of a small settlement and provide residents with the necessary resources, houses, as well as protect their subjects from bloodthirsty enemies and dishonest bandits from a high road. The variability of the development of the plot provides the gamer with wide opportunities for the construction of the city of his own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-dungeon-awaits/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon-Dungeon AWAITS is a step-by-step game where survival depends on spatial thinking. Each enemy and type of weapons act according to a unique scheme on the battlefield, forming a tactical environment from intersecting zones of defeat. Success is maneuvering for the operation of enemy vulnerability, while trying to cover the maximum area with his own arsenal. Any movement, the use of an object or attack completes the move, giving opponents the opportunity to deliver a response.</description></item><item><title>Tendryll</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tendryll/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tendryll/</guid><description>Game Description Tendryll uses tactical battles on the grid as part of a horny structure, where players go through a series of enemies. You have to command a detachment of heroes, which requires careful coordination of their unique skills to survive in every clash. The battlefield itself poses a threat due to a distorting map of the area, which directly affects the characters' hands, imposing a curse on their ability.</description></item><item><title>Nordic ashes: Survivors of Ragnarok</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nordic-ashes-survivors-of-ragnarok/</guid><description>Game Description Nordic ashes: survivors of ragnarok - Dynamic adventure with elements of action and simplified cuckle. The plot is inspired by Scandinavian legends and motives. The main character finds himself in a dangerous environment in which he will face hordes of enemy and deadly creatures. He needs to stay alive among hundreds of opponents and traps, gradually pumping his abilities and finding more powerful equipment.
The central character will move between worlds, fight with powerful bosses, overcome traps and find objects of equipment.</description></item><item><title>Keeperrl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keeperrl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keeperrl/</guid><description>Game Description Keeperrl is a simulator with elements of a slide in which it is necessary to build an underground base and develop society. You play for a powerful wizard studying black magic. Teach minions to military affairs, forcing to attack civilians of settlements, taking their belongings and burning to the ground at home.
Engage in the construction of the dungeons, arrange traps and build up military power to storm miserable people.</description></item><item><title>Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dino-hazard-chronos-blackout/</guid><description>Game Description Dino Hazard: Chronos Blackout - an adventure action in which a group of people falls on a tropical island equipped with high -tech objects. The territory is governed by AI, which produces a huge number of combat robots and artificially nurtures of dinosaurs. The game is made in the Cyberpanus setting and contains elements of metroid.
Once on the island, it must be examined by opening the results of a monstrous experiment.</description></item><item><title>Lost Hope: Backrooms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-hope-backrooms/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Hope: BackRooms offers a single first -person adventure in the alarming locations of backstage. Key classes include navigation for these confusing, interconnected places and active interaction with the environment for solving logical puzzles, which contributes to the development of the main plot. The area often demonstrates strange and inexplicable phenomena, which are difficult to immediately comprehend. Gamers have to carefully study these elements in order to reveal the secrets hidden in this tense journey.</description></item><item><title>Railgrade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</guid><description>Game Description Railgrade gameplay combines elements of strategy and construction. The plot covers the times of the great construction of railways around the world in order to connect fast transportation between foreign cities with valuable industry. The main character will save the future of mankind, since he is the last employee of the earth colony. Megacorporations asked him to fulfill a difficult mission and save everything that remained on the planet after the disaster that occurred due to errors in the calculations of management.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the White Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of the White Sun transfers to the chaos of China of the 1920s, the period of riots and fragmented leadership. In this grandiose strategic game, you have to pave the way through a fragmented nation controlled by military leaders, rebels and political groups. The action unfolds at a time when various groups dispute control of vast territories and armies, each of which has its own goals, objectives and motives.</description></item><item><title>High Sea Saga DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</guid><description>Game Description High Sea Saga DX immerses players in the marine environment, focused on the accumulation of wealth and global research. In this Title, gamers control the pirate team crossing the oceans in search of hidden treasures scattered through a variety of geographical zones. Each such journey entails a clash with various wild creatures and battles with warring pirate fractions that pursue similar goals. Success requires the collection of an effective detachment and the construction of a swimming agent, ready for long -term crossings by open waters.</description></item><item><title>Railway Empire 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</guid><description>Game Description Railway Empire 2 is a transport strategy that offers to go into the past, at the beginning of the 19th century, and lead a small railway company, which will become the leader of the economy thanks to steam cars. Here you have to compete with competitors and build a network of railways, which will connect cities and companies throughout the continent. At your disposal 60 famous steam machines that pull freight and passenger cars, opening the historically significant era of the time of the industrial revolution.</description></item><item><title>Darkest Dungeon 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</guid><description>Game Description Darkest Dungeon II, exciting and tense Roguelike-game, immerses players in the nightmare world, standing on the verge of an apocalypse. In the game, you have to become a brave leader, assemble a detachment, equip your faithful diligyans and go on a difficult journey through a destroying landscape. Plunging into the abyss, you will soon find that the most terrible threat may come from your detachment.
The combat system, known for its innovations in the original Darkest Dungeon, triumphantly returns to the sequel.</description></item><item><title>Silica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silica/</guid><description>Game Description Silica is a dynamic alloy of action and a science fiction strategy that revolves around a fierce struggle for power over a Baltarus, a planet who is replete with quartz crystals, desired for all fractions. Players can manage their armies as commanders from orbit or plunge into battle with their heads as an infantry, vehicles or various insect -like aliens.
Silica allows gamers to choose their game style without limiting them to specific rules.</description></item><item><title>DREADFUL River</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadful-river/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dreadful-river/</guid><description>Game Description DREADFUL River is an arcade rafting simulator on the river on a raft with elements of role -playing play, action and tactics. The project was carried out in medieval setting. The plot tie begins with the attack of enemies on the kingdom. While the enemies are storming the castle, the king with a small group of the most faithful guards goes in search of an eternal crown, about which different legends go.</description></item><item><title>Caves of Lore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of lore-role-playing game with two-dimensional pixel art style graphics and from above. Moving by locations occurs in real time. During the study of the area, you can neutralize traps, look for secrets and hack chests with loot. Equipment can be of different colors. Coloring depends on the rarity of the object. There are hundreds of things here. Battles with monsters are held in step -by -step mode. In battle, heroes can move around the cells.</description></item><item><title>Winter Falling: Battle Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Falling: Battle Tactics invites gamers to lead the troops and lead them to victory in the most stressful and tactical battles. And only your mind can save the dying world from devastation. You control a detachment of mercenaries, collect supplies and troops, perform tasks and even you can burn villages if you decide that you need it. But do not forget that all your actions have consequences.</description></item><item><title>Out of Ore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</guid><description>Game Description In Out of Ore, gamers have to take many heavy equipment under their control, with the help of which it will be possible to extract ore, move the ground, dig pits, build or repair buildings and much more. It is necessary to test yourself as a driver of construction equipment, which is intended for various purposes. The main character goes on the plot for the very north of the country where there is a small base from Company Mining Corp.</description></item><item><title>Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/symphony-of-war-the-nephilim-saga/</guid><description>Game Description Symphony of War: The Nephilim Saga tells about the events that erupted after the conflict between the Empire of Veridia and Tanra. They fought for a long time, and in the end all these events led to the fact that the first empire remained in losses. However, thanks to the young ruler of Florin, a shaky, but peace finally formed. Everyone began to gradually recover until something terrible happened.</description></item><item><title>Venture Towns</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</guid><description>Game Description Venture Towns allows players to build a city landscape. This project transfers to the gamers the corporation forming a settlement. From the initial structures to vast skyscrapers, the player leads the development, striving for economic superiority. The game emphasizes the deliberate arrangement of various architectural elements, contributing to a systematic approach to urbanistic growth and current economic activity.
In Venture Towns, the processes of the construction of objects open the ways for development.</description></item><item><title>Polimines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/polimines/</guid><description>Game Description Thanks to** Polimines** you can try to swing your own intelligence, as well as strangle to strain your brains. Yes, this is a head-headed game in which the levels will need to go through the locations. But it will not be at all as easy as it might seem at first glance. Therefore, it will be necessary to make all your efforts, as well as understand the basic principle.</description></item><item><title>City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</guid><description>Game Description City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV is a strategic simulator in which it is important not only to chase the demand of players, but also be able to reduce expenses and vice versa, be able to spend money where they are actually needed. Games developers presented a simulator in which you will have to develop a company that develops games. A small studio creating video games decided to expand, so you must make every effort to create a whole headquarters of developers who can satisfy the needs of modern gamers.</description></item><item><title>The Doors of Trithius</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</guid><description>Game Description The Doors of Trithius is a RPG -Rogalik in the fantasy world with procedurally generated content. Here you have to fight monsters, avoid traps, collect prey and much more, traveling along the mysterious world of Enalia. Every time you start the game, you have to explore the new generated city, dungeon and map of the world. Movement and battle use a unique time system, returning the priority of the player based on the speed of weapons or action, maintaining tactical decisions, as well as knowledge about your enemies.</description></item><item><title>Going Medieval</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</guid><description>Game Description Going Medieval is a simulator in which you need to build a fortress on the ruins of an old castle and equip it to protect your settlement. Any event can affect the mood of your people, so you need to satisfy all their needs and be a good king. Events unfold in the era of the dark Middle Ages of the late XIV century.
Only five percent of the population survived after a heavy plague epidemic.</description></item><item><title>Kakatte Koi Yo!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kakatte-koi-yo/</guid><description>Game Description kakatte koi yo! - This is a two -dimensional action platform with the possibility of local multiplayer. This is a real cat’s battle, in which you have to take control of powerful cats and master even more powerful fish to defeat your opponents in a fierce 2D platform battle. This game with charming aesthetics in the Japanese style and irresistibly cute characters is an obligatory game for any cat lover.</description></item><item><title>Easy Red 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</guid><description>Game Description Easy Red 2 is a first -person shooter with elements of a strategy that immerses in an authentic atmosphere of World War II. The gameplay can plunge into tense and cruel battles, where the main thing is planning and tactics. The gameplay relies on realism. Take a break through the tanks and the enemy’s huge army. Do not fall into the explosion zone and look for ways to survive on the battlefield with your partners.</description></item><item><title>Ostriv</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</guid><description>Game Description OSTRIV, this is a city -building simulator that makes you the ruler of the monarch of the 18th century. The player will have to work hard and show his ability to the manager, as well as creative abilities. The goal of the game to transfer the gameplay of simulators of this kind to a new level, by means of adding a huge number of opportunities and abandoning the usual restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Hex of Steel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hex-of-steel/</guid><description>Game Description Players in Hex of Steel have to go during the Second World War, where you will have to control the troops on land, water and in the air. The project is a full -scale Vargam, where you have to perform step -by -step actions on the global map of the world, which includes Europe, Africa and the Pacific regions. Users will be able to fight against AI in a single campaign or special historical scenarios, as well as in the cross -platform mode of PBEM and multiplayer skirmishes against other users (there is the possibility of cooperative passage).</description></item><item><title>On the Western Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</guid><description>Game Description On the Western Front - this is a tactical strategy, the action of which unfolds against the background of the First World War, namely on the infamous Western Front. Users take on the role of the division commander, who are instructed to manage various aspects of military operations in one of the most exhausting and complex periods in history. The Title emphasizes the harsh realities of the trench war, where the soldiers are faced with many problems, from the constant threat of enemy fire to the constant need to manage resources.</description></item><item><title>Mad Restaurant People</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</guid><description>Game Description Mad Restaurant People makes it possible to feel all the difficulty of working as a waiter. The game is presented with a top distance, which makes it possible to observe the entire hall at once. Take orders, serve customers, serve dishes in time, count the guests and much more. Mad Restaurant People is a full -fledged waiter’s simulator who will not let you relax for a second.
The gameplay requires attentiveness, reaction speed, good memory and many other important qualities.</description></item><item><title>Heroes of Might and Magic: Olden Era</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heroes-of-might-and-magic-olden-era/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heroes-of-might-and-magic-olden-era/</guid><description>Game Description Heroes of Might and Magic: Olden Era returns to the world of Enrot, inviting both veterans and new gamers to the strategic campaign on the continent of Jadam. This prequel returns to the origins of the determining genre and the recognition of critics of a series of step -by -step strategic games. Here, the rival factions should unite against the hive - the swarm of the insectoids, led by the master of the demons of Inferno.</description></item><item><title>Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth abandoned long walks and romantic novels with stars that are found in other farm sigas. It’s enough just to click a cursor. The Title with a strategic farm bias with your head immerses you in the creation, construction, collection and management of a prosperous farm. Starting from a modest site, do not allow the initial sizes to deceive you. Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth is all about potential.</description></item><item><title>Let's Build a Zoo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</guid><description>Game Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Zoo - A bright sandbox with a simulator elements, which provides players with the opportunity to build their own zoo. It is required to install enclosures, buy rare animals, hire employees for service and much more. It is allowed to cross animal DNA, producing more than 300,000 unique rocks into the world.
In order for the reserve to function, it will be necessary to hire veterinarians, trainers, cleaners, repairmen and other performers who support their lives in the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item><item><title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Splintered Fate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-splintered-fate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-splintered-fate/</guid><description>Game Description Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Splintered Fate immerses players in a Roguelike adventure, in the center of which are your favorite ninja turtles. Here, gamers take on the roles of Leonardo, Michelangelo, Donatello and Raphael, each of which is endowed with certain abilities. The narrative begins with the abduction of their mentor, Splinter, an evil Shredder. This laid the foundation for the study of various areas of New York, full of difficulties and enemies hiding behind each angle.</description></item></channel></rss>