<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Strategy on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategy/</link><description>Recent content in Strategy on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Plants vs. Zombies: Replanted</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-replanted/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-replanted/</guid><description>Game Description Plants vs. Zombies Replanted is a tactical survival test where every defeat forces you to start all over again. In a special mode called Rest in Peace, players will have to face the consequences of their mistakes without the right to correct them, because the mechanics of permanent death return you to the very beginning of the journey. The conditions for completing each race are determined by the eccentric character Crazy Dave, who provides a limited and sometimes completely random set of plants for defense.</description></item><item><title>Becastled</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/becastled/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/becastled/</guid><description>Game Description Becastled is an indie real-time strategy game that was created over a long period of time due to many changes that the developers made. The game uses an isometric camera standard for the genre, which allows you to see all controlled territories and instantly react to events both in peacetime and during military operations. The project has only a single-player mode with a built-in list of achievements, in which rewards are given to the gamer for certain successes during the passage.</description></item><item><title>Dispatch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dispatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dispatch/</guid><description>Game Description Dispatch takes the superhero genre and turns it on its head, placing it in the mundane yet unpredictable world of office life. Instead of fighting evil aliens or saving cities, the title follows Robert Robertson, a former superhero called Mecha Man, who is now forced to find his place in a superhero control center after his trusty mech suit is destroyed in a fight with his nemesis. So what?</description></item><item><title>Cal and Bomba</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cal-and-bomba/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cal-and-bomba/</guid><description>Game Description Cal and Bomba is an adventure game where you solve puzzles by programming a sequence of actions to destroy your enemies. Players will have to use logic and mathematics to defeat their opponents on the battlefield. Each mission offers a set of special tiles with actions that must be placed in a specific sequence to achieve the goal. A key mechanic is the use of percentage calculations to fine-tune the gun&amp;rsquo;s firing range, turning abstract mathematical concepts into a visual and interactive process.</description></item><item><title>Lords of Ravage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lords-of-ravage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lords-of-ravage/</guid><description>Game Description The action-adventure of the Lord of Ruin takes the player into a fictional world where he must fight powerful monsters and overcome dangerous territories. The user will take control of a powerful final boss to fight the heroes and wear them down with traps before a personal meeting. You can control a variety of wards and followers in order to preemptively tense up your opponents or kill them.</description></item><item><title>Treasure 'n Trio</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/treasure-n-trio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/treasure-n-trio/</guid><description>Game Description Treasure &amp;lsquo;n Trio offers challenges that only a team of three adventurers can overcome. A warrior relies on brute force, while a nimble thief passes many dangers unharmed. The wizard in the squad has teleportation magic, which opens up new paths and allows you to change position. The gamer will have to alternately control three heroes, because none of them alone will be able to solve the riddles. Their coordinated actions are needed to interact with the environment and collect unusual treasures.</description></item><item><title>Beacon of Neyda</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beacon-of-neyda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beacon-of-neyda/</guid><description>Game Description In Beacon of Neyda, a failed robot uprising has left the world in ruins. The last handful of humanity are trying to leave lifeless lands patrolled by hostile automata. Players will have to guide survivors through abandoned areas, building temporary fortifications to protect against mechanical threats. The main task is to organize an exodus from the dead wastelands. Each location offers a new challenge in the ongoing struggle for the future of the remaining people, forced to survive in a world under the rule of their former servants.</description></item><item><title>Rise Eterna 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna-2/</guid><description>Game Description Rise Eterna 2 offers you to take control of Yacht, a soldier of the Atrakian Empire, whose goal is to return the former power to his state. The story continues the narrative of the original several years later, plunging the gamer into the epicenter of a conflict for the throne between two influential houses. The situation is complicated by a mysterious third faction, hatching a plan for final retribution and weaving its own intrigues.</description></item><item><title>This Be Mutiny</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-be-mutiny/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-be-mutiny/</guid><description>Game Description This Be Mutiny is a tactical adventure centered around betrayal and infighting among the team. At the center of the story is a squad of 11 colorful characters united by a common goal, but everyone&amp;rsquo;s personal ambitions lead to inevitable rebellion. The gameplay is built on complex decisions, forcing the user to constantly choose which of his teammates to keep on the team and which to mercilessly throw overboard.</description></item><item><title>Moros Protocol</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moros-protocol/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moros-protocol/</guid><description>Game Description Shootouts in Moros Protocol take place in a sci-fi setting where users have to face a variety of mutated monsters. The game is stylized as old-school designs drawn in pixel graphics. The gameplay is an action first-person shooter with roguelike elements. The main character is forced to confront the monsters and bandits that appeared in the universe due to the activities of two megacorporations involved in neurobiology.
In the Darkverse universe, users have the opportunity to explore dark laboratory dungeons that will be formed randomly.</description></item><item><title>eXoSpace Combat Engineer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exospace-combat-engineer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exospace-combat-engineer/</guid><description>Game Description eXoSpace Combat Engineer is a journey into the depths of a procedurally generated galaxy, where survival depends solely on engineering savvy and piloting skill. In the role of a bounty hunter, you will have to chart a course through unexplored sectors of space, each hyperjump in which promises unpredictable events. Fate can lead you to a research station in distress, throw you into the thick of a battle with pirates, or force you to face a moral choice - to provide assistance or engage in robbery.</description></item><item><title>Troublemaker 2: Beyond Dream</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/troublemaker-2-beyond-dream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/troublemaker-2-beyond-dream/</guid><description>Game Description In Troublemaker 2: Beyond Dream, the story takes place in South Jakarta two years after the ending of the original game. The plot follows the intertwined destinies of the Parakacuk gang and the music group Beyond Dream as they pursue their own ambitions. The central conflict revolves around uncovering secrets surrounding drugs and conspiracies affecting the city&amp;rsquo;s youth. This game&amp;rsquo;s narrative combines action with elements of comedy, emotional drama and investigation.</description></item><item><title>Dimwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dimwood/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dimwood/</guid><description>Game Description Dimwood is a card roguelike that takes you on a journey through the dark forest of the same name, where the main goal is to defeat the powerful Beast that lives in the thicket. The visual execution of the project is made in minimalistic 1-bit pixel graphics, creating a special atmosphere. Each enemy encounter is a tactical puzzle, the outcome of which depends on the careful use of cards with modal effects that change depending on the level of light.</description></item><item><title>Death end re;Quest: Code Z</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-end-request-code-z/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/death-end-request-code-z/</guid><description>Game Description Death end re;Quest: Code Z sends Sayaka Hiwatari into the Voltage Area, a parallel universe made up of deadly dungeons. These locations contain randomly generated monsters and traps that react to her actions. For every movement of the player character, hostile creatures respond with their own move to move or attack. The gameplay involves navigating the dungeon floors to find items and try to go deeper. In this reality, people who were once allies may now turn out to be enemies.</description></item><item><title>Ways of Alchemy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</guid><description>Game Description In Ways of Alchemy, the player begins his journey in a secluded hut, where he uses card mechanics to create powerful elixirs from many ingredients. The final goal is to build an entire alchemical empire on the basis of a modest shack, using intelligence and tactical thinking. To do this, you will have to look for ancient recipes and recruit adventurers, constantly avoiding the close attention of the Inquisition.</description></item><item><title>Shields of Loyalty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shields-of-loyalty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shields-of-loyalty/</guid><description>Game Description Shields of Loyalty - Turn-based strategy in which you need to take command of an army consisting of several units and classes. Set out to explore a mysterious island, moving across the battlefield using hexagonal hexes. Develop a strategy and increase the efficiency of your army.
Fight powerful warriors who are followers of darkness. Shields of Loyalty takes place in the dark fantasy world of Mantaria. There are several small armies under your command.</description></item><item><title>The Scouring</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-scouring/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-scouring/</guid><description>Game Description The Scouring is a real-time strategy game about the conflict between the human and orc factions. Players can choose a mode that includes building fortifications, collecting materials, and commanding military units. This gameplay requires strategic leadership of forces using both magic and guns to wage war. All factions must also defend their positions from waves of attacking undead that appear at night, which adds a survival element to base management.</description></item><item><title>Yield! Fall of Rome</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yield-fall-of-rome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/yield-fall-of-rome/</guid><description>Game Description Yield! Fall of Rome is a turn-based 4X strategy game that places gamers at the crossroads of history, specifically during the decline of the Roman Empire. Here you have to lead one of eight unique factions, each of which has its own advantages and weaknesses. These factions vary in style, requiring users to adapt to different tactical and strategic approaches. As a result, no two sessions are the same.</description></item><item><title>The Alters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-alters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-alters/</guid><description>Game Description The Alters is a science fiction adventure that immerses in the world of choice and consequences. Imagine yourself stuck on an unfriendly planet, where there is no one to rely on, except for your own ingenuity. This is the intriguing plan of this innovative game, which immerses in the world of parallel lives and alternative realities. Going on this journey, you take on the role of Jan Dolsky, a worker who made an emergency landing on a foreign world and is now facing the problem of survival and salvation.</description></item><item><title>Unlighted</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unlighted/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/unlighted/</guid><description>Game Description Unlighted is a journey into a dystopian world teetering on the edge between oblivion and memory, where a great secret hidden from humanity awaits to be revealed. At the heart of this world is the phenomenon of Umbralite - rare stones with previously unseen properties. These mysterious materials are invisible to the naked eye and only take on physical form when bathed in a stream of light. It was the study of the origin of these anomalies that became the main task of the Umbral Alchemy Corporation.</description></item><item><title>Wool at the Gates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wool-at-the-gates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wool-at-the-gates/</guid><description>Game Description Wool at the Gates presents a tactical defense experience. This project combines base defense mechanics, auto-battler-style synergy elements, and hero character control. User takes on the role of commander, leading the allied forces and building defenses for the city. This structure creates a cycle involving strategic preparation and subsequent combat engagements against advancing swarms of sheep.
The gameplay unfolds in stages, the complexity of which increases. Each stage in Wool at the Gates consists of a construction phase and a subsequent battle against enemy formations.</description></item><item><title>Rift Riff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rift-riff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rift-riff/</guid><description>Game Description Rift Riff throws gamers into the cracks between worlds to battle monsters and collect valuables. Gameplay is built around tower defense, requiring careful placement and control of structures. Before the start of the mission, you will have to determine a set of defense structures and then build them on the map at the designated points.
A key aspect of Rift Riff is selecting defensive structures to counter enemy types and their attacks.</description></item><item><title>Vambrace: Dungeon Monarch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vambrace-dungeon-monarch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/vambrace-dungeon-monarch/</guid><description>Game Description Vambrace: Dungeon Monarch weaves together multiple genres to create a tapestry of strategy and decision-making that keeps players on their toes. It is based on the role of the monarch - a figure chosen by higher powers to protect the dungeon from invasion. The Dungeon is not just a place, it is a realm of wealth and power, coveted by those who think they can lay claim to its treasures.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom's Deck</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-deck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdoms-deck/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom&amp;rsquo;s Deck presents a card-based experience that combines city building with nightly repelling attacks. Gamers will become rulers of the lands, faced with the task of expanding their personal possessions and at the same time ensuring the safety of the inhabitants from enemy attacks. Gameplay focuses on deck building and the strategic placement of these assets to control and develop a power. The main actions alternate between the construction of structures during daylight hours and the organization of the defense of fortifications at nightfall.</description></item><item><title>Phantom Brave: The Lost Hero</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phantom-brave-the-lost-hero/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/phantom-brave-the-lost-hero/</guid><description>Game Description Phantom Brave: The Lost Hero introduces Marona, a young girl with the ability to communicate with the spirits of the departed. She travels through the oceanic game world of Ivoire with the ghost Ash, assisting residents along the way. Their travels are interrupted by an attack by a fleet of ghost ships, leading to Marona&amp;rsquo;s separation from Ash. This event kicks off her campaign against the sea aggressors.</description></item><item><title>Maestro's Cold War 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maestros-cold-war-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/maestros-cold-war-2/</guid><description>Game Description Maestro&amp;rsquo;s Cold War 2 puts players at the center of a global rivalry defined by opposing political systems. There are two main forces operating on the world stage, the USA and the USSR, drawn into an ideological confrontation backed by significant nuclear arsenals. A direct military confrontation between these parties has the potential to cause widespread destruction, changing the course of civilization.
Participants choose one of two superpowers to govern while navigating this tense international environment.</description></item><item><title>Grit and Valor - 1949</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grit-and-valor-1949/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grit-and-valor-1949/</guid><description>Game Description In Grit and Valor - 1949, gamers will take control of an elite squad of mechs during an alternate history of World War II. It is 1949 and Europe is deeply scarred by the ongoing war. The Axis forces, using terrifying &amp;lsquo;Mechs, virtually crushed the resistance. Users lead their squad into this dangerous world to turn the tide by deploying destructive EMP weapons deep in enemy territory.
Every mission in Grit and Valor - 1949 forces gamers to think on their feet as they control their swords in dynamic, real-time combat.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Conflict</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-conflict/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-conflict/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Conflict is a tactical project where a freshly formed army is placed under the control of a commander to repel an enemy invasion. In a world gripped by endless wars between monarchs for territories under a new feudalism, the gamer will have to become a general and lead his troops to glory. To achieve victory, you must carefully plan every step, using a variety of types of troops.</description></item><item><title>Knights in Tight Spaces</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-in-tight-spaces/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-in-tight-spaces/</guid><description>Game Description Knights in Tight Spaces takes place in a medieval fantasy setting. Your main task is to control the environment and assemble a squad to face various bandits and supernatural threats. The mechanic is based on deck building, where strategic choice and card synergy play a crucial role in defeating your enemies. You will need to carefully plan each move, taking into account the environment, team composition and available resources.</description></item><item><title>Rift Wizard 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rift-wizard-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rift-wizard-2/</guid><description>Game Description Rift Wizard 2 is a roguelike wizard simulator that puts players in the shoes of an immortal amnesiac wizard. Main goal? Travel through space and fight an old enemy. Each playthrough of the game is a new adventure in which no two tasks are the same. Procedural generation ensures that users will always encounter different obstacles, monsters and environments, which makes the game fresh and unpredictable. The challenge lies in how gamers adapt their strategies as they progress through different levels, where every decision matters and every spell cast can be the difference between life and death.</description></item><item><title>Glorious Companions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/glorious-companions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/glorious-companions/</guid><description>Game Description Glorious Companions immerses gamers in the vast and ever-changing world of Navaroth. The title is characterized by procedural generation, thanks to which there is something different to be found in each journey, be it collecting vault crystals or navigating complex political landscapes. You lead a team of experienced mercenaries and the stakes are high. The goal is to defeat the Wrath of Xandar by collecting Vault Crystals scattered throughout the world while engaging in combat, strategic planning, and resource management.</description></item><item><title>Endless Dark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-dark/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-dark/</guid><description>Game Description In Endless Dark you will have to serve a sleeping colony ship alone. As the Guardian, a sentient machine, your job is to keep the ship&amp;rsquo;s systems running, but you also face an eerie sense of isolation. There is no combat here, but instead you are faced with system failures, unpredictable events and the gradual destruction of your sanity. This combination of mechanical problems and mental stress creates a unique sensation.</description></item><item><title>Myths and Legends</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myths-and-legends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myths-and-legends/</guid><description>Game Description Myths and Legends takes gamers into a world created 2,500 years ago where they can take part in various strategic activities. The title combines exploration, combat, trade and diplomacy, offering a new take on real-time strategy. Its design focuses on creating and managing city-states on procedurally generated islands, where no two playthroughs are the same. With a focus on resource management and tactical decision-making, users have a lot to think about as they try to build and maintain their power.</description></item><item><title>Urban Strife</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-strife/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-strife/</guid><description>Game Description Urban Strife takes place in a post-apocalyptic world, and the gameplay is presented in the style of old school TBS. The main character lives in a dangerous environment, where every resident does everything for his own benefit. Resources are running out, there are no jobs, and most kill and rob to survive. The player can enter into alliances by choosing 1 of several factions, automatically becoming an enemy of the remaining factions.</description></item><item><title>Lost But Found</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-but-found/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-but-found/</guid><description>Game Description InLost But Found, gamers will take on the role of an airport employee dealing with lost and found items. The idea is simple: sort, organize and return lost items to their rightful owners. The setting is an airport, where the task of returning passengers to their belongings takes place on a cluttered table with an overhead view. The title revolves around decisions, management and moral issues. This mixture of job simulator and hidden object mechanics defines the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Sin Slayers: Reign of The 8th</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sin-slayers-reign-of-the-8th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sin-slayers-reign-of-the-8th/</guid><description>Game Description Sin Slayers: Reign of The 8th immerses users in a dark, unforgiving world, where every corner is fraught with new dangers and moral dilemmas. In this turn-based strategy game, players take on the role of a group of adventurers, each representing one of the Seven Deadly Sins. Their mission? Confront monstrous enemies, travel through dark and twisted places, and ultimately confront the formidable Eighth Sin - Fate.
This latest installment in the Sin Slayers series expands on the formula of its predecessor, introducing new regions, improved mechanics, and an even deeper story that will force players to question not only the fate of their characters, but the very nature of sin.</description></item><item><title>Node Farm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/node-farm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/node-farm/</guid><description>Game Description Node Farm is an adventure game, the essence of which is to create an automated farm using nodes. The concept is simple: connect nodes to grow crops, harvest them and sell them for profit. Gamers can then reinvest this money to expand their farms and discover new islands. Over time, the farm becomes more efficient as users develop strategies to automate every step of the farming process. This constant development is at the heart of the game, offering a satisfying combination of resource management and strategic planning.</description></item><item><title>Forgotten but Unbroken</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forgotten-but-unbroken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forgotten-but-unbroken/</guid><description>Game Description Forgotten but Unbroken is an exciting tactical turn-based strategy game that takes inspiration from XCOM but offers its own unique and unforgettable twist. You will have the opportunity to fight with or against real heroes of World War II, unjustly forgotten by history. It&amp;rsquo;s time to take your place as the leader of a small but powerful resistance group and fight the might of the Axis forces to help liberate Europe!</description></item><item><title>Rogue Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-command/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Command is a strategy with elements of a bagel and a card game. You need to collect resources, form a unique deck of cards and fight against robots. When gathering an army, you need to study the enemy&amp;rsquo;s tactics in order to deal a crushing blow to him. While exploring locations, you need to obtain resources to build buildings and hire units. There are factories, auxiliary buildings, turrets and special weapons of mass destruction.</description></item><item><title>My Hotel</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-hotel/</guid><description>Game Description Users inMy Hotel have to try their hand at being a novice businessman who is going to set up a small hotel and gradually develop it. You will have to buy a dirty and in terrible condition of a house in which you can arrange rooms for living and set up a reception. It is necessary to wash all the floors, clean the furniture from dust and do everything possible to make an attractive and prestigious appearance for the building.</description></item><item><title>Songs of Silence</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/songs-of-silence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/songs-of-silence/</guid><description>Game Description Songs of Silence immerses players in a fantasy world under the threat of an impending Silence. This strategy game combines kingdom management, hero development and auto-combat elements, culminating in exciting real-time battles. Immerse yourself in a rich narrative as you lead your kingdom against the encroaching darkness. Manage resources, explore vast maps, and outsmart your opponents to achieve victory. Experience varied gameplay with turn-based strategic maneuvering and fast-paced, action-packed combat.</description></item><item><title>Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sea-power-naval-combat-in-the-missile-age/</guid><description>Game Description Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is a naval combat game in which you control two warring factions: NATO forces and representatives of the Warsaw Pact. Take part in the naval conflicts of the 80s. Control a huge number of different ships, use all modern types of weapons and technologies. Your main task in Sea Power: Naval Combat in the Missile Age is to defeat the enemy army.</description></item><item><title>HeistGeist</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heistgeist/</guid><description>Game Description HeistGeist immerses gamers in the cyberpunk universe, putting them in the shoes of Alexandra, a cunning thief who overcomes the consequences of a failed mission. The title revolves around the challenge of assembling a diverse team of specialists to carry out complex heists. Each heist presents tactical obstacles and opportunities, turning each mission into a unique puzzle. Users take part in battles based on a card-based battle system that brings an innovative twist to the traditional strategy genre.</description></item><item><title>Terror of the Seven Seas</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terror-of-the-seven-seas/</guid><description>Game Description Terror of the Seven Seas is a game that immerses gamers in the complex maritime life of an era of exploration and piracy. The game takes place in a vast open world and offers a wide range of entertainment - from participating in large-scale naval battles to treasure hunting. Users take on the roles of various characters, each with their own unique responsibilities and abilities. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a captain leading a ship through stormy seas, an officer commanding a crew, a merchant transporting goods across vast oceans, or an explorer reaching into the unknown, there is something for every type of adventurer.</description></item><item><title>Metal Slug Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-slug-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description TheMetal Slug Tactics player chooses his warriors to create a suitable powerful team capable of stopping the hostilities. Run n' Gun has roguelike elements as well as intense combat. The continuation of the series of the same name allows you to look at the war from a new angle with a greater share of adrenaline, gaining experience after each fight, which helps to unlock additional skills or weapons. The game was the first tactical RPG, unlike its predecessors, and features replayability, pixel graphics and complex replay mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Warlords Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warlords-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Warlords Battle Simulator is a game that places gamers in the role of generals who must lead armies in strategic and often unpredictable battles. In this tactical roguelike auto-action game, success largely depends on how well users manage resources, select units and place them on the battlefield. Each faction - be it the Kingdom, Greenskins, Undead or Barbarians - offers a unique set of units and commanders, each with special abilities that can change the tide of battle.</description></item><item><title>Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</guid><description>Game Description Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing immerses users in battles between armies that take place during the Dark Middle Ages. The game is made in the genre of real-time strategy, where you have to deal with printing and solving multi-task missions. The protagonist is a guy named Paul who wants to prevail over the evil forces. Gameplay mechanics allow you to test the typing speed of users, where the ability to type the necessary keys blindly is useful in order to keep control over the events that are happening.</description></item><item><title>Quadrober Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quadrober-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Quadrober Simulator invites users to test themselves as a four-legged creature in a diverse environment. There is a lot of choice in this game. Users can choose from a variety of animals, each with specific traits and skills. These choices set the stage for a unique journey through different ecosystems. As gamers navigate these landscapes, they are faced with opportunities to explore, survive, and interact with the environment. Gameplay revolves around several key activities, including hunting, foraging, and building shelters.</description></item><item><title>Quarterstaff</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quarterstaff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quarterstaff/</guid><description>Game Description Quarterstaff is a turn-based action strategy game that invites gamers into a fantasy realm full of intrigue and conflict. Set against the backdrop of a land under siege by a ruthless sorcerous conqueror, the adventure revolves around the character of Kalresh, a wizard skilled in the arts of magic and acrobatics. Having taken control of Kalresh, users are tasked with liberating the kingdom through a series of strategic battles.</description></item><item><title>Clank!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clank/</guid><description>Game Description Clank! throws players headlong into an exciting world of dungeons and daring theft. This board game marks their physical debut, offering a unique blend of deck building and push-your-luck mechanics. Main task? Infiltrate the legendary Dragon Vault, steal the most coveted artifacts, and escape with the loot before the dragon turns you into a crunchy beast. Sounds simple enough, right? But no.
Every false step, every clink of metal on stone echoes through the caves, serving as an uninvited call to the slumbering dragon.</description></item><item><title>Tech Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Tech Store Simulator immerses gamers in the fast-paced world of tech retail, giving them hands-on experience in running their own electronics store. The title&amp;rsquo;s focus is on strategic decision-making, requiring users to balance inventory management with customer satisfaction. Gamers will have to navigate the ins and outs of running a successful tech business, from stocking shelves with the latest gadgets to setting competitive prices.
Hiring and managing staff is another key aspect of the game to keep the store running smoothly and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Thronefall</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thronefall/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thronefall/</guid><description>Game Description Thronefall is a game that truly captures the essence of strategy and action. Here, players are tasked with balancing resources, armies, and defenses while constantly facing waves of relentless enemies that relentlessly attack their base every night. The project offers users the freedom to choose their style, allowing them to either hold positions behind fortified walls and rely on archers and catapults to repel invaders, or take charge and lead their knights into exciting combat.</description></item><item><title>Necro Story</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/necro-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/necro-story/</guid><description>Game Description Necro Story provides users with a unique opportunity to step into the shoes of a slightly evil necromancer. The title combines elements of humor and the conventions of traditional role-playing games, inviting gamers into a world where the undead and dark magic are part of everyday life. The narrative unfolds with the help of a ghostly white magician who brings playfulness to the often dark theme of necromancy. Together they embark on a journey through the underworld to save humanity from an impending threat.</description></item><item><title>Diplomacy is Not an Option</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diplomacy-is-not-an-option/</guid><description>Game Description InDiplomacy is Not an Option the player becomes a feudal lord in the Middle Ages. The main character is going through a midlife crisis. Every day the protagonist comes up with hundreds of ways to improve his own economy, how to properly lead his subjects and competently develop the city. He lived like this for a long time. He was tired of monotonous and meaningless intellectual stress.
New adventures in the life of the central character begin when hordes of monsters began to attack settlements, and the townspeople rebelled together.</description></item><item><title>exclusive memory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exclusive-memory/</guid><description>Game Description Exclusive Memory draws gamers into a narrative where every choice and interaction can change the storyline. The protagonist finds himself in a maze of memories, each of which serves as a puzzle box that needs to be opened. As users delve deeper, they uncover layers of the character&amp;rsquo;s past, encountering various figures that are pieces of a larger puzzle. These interactions not only move the narrative forward, but also provide insight into the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s psyche, shaping his journey.</description></item><item><title>Axon TD: Uprising - Tower Defense</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/axon-td-uprising-tower-defense/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/axon-td-uprising-tower-defense/</guid><description>Game Description Axon TD: Uprising - Tower Defense is a fast-paced and fun tower defense game that gives users the freedom to create their own mazes and paths using a tile-based system. With the ability to connect to different islands and control your destination, players can strategize and customize their defenses to fend off the relentless waves of enemies.
The main difference between Axon TD: Uprising - Tower Defense is its authentic modes.</description></item><item><title>Mechabellum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mechabellum/</guid><description>Game Description Mechabellum is an epic auto battler set in a sci-fi setting that puts you in the shoes of a commander leading an army of mechs on the newly colonized planet Far-Away. Your opponents will tremble in fear as you customize and level up your units, strategically place them on the battlefield and watch them ruthlessly destroy your enemies. You&amp;rsquo;ll have an arsenal of unique &amp;lsquo;Mechs at your disposal, from the nimble light craft of Wasps to the massive Vulcans.</description></item><item><title>The Nameless: Slay Dragon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-nameless-slay-dragon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-nameless-slay-dragon/</guid><description>Game Description The Nameless: Slay Dragon is a turn-based role-playing adventure game that immerses gamers in a world of strategic combat and deep storytelling. In the center is a young protagonist who must take revenge on a powerful dragon. Users will have to go through a series of battles and clashes, each of which requires careful planning and tactical execution. The title emphasizes the importance of choice; every decision can change the course of the plot.</description></item><item><title>Ara: History Untold</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ara-history-untold/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ara-history-untold/</guid><description>Game Description Ara: History Untold is a turn-based grand strategy game that puts players in the shoes of the leader of a nation and guides its destiny on an exciting journey through alternate history. Users embark on a journey of exploration, development and diplomacy, defining the unique path of their civilization. From the very beginning, gamers are immersed in a procedurally generated world rife with opportunities and challenges. The game encourages exploration, rewarding those who venture into the unknown with the discovery of new lands and resources.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk-2/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk 2 is a continuation of the survival game, which is based on management and construction. The events of the game take place 30 years after the catastrophe that covered the Earth. Now the planet has experienced severe cooling and people are suffering from constant frosts. In the urban planning simulator, you are asked to try on the role of a hero who, in the process, must lead an entire metropolis and take care of the well-being of local residents.</description></item><item><title>Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scary-shadow-spot-last-farewell/</guid><description>Game Description Scary Shadow Spot: Last Farewell is a first-person psychological horror game that explores themes of grief, guilt, and the paranormal. Players take on the role of Mark, a man coping with the recent loss of his wife Jane. The game begins with Mark returning to his and Jane&amp;rsquo;s old country house to prepare for her funeral. However, what is meant to be a grim homecoming quickly turns into a terrifying ordeal.</description></item><item><title>Toy Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/toy-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Toy Tactics is a colorful action strategy game that will take you into the world of exciting strategies and physics experiments. Here you will become the main general, tasked with controlling little toy soldiers and defeating the enemy. You will have to place units on the battlefield and create various formations to guide your toy army towards victory. But don’t forget that physics plays an important role here! When the toy soldiers collide with each other, their helmets will fly in all directions, just like in a cartoon.</description></item><item><title>Pyrene</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pyrene/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pyrene/</guid><description>Game Description Pyrene is a fast-paced roguelike dungeon-crawler in which gamers must plunge into the depths of hell and rebuild their home. With a variety of heroes and spells, users can experiment with different strategies and find their own unique approach to the game. As they progress, they will collect powerful relics to upgrade their deck, increasing their abilities and chances of survival. The narrative unfolds as users uncover the secrets behind the destruction of their village, adding depth to the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Archons: Arena</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/archons-arena/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/archons-arena/</guid><description>Game Description Archons: Arena combines deckbuilding and RPG elements, throwing gamers into a harsh world where skill, equipment and tactics are crucial. There are several character classes, each with their own special abilities, allowing users to customize their style to suit their preferences. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a secretive rogue, a stalwart knight, or a powerful sorcerer, there&amp;rsquo;s a class for you.
The main mechanic is deckbuilding, in which gamers create their decks without any random elements.</description></item><item><title>Surreal Farm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/surreal-farm/</guid><description>Game Description Surreal Farm is an adventure game that invites gamers into a vibrant world where imagination and strategy intertwine. Starting with a modest plot of land, gamers grow crops, care for unique animals and turn their farm into a thriving enterprise. As they progress, they discover many fantastical elements, from magical tools to surreal cultures and mythical creatures. The charm lies in the combination of casual gameplay and strategic depth.</description></item><item><title>Drill Core</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drill-core/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drill-core/</guid><description>Game Description Drill Core throws you headlong into the unforgiving depths of alien planets. You are in charge, tasked with managing a motley crew of miners and security guards. Their task? Extract valuable minerals and maintain the drill in working condition. Every swing of the pickaxe, every mounted turret - everything depends on your decisions. One wrong move can spell disaster for your team and the entire mission. But hold on, sunshine and cosmic rainbows don&amp;rsquo;t last forever here.</description></item><item><title>EVOTINCTION</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/evotinction/</guid><description>Game Description EVOTINCTION is a futuristic hacking and stealth game that puts gamers in the role of Dr. Liu, a scientist running a research facility that has been taken over by rogue AIs. The core gameplay centers on using hacking skills to overcome robotic threats and uncover secrets vital to humanity&amp;rsquo;s survival. The facility is teeming with enemies, ranging from ordinary service robots to deadly, specially created killer bots.
These robots follow specific patrol routes and work together under the guidance of a sophisticated artificial intelligence system.</description></item><item><title>Fealty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fealty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fealty/</guid><description>Game Description Fealty is a tactical turn-based strategy game that has gamers chasing the throne. The action takes place on a procedurally generated island, where a new location appears with each playthrough. At first glance, the goal is simple - to build your lands, expand power and force your rivals to bend the knee, but the adventure game does not let you off the hook so easily. From the very beginning, users have to think ahead.</description></item><item><title>Wild Bastards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</guid><description>Game Description InWild Bastards you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself in the captain&amp;rsquo;s chair of a ragtag spaceship filled with the galaxy&amp;rsquo;s most notorious criminals. Think space pirates with a penchant for trouble. This isn&amp;rsquo;t your grandpa&amp;rsquo;s space opera, but a roguelike shooter where every decision can mean the difference between exploding into stardom or becoming cosmic dust. The missions are spread across a series of tactical campaigns, each of which is an adventure.</description></item><item><title>Demolish and Build 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demolish-and-build-3/</guid><description>Game Description Demolish and Build 3 is a first-person simulator that puts you in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat of a demolition company. You will complete orders and lead your team to victory using a variety of tools and heavy equipment. This game will test your skills as you manage your business and complete every project with precision and efficiency. A completely new realistic model of destruction will make you marvel at what you see more than once, since each fragment is physically simulated.</description></item><item><title>Satisfactory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/satisfactory/</guid><description>Game Description Satisfactory is an open-world first-person adventure where you build industrial buildings, explore, and fight. Explore a new planet alone or with other users. Build huge structures and do whatever you want in assembly line paradise. You are an employee of FICSIT Corporation.
Players can build wherever they want. Expand production in all directions, install factories in the mountains, forests or plains. Mine natural resources found all around you. Build complex networks and transport routes, automate all mechanics, without forgetting about safety.</description></item><item><title>Terrorformer TD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrorformer-td/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrorformer-td/</guid><description>Game Description Terrorformer TD is a tower defense adventure game based on the concept of shaping the battlefield to gain an advantage. Here, users not only place towers and upgrade them, but also change the terrain to control the movement of waves of enemies. The idea of ​​being able to raise or lower tiles adds an extra layer to traditional tower defense gameplay. You can change paths, create barriers and generally confuse enemy routes.</description></item><item><title>Zero Hour</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Hour is a multiplayer tactical first-person shooter with realistic game mechanics that replicate the behavior of real special forces units in anti-terrorist operations. The setting for the action is criminal Bangladesh, where banditry is at a high level and is not going to give up ground to law enforcement officers. The locations where clashes between groups of terrorists and special forces occur are made using real scale, which greatly helps the atmosphere and involves gamers in the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Roots of Yggdrasil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roots-of-yggdrasil/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roots-of-yggdrasil/</guid><description>Game Description Roots of Yggdrasil is a roguelike city-building adventure set in a post-Ragnarok world. Players take on the role of Sunna, a Viking leader, and her tribe who must rebuild their society amidst the shattered World Tree. In the title you need to build settlements, explore the Nine Kingdoms and collect artifacts. Each run is a race against time to escape Ginnungagap, the void that threatens to swallow everything.</description></item><item><title>The Corpsmen</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-corpsmen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-corpsmen/</guid><description>Game Description The Corpsmen is a title that offers users a unique task: create and lead teams of creatures in battles with a variety of monsters. From the very beginning, gamers collect monster parts to build creatures of their own design. Each assembled part - be it a leg, tail or head - provides certain skills, leaving room for experimentation. The title relies heavily on strategic planning and creativity. You don&amp;rsquo;t just throw parts together and hope for the best.</description></item><item><title>Castle of Lord Velimir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/castle-of-lord-velimir/</guid><description>Game Description Castle of Lord Velimir takes users on a dangerous journey with the titular hero, a warrior seeking atonement for the sins of humanity. As Velimir journeys through the dungeons, wastelands, and mysterious underworld of Agartha, he will face countless challenges and uncover the secrets of his world. The gameplay is a mixture of strategic combat and exploration. Users must master a variety of fighting techniques to defeat a variety of enemies, each requiring a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Age of Mythology: Retold</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-mythology-retold/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-mythology-retold/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Mythology: Retold is not your average strategy game. It brings mythology into play, allowing you to wage war with a twist. The title features Greek, Norwegian, Egyptian and even Atlantean troops, each with their own special abilities provided by the big men above. Do you think divine intervention will change the course of the battle? Yes, this happens. The campaign is a 50-mission odyssey through a world filled with legendary stories.</description></item><item><title>Fantasy Map Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fantasy-map-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fantasy-map-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Fantasy Map Simulator will be an exciting experience, because this simulator invites history and fantasy lovers to create and watch the development of fictional worlds. Imagine a canvas stretched across centuries, where empires rise and fall, nations emerge, and destinies intertwine. The title allows users to create complex maps, each of which is a testament to their creativity. These cards, like living organisms, develop autonomously, guided by logic.</description></item><item><title>We Heist Too</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/we-heist-too/</guid><description>Game Description We Heist Too takes place in Rivadorium, a city where nothing ever stays the same. Users get used to the role of a thief, move silently through the streets, plan and carry out high-stakes robberies. This world doesn&amp;rsquo;t require much care, and from the very beginning you will notice that every corner of the city is fraught with opportunity. But the tricky part is knowing which opportunities are worth pursuing.</description></item><item><title>Sumerian Six</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerian-six/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerian-six/</guid><description>Game Description Sumerian Six is not your typical war story. Sure, it throws you right into the middle of World War II, but it&amp;rsquo;s an alternate history where whispers of folklore and conspiracy theories are as real as the Nazi threat. You take command of Enigma Squad, a strange team of scientist-soldiers. These are brainy people who can outwit and outwit their enemies. Their mission? Prevent the Third Reich from getting its hands on occult weapons.</description></item><item><title>Angola '86</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/angola-86/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/angola-86/</guid><description>Game Description Angola &amp;lsquo;86 is a strategy game that immerses gamers in a tense and multifaceted border war in South Africa. Users take on the role of a South African Defense Force (SADF) commander who is faced with the challenging task of conducting counter-insurgency operations in a hostile environment. The story, an unstable border region between South Africa and Angola, provides a unique and historically accurate backdrop for strategic decision-making.</description></item><item><title>Dale and Dawson Stationery Supplies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dale-and-dawson-stationery-supplies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dale-and-dawson-stationery-supplies/</guid><description>Game Description Dale and Dawson Stationery Supplies, inspired by an early 2000s office drama, immerses gamers in the mundane yet intriguing world of a seemingly typical stationery company. The title randomly assigns you one of three roles: Manager, Specialist or Slacker. Your fate is sealed and your mission begins. Targeted Gameplay: Specialists diligently complete tasks to move the company forward, and slackers imitate specialists so as not to arouse suspicion.</description></item><item><title>Megaloot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megaloot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/megaloot/</guid><description>Game Description Megaloot occupies a unique niche in the world of role-playing games, requiring gamers to pay meticulous attention to inventory management. Unraveling a mysterious world in which a colossal structure has the ability to replicate objects from countless realities, the title sets the stage for an odyssey filled with strategic choices and tactical delights. Users will find more than 100 different items, each of which boasts its own characteristics. Combine them cleverly to create a dominant build - the possibilities are mind-boggling.</description></item><item><title>MEMORIAPOLIS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/memoriapolis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/memoriapolis/</guid><description>Game Description MEMORIAPOLIS is an urban construction set unlike any other. This is a time machine, a sandbox for history buffs. Studio 5PM created this brainchild, offering users a playground for 2500 years. From the dawn of civilization to the Age of Enlightenment, gamers create a city. It&amp;rsquo;s not just bricks and mortar, it&amp;rsquo;s a living, breathing organism that reacts to your every move. Time is the currency here. Users go through Antiquity, the Middle Ages, the Renaissance and the Enlightenment.</description></item><item><title>Star Command Galaxies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-command-galaxies/</guid><description>Game Description Star Command Galaxies is a space simulator in which you play as a ship captain. You need to build your own shuttle, recruit staff and go explore the randomly generated expanses of outer space. Manage your staff, collect resources, fight the alien threat and upgrade your ship. Clear the galaxy from enemies and various parasites. Fight pirates, zombies and many other opponents.
You need to monitor the status of your team.</description></item><item><title>Peglin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/peglin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/peglin/</guid><description>Game Description Peglin is a side-scrolling RPG adventure with a 2D world. The player will play the role of a fictional peglin creature trying to fight dragons that steal and eat representatives of his race. The main character is a small green creature with big ears. He decided to go to the forest, where the faction&amp;rsquo;s longtime enemies live. There he will meet his enemies and take back what was stolen by the dragons.</description></item><item><title>9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/9-bit-armies-a-bit-too-far/</guid><description>Game Description 9-Bit Armies: A Bit Too Far is a real-time strategy game developed by Petroglyph Games, a continuation of the 8-Bit Armies series. Gamers lead modern military forces across various battlefields, participating in land, sea and air battles. The project offers more than two dozen missions, online skirmishes and cooperative play. A base construction system has been implemented in which players build structures, unlock units and launch attacks. The game is designed for both new and experienced RTS players with an easy to learn interface but a challenging skill ceiling.</description></item><item><title>Tactical Breach Wizards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tactical-breach-wizards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tactical-breach-wizards/</guid><description>Game Description Tactical Breach Wizards is a tactical role-playing adventure with an isometric camera that allows you to better assess the situation in the location to make the most successful decisions. The user will be transported to an alternative universe, where a distant futuristic future has arrived. The gamer takes control of a group of soldiers who have magical abilities that allow them to be combined with shots from firearms.</description></item><item><title>shapez 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapez-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shapez-2/</guid><description>Game Description Shapez 2 is a simulator about the construction of factories with a top view, in which you need to automate the process of processing geometric shapes. Players must build and optimize massive production facilities to solve increasingly complex logistics problems. Gameplay involves cutting, rotating, stacking, painting and delivering shapes to unlock advanced technologies and expand enterprise capabilities.
What&amp;rsquo;s unique is that each object is a separate set of building blocks that can be disassembled, folded, painted and put back together in special ways.</description></item><item><title>UBOAT</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/uboat/</guid><description>Game Description UBOAT is a unique simulator of submarine control during the Second World War. Observe and take direct part in the life of German submariners in the midst of war, when at any moment their refuge could turn into the place of their death. Survive in the open world and control all processes occurring on the submarine. Your players must be well-fed and energized so that your gameplay is not doomed to failure.</description></item><item><title>7 Days to Die</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/7-days-to-die/</guid><description>Game Description In7 Days to Die you will need the ability to loot, kill other players, take loot, build buildings, craft items, shoot accurately and keep track of time, because in the open world there is a night in which zombies and other undead sharpen their attention . A horror first-person shooter that combines city building, multiplayer, survival, tower defense and character leveling in an RPG style. Despite the fact that a severe epidemic has struck the world, you will be able to kill animals to take their meat and skin.</description></item><item><title>LOCKDOWN Protocol</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lockdown-protocol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lockdown-protocol/</guid><description>Game Description LOCKDOWN Protocol throws players into a high-stakes world of deception and cooperation. The title combines real-time action and communication, creating a dynamic experience for groups of three to eight people. The idea is simple: players cooperate to complete tasks within a strict time limit. Beneath the surface of unity, however, lies a sinister undercurrent. Trust is a fragile commodity in this environment. Every interaction offers a chance to gather information or sow discord.</description></item><item><title>Workers and Resources: Soviet Republic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/workers-and-resources-soviet-republic/</guid><description>Game Description InWorkers and Resources: Soviet Republic you have to lead a fallen country and turn it into the strongest republic, making it a superpower with the happiest inhabitants who have built world progress. The urban planning strategy will show you a country that is very similar to the Soviet Union. You accept it broken, plundered, ruined. There is absolutely no money in the treasury, and people have no opportunity to raise territories, plant crops, go to work, simply because there is no money even for food, but you understand that all this can be corrected.</description></item><item><title>Legend of Mortal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/legend-of-mortal/</guid><description>Game Description InLegend of Mortal you have to become a nobody in the Tang Man sector. Not a prophetic hero, not a legendary warrior - you&amp;rsquo;re just trying to survive in a world on the edge of the abyss. But even lowlifes have it tough, right? This is what Legend of Mortal is all about: your decisions determine the fate of you and those around you. Think of it this way: every meeting, every battle, every seemingly insignificant conversation is a twist in the kaleidoscope.</description></item><item><title>Bodycam</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</guid><description>Game Description Bodycam throws you headlong into a hyper-realistic multiplayer battlefield. Powered by Unreal Engine 5, this all-new shooter promises a next-gen experience that will redefine your expectations. Teamwork is key here. Every bullet counts, and the victory or defeat of your squad depends on your every decision.
Forget playing Rambo. Bodycam requires strategic thinking and coordinated attacks. Team up with your teammates, map out a plan of action, and use your arsenal to outmaneuver your opponents.</description></item><item><title>Empires of the Undergrowth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empires-of-the-undergrowth/</guid><description>Game Description Empires of the Undergrowth is a simulation and real-time strategy game with unique mechanics. In the game you will have to manage a colony of ants. Starting to play as one ant, you will hunt, manage builders, and create a unique hive. The design of your hive will determine whether your colony can survive in this harsh world. Why harsh?
Throughout the game you will face various obstacles. First of all, these are your enemies!</description></item><item><title>WARNO</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warno/</guid><description>Game Description Tactical battles inWARNO take place in real time, where users will be able to take control of modern combat vehicles and go to the front, plunging into the Third World War. The game is made in the genre of strategy and army command simulator, where you need to think through the movement of units and observe the events taking place. The storyline is about a coup that occurs after Gorbachev leaves, creating a tense conflict between states in 1989.</description></item><item><title>Homeworld 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/homeworld-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/homeworld-3/</guid><description>Game Description Homeworld 3 is a new part of the famous space battle franchise, which is a sequel and continues the storyline. Nevertheless, the game is also suitable for those who are not familiar with the universe, if you only dive into the mode of multiplayer confrontations on ships. Now abandoned galactic stations are scattered across the universe, which have turned into arenas where you can feel the battle with a random user.</description></item><item><title>Chrono Ark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chrono-ark/</guid><description>Game Description Chrono Ark is a classic Japanese-style RPG adventure that supports high-resolution textures, but uses similar camera views and turn-based dialogue and battle system rendering. The story campaign is available for completion only in single-player mode; multiplayer is not provided in this project.
The gameplay is based on gathering a team, which includes 4 characters, for further leveling up and creating an invincible squad, ready to fight on equal terms with all opponents presented in the locations of the bizarre Distorted World.</description></item><item><title>Manor Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/manor-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Manor Lords is a strategy game set in the Middle Ages. The game mechanics center on the realistic process of constructing buildings and intense fights with the enemy army. The building element is based on historical data about cities and villages. All buildings presented in Manor Lords are as authentic as possible. Landscapes and types of terrain influence the process of settlement formation.
Create trade routes, establish market relations with neighboring cities and promote the economic prosperity of the settlement.</description></item><item><title>Rusty's Retirement</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-retirement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-retirement/</guid><description>Game Description Rusty&amp;rsquo;s Retirement allows players to experience farming on the go. Designed as a project for idlers, it allows you to manage a virtual farm while doing other things. Gamers take on the role of Rusty, a retired robot who tends to his crops. The game develops automatically: Rusty plants, waters and harvests crops without constant player interaction. As you progress, you can discover new cultures, adding variety to your virtual fields.</description></item><item><title>Bellwright</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellwright/</guid><description>Game Description Bellwright throws you into a world of rebellion and intrigue. Finding yourself in prison for a heinous crime, you must not only clear your name, but also organize a revolution against a tyrannical ruler. Build and manage settlements, collect resources and recruit villagers into your ranks. Each new adept brings valuable skills, strengthening your rebellion and unlocking new technologies for your cities.
Combat is based on skill and focus.</description></item><item><title>The Lost Village</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-lost-village/</guid><description>Game Description InThe Lost Village you have to restore a once great sect. You take on the role of the heir to a leader who has returned to an abandoned mountain and is tasked with restoring it to its former glory. The game combines a management simulator with roguelike elements. Gamers will guide students by collecting resources, building structures and cultivating the land. Students have unique personalities and talents, allowing assignments to be specialized.</description></item><item><title>Buckshot Roulette</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/buckshot-roulette/</guid><description>Game Description Two enter, one leaves. That&amp;rsquo;s the motto ofBuckshot Roulette, a horror game that takes the classic game of Russian Roulette and turns it into a high-stakes shotgun game. Immerse yourself in the dark atmosphere of an underground nightclub, where metal railings beat to the beat of forgotten drum kits and the stakes couldn&amp;rsquo;t be higher. This is not Russian roulette. This is where you swap the revolver for a 12 gauge shotgun, because shotguns are just better, right?</description></item><item><title>Knowledge, or know Lady</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</guid><description>Game Description Knowledge, or know Lady throws you into the heart of a unique dating simulator. As the only guy at an all-girl university, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself caught up in a whirlwind of romance and college life. Will you succumb to the charms of the beauties around you or forge your own path to become a campus legend? Ladies School Prince unfolds through your eyes, offering a first-person perspective. Your</description></item><item><title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</guid><description>Game Description Outpost: Infinity Siege is a fun sci-fi first-person shooter with elements of base building and tower defense. You command the Mobile Outpost and go with the Protoslug Cannon to deeply explore the forbidden zone of Cygnet, where many dangers await you. Collect unique weapon units and strengthen the firepower of the outpost that is fighting with you. This game combines elements of TD, FPS and RTS at the same time, making the gameplay incredibly exciting.</description></item><item><title>Backpack Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backpack-battles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backpack-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Backpack Battles is a unique PvP game where everything depends on the contents of your backpack. Forget about deft kicking or pressing buttons - here, winning is achieved by assembling the perfect bag arsenal. The core gameplay revolves around purchasing and arranging items in your inventory. These items come in different shapes, sizes and rarities, presenting a strategic puzzle as you put them together for maximum effectiveness. Don&amp;rsquo;t limit yourself to simply stockpiling - by combining these items, you can unlock even more powerful equipment, such as brewing a potion or forging a legendary weapon.</description></item><item><title>Between the Stars</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/between-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/between-the-stars/</guid><description>Game Description In Between the Stars, a space simulator, the gamer discovers new territories, fights with numerous opponents and upgrades his own ship. The hero&amp;rsquo;s goal is to save the Interstellar Republic. The game has procedural generation of the environment, enemies and stations.
The protagonist&amp;rsquo;s universe is suffering from attacks from the Children of the Sun clan. Enemy representatives have appeared from other worlds and are trying to capture these spaces.</description></item><item><title>Quilts and Cats of Calico</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quilts-and-cats-of-calico/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quilts-and-cats-of-calico/</guid><description>Game Description Quilts &amp;amp; Cats of Calico is a unique, warm and cozy puzzle game. Here you will have the opportunity to work as a tailor and create a unique quilt from scraps. Combine colors and patterns on your scraps to not only score points, but also attract cute cats who will decide where to snooze on your creation. If you&amp;rsquo;re a board game fan, you&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to know that this is a digital version of the already beloved board game.</description></item><item><title>ChronoDojo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chronodojo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chronodojo/</guid><description>Game Description ChronoDojo is a co-op adventure in which a group of humble heroes embark on a journey through time to save the world. Under the guidance of their mentor Sensei, the characters will have to master the martial art of Chrono-Fu. Their headquarters is ChronoDojo itself, a martial arts school that can travel between eras and doubles as a tea house. You will have to confront waves of bizarre enemies in three different historical periods, using unique abilities and well-coordinated teamwork.</description></item><item><title>Myth of Empires</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/myth-of-empires/</guid><description>Game Description The goal ofMyth of Empires is to teach the user to fight for their own place in a huge world. The game is positioned as a multiplayer sandbox in which the user creates an Empire, forming troops that participate in massive battles and sieges of cities, and also builds their own fortresses for defense.
The action takes place in the East during the era of antiquity, when many states constantly fought among themselves, which led to chaos, famine and destruction.</description></item><item><title>Balatro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/balatro/</guid><description>Game Description Balatro - the word &amp;ldquo;poker&amp;rdquo; crackles with energy, whispering promises of high stakes and cunning deals. This poker roguelike beckons players into a deck-building odyssey where bluffing becomes the spell and chips become your lifeblood. Forget about limping into pots with low pairs. Here you create powerful synergies by weaving intricate combinations that unleash explosive power. Valid poker hands dance with unique wild cards, their abilities changing the course of the game like a magician.</description></item><item><title>GU LONG FENGYUN LU</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gu-long-fengyun-lu/</guid><description>Game Description GU LONG FENGYUN LU is a massive martial arts RPG based on the classic works of Gu Long, the famous Chinese writer. The plot tells about the turbulent times of the end of the Ming Dynasty, when various heroes and factions fought for power and glory. The main character is Feng Yun, a young martial artist traveling across the country, encountering friends, enemies, love, hate, loyalty and betrayal.</description></item><item><title>Stargate: Timekeepers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stargate-timekeepers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stargate-timekeepers/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the Stargate: Timekeepers project take place within a separate universe called SG-1. It all begins with the Battle of Antarctica, where Commander Eve McKine leads the battle against Anubis' fleet. After this, the user will be able to take control of a squad subordinate to this very Eve in order to penetrate behind enemy lines and complete a number of dangerous tasks. The outcome of the war depends on this, so no one has the right to make a mistake.</description></item><item><title>The Universim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-universim/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city construction, the development of an entire planet and a ward civilization -The Universim is a short sand strategy in which you have to try on the role of God. The game begins with the fact that you settle several people on one of the planets, give them food, indicate what needs to be done - set priorities. And then watch how people develop on their own, without your help.</description></item><item><title>Soulash 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulash-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/soulash-2/</guid><description>Game Description Soulash 2 is an intriguing RPG in which you step into the shoes of an exiled god seeking revenge. The expansive procedurally generated world is a playground replete with simulated history, a dynamic economy, and a huge number of races, factions, and creatures just waiting to be interacted with. The power to conquer and rebuild this world lies in the hands of the player, who wields divine powers and abilities.</description></item><item><title>Arma Reforger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-reforger/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-reforger/</guid><description>Game Description Arma Reforger is an action game that places great emphasis on the realism of what is happening and allows you to fight on a huge territory of 51 square kilometers. The action takes place during the Cold War. Players can create their own unique scenarios in Game Master mode. The shooter allows you to return to Everon - a microstate with Cold War Assault. Essentially, Arma Reforger acts as a modifiable platform, inviting participants to create their own stories and combat scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Stronghold: Definitive Edition brings medieval England to life in a strategic and addictive game. In this classic real-time strategy, gamers will have to restore a destroyed kingdom, unite disparate forces and fight the insidious villains - the Rat, the Pig, the Snake and the Wolf. The story takes place on a war-torn frontier where the king has been betrayed and the kingdom is on the brink of collapse. The user will have to go through a series of missions - from lifting sieges and capturing enemy castles to building grandiose fortresses and defending against continuous assaults.</description></item><item><title>Cavalry Girls</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cavalry-girls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cavalry-girls/</guid><description>Game Description Cavalry Girls is an exciting top-down shooter that immerses you in a futuristic world where brave and fearless girl soldiers fight unforgiving enemies. This addicting game seamlessly combines action, strategy and customization to deliver an immersive gaming experience. In a world where the versatile mineral &amp;ldquo;jade&amp;rdquo; fuels a bionic revolution and sparks conflict, players take on the role of commander of a team that directs mechanized armor-piercing girls to defend a besieged city from enemy forces.</description></item><item><title>Endless Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endless-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Endless Dungeon belongs to the Roguelite and Action genre. The title is directly related to the Endless franchise. It includes several global turn-based strategies, as well as one hybrid of Roguelike and Tower Defense. So this is the second roguelike in the series.
The name of the project is similar to Dungeon of the Endless, a previous game from the same developers. And for good reason, because both projects have a lot in common.</description></item><item><title>Sumerians</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerians/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sumerians/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay of Sumerians is based on the story of 3000 BC in Mesopotamia, a time of rapid settlement growth and the development of Sumerian cities. The player will play the role of a ruler and will build his own city, manage resources, plan future infrastructure and try to cope with the economy.
In the process you only have to improve the city, build and manage the economy, there are no wars or attacks, but there will be numerous obstacles created by the population or nature.</description></item><item><title>InfraSpace</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/infraspace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/infraspace/</guid><description>Game Description InfraSpace gives users the opportunity to become mayors of the cities of the future. This city-planning simulator uses a sci-fi setting. Users manage Martian colonies. Gradually, these settlements grow into megacities. The indie title offers relaxing gameplay. In InfraSpace, gamers mine resources, build buildings, and satisfy the needs of the population. There is training and sandbox mode. You can place residential buildings, set up concrete steel mills and other factories, and build roads.</description></item><item><title>Moonstone Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moonstone-island/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/moonstone-island/</guid><description>Game Description Moonstone Island is a life-sim with collecting creatures, immersing you in a huge open world full of adventures. The game has 100 islands to explore, promising an exciting journey like no other. As someone who has visited this enchanting world, I can say that Moonstone Island offers a truly unique and exciting experience. You step into the shoes of a novice alchemist, following village traditions. Your task is to undergo alchemy training on a floating island in the sky.</description></item><item><title>ABRISS - build to destroy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abriss-build-to-destroy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/abriss-build-to-destroy/</guid><description>Game Description ABRISS - build to destroy is a simulator based on physical laws. The gameplay is focused on building an atmospheric layer that destroys physics. The user has access to many designs that can crash into specified targets and destroy them. The story campaign gradually opens up access to new details, which will allow you to destroy large creations and observe entropy in digital and futuristic landscapes.
Opportunities in construction and destruction:</description></item><item><title>The Matchless KungFu</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-matchless-kungfu/</guid><description>Game Description The Matchless KungFu immerses users in a world where martial arts are at the forefront. The gamer can choose the path of any warrior he likes and go on a journey through these lands. Be a loner or join a group of like-minded people - you can choose any convenient way. Only the decisions made will shape the character’s story, throwing him into different circumstances, giving him complete freedom of action in certain aspects.</description></item><item><title>Baldur's Gate 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldurs-gate-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baldurs-gate-3/</guid><description>Game Description Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 is a continuation of the cult turn-based RPG, in which you will take control of a small squad consisting of unique characters. Each party member is of great importance to tactics and represents an individual with his own character, history and abilities. Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 invites you to explore the large open world of the Forgotten Realm.
The plot does not act as a direct continuation of the previous part, however, illithids appear in the narrative - they are also mind flayers.</description></item><item><title>Techtonica</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/techtonica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/techtonica/</guid><description>Game Description Techtonica is a factory construction and management simulator. Compared to many other similar games, this title stands out in that all actions here must be carried out from a first-person view. The second feature is that the plant itself is underground. Unlike most sandboxes, there is an end goal. There is also end-game content. Here you need to extract resources, build and move objects, stretch conveyor belts, automate production, craft improved tools to be able to go even deeper.</description></item><item><title>Space Reign</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-reign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-reign/</guid><description>Game Description Space Reign is an exciting project that combines several colorful formats. In addition to the main storyline, there is a sandbox mode in which you can freely explore the universe and engage in open-ended gameplay. Here you need to try different strategies, experiment with the configuration of ships, discover hidden secrets and rare resources. One of the product&amp;rsquo;s strengths is its attention to detail and immersion. The universe feels alive - bustling space stations, bustling trade routes, clashes with friendly and hostile factions.</description></item><item><title>Age of Fear: Total</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-fear-total/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-fear-total/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Fear: Total is a comprehensive package that combines the titles in the series into a single whole. It brings together past releases, future updates and downloadable content - all designed to provide a rich experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a longtime fan or a newcomer, the set offers a unique opportunity to delve into the series' expansive universe. Over 100 hours of gameplay promise a world filled with different characters, factions and challenges.</description></item><item><title>Darkest Dungeon 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon-2/</guid><description>Game Description Darkest Dungeon II, an exciting and intense roguelike game, immerses players in a nightmarish world on the brink of the apocalypse. In the game you have to become a brave leader, assemble a squad, equip your trusty stagecoach and go on a difficult journey through a crumbling landscape. As you plunge into the depths, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon discover that the biggest threat may come from your squad.
The combat system, renowned for its innovation in the original Darkest Dungeon, makes a triumphant return in the sequel.</description></item><item><title>Staffer Case: A Supernatural Mystery Adventure</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/staffer-case-a-supernatural-mystery-adventure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/staffer-case-a-supernatural-mystery-adventure/</guid><description>Game Description Staffer Case: A Supernatural Mystery Adventure is a supernatural mystery adventure set in a fictional London in the 1960s, where people with unique skills, known as staffers, find themselves at the center of increasingly strange incidents. The user will have to take the place of Notrik, a detective from the Mana affairs department, who is tasked with unraveling a series of crimes. Unlike ordinary criminal investigations, this title requires a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>Meet Your Maker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/meet-your-maker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/meet-your-maker/</guid><description>Game Description Meet Your Maker invites you to plunge into a post-apocalyptic world, where each level is created by gamers themselves. You have to fight both alone and in pairs with a friend, building cunning labyrinths of terrible traps and guards at your bases in order to protect the most valuable thing - genetic material. As Guardian of the Chimera, a living experiment created to save life on Earth, you must capture other players' bases and extract even more material from them.</description></item><item><title>Spectator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spectator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spectator/</guid><description>Game Description Spectator can please fans of Internet folklore. This game is inspired by popular urban legends. Here you can go Backstage, visit Slenderman’s habitat and visit other locations. It&amp;rsquo;s full of all kinds of references. The video game is a representative of the point-and-click survival horror genre. The indie title uses a first-person perspective. Before you start, you can choose one of 3 difficulty types: normal, hard and nightmare. There are 6 levels (days) in total.</description></item><item><title>Master of Magic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/master-of-magic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/master-of-magic/</guid><description>Game Description Master of Magic (2022) is a remake of the once classic project, which at one time attracted the attention of a large number of people. Users, as before, will have to go a long way through the territory of two neighboring worlds - Arcanus and Mirror - in order to face the strongest sorcerers for the title of the strongest. In total, there are 14 different wizards to choose from with their own unique abilities, who, among other things, are representatives of different schools.</description></item><item><title>In Nightmare</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/in-nightmare/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/in-nightmare/</guid><description>Game Description In Nightmare allows gamers to plunge into a dark atmosphere where they have to take control of a boy who has lost his beloved. The protagonist will make his way through dangerous locations where monsters live. The project is a horror adventure game with elements of an action platformer, where you need to overcome various obstacles on the hero’s path, solve puzzles, deal with monsters and look for the right path out of the frightening kingdom of darkness.</description></item><item><title>ZERO Sievert</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-sievert/</guid><description>Game Description Plunging intoZERO Sievert, you will have to go on dangerous journeys through the post-apocalyptic expanses of a dying world, taking you to the terrain of a desolate alternative race. Taking control of one of the characters, you have to go on dangerous adventures, delving into creepy and gloomy places filled with strange phenomena and creatures that live beyond the limits of human vision.
Adventures in ZERO Sievert immerse you in an atmosphere of loneliness and independent survival in wild conditions, full of unexplored places and unexplored locations through which the protagonist will have to wander and look for useful items for life support.</description></item><item><title>Silver Nornir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silver-nornir/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/silver-nornir/</guid><description>Game Description Silver Nornir invites gamers to plunge into an exciting world where the fate of the entire world is at stake. This is an exciting old school RPG in a fantasy setting. Survivors of two disasters are ready to fight to the end to stop the end of the world. But they need your help! Exciting adventures and exciting battles using magical gems and combo techniques with friends and allies await you.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord/</guid><description>Game Description Mount and Blade 2 Bannerlord is a role-playing game with elements of medieval wars, the action of which takes place 200 years before the start of Part 1. In this sequel you will find an improved combat system and an enlarged game world - Calradia. Fight with hundreds of troops under your command and take direct part in the battles as one of the soldiers. You can storm enemy fortresses and destroy fortifications with siege weapons in Mount &amp;amp; Blade II: Bannerlord.</description></item><item><title>Lost Eidolons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-eidolons/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-eidolons/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Eidolons is a tactical role-playing game that allows you to plunge into the world of dark fantasy. The combat is made in a turn-based style. The action takes place in a world called Artemesia. Starring the adventurer Eden. He, along with a small detachment, is trying to fight for the free future of the empire. During the game, you can switch between turn-based combat and NPCs to strategize and try to find a way to outsmart your opponent.</description></item><item><title>Stardeus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardeus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardeus/</guid><description>Game Description The city-planning simulator Stardeus will plunge you into a cosmic world where there are no familiar objects, and, of course, there are robotic systems, spaceships, and advanced artificial intelligence that helps with everything. The main character, in the role of AI, is called upon to restore order on a large space cruiser, simultaneously building his own colony and introducing automation into the spheres of life of the newly built city.</description></item><item><title>Cult of the Lamb</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cult-of-the-lamb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cult-of-the-lamb/</guid><description>Game Description InCult of the Lamb, finding himself in the lands belonging to the false prophets, the gamer is invited to found his own cult, creating a powerful community of admirers. In an adventure game with roguelike elements, the player needs to spread his word to the forest dwellers, gradually making various forays into countries and regions in order to try to expand the sphere of influence of his religion, making it cover all regions.</description></item><item><title>Alaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaloth-champions-of-the-four-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Action RPGAlaloth: Champions of The Four Kingdoms takes the player into the magical Middle Ages. The story begins in the Valley of Storms - a place where four legendary peoples intersect: Humans, Elves, Dwarves and Orcs. It is here that the cruel god Alaloth is imprisoned. From the very kingdom of the dead, he poisons all kingdoms with his evil. Soon monsters, storms, diseases and mighty dragons will strike this world.</description></item><item><title>Raft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/raft/</guid><description>Game Description Raft is a first-person survival sandbox in which the player will have to survive on a small raft and explore new lands. The main character will begin his journey by waking up hungry and dehydrated on a small wreck of a ship. Get food and drink by catching garbage floating past the hero on the waves. To catch the item, you can use the hook. Find useful items and materials to craft a mug, light a fire, and filter sea water.</description></item><item><title>Attack at Dawn: North Africa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/attack-at-dawn-north-africa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/attack-at-dawn-north-africa/</guid><description>Game Description Attack at Dawn North Africa is a military-strategic project that takes participants into the conditions of the North African campaign during the Second World War. Players will lead the Axis or Allied forces, taking command of battalions, divisions and air forces across the vast expanses of Libya and Egypt. Set across a vast map stretching from the Gulf of Sirte to the Suez Canal, the action spans the period 1940 to 1943.</description></item><item><title>Nemesis: Lockdown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nemesis-lockdown/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nemesis-lockdown/</guid><description>Game Description Nemesis: Lockdown immerses users in dark adventures that are designed for multiplayer playthroughs with a team. Users will survive and fight off the monsters that are in the dark. You have to cooperate with your partners or go into solo mode. The project is a survival horror game where you need to perform step-by-step actions and think through your moves in advance. The game is based on a board game, which shows a sci-fi setting.</description></item><item><title>Dorfromantik</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dorfromantik/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dorfromantik/</guid><description>Game Description Dorfromantik - strategy in low-poly style. The game encourages you not to think about military strategies and operations. enjoy peaceful buildings and development of your lands. Game mechanics of Dorfromantic combine classic RTS and puzzle. Create a village, developing and expanding, building new buildings on hexagonal tiles.
Explore a procedurally generated world filled with diverse and colorful biomes. Complete tasks to fill locations with new life and create truly unique worlds.</description></item><item><title>Teardown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teardown/</guid><description>Game Description Teardown is a robbery simulator in a variety of conditions prepared by indie developers from Tuxedo Labs. Stylistically, the project was made using a voxel graphic component. This solution made it possible to implement complete destructibility of all available objects in the location. This freedom opens up the possibility of performing operations in a variety of ways, improvising on the fly. The gamer will have at his disposal explosives and a sledgehammer for destroying all kinds of surfaces to penetrate the territory, as well as several types of vehicles of different sizes for loading valuables and other things that need to be stolen according to the terms of a particular task.</description></item><item><title>Stacklands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stacklands/</guid><description>Game Description InStacklands you have to build a village, completing various levels in the style of a deck-building battler. Users will collect food, build buildings and fight monsters on a special field using ability cards. It will be possible to use combinations of cards. For example, when you move a “village dweller” to a “berry bush”, “berries” will appear, which the city dweller will consume as food and get a chance to survive.</description></item><item><title>Total War: WARHAMMER 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-3/</guid><description>Game Description GameplayTotal War: WARHAMMER 3 is a mixture of turn-based strategy and RTS. It is necessary to gather an army and move it around the global map, capturing all areas. By extracting resources and recruiting units, you will need to create settlements. You can enter into diplomacy with different factions, enter into alliances with them, or declare war. The economic part of Total War: Warhammer 3 is presented by TBS mechanics, while battles take place in real time.</description></item><item><title>Noble Fates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</guid><description>Game Description The fantasy world of Noble Fates immerses you in adventures taking place in a fairy-tale kingdom. A group of gods oversee the plane of human material existence while mortals vie for control over territories and new lands. The main character is Contra, who is a demigod and capable of influencing people and other inhabitants of the planet. It will be possible to manage entire colonies of settlers in order to achieve prosperity for the future great civilization.</description></item><item><title>Inscryption</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inscryption/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inscryption/</guid><description>Game Description Inscryption is a card adventure with roguelike elements that focuses on the fact that the darkness still hides many unknown secrets. The strategy is made in an escape the room format, has multiple puzzles and a terrifying atmosphere. The user is transported to the goblin&amp;rsquo;s hut, where he needs to embark on dangerous adventures to find out what secrets are hidden in this building. The events take place in a forest house, where the protagonist is trapped by some sinister creature who wants the guy to play board games with him.</description></item><item><title>The Riftbreaker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-riftbreaker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-riftbreaker/</guid><description>Game Description The Riftbreaker is a survival adventure role-playing game that has some mechanics taken straight from real-time strategy and action games. The project has dynamic gameplay, using an isometric camera to create the most convenient and complete view around the female protagonist named Ashley Novak. She has a powerful invention of mankind - a combat mech named &amp;ldquo;Mr. Riggs&amp;rdquo;, which helps to most effectively fight the various monsters that inhabit the planet Galatea-37, where the single-player campaign takes place, designed for dozens of hours of gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Erannorth Chronicles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/erannorth-chronicles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/erannorth-chronicles/</guid><description>Game Description Erannorth Chronicles combines an RPG and a card game. It&amp;rsquo;s also a sandbox. There is no complete single plot here. The indie title invites users to entertain themselves: explore the open world, fight monsters, upgrade their character, and participate in random events. You can also go treasure hunting or take tests. This CCG has a high barrier to entry due to the large number of deep mechanics that gamers have to figure out for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Cookie Clicker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cookie-clicker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cookie-clicker/</guid><description>Game Description Cookie Clicker lives up to its name. This is a clicker about earning cookies. The title is considered one of the first such games. The project developed and popularized an entire genre.
Initially it was a browser. Here is an improved version of Cookie Clicker. The re-release boasts an achievement system with 500 achievements, 600 improvements, the ability to exchange some goodies for others, and receiving constant upgrades. There are also mini-games here.</description></item><item><title>Rise Eterna</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-eterna/</guid><description>Game Description The story of Rise Eterna follows Lua as she attempts to uncover the secrets of her own origins. The gameplay combines tactical elements and RPG in a Japanese animated style. The user will assemble a squad of characters with special skills and characteristics. A squad can have up to 14 wards. The heroes will go through brutal battles, dungeons and boss encounters.
As the player progresses, he discovers a dark and mature story centered around the relationship between two lost souls.</description></item><item><title>Demeo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demeo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/demeo/</guid><description>Game Description Dark fantasy in Demeo plunges a party of adventurers into dangerous adventures where they have to fight against monsters. The game is made in the form of a role-playing turn-based adventure game, which you can play using virtual reality glasses. The project combines the dungeon crawler genre and tactical strategy, allowing you to take turns on the field and clear locations from opponents. Gamers will extract loot from enemies and strengthen their characters with found artifacts and things.</description></item><item><title>Totally Accurate Battle Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/totally-accurate-battle-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Totally Accurate Battle Simulator is a crazy tactical war game, heavily tied to physics. The battles take place in real time using weapons from different eras. The game is built on the laws of physics, so you can witness the most incredible combat in the history of video games!
One of the main features of the game is its caricature and the creation of the most insane atmosphere of battles.</description></item><item><title>Dyson Sphere Program</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dyson-sphere-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dyson-sphere-program/</guid><description>Game Description Dyson Sphere Program is a space simulator that allows you to develop your base and explore the galaxy. Go into the vastness of outer space to colonize distant planets. Build an intergalactic factory using the power of the stars. Design and plan production chains. Collect resources and develop your base. Start your journey as a small workshop and progress to the Dyson Sphere - a megastructure that orbits the stars.</description></item><item><title>Founders' Fortune</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/founders-fortune/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/founders-fortune/</guid><description>Game Description Founders' Fortune is a fantasy sim where, in addition to building and defending a base, you need to monitor the psychological state of the heroes. The colonists reach the island empty-handed to settle in a new place. By collecting resources, they build houses and various objects. Construction begins with walls and floors, after which furniture is placed and the façade is put in order.
Colonists are the main element of Founders' Fortune.</description></item><item><title>Bridge Constructor: The Walking Dead</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-the-walking-dead/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-the-walking-dead/</guid><description>Game Description Bridge Constructor: The Walking Dead is a collaboration between two famous franchises. “The Walking Dead” is a famous series based on a comic book, “Bridge Builder” is an arcade simulator of a construction worker using ragdoll animation and a realistic physical model that follows the laws of the real world. The gamer will have to join a group of survivors in a universe where an apocalypse has occurred due to the appearance of zombies due to an unknown disease.</description></item><item><title>Stirring Abyss</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stirring-abyss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stirring-abyss/</guid><description>Game Description Stirring Abyss is a turn-based strategy with role-playing game elements. Uncover the ancient secrets of the undersea depths in a twisted and mystical story inspired by the works of famous writer Howard Phillips Lovecraft. The main character is the captain of the surviving underwater crew of the submarine Salem. The shipwreck occurred during the Cold War. The soldiers survived, but found themselves at the ruins of an extinct civilization.</description></item><item><title>Neighbors back from Hell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neighbours-back-from-hell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neighbours-back-from-hell/</guid><description>Game Description Neighbors back From Hell is a re-release of the famous adventure puzzle game with charismatic main characters. The player takes on the role of a young guy named Woody, who was unable to make friends with his grumpy neighbor in an apartment building. To teach the evil man a lesson, the protagonist organizes the filming of the TV show “Neighbors from Hell,” which was continued for a second season.</description></item><item><title>Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squad/</guid><description>Game Description Squad is a military tactical first person shooter game. This is a multiplayer game with an emphasis on realism. An important role is assigned to team interaction between users. This project does not have a story campaign or single player modes. Instead, players in it capture points, destroy weapons depots, or hold the defense.
The title was originally called Project Reality. This was a modification for the second &amp;ldquo;Battle&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>The Dungeon Of Naheulbeuk: The Amulet Of Chaos</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-of-naheulbeuk-the-amulet-of-chaos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dungeon-of-naheulbeuk-the-amulet-of-chaos/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon Of Naheulbeuk: The Amulet Of Chaos is a humorous adventure set in the Naheulbeuk Universe. John Lang wrote a comedy series based on role-playing game parodies and heroic adventures. The developers decided to create a game based on the author’s universe. In a dungeon set in a fantasy setting, clumsy characters try to get their hands on treasure.
The RPG has complex tactical elements, with a dose of humor, unexpected surprises and ridiculous encounters.</description></item><item><title>Crusader Kings 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crusader-kings-3/</guid><description>Game Description Crusader Kings 3 is a global strategy that significantly expands the capabilities of the previous part. Crusader Kings 3 covers the time period from 1066 to 1453. Unlike the second part, you won’t be able to start the game at any time. The new map stretches from Spain to Burma and Mongolia, and from Scandinavia to Central Africa. The scale of the game is quadrupled. The points on the map represent not only counties, but also baronial possessions.</description></item><item><title>Factorio</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/factorio/</guid><description>Game Description The new planet should have everything to provide people with a comfortable, peaceful existence. Factorio is a sandbox in 2D graphics, where a new planet should be fully equipped for the future life of people. As soon as we arrive in a new place, we need to extract resources, assemble elements from them, and build structures so that people in the future can settle in and exist peacefully. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that the planet reacts aggressively to colonizers.</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Polytopia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-battle-of-polytopia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-battle-of-polytopia/</guid><description>Game Description The Battle of Polytopia is a turn-based strategy game with city builder elements. The events of the game develop in the fictional world of Square. There are 12 factions to choose from, one of which you can start a campaign for. Lead your people to world domination by expanding your sphere of influence and exploring new technologies.
You will explore the surrounding lands, develop various technologies and collect useful materials, on the basis of which your base will develop.</description></item><item><title>Persona 4 Golden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 4 Golden is a role-playing game about a group of friends who are able to summon demons from the other world. To do this, it is enough to shoot yourself in the temple. The events take place in the small Japanese town of Inaba. The children in Persona 4 are teenagers going through puberty. The heroes are investigating a mysterious series of murders.
The gameplay of Persona 4 Golden contains elements of a visual novel.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Battles 4 Guadalcanal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carrier-battles-4-guadalcanal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/carrier-battles-4-guadalcanal/</guid><description>Game Description Carrier Battles 4 Guadalcanal - Pacific War Naval Warfare dives into the air conflicts that unfolded in the Pacific during World War II. This strategy game puts you in the middle of the historical battles between the US and Japan in 1942-1943. Using a system of hexes and counters, the title tasks you with outflanking your opponent while defending critical areas or attacking key enemy positions. It&amp;rsquo;s all about decision making: when to strike, when to retreat, how to preserve your carriers and prevent the enemy from gaining a foothold.</description></item><item><title>Plutocracy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plutocracy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plutocracy/</guid><description>Game Description Plutocracy is a strategy in which you will be transported to the Golden Age, to the time when the first rich people of the United States of America just appeared. The gameplay will begin in 1870 and continue until the present day. During this gap, you will need to buy out many companies and put your name on the highest line of the board.
You will start from scratch and will earn and work to become a shadow ruler.</description></item><item><title>Railroad Corporation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railroad-corporation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railroad-corporation/</guid><description>Game Description Railroad Corporation is a railway construction simulator. You have to build your own empire from numerous freight and passenger routes. The game takes place in North America in the 19th century. The gamer will have to master the road to new lands. The player needs to establish friendly relations with various foreign enterprises. Build your own factories and populate residential buildings.
From the very beginning you will only have a small amount of money.</description></item><item><title>Age of Empires 2: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Empires 2: Definitive Edition is a re-release of the classic real-time strategy game released in 1999 under the name &amp;ldquo;The Age of Kings&amp;rdquo;. The game is famous for the fact that the player develops his civilization from the Stone Age to the Modern Age. The gameplay is based on the fact that it is necessary to hire peasants, gather troops, erect buildings, study maps, develop the era and explore new capabilities, technologies and, most importantly, destroy the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Little Big Workshop</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-workshop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-big-workshop/</guid><description>Game Description Little Big Workshop is a meditation game with calm, measured gameplay. The passage begins very strangely, someone left a game with figures of little human workers on his desktop. And this someone begins to fantasize that these little men come to life, and work is in full swing in their toy workshop. It is the fantasies of the mysterious protagonist that gamers will have to watch.
The strategy will not give the player time to rest, because orders will immediately begin to arrive, and the virtual phone will be ringing off the hook with constant calls to it.</description></item><item><title>Oxygen Not Included</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/oxygen-not-included/</guid><description>Game Description The player&amp;rsquo;s task inOxygen Not Included is to obtain food, water, oxygen, valuable resources and happiness for the duplicates - the inhabitants of his colony. The world settled into different parts, because of this, half of the people went to other planets, and the second part called themselves duplicates and decided to travel through space, flying between asteroids.
The idea of ​​the most hardcore survival simulator in a strategic shell - Oxygen Not Included - shows that maintaining your own base and several people on it is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Interstellar Space: Genesis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/interstellar-space-genesis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/interstellar-space-genesis/</guid><description>Game Description Interstellar Space: Genesis is a turn-based strategy on a global map that uses the popular setting of outer space in an alternative universe where the distant future has arrived. The world is inhabited by various races that have their own history, advantages over others and disadvantages that they try to hide. Before starting a new save, the player is given a choice of 6 available factions. There is functionality that makes it possible to create a unique state for governance.</description></item><item><title>Total War: THREE KINGDOMS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-three-kingdoms/</guid><description>Game Description Total War: THREE KINGDOMS is the first game in the series that recreates epic conflicts in Ancient China. The game combines a turn-based campaign of empire building and conquest with epic real-time battles. 190 AD. A beautiful but fragmented country awaits a new emperor and a new life. The player will have to unify China, create the next great dynasty and leave a legacy that will endure for millennia.</description></item><item><title>Baba Is You</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baba-is-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/baba-is-you/</guid><description>Game Description Baba Is You is a game in the popular puzzle genre. The project, developed by indie programmer Hempuli Oi, uses pixel graphics and a camera positioned high above, which creates conditions for greater visibility around the protagonist for faster response to changes. The single-player campaign is divided into 200 separate levels with increasing difficulty, introducing much more intricate puzzles on the way to the final scene, and the use of new mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers/</guid><description>Game Description The gameplay ofSpace Engineers is that you will build space stations, ships, and begin to study neighboring planets and passing asteroids, where you will find many useful resources. Control is carried out from the perspective of a person, a ship, a base, a flying station, and you can change the camera view from both the third and first person.
When you create a world, the game automatically generates a random sequence of planets on which you can find valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/slay-the-spire/</guid><description>Game Description InSlay the Spire the main task of the gamer is to climb to the upper levels of a tower consisting of many rooms. During the passage, you can have one of 4 characters, collect a collection of cards, defeat intermediate enemies and defeat the main villain. The locations and forks of the tower are constantly changing, the whole process can be divided into three acts and at the end of each of them the main character must defeat the local boss.</description></item><item><title>Penkura</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/penkura/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/penkura/</guid><description>Game Description Penkura combines several genres: action, adventure, RPG and strategy. Gamers find themselves in a unique world where they have to survive and thrive in an alien environment. The title begins with users traveling through an ancient singularity and landing on the distant world of Karenos. Here they will have to collect resources, explore ancient ruins and build a base that will help them cope with the upcoming trials. The combination of different gameplay styles creates an atmosphere that requires strategic thinking and adaptation at every turn.</description></item><item><title>Bloons TD 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bloons-td-6/</guid><description>Game Description Bloons TD 6 (Bloons Tower Defense 6) is a 2018 action strategy game where the player will have to defend a fortress with the help of monkeys. The goal of the game is to destroy a stream of fast-moving balloons. The fewer goals missed, the greater the chances of winning. The balls differ in appearance and characteristics - new ones have been added in this part: purple, reinforced and impenetrable.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Two Crows</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-two-crowns/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Two Crowns is a cooperative microstrategy that tells about the brave, who has become a king and now he needs to gather his army. Having saddled the right horse, he goes on a long journey to expand the kingdom. He will be opposed by the army of greed, trying to take everything from him that he has set up with his own labor. The game offers to rush not only in European medieval landscapes, but also to see many radically new ones.</description></item><item><title>Kenshi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kenshi/</guid><description>Game Description Kenshi forces you to survive from the very first minutes of the game. An impressive RPG with an open world and the ability to create your own squad, the remaining player privileges are gradually revealed to us. For example, you can build your own buildings in any location, conquer them from other factions, create your own business, sell goods in peaceful settlements, craft whatever you want, explore the environment and do whatever you want.</description></item><item><title>RimWorld</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rimworld/</guid><description>Game Description A simulator of city planning and strategic base development on a planet unknown to the player. The player inRimWorld must build a base where the last forces of people are concentrated. To survive, get food, study the technology tree and understand what the planet wants from you is the main task of the player. The project itself is characterized by the enormous depth of built mechanics that you can apply to your buildings and the base as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Airships: Conquer the Skies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/airships-conquer-the-skies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/airships-conquer-the-skies/</guid><description>Game Description Airships: Conquer the Skies (2018) is a multiplayer sandbox indie action and strategy game developed by David Stark under his own publishing house for various platforms, including PC. Airships has extremely positive reviews on various resources. The game is truly loved by gamers from all over the world.
So what will you have to do? Build pixelated skyships in steampunk style! The buildings are shown in cross-section and from the side, and their modules are controlled by crew members.</description></item><item><title>Football, Tactics &amp; Glory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/football-tactics-amp-glory/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/football-tactics-amp-glory/</guid><description>Game Description Football, Tactics &amp;amp; Glory is a football team management simulator with strategy elements. As a coach, the player will need to identify the weaknesses and strengths of his opponent in order to identify unique tactics. With the help of a well-chosen strategy, you can defeat even a stronger opponent. Each match is like a puzzle where you need to find the key that helps you win. Each athlete on the field is a unique character, and you can even develop a relationship with each of them.</description></item><item><title>Just Shapes &amp; Beats</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-shapes-amp-beats/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-shapes-amp-beats/</guid><description>Game Description Just Shapes &amp;amp; Beats offers gameplay based on the sound of music and beats. The difficulty level of the game depends on the rhythm of the soundtrack. The user takes control of a blue square; Many difficulties await him ahead. In the process, the hero is helped by friends, with whom he fights enemies. The game supports online and local co-op with 4 players in Story Mode and Challenge Runs.</description></item><item><title>Conan Exiles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/conan-exiles/</guid><description>Game Description Conan Exiles is an amazing multiplayer survival game with RPG and action elements. Employees of the Norwegian company Funcom worked on the project. The project was released at the end of spring 2018. Stunning graphics are a rare quality that developers of various MMORPG games pay attention to. But this time everything happened exactly the opposite. Funcom, 10 years before Conan Exiles, had already released a similar game called Age Of Conan.</description></item><item><title>Frostpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frostpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Frostpunk is an economic strategy game, a simulator of city construction in extremely harsh climatic conditions, where there are no wars, but there is a main enemy in the form of global cooling. The employees of the main office of 11 bit studios worked on the creation of this project. The official release of the game took place in April 2018.
In technical terms, we have a three-dimensional strategy game, with a top-down view, a simulator of the leader of a surviving human population in the Arctic cold.</description></item><item><title>Bridge Constructor Portal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-portal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-portal/</guid><description>Game Description The Bridge Constructor Portal project was made into one big puzzle. We play as an employee of the Portal Nature Research Laboratory. Having a constructor under our control, we will build bridges, ramps and other objects in 60 different levels. Each built bridge will help the little men achieve a result - exiting a level to move to another, so Bridge Constructor Portal perfectly combines logical planning and tactical construction of levels.</description></item><item><title>Cogmind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cogmind/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cogmind/</guid><description>Game Description Cogmind is a sci-fi roguelike in which you play as a robot assembled from components of other machines. Cogmind combat is presented in a turn-based style. You can explore the big world, hack devices, quietly sneak into strategic places, or act directly and attack your opponents head-on. The gameplay does not limit you to actions. Play the way you want.
Your task is to assemble yourself from various modules.</description></item><item><title>Middle-earth: Shadow of War - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/middle-earth-shadow-of-war-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description The action takes place in the fictional world of the writer Tolkien. The Middle Lands are full of adventures for our player, so the plot unfolds from half of them. Events introduce us to the continuation of the previous part. Talion and Celebrimbor forge a new ring, which Sauron does not know about - he will not be able to influence it. The new ring carries with it another responsibility: inMiddle-earth: Shadow of War, Celebrimbor loses his freedom in exchange for a new One Ring.</description></item><item><title>Stick Fight: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Stick Fight: The Game is a multiplayer platformer with fighting game elements. Players control colorful people, overcoming obstacles and fighting each other. The main gameplay consists of moving, jumping and reacting quickly. On the path of the heroes there will be deadly obstacles that will take the lives of all those who hesitated even a little and did not react to the situation. Game features: from 2 to 4 players over a local or online network; physics-based combat system; about 100 well-developed and detailed locations; includes a level editor; various ranged and melee weapons; procedurally generated and contextual animations based on the system Totally Accurate Battle Simulator.</description></item><item><title>Total War: WARHAMMER 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-warhammer-2/</guid><description>Game Description Total War: WARHAMMER 2 is a turn-based strategy that invites you to immerse yourself in the gloomy campaign of the New World. The gameplay is highlighted by large-scale battles between six races. Enter the battlefield to save or destroy the world. Total War Warhammer 2 consists of two parts: a turn-based campaign in the open world and tactical battles in real time.
Play both in single mode and take part in multiplayer battles.</description></item><item><title>Divinity: Original Sin 2 - Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/divinity-original-sin-2-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/divinity-original-sin-2-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description In this game, elves and other heroes gather in one flock. InDivinity: Original Sin 2 - Definitive Edition even Rivellon has undergone significant changes. The developers completely remade the entire game. No one knows where to start.
The graphics in the game became more like realistic ones for some other world. There is nothing superfluous on the screen, and procasts, magical effects and the death of other heroes look better.</description></item><item><title>The Long Dark</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-long-dark/</guid><description>Game Description A game about survival in a world without electricity. The Long Dark is eternal darkness in locations, gorgeous graphics from developers who love the sky and stars as their second home. Players were pleased that the entire gameplay is divided into two modes. The first is a story-based passage of 5 episodes, the total duration of which is 60-70 hours, depending on how the plot is followed. The second mode is survival in an excellent open world, where you will have to keep an eye on the contents of your backpack, check for items, collect skins, fry meat, take refuge in shelters, furnish your own house or a small corner in a house for survivors, where the owner of this establishment will shelter you.</description></item><item><title>Ravenfield</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ravenfield/</guid><description>Game Description The team-tactical shooterRavenfield will allow you to plunge into furious battles, where you have everything - from tanks to fleets. There is a complete lack of storyline and even multiplayer. The latter fact is extremely unusual for projects of this genre. It would seem that it is interesting to play against bots and when there are no real users on the map. This omission at first glance is more than compensated for by a fairly developed artificial intelligence - opponents and allies behave extremely intelligently and together with them you can perform a variety of tactics using numerous commands and options.</description></item><item><title>Little Nightmares</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-nightmares/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/little-nightmares/</guid><description>Game Description Little Six is ​​a girl who was brought on board the ship as a servant. She, like many nomes - the characters of the game - hides her face for unknown reasons. In the game we have to get out from the lowest sector to the upper decks, but the levels will not immediately allow us to do this. First, the player needs to know that sinister hands will always hunt for us.</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Wildlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the new part -Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands - truly inspires what the developers tried to convict all players of. It must be said, but there is no plot in a third-person shooter. You independently write the story of your team, which is initially aimed at destroying the cartel that trades and produces drugs. But more on that later.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s worth discussing the inner world of Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands.</description></item><item><title>Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shadow-tactics-blades-of-the-shogun/</guid><description>Game Description Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun is a tactical stealth action game set in the Japanese Edo era (1603-1868). A conspiracy led by Kage-sama is carried out against the new shogun, after he was able to unite the lands of Japan. In order not to destroy the world, the ruler instructs his henchman samurai named Mugen to track down Kage-sama and his organization. For these purposes, the hero enlists the support of four companions - masters of secrecy and penetration.</description></item><item><title>Sid Meiers Civilization 6</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-6/</guid><description>Game Description A turn-based strategy from famous developers -Sid Meier&amp;rsquo;s Civilization VI, where the player&amp;rsquo;s main goal is to develop his own settlement from a small group of people. They build cities, become diplomats, politicians, officials, and make scientific achievements. The population of your city, and then the state, is gradually increasing, and you are moving towards capturing the land around you. Together with allies or alone, you fight against opponents controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Stellar Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellar-tactics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellar-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Stellar Tactics is an exciting journey through the unknown expanses of space. This game combines mechanics from a variety of genres, for example, from group tactical turn-based strategies or exploratory adventure games. The player is offered the role of a discoverer of many star systems that remained untouched during the colonization of space. There are 160,000 universes with their own stars and varying numbers of planets in them. The player always chooses what he wants to do - story missions or side activities that are not required to be mastered.</description></item><item><title>Niche - a genetics survival game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/niche-a-genetics-survival-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/niche-a-genetics-survival-game/</guid><description>Game Description Genetic survival game Niche - a genetics survival game will allow you to deal with the population of special foxes. To survive, you need to collect edible plants or hunt very nimble game that brings a large supply of meat. The gameplay feature is the gene. The game allows you to experiment with DNA and pair a dominant gene with a recessive one, and then observe the result. Then find a new nest of other creatures and hatch completely new individuals.</description></item><item><title>Dead Age</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-age/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Age has an excellent and non-linear story, consisting of many choices that lead to 6 different endings. You will have to carefully study the text of the tasks, otherwise the members of your squad of survivors will inexorably dwindle.
The point of the game is to survive as many days as possible, replenishing food supplies, tools and new survivors. But don’t think that everything is so simple, in addition to collecting, the game has daily events that will fill your every new day in the game with various difficulties or opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Dead by Daylight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-by-daylight/</guid><description>Game Description Dead by Daylight is an asymmetrical cooperative horror game inspired by youth slashers. The story centers on four survivors facing off against a fifth player who controls a bloodthirsty maniac. The defending team&amp;rsquo;s job is to do everything possible to ensure they aren&amp;rsquo;t dead by dawn. Finding yourself in the same location with the killer, you need to use the environment and interact with your partners, trying to resist the monster.</description></item><item><title>Hearts of Iron 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hearts-of-iron-4/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the fact thatHearts of Iron 4 is famous for its realism, the new part has completely redesigned the focus tree for individual countries and nationalities. The strategy, dedicated to the Second World War, invites you to play in countries such as Italy, Ethiopia, Spain, Japan and China. Two scenarios that differ in their dates: 1936 and 1939. In one of them you will take part in the Second Italo-Ethiopian War and the Spanish Civil War, and in the second you will see how Japan invaded China, and the Second World War was fought.</description></item><item><title>Stellaris</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellaris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stellaris/</guid><description>Game Description Real-time strategy -Stellaris - immerses us in outer space, where we become kings of the galaxy from the very first minutes. The gameplay surrounds you with a huge number of ships and their types. For example, merchant spaceships will travel between different planets and sell/buy resources, reconnaissance ships will be able to explore new distances, and construction ships will help occupy - for friendly purposes - a new planet and recreate an entire empire on it.</description></item><item><title>Don't Starve Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-starve-together/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;t Starve Together is a survival simulator in an unknown world, where our character, pre-selected in the editor, wakes up and immediately goes to look for firewood, because Maxwell said so. The game is cooperative, since the story passage is divided into 2 parts. The first is survival. It is built on three phases of the day: day, evening and night.
During the day, your character calmly survives, collects items, crafts new ones, eats and carries out orders for Maxwell.</description></item><item><title>XCOM 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/xcom-2/</guid><description>Game Description Twenty years ago, people signed an act of complete surrender of the earth to the aliens. Another civilization has shown that there is no hope for salvation, and therefore alien invaders have taken over the entire planet. At the beginning ofXCOM 2 we are shown a video from the current ruler of the planet (in fact, this is a staged, drawn character, he is controlled by aliens), who says that today is the day when the aliens captured us, and the earth plunged into peace; Today we celebrate 20 years of freedom.</description></item><item><title>Darkest Dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/darkest-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Turn-based strategy with a side view -Darkest Dungeon - developed in a dark style and with rogue-like elements. A huge number of characters will not let you calm down until everyone on the playing field creates the perfect combination for victory. Each battle with opponents is a fascinating tactical adventure, where victory is 80% knowledge of the game and 20% knowledge of logic.
Your characters are ordinary people with extraordinary health.</description></item><item><title>The Isle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-isle/</guid><description>Game Description The island on whichThe Isle takes place has a rich and varied environment that is randomly generated. All artifacts, items and events will be located in different places with each new launch. Players must team up to effectively explore the area, which contains many secrets, including various quest items that further advance the plot. The map contains an area of ​​16x16 square kilometers. Multiplayer survival game The Isle allows you to play with three different factions in three different modes:</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</guid><description>Game Description A new installment in the first-person shooter,Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Rainbow Six Siege is a game of multiplayer destruction. We will not just destroy the map to which we and our friends were sent, but we will build traps, plant a bomb, and all this at a distance of a bow shot. The technical equipment of the new part is made specifically so that you can blow up everything in the open location of each level.</description></item><item><title>Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes/</guid><description>Game Description Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes is a cooperative sapper simulator. You are locked up with your friends. No one knows where the explosives are, but instructions are issued on how to disarm them. They must verbally explain what elements the bomb consists of and ensure that the player, acting as a sapper, can defuse it.
Each round will be quite intense. Everything depends only on the correct and competent relationship between the participants.</description></item><item><title>Batman: Arkham Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-knight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/batman-arkham-knight/</guid><description>Game Description InBatman: Arkham Knight - a third-person action game, we eliminate this problem, and the Scarecrow himself too. After the events of the last part of Batman, Gotham City finally has a normal, friendly environment. Fights, robberies and murders continue, but if the protagonist does not hear about them, it means that everything is covered up by the police, or these are just rumors. Suddenly the Scarecrow appears and says that during the last incident he only used 100 grams of his drug.</description></item><item><title>Kerbal Space Program</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kerbal-space-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kerbal-space-program/</guid><description>Game Description In the space simulatorKerbal Space Program the player will lead the Kerbal race exploring the vastness of space. Be the one who guides them towards a brighter future, inventing new technologies, constructing many new mechanisms and helping in the exploration of the galaxy.
Start your journey in one of three modes. In “Career” you will need to monitor the education and training of your charges, as well as help in modernizing their devices.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elite-dangerous/</guid><description>Game Description Elite Dangerous is an online multiplayer game, the third part of the &amp;ldquo;Elite&amp;rdquo; franchise, which began in 1984. The player is given complete freedom to explore and travel, and has the opportunity to influence the storyline. The action takes place thousands of years later in the distant future on the territory of several million star galaxies. Most of the stars, planets, asteroids and other cosmic bodies that exist in the real world.</description></item><item><title>Cities: Skylines</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cities-skylines/</guid><description>Game Description The city-planning simulator -Cities: Skylines - is in the best traditions of the real game, in which its own physical laws were created to transfer them into gaming reality. On the territory of your new city, it will be taken into account that the profile road is built in one way, and the road at the airport - in another. It will count if you correctly lay the pipeline for the heating system, and also if you can show people that they live in a real paradise, and not just a metropolis where they want to buy them at the expense of shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Geometry Dash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Geometry Dash is a 2D arcade game aimed at hardcore level completion. You will take control of a unique character, which can be in the form of a geometric figure, to pass the most difficult levels and open up new opportunities in the gameplay. Here you will find more than 100 original and challenging missions, as well as the opportunity to create your own main character and share your results on the leaderboard.</description></item><item><title>This War of Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/this-war-of-mine/</guid><description>Game Description This War of Mine is a cross-platform platformer game with elements of survival for an entire group of people. At the beginning of the game, you are given several characters to control the group, and you develop them depending on the time of day. During the day, the characters live in a house located in a city besieged by rebels. They arrange their everyday life, help each other, perform joint tasks and craft the necessary items.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency is a first-person shooter, in which the developers focused on playing in cooperative or multiplayer mode, about the Iraq War. The protagonist is a member of the US PMC, and he is fighting against Iraqi insurgents. The player chooses one side at the beginning of the match, and after that a brutal fight begins between the two factions. The basis of the game is a confrontation between two teams, which include 16 people.</description></item><item><title>Kingdom Rush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kingdom-rush/</guid><description>Game Description Kingdom Rush is a project in the &amp;ldquo;tower defense&amp;rdquo; genre, in the style of the Middle Ages, interspersed with magic, creatures that do not exist in real life, like trolls, and real-time control of heroes with a choice of the direction and course of their attacks. This game received recognition on many platforms and later reached personal computers.
The gameplay is standard for the genre, the advantage over other projects is the refined balance and exciting, moderately difficult levels that challenge and force you to change battle tactics and constantly be on the alert.</description></item><item><title>Arma 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</guid><description>Game Description InArma 3 we regain our independence by playing as a neutral side of this war. Inside the universe of the third Arma - 2030. Key opponents are still fighting for independence in economic and commodity terms. Among the enemies, a new structural organization CSAT appears, acting as a military-political alliance. While the crisis rages in Europe, the United States is at odds with China in the Pacific.
More than 400 square kilometers of gaming space, where the player, playing the role of a NATO peacekeeper, will save his group from real traitors who show themselves at the beginning of the story campaign.</description></item><item><title>Total War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-war-rome-2-emperor-edition/</guid><description>Game Description InTotal War: ROME 2 - Emperor Edition we are allowed to play as one of Caesar&amp;rsquo;s three followers. This is Octavian, the adopted son of a former ruler who is obliged to become the ruler of Rome; Mark Antony is Caesar&amp;rsquo;s loyal friend and best military leader; and Lepidus, the man through whom Caesar achieved universal recognition. After Caesar was killed, chaos erupted within the Roman Empire. The foreign policy of the empire maintained proper balance, while civil war was taking place inside, and the territory was divided into three parts.</description></item><item><title>Europa Universalis 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/europa-universalis-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/europa-universalis-4/</guid><description>Game Description A new part of the real-time strategyEuropa Universalis 4, the multiplayer mode of which allows up to 32 people to play on one server. Based on the previous parts, we can say that there are no more spies in the game, since they upset the overall balance of the game. The magistrate system has also changed greatly as the city&amp;rsquo;s development has undergone significant changes. The trading system has improved the most.</description></item><item><title>Papers, Please</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/papers-please/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/papers-please/</guid><description>Game Description The fictional country of Arstotzka is a small world of the game’s protagonist, where he will check documents at customs every day. The plot ofPapers, Please - a puzzle game with an unusual approach and graphics, as well as the beginning of the simulator - shows the events with the main character winning the profession of a customs officer at a checkpoint in the lottery. His task will be to check documents and apply stamps.</description></item><item><title>Company of Heroes 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/company-of-heroes-2/</guid><description>Game Description The events ofCompany of Heroes 2 unfold before us in snowy Norilsk, where one of the largest Stalinist Gulags is located. NKVD officer Churkin comes here, who understands that he will not survive the next Stalinist purge of officers. In the Gulag he finds his comrade from the front, who is serving his sentence and preparing to be shot. Isakovich is the name of the character, he wrote a tome with the real actions of the commanders of the Red Army, for which he was sentenced to death.</description></item><item><title>Gunpoint</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunpoint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gunpoint/</guid><description>Game Description Gunpoint takes the user to the near future, where many interesting spy things have been invented. Richard Conway works as a spy for hire, performing a variety of tasks. One day he gets a special copy - hyperpants. This item of clothing helps you jump over huge distances, and also help you fall from a height without harm to your health. The protagonist receives a new task - to investigate the murder of an employee of a weapons company.</description></item><item><title>Age of Empires 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/age-of-empires-2/</guid><description>Game Description Age of Empires 2 is a re-release of the classic real-time strategy game with many different improvements. Many years later, this game still remains unique and serves as an example for many strategy developers to follow. In the game, the player will have to take control of a small settlement of a certain faction and lead it to victory and prosperity. Events take place in the Middle Ages, roughly starting from the fall of the Roman Empire and up to the Renaissance.</description></item><item><title>FTL: Faster Than Light</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ftl-faster-than-light/</guid><description>Game Description FTL: Faster Than Light - this project is a two-dimensional simulator of a space combat ship. The creation and publication of this media product was carried out by the Subset Games studio. The official release took place in the first half of autumn 2012. The gameplay is based on the interaction between the player and the crew of the combat starship.
The success of this space tactical strategy will depend on how successful this cooperation is.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Defenders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-defenders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-defenders/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Defenders is an interesting game that combines a huge number of different genres: action, strategy, role-playing, RPG. This game is initially designed for multiplayer connections. Before we start, we have to choose the most interesting character class, his equipment style and the color of the magic crystal. This item is the most vital for the hero; if its structure is disrupted, the character’s death may occur.
There are many different types of improvements in the game: hero characteristics, crystals and passive abilities, and most importantly, basic combat spells.</description></item><item><title>Sid Meier's Civilization 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sid-meiers-civilization-5/</guid><description>Game Description Sid Meier&amp;rsquo;s Civilization V is a strategy game with an RTS style, where we still build a civilization from primitive times to the present. You can choose from 18 strong powers of this world, within which you can add 7 wonders of the world, put in control a leader who has individual characteristics, and also does everything in his own way. The legendary turn-based strategy series introduces us to the sequel, in which a huge number of additional areas have been added.</description></item><item><title>Mount and Blade: Warband</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mount-and-blade-warband/</guid><description>Game Description Mount &amp;amp; Blade: Warband is a standalone add-on that brings many improvements and innovations to the game. New textures, object and character models, as well as sophisticated visualization settings. Change FSAA anti-aliasing, tone mapping and other effects in the settings. Modernized animations, improved combat system and the spirit of the heroes. People will flee if they are in imminent danger or, conversely, fight to the last if their morality is high.</description></item><item><title>Plants vs. Zombies GOTY Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-goty-edition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plants-vs-zombies-goty-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Plants vs. Zombies became the game of the year, winning in many categories. The developers invite us to once again plunge into battles in a small location in order to free ourselves from the shackles of various zombies, hold back all the ardor of the monsters and save the city by using the latest technologies in the agricultural industry. Among the primary weapons in strategy, we have a pea shooter, a cherry bomb and sunflowers, which we use to earn money to purchase new strategic weapons.</description></item><item><title>STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-empire-at-war-gold-pack/</guid><description>Game Description STAR WARS Empire at War - Gold Pack is a collection of real-time strategies based on the Star Wars plot. You will play the role of an army manager on one of the sides in an intergalactic civil war. Command units of the Empire, Rebels, Republic or other civilizations.
In Star Wars Empire at War, you will command your team, completing tasks and freeing planets from enemies. Visit Tatooine, Kashyyyk, Dagobah or other hot spots in the galaxy.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike: Source</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike-source/</guid><description>Game Description Emerging as a worthy competitor to its previous installment,Counter-Strike: Source is an updated version 1.6 in which players found both disadvantages and advantages. For example, in the new part, many weapons have a completely different bullet spread, which is why players had to get used to it for a long time. The ballistics and shooting technique have not changed, but the graphics and the “atmosphere of an open location” added additional charm to the game for fans of the first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>Stronghold Crusader HD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-hd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-hd/</guid><description>Game Description A real-time strategy with an in-depth system for leveling up your settlement -Stronghold Crusader HD - was released with an addition that allows you to display the picture on a large screen with good quality. The basis of the game remains the same: we develop, build a large army, attack the enemy, whoever he is, win and move on. **The game has 4 historical campaigns, which are divided into stages in history.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</guid><description>Game Description Counter-strike is a legendary multiplayer shooter, the founder of one of the most popular series in the history of the gaming industry.
The concept is simple but ingenious. Two teams - terrorists and special forces - are trying to destroy each other on the map. Terrorists have the ability to plant a bomb at one of the key points. and the counterterrorism department tries to predict which point the opponents will attack.</description></item><item><title>AGRONOM</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/agronom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/agronom/</guid><description>Game Description AGRONOM sends players to 22nd century Mars to build a working estate. You arrive on a specific piece of Martian land with a specific task. This mission involves creating a living space designed to fulfill the wishes of Grandfather Makar and dedicated to the memory of his late wife Sofia. The idea extends beyond the simple construction of buildings, seeking to recreate the atmosphere symbolized by pancakes with plum jam, pickled cucumbers and home-made moonshine.</description></item><item><title>Alchemist's Alcove</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemists-alcove/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alchemists-alcove/</guid><description>Game Description Alchemist&amp;rsquo;s Alcove takes the player on a journey through ancient lands, collecting components from defeated enemies to create spells, tools and weapons. The process of battle and discovery is central to the gameplay, and the remains of opponents become the basis for a growing arsenal. Heroes navigate the territories of warring factions using a grid-based map, pursuing the ultimate goal of creating the Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Stone through turn-based combat and exploration of the world.</description></item><item><title>Cultist Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultist-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultist-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Cultist Simulator is a role-playing card game that allows you to create your own unique card deck. The plot tells us about a magical world, in which they give the opportunity to find out all the mysterious and mysterious events that happened in the real world. You can go fight witches, find Masons and go in search of other adventures.
At the very beginning, gamers have the opportunity to choose starting cards, and then start completing missions and exploring a huge text world.</description></item></channel></rss>