<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Indi on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/indi/</link><description>Recent content in Indi on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/indi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A FISTFUL of YANKEES</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-fistful-of-yankees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-fistful-of-yankees/</guid><description>Game Description A FISTFUL of Yankes offers the player to lead a detachment of government soldiers sent to the American West in 1865 to combat desperate criminals and robber barons. On this post -war frontier, life and death solve weapons. The key task of the unit is to establish order by tracking the robbers attacking the settlers. However, this mission draws the fighters into a much larger conflict with serious consequences, going beyond initial orders.</description></item><item><title>Dice Gambit</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dice-gambit/</guid><description>Game Description Step -by -step battles in Dice Gambit allow us to plunge into tactical competitions, where the victory determines the cubes that affect the management of the characters. The game is designed for strategic miscalculations where a variety and excitement makes a bone throw. Each result on dits permits to obtain a limited number of actions for heroes fighting on combat arenas. The characters will be able to move, perform interactions with the environment or inflict damage to the opponents on the field.</description></item><item><title>The King Is Watching</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-king-is-watching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-king-is-watching/</guid><description>Game Description The King Is Watching is a unique combination of strategy, Roguelike and controls. In this Title, users take on the role of the ruler, whose presence affects the productivity of the kingdom. The central mechanics revolves around the strength of the gamer&amp;rsquo;s gaze, which dictates the effectiveness of various tasks, including resources, military training and much more.
At any moment in time, the ruler must choose what to focus on, balancing between agriculture, mining and protection from external threats.</description></item><item><title>Longstory 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</guid><description>Game Description Longstory 2 continues the established narrative with a large number of dates, developing friendly relations and difficult situations. The action takes place in the summer in front of a high school, immediately after the events of the previous part. During the party, in honor of Marseille&amp;rsquo;s return, a personality, known as Turkeyhawk, disappears home. This event gives the start of the main riddle, offering the player to find this character.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Mori</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-mori/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-mori/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Mori begins with the return of monsters to the world, which has long expelled them. The main task of the player is to get rid of the lands of these creatures and the victory over the great eternal dragon. The research process is built on a choice system that determines the movement and events in the dungeons. The structure is based on step -by -step mechanics combined with solutions during the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Merge Maestro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/merge-maestro/</guid><description>Game Description Merge Maestro suggests placing an emoji chip on a mesh field. These elements are combined with others of the same type to create stronger and more high -level units. The main task is to overcome the advancing waves of opponents using these improved tokens. After each round, Gamer chooses a new element for its set, expanding tactical opportunities for future clashes. Such a cycle of placement and fusion forms a key game process that requires step -by -step solutions to clean the field and survival.</description></item><item><title>Voidsayer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voidsayer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voidsayer/</guid><description>Game Description Voidsayer takes users to the world, captured by the abyss - all -consuming power, which leaves nothing behind. As one of the few survivors, you must accept this gloomy challenge, armed with a team of monsters. However, unlike others, you can repulse not with simple weapons, but taming and developing creatures. These are not just pets - they will become an integral part of your survival. However, there is one catch.</description></item><item><title>CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator sends gamers on a trip to the world of Windspell, a port city filled with potential and adventures. Users stand in place of a merchant, ready to create unique items that can change the fate of the city. This game is not just about the trade in goods, it is about how to pave your way through creativity. Whether you create intricate necklaces for royal mermaids or a weapon from the blood of dragons - each item has its own charm.</description></item><item><title>As We Descend</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</guid><description>Game Description AS We Descend combines Roguelike debiting with strategic gameplay. Gamers command forces in card battles against enemies in the post -apocalyptic city. The fate of mankind is determined by the tactical decisions made on the battlefield and in the political structure of the city. The project includes the creation and development of detachments using the found technologies. Each group has a special set of cards that can be expanded and modified.</description></item><item><title>Velocity Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/velocity-rift/</guid><description>Game Description Velocity Rift puts a player for driving a vehicle with a view of the top, setting him the task of competing on tracks located on a secluded island. A single gameplay is built around 3 separate game modes, each of which has its own rules and conditions for victory. Promotion on these diverse competitions requires a constant concentration from the racer to pass complicated routes and maneuvers of computer opponents.</description></item><item><title>SpellroGue</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spellrogue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spellrogue/</guid><description>Game Description SpellroGue immerses players in a world captured by corrupted hollowers. You pick up weapons, but not blades and bows, but powerful spells, fed by unpredictable mana cubes. In this step -by -step game, based on the construction of the decks, spells are pronouncing the manipulation of these cubes. The desired combination will fall out, and you will release fire balls, earthen walls or ark explosions. But the bones are unstable.</description></item><item><title>Escape the Mad Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/escape-the-mad-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Escape the Mad Empire is a Roguelike Dungeon Crawler, promising a mixture of tactical battles and base control. Players collect a detachment of heroes whose survival depends on strategy and resourcefulness. The combat system requires an attentive approach. Each move, each action has weight. Using the area, shelters and objects becomes the second nature, when users move around the battlefield with high rates. The Title is not amenable to simple classification, combining the elements of Roguelike, RPG and Base-Building into unique experience.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/burden-of-command/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/burden-of-command/</guid><description>Game Description Burden of Command gives players a completely different idea of what projects can be in the theme of World War II. The local scale is considered here, and the focus is a small group of fighters. The gamer is given the opportunity to become the commander of this group, making important decisions in key situations. The guys have to visit hot spots around the world, from Western Europe and ending with Morocco, where the remnants of enemy forces were still based at that moment.</description></item><item><title>Die in the dungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/die-in-the-dungeon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/die-in-the-dungeon/</guid><description>Game Description Die in the Dungeon throws another set of cubes in the Roguelike genre. Forget about the meticulously compiled deck of cards. Instead, you collect your arsenal from a set of cubes, each of which indicates the action: attack enemies, treat wounds or control yourself a throw of fate. Each meeting becomes a gambling game, an exciting test of luck, where one throw can turn the course of the battle.</description></item><item><title>Dawnfolk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawnfolk/</guid><description>Game Description In Dawnfolk, the action of which takes place in a world covered by darkness. As a ruler of the kingdom lost to the shadows, you must restore and protect your people. With the help of a mystical creature, Luer, you must navigate in the darkness and work on the restoration of light on Earth. In the center - research, resource management and decision -making when you restore your kingdom from scratch.</description></item><item><title>Those Who Rule</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/those-who-rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/those-who-rule/</guid><description>Game Description In Those Who Rule, users find themselves in the place of recruits who fell into a whirlwind of deception and war. Title begins with the team of characters that should be guided in a complex world where decisions have weight, and unions change from the wind. Users gain allies, each of which has special abilities and personal history, and spend them through more and more complex battles. The main goal is to reveal the true forces standing behind the current conflict, while trying to be one step ahead of enemies and changing loyalty.</description></item><item><title>The Dead Await</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-dead-await/</guid><description>Game Description The Dead Await immerses users in gloomy adventures, where it is necessary to survive during the zombie apocalypse. The users will have to participate in cruel step-by-step battles with walking dead, gradually gathering their own deck with cards-abilities. It will be possible to configure and pump the characters in the detachment, engage in the study of the open world, to extract resources, trade with secondary NPS and manage its own caravan for survival.</description></item><item><title>Dungeons &amp; Degenerate Gamblers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-degenerate-gamblers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-degenerate-gamblers/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeons &amp;amp; Degenerate Gamblers throws a crooked ball into traditional card games. Forget about the ink, peaks and trefches. Here the king is a blackjack, but with a highlight - a Roguelike -inventor, that is. Imagine yourself in a dull lighted tavern, smoke falls from your tube while you evaluate your opponent at a shabby table. But instead of swords and witchcraft, your weapons are cards. Unique cards that can improve your hand, ruin the enemy’s deck or even affect the course of history.</description></item><item><title>Endgame of Devil</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endgame-of-devil/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endgame-of-devil/</guid><description>Game Description Endgame of Devil will put a player in the role of a devil who is entrusted with protecting the castle. The task is to stop the adventurers' units trying to take possession of treasures in your possessions. To do this, it is necessary to call on and command the servants to reflect the onslaught of the invaders. Combat clashes are automatic, moving the gameplay towards the strategic formation of the detachment before the battle.</description></item><item><title>Caves of Lore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/caves-of-lore/</guid><description>Game Description Caves of lore-role-playing game with two-dimensional pixel art style graphics and from above. Moving by locations occurs in real time. During the study of the area, you can neutralize traps, look for secrets and hack chests with loot. Equipment can be of different colors. Coloring depends on the rarity of the object. There are hundreds of things here. Battles with monsters are held in step -by -step mode. In battle, heroes can move around the cells.</description></item><item><title>Squishcraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squishcraft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squishcraft/</guid><description>Game Description Squishcraft is a series of logical tasks focused on manipulating blocks in a closed space. The fundamental action is the movement of cubes, however, the main feature is the ability to squeeze them together under certain conditions. Such compression can combine several elements into one or change their properties, irrevocably transforming the current state of the riddle. Players have to carefully think through each movement, since one wrong step is able to change the location of the objects and make a dead end.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Day Racer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rainy-day-racer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rainy-day-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Rainy Day Racer sends drivers to the wet streets of the Scottish city, where strong rains are constantly pouring. The main occupation is the races for a while, with the main goal - to overcome the ring routes for the shortest period. Movement in urban conditions requires control over the machine with an ongoing bad weather. Each attempt is a single competition with a stopwatch, aimed exclusively to establish a personal record or ahead of other riders in the leaders table.</description></item><item><title>Tower of Time</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tower-of-time/</guid><description>Game Description At sunset, artara gradually open up new horizons of another world. Thousands of pages of books, manuscripts and video stations tell us the plot of Tower of Time through the prism of distant views on the plot from the game character. The new system in the RPG game is revealed from the first minutes of gameplay. We create a unique character who does not know what is happening in his world.</description></item><item><title>Solitaire Battle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/solitaire-battle/</guid><description>Game Description Solitaire Battle combines the mechanics of the card game with the progression of the Autobatler&amp;rsquo;s Horned. Players are faced with opponents where key interaction is a party in the solitaire of three peaks. Each card taken from the field or from the deck is converted into an offensive or defensive action, creating automated combat sequences. The main task is to strategically disassemble the layout to win enemies, while forming a set of random pool of tools that contribute to powerful synergies and encouraging new combinations in each passage.</description></item></channel></rss>