<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Simulators on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulators/</link><description>Recent content in Simulators on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuga: Melodies of Steel 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</guid><description>Game Description fuga: Melodies of Steel 3 unfolds the story of desperate efforts. The inexplicable disappearance of Malta forces the group of children to head to the forbidden cave, where they are leaded by a mysterious voice to Taranis - a powerful armored vehicle, which was considered lost. The determination to find Malta returns them aboard this combat vehicle, starting a direct attack on the central regions of the Berman Empire.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>Contractville</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contractville/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contractville/</guid><description>Game Description Contraactville beckoning lovers of simulators with their history about how to turn from rags into rich. Forget about gorgeous houses, you start with a penny in a port town. But do not be afraid, starting a tycoon! In Contractville you can build your own fate yourself by demolition, construction and interior design. And what is interesting: you can sell your architectural masterpieces at the auction, turning your sweat and ingenuity into cold, firm money.</description></item><item><title>Clink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</guid><description>Game Description Clink puts a player in the role of a woman living in voluntary solitude in an old house only with her cat and buried memories. The central conflict lies in the question of whether its experiences are symptoms of a prescribed disease or a manifestation of something otherworldly. One morning, the familiar way of the heroine is broken: one of the doors is locked, the key disappeared, and a metal ringing echoed in his head.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2 - fishing simulator, offering to participate in a huge number of tests and demonstrate many different techniques. Use a wide set of tools and gear: feeder, overlap, spinning, classic float and much more. Continuation of the game significantly improves the graphic component, adds many mechanics, tools and improves all aspects of the gameplay. More and better - the basic principle of Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2.</description></item><item><title>Doloc Town</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</guid><description>Game Description Doloc Town - this is a farm simulator in the conditions of post -apocalypse. The player accepts the role of a beginner whose task is to build an existing economy in the desert territory. The environment pushes to the study of its predominantly unexplored areas. Key activity includes the landing of cultures, the construction of the necessary structures and the consistent search for information about the past of this changed world.</description></item><item><title>Tank Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Tank Squad transfers players during the Second World War, to the most intense territories, whose fate will affect the outcome of the clash. The user will visit the role of captain of the tank detachment, taking part in the iconic battles of that time. Scenarios will include historical battles for a single -user or cooperative passage of three participants at the same time.
In the multiplayer, each gamer is able to control their own team, or unite among themselves and become a separate crew member.</description></item><item><title>Teddy's Haven - A Fantasy Inspired Shop Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teddys-haven-a-fantasy-inspired-shop-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teddys-haven-a-fantasy-inspired-shop-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Teddy&amp;rsquo;s Haven - A Fantasy Inspired Shop Simulator puts the player in the role of the owner who controls a small store on the periphery of the mysterious island. The shop specializes in the sale of potions, weapons and various magic wonders for a variety of clientele. Among the buyers are adventurers preparing for campaigns, magicians in search of rare components and other mystical creatures. The main cycle of classes is to replenish the shelves, manage the inventory, set up each aspect of the interior and hiring employees.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Mogul 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Mogul 4 — это текстовый бизнес-симулятор, ставящий человека во главе киностудии. Система позволяет создавать кинофильмы и мини-сериалы на основе библиотеки из более чем 14 000 исходных материалов или собственных идей. Ready -made paintings can be planned for global film distribution or for distribution through streaming service. The process includes the formation of accurate budgets, the conclusion of agreements on rental in 19 foreign territories and the management of advertising expenses.</description></item><item><title>Synergy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</guid><description>Game Description synergy dedicated to survival on a hostile planet. In this urban planning strategy, players have to develop their city, face natural cataclysms and make the right decisions that will certainly have consequences. Explore this constantly changing world, preserving the happiness of the townspeople in extreme weather conditions.
Gamers will control the weather, seasons, extreme conditions and natural disasters. The main goal is to build a city where residents will be happy and satisfied, respecting the natural needs of the inhabitants and living in harmony with the local fauna and flora.</description></item><item><title>A Merchant's Promise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-merchants-promise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-merchants-promise/</guid><description>Game Description A Merchant&amp;rsquo;s Promise Places the player in the stylized Middle Ages, concentrated on commerce and transportation through direct physical handling of objects. The path begins with the role of a worthless merchant, who is instructed to manually move goods using a system based on physics. There is no usual inventory here; Each object needs to be raised, carried and placed, which creates a constant risk of dropping or even throwing a luggage.</description></item><item><title>Learning Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</guid><description>Game Description learning factory - a simulator that is designed to create an automated process of processes and, most importantly, understand one simple truth: what do cats want? The gameplay allows you to head the Kotovod factory. It was once closed, but now it has been possible to renew the process and create your own cat store. Learning factory gameplay largely gives an idea of ​​how machine learning works.
Your factory is analyzing a huge database, trying to study the behavior of pets.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Zephon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in Zephon have to take control of the remnants of mankind in order to survive on the territory of the Earth. On the planet, there are few areas that are not suitable for life, and most of the cities were destroyed. In wild territories are mutating creatures that they gather in small groups and begin to hunt for surviving people. Alien robots with damaged systems roam on the surface, and the aliens themselves are hidden and try to secure survival.</description></item><item><title>Citadelum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</guid><description>Game Description Citadelum throws its hat to the ring of strategic games, offering the experience of building cities with an admixture of mythology and strategic conquests. Ancient Rome serves as a background for the game: gamers take control of a nascent settlement and should turn it into a lively metropolis. Resource management is a paramount task for any novice urban planner. But Citadelum is not only overgrown suburbs and towering monuments.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>E-Startup 2: Business Tycoon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/e-startup-2-business-tycoon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/e-startup-2-business-tycoon/</guid><description>Game Description E-Startup 2: Business Tycoon throws you headlong into the world of product management. Development, production, sale - all this is on your conscience. Fasten the belts because you will also have to juggle with resources, monitor the constantly changing market and make sure that your office does not turn into a productivity cemetery. Do you think you have the next big thing? Title will allow you to bring your concept from a sketch on a napkin to a store shelf.</description></item><item><title>Le Mans Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Le Mans Ultimate - The official game FIA ​​World Enduraance Championship and &amp;ldquo;24 hours of Le Man&amp;rdquo;, promises exciting experience to both experienced riders and beginners. Runned in early access, the game offers to try the exciting season of 2023 with official cars, legendary tracks and online media. Sit behind the wheel of ultramodern hypercars from manufacturers such as Toyota, Ferrari and Porsche, and recreate the battles on prestigious tracks.</description></item><item><title>Underdogs</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underdogs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underdogs/</guid><description>Game Description Underdogs - this is the Title in virtual reality, in which gamers fall into the very heart of the gloomy Cyberpanovsky world, where the fight of the furs reigns. The project does not hold back itself, pushing you with fierce enemies in cruel contractions. From the very first minutes, gamers plunge into the world of risk, where every step can mean the difference between life and death. Here you need to not just fight, but survive in conditions when the danger lurks around every angle.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Option</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-option/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-option/</guid><description>Game Description In the game** Nuclear Option** you will find yourself in the cabin of modern combat aircraft on the battlefield of the near future, where the roar of engines and the crackling of tracers draw a bright picture of air battles. Each plane, from agile fighters to bulky bombers, is asked in hands, and its cabin pulsates with vital information while you scan targets and evade fire. The world unfolds under you - a dynamic tapestry of vast landscapes, raging seas and bristling enemy objects.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the White Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of the White Sun transfers to the chaos of China of the 1920s, the period of riots and fragmented leadership. In this grandiose strategic game, you have to pave the way through a fragmented nation controlled by military leaders, rebels and political groups. The action unfolds at a time when various groups dispute control of vast territories and armies, each of which has its own goals, objectives and motives.</description></item><item><title>Pumping Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pumping-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pumping-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pumping Simulator 2 sends you on a trip to the world of management of gas stations. Start your entrepreneurial adventure by the sale of a classic car to get the funds necessary for the reconstruction of an abandoned gas station in a busy city. Your goal is to turn an abandoned station into a prosperous center for local residents and travelers. From the very beginning, you will build, expand and modernize your gas station.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-life/</guid><description>Game Description The developers** Tiny Life** were inspired by The Sims series, trying to transfer the gameplay to their own project. The gameplay presents pixel graphics and the vast capabilities of the simulator of the life of controlled characters. Before the start of the passage, the player can choose a certain group of people, one ward or use the function of creating.
In Tiny Life, the user will have to control all aspects of the life of a group of people living together in the same house.</description></item><item><title>Contraband Police</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</guid><description>Game Description Contraband Police - The simulator of the border guard in the first person. The player in the role of the commander of the border post makes an inspection of transport for the presence of smuggling on the border of the third world countries. The inspection tasks include: checking documents: inspection and permit for entry criminals &amp;hellip; or take a bribe. What? Nobody heard this! To carry out reports on the successful completion of tasks through the mail; the accumulated experience can be spent on pumping the department, buying new equipment or training dogs;</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Wrestling Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrestling-empire/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrestling-empire/</guid><description>Game Description In Wrestling Empire the player becomes a participant in the World Lightweight Championship. It is necessary to manage an athlete in the ring, apply his abilities and win rivals. The battles are presented in real time with extensive visual effects. This part includes a smooth frequency of personnel and modern graphics, while leaving the atmosphere of retro-style.
This version has more functions and capabilities in pumping and battles. The user will face unique opponents with the original characteristic and special skills.</description></item><item><title>On the Western Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</guid><description>Game Description On the Western Front - this is a tactical strategy, the action of which unfolds against the background of the First World War, namely on the infamous Western Front. Users take on the role of the division commander, who are instructed to manage various aspects of military operations in one of the most exhausting and complex periods in history. The Title emphasizes the harsh realities of the trench war, where the soldiers are faced with many problems, from the constant threat of enemy fire to the constant need to manage resources.</description></item><item><title>PayDay 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</guid><description>Game Description Re-join thePayDay 2 gang as Dallas, Hoxton, Chains or Wolfe, who have come to Washington to rob and make a lot of money. Put the mask on your favorite hero and set off to carry out your next crime, in which you will need to overcome many obstacles before reaching your goal.
Now you will have a wide variety of contracts to choose from, from which you can choose any one.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description Salvus: aries throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item><item><title>Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth abandoned long walks and romantic novels with stars that are found in other farm sigas. It’s enough just to click a cursor. The Title with a strategic farm bias with your head immerses you in the creation, construction, collection and management of a prosperous farm. Starting from a modest site, do not allow the initial sizes to deceive you. Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth is all about potential.</description></item><item><title>Drive Beyond Horizons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Beond Horizons Refuses the line path and throws gamers into a huge, constantly changing world. Fasten the belts and get ready for the study - the procedurally generated landscapes make each game unique. Leave the comfort zone and choose your own route. Travel through spacious deserts, lush forests, on any roads (or their absence). But this is not just an excursion trip. Drive Beond Horizons is fraught with many secrets and difficulties that have to be solved.</description></item><item><title>Let's Build a Zoo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</guid><description>Game Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Zoo - A bright sandbox with a simulator elements, which provides players with the opportunity to build their own zoo. It is required to install enclosures, buy rare animals, hire employees for service and much more. It is allowed to cross animal DNA, producing more than 300,000 unique rocks into the world.
In order for the reserve to function, it will be necessary to hire veterinarians, trainers, cleaners, repairmen and other performers who support their lives in the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item></channel></rss>