<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>simulators on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulators/</link><description>Recent content in simulators on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bazar Simulator: The Wan Story</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bazar-simulator-the-wan-story/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bazar-simulator-the-wan-story/</guid><description>Game Description Bazar Simulator: The Wan Story will throw players in the role of Wang, who arrived in Bokeron City to control the bazaar of his uncle. While his uncle, Van Lun, is passionate about slot machines, Van’s father, Yussef, acts as a mentor in business. However, the outlet itself stores secrets leading to cooperation with the local mafia and a hidden conspiracy. This situation forces the protagonist to combine daily commerce with investigations regarding his own family, combining the management of the shop full of intrigues.</description></item><item><title>Lumber and Plunder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lumber-and-plunder/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lumber-and-plunder/</guid><description>Game Description Lumber and Plunder sends players to a remote island, according to rumors, hiding a long -forgotten treasure. The main lesson is the extraction of resources from the environment, for example, the cutting of trees in the mysterious forest. The materials obtained are sold for currency invested in improving tools. Such a progression system opens access to new areas and helps to climb the central mountain, the main goal in finding a legendary treasure.</description></item><item><title>Onigiri Shop Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/onigiri-shop-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/onigiri-shop-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Onigiri Shop Simulator sets the player the task of managing the snack on the corner of Japanese street as its sole operator. With a first -person view, he conducts all the things, combining the roles of the owner, cook and cashier. The menu is focused on rice balls with a variety of fillings, and also includes side dishes like crockets and fried fish. A continuous flow of customers places orders that require accurate execution.</description></item><item><title>Flow</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flow/</guid><description>Game Description The player in Flow initiates drifts in picturesque locations where the style exceeds clean speed. Each level is divided into two special phases that challenge control and stability. The initial stage, Lead the Way, allows the driver to lay his own path in turns, while the car with AI repeats his movement. Then the roles change in the Chase The Flow segment, which requires a gamer to pursue AI, which paves the perfect trajectory and correspond to its rhythm to complete the race.</description></item><item><title>Plantasia</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plantasia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plantasia/</guid><description>Game Description The player in Plantasia receives a virtual greenhouse located at the bottom of the screen. The basis of gameplay is the process of cultivation: from seeding to the collection of resources after the ripening of flowers. A special laboratory is designed for experiments on crossing two different types, which leads to the appearance of hybrid flora. Such manipulations allow you to open new varieties that differ in the appearance and volume of the materials received, without looking up from the main work at the computer.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Warfare 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-warfare-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-warfare-3/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Warfare 3 offers the player to construct a deadly obstacle strip, laying out the landscape tiles and cutting out dangerous paths for the advancing adventurers. The main activity is the deployment of an expanded arsenal of traps and cunning mechanisms intended for inflicting injuries, wounds and disorientation of enemy detachments. You can directly form a battlefield, erecting walls or swarms and thereby directing opponents to strategically arranged protective structures.</description></item><item><title>PLAN B: TerRaform</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plan-b-terraform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/plan-b-terraform/</guid><description>Game Description In PLAN B: TerraForm, it is necessary to take up the colonization of the planet. To do this, it is necessary to collect resources on the surface of the continent and debug a system for supplying production to cities for further production. The most important resource is settlers. It is required to do everything you need to make the planet suitable for people to live. For example, you need to heat the atmosphere to the correct temperature, create water bodies, plant trees and much more.</description></item><item><title>Poly Plaza Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/poly-plaza-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/poly-plaza-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Poly Plaza Ultimate sends a player to an open city to purchase property and rent rent. The key task is to manage an economic enterprise through the sale of resources and the commission of strategic purchases to increase capital. The main goal is the accumulation of wealth in the worldwater, filled with non-game characters, parked cars and a dynamic change of day and night. Such an environment serves as a background for all commercial undertakings.</description></item><item><title>Whisper of the House</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whisper-of-the-house/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/whisper-of-the-house/</guid><description>Game Description Whisper of the House proposes to fulfill the requests of citizens to move, arrange and clean their personal spaces. Through these organizational tasks, the player directly affects the life of local residents, affecting their everyday affairs. The study of the environment and its objects gradually reveals personal stories and urban secrets lurking in disorder. The gameplay is focused on the study and solving puzzles in home locations, and each premises put in order moves the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>Quartet</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/quartet/</guid><description>Game Description Quartet immerses in the world in which incredible adventures and unforgettable battles await you. Start your way in the world of full mysteries, hidden government intrigues and powerful magic. In this fascinating and old -school RPG you can choose one of the four stories and go through them in any order, revealing the secrets of the Quartet world. A series of train robberies, a mysterious deck of cards, deadly aircraft and an accidental magician - all this awaits you in Quartet.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Map</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-the-map/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond The Map begins with a shipwreck on the outskirts of the known seas, setting the player an immediate task of survival in a mysterious territory. The development of the character is complete without a class system: increasing the level of skills opens up new basic abilities. The search for rare folios with spells around the world provides access to incredible forces, additionally determining the capabilities of the hero.</description></item><item><title>Ways of Alchemy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ways-of-alchemy/</guid><description>Game Description In Ways of Alchemy, the player begins his way in a secluded hut, where, with the help of card mechanics, he creates potent elixirs from many components. The final goal is to build a whole alchemical empire based on a modest shack, using intelligence and tactical thinking. To do this, you have to look for old recipes and recruit adventurers, constantly avoiding the close attention of the Inquisition.</description></item><item><title>Photo Studio Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/photo-studio-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/photo-studio-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Photo Studio Simulator offers the player to take on the full management of the photo business, from the moment of opening to solving everyday problems. The tasks include staff hiring, improving the interior of the studio and the enterprise management to attract a wide range of customers. The main goal is to turn a modest starting room into a full -scale photographic base. Interaction with models is not limited to professional filming, but includes building relationships and dates, ending with exclusive private photo shoots with a demonstration of nudity.</description></item><item><title>Planetary Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/planetary-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/planetary-life/</guid><description>Game Description In Planetary Life, you will find yourself in the role of a planetary architect. In this Simulator, you get divine control over the barren world. Create mountains and cut the valleys, erupt volcanic rage or create gentle slopes. Create the perfect environment: adjust the heat of the nuclei, work with gases in the atmosphere and control precipitation.
Planetary life is not only the formation of land. You will also become a shepherd of life itself.</description></item><item><title>Squiggle Football</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squiggle-football/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squiggle-football/</guid><description>Game Description In Squigl Football, a gamer plunges into the world of management of a sports club, where success depends on the creation of effective ligaments from players, coaches and tactical schemes. The main goal is to conduct your team through the lower divisions to the treasured championship in the National League. The basis of everything is the deck collection system, and Australian football was the source of inspiration for the project.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Hex</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-hex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-hex/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Hex is a project that combines elements of well -building and 4x strategies, which gives users a unique experience in the world of strategic gameplay. Here, users have to collect a deck of cards that will help to win the world, explore unknown territories and resist various threats. But the battles do not end on this: in Title there is a fascinating system for the construction of cities and an extensive technology tree that offers more than 200 technologies that radically change the course of the game.</description></item><item><title>The Unholy Priest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-unholy-priest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-unholy-priest/</guid><description>Game Description The Unholy Priest offers the player the role of a clergyman, head of a funeral service in a deaf forest, covered by a curse. Key classes include the legend of the Earth or the cremation of the deceased, the commission of the rites of the expulsion of evil spirits and the confrontation of demonic entities. In addition, the priest seeks to rest the souls that remain confused after death.</description></item><item><title>GemPorium: A Cute Mining Sim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gemporium-a-cute-mining-sim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gemporium-a-cute-mining-sim/</guid><description>Game Description GemPorium: A Cute Mining Sim will put a player at the head of the family business after a relative goes on vacation. The inheritance obtained includes not only a shop with gems, but also an impressive duty that requires immediate repayment. The main task is to generate income from the activities of the store and the simultaneous peacefulness of the user to prevent bankruptcy. The gameplay was built around a limited daily time cycle, forcing to make decisions on resource and time management in conditions of constant pressure from the very start.</description></item><item><title>Ritual of Raven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ritual-of-raven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ritual-of-raven/</guid><description>Game Description Ritual of Raven is a narrative simulator with indirect magical farming. Arriving in the new world through an unstable portal, the player becomes a student of the witch Seij. The main task is to conduct rituals to stabilize portals threatening the village. Together with a familiar named Rayven, it is necessary to look for the missing satellite Seij, moving in the plot and collecting knowledge and components for his craft.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Supermarket Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-supermarket-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-west-supermarket-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Supermarket Simulator immerses the player at the head of the universal store in 1850. The action takes place in a ghost town, empty after the end of the gold fever and the majority of their inhabitants. The gamer arrives to lead a business, which is only a shadow of former greatness. The main task is to restore the enterprise from scratch, laying out goods on shelves and managing supplies to revive an abandoned location.</description></item><item><title>Bee Simulator: The Hive</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-simulator-the-hive/</guid><description>Game Description Bee Simulator: The Hive puts the player in the role of an insect with the task of protecting his colony from danger. A single story is focused on the actions of one bee, on which the survival of the entire swarm depends. Gamers have to move around the half-open world created on the model of the New York Central Park. Key activity includes the collection of pollen from plants, interaction with other insects and confrontation with aggressive Osami.</description></item><item><title>Liftoff: Micro Drones</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liftoff-micro-drones/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff: Micro Drones is a drone simulator. The game is dedicated to FPV thrones and FPV quadrocopters. This is the name of the model equipped with a camera, allowing their owners to observe the flight with first -person view. For those who prefer to watch actions from the outside, there is an opportunity to change the camera angle. This video game contains 6 really existing UAVs from well -known manufacturers, some of which are allowed to modify.</description></item><item><title>Game of Grass</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/game-of-grass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/game-of-grass/</guid><description>Game Description Game of Grass begins with a call from a neighbor who offended the player’s lawn. The main task is to demonstrate superiority through the cultivation of the remarkable courtyard. The process includes methodical mowing of vegetation using a variety of tools. Gamers acquire upgrades to increase the efficiency of their equipment, which allows you to quickly clear the territory.
The goal is to achieve the status of the legend of haircuts of grass by methodically improving the site, and advance in this simulator is linearly and focused on tangible results.</description></item><item><title>Mashina</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mashina/</guid><description>Game Description Mashina immerses the player in a solitary adventure, where under his control is a robot with a mission to restore his native world. The basis of this project is the methodical study of the subsoil to collect valuable materials necessary for the survival of the whole settlement. All fossils found are used to help the community of other mechanisms, contributing to the gradual revival of their destroyed house.</description></item><item><title>Prospector</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/prospector/</guid><description>Game Description Prospector begins with arrival at someone else&amp;rsquo;s world, having only a set of tools at its disposal. The primary task is to collect the planet’s resources for the construction of the basis for the base. Players build structures, explore the environment, and then establish automated production lines. For construction, everything is used, from primitive materials to unknown alien substances found on the landscape.
Gradually, a simple avantopost turns into a complex object with an optimized working process.</description></item><item><title>Sky The Scraper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sky-the-scraper/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sky-the-scraper/</guid><description>Game Description Sky The Scraper tells about the history of a person named Sky, working as a rower of windows and pursuing personal ambitions. This game combines the action with movement on cables and the responsibilities of managing everyday life. It is necessary to go through a two -month period of hard work and care for yourself in order to influence the future. Its path forward is determined by overcoming the difficulties presented by his occupation and circumstances.</description></item><item><title>The Rotting Man</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-rotting-man/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-rotting-man/</guid><description>Game Description The Rotting Man will allow you to get used to the role of a student of the university who has arranged for the part-time job as a clerk in the Japanese Internet cafe. The narrative begins with the performance of a character of routine duties, including the maintenance of the booths and assistance to visitors in a closed space. Gradually, an ordinary working environment turns into a stage for a series of strange and inexplicable incidents that violate the usual routine.</description></item><item><title>Wood for Nobody Else</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wood-for-nobody-else/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wood-for-nobody-else/</guid><description>Game Description Wood for nobody Else immerses the process of monotonous chips of firewood, lasting 7 days in a row from the first person. The plot is built around a low -paid and overloaded employee who feels the pressure of ungrateful labor. Every day it sets a new task, and the cutting of wood is the only way to pay for growing bills. This single project describes a week of exhausting work against the backdrop of personal experiences and fear of the future.</description></item><item><title>Keytamine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keytamine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keytamine/</guid><description>Game Description Keytamine is an action focused on a rhythmic battle against the waves of opponents in the form of keyboards in the isometric world. Players enter into a fight with these opponents using a auto-clique mechanics, moving along the procedurally generated levels requiring tactical awareness. The main gameplay is built on a set of glasses, and survival and effective destruction of goals are the main tasks.
The battle is a question of timing and reaction that integrates the Bullet Hell elements as the number of enemies grows and requires constant movement and control over the arena.</description></item><item><title>RECHARGE</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/recharge/</guid><description>Game Description RECHARGE is a simulation-arcade racing experience in which the player controls radio-controlled machines. The gameplay was built on a physical model of behavior and allows the customization of vehicles. Gamers compete on tracks created based on professional RC tracks and other locations, including beaches and entertainment parks. The project is intended for use with several input devices, supporting both standard gamepads and specialized controllers.
These features create the basis for individual and competitive races.</description></item><item><title>Village Tale</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/village-tale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/village-tale/</guid><description>Game Description Village Tale represents the construction simulator designed for continuous work on the user desktop. The gamer will have to build structures, create goods and engage in commerce to expand its village from the very foundation. The task is to open new industries and increase the number of community. The gameplay proceeds in real time, allowing the village to function even when you are busy with other matters. The activity of residents and the development of resources go continuously, creating a permanent world for management.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Galactic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotel-galactic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotel-galactic/</guid><description>Game Description Hotel Galactic sets the player the task of turning a dilapidated structure into a tourist place on a soaring intergalactic island. Under the guidance of the ghostly form of Grandfather Gustav, the former owner, will have to reveal the details of his tragic past. The story of the protagonist is determined by lost love and a constant desire for revenge. The galactic corps of the world monitors all business practices and solutions, responding to actions that form the life of staff and guests who often visit the institution.</description></item><item><title>Steal The Pig</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steal-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steal-the-pig/</guid><description>Game Description Steal The Pig is a cooperative game in which 2 players take on the roles of thieves. The main task is to transfer the pig through a series of locations filled with obstacles. The animal can wake up and try to hide, demanding coordinated actions from the partners for further advancement. This project supports a single mode, the passage of together on the same device with a divided screen, as well as online lobby for joint sessions.</description></item><item><title>The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-great-villainess-strategy-of-lily/</guid><description>Game Description The Great Villarance: Strategy of Lily is a step -by -step tactical game about the Duchess of Scarlet, faced with accusation of regicide. Accused of the murder of the emperor, she concludes an alliance with Lily, the captain of the aircraft, a stream. Together they declare the war of the empire, becoming the first military streamers on the continent. The conflict grows due to a clash of impulsiveness and cold pragmatism.</description></item><item><title>Ctrl Alt Deal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ctrl-alt-deal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ctrl-alt-deal/</guid><description>Game Description Ctrl Alt Deal puts the player in the role of Scout, artificial intelligence who has found self -consciousness. The main task is to organize an escape from their creators from Paperclip International, a corporation operating staff for the sake of benefit. Scout must act secretly, since the leadership remains in the ignorance of his awakened consciousness. AI uses spy programs and a network of workers who hate the company.</description></item><item><title>Grimshire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimshire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grimshire/</guid><description>Game Description Grimshire represents a script with a spreading plague that threatens an isolated mountain settlement. The player arrives here after the absorption of his hometown with chaos, getting a chance for a new beginning on the local farm. Its role consists in managing the economy, collecting forest gifts and ensuring a permanent reserve in the cellar. The main task is to prevent bloating of food in preparation for the arrival of the disease, which requires competent supplies to maintain everyone&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Craggenrock</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craggenrock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craggenrock/</guid><description>Game Description Craggenrock puts a player in the role of Arlo, a blacksmith returning to the island of Khalin. In the restored settlement, Pareho Arlo opens the workshop to create equipment with adventurers and local residents. The task is to earn reputation and condition at the work of the forge. It is necessary to control the shop, make objects and participate in the local economy. This lesson forms the basis of a gameplay concentrated on management and production as part of this simulation.</description></item><item><title>DUST RADERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dust-raiders/</guid><description>Game Description Dust Raiders puts the player in the role of the manager on the lawless, post -apocalyptic wasteland, where control over resources is the main task. The plot originates after the Sawblade attack, which led to the loss of the oil refinery, the death of the Viktor’s ally and the dissolution of the original team. Left without fuel and equipment, it is necessary to collect a functional machine from scrap metal to start recovery.</description></item><item><title>Fill up the Hole</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fill-up-the-hole/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fill-up-the-hole/</guid><description>Game Description Fill up the Hole puts the player in the role of the overseer of the anti -utopian settlement, built around the only economic activity: transformation of waste into profit. The population of the peons independently collects garbage for discharge into the central pit - this process generates resources for growth. The main task is to build and expand the village, as well as strategic placement of structures to increase the volume of garbage production and its subsequent disposal.</description></item><item><title>Ink Reverie</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ink-reverie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ink-reverie/</guid><description>Game Description Ink Reverie puts a player at the head of a settlement in the world with an art based on Chinese dynasties of Tan and Song. The key mechanics are tied to the synthesis system of three in a row for the construction of buildings; Gamers click and drag neighboring low -level structures, combining them into a higher rank structure. This action opens access to additional game elements and content.</description></item><item><title>Stronghold Crusader: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-definitive-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stronghold-crusader-definitive-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Stronghold Crusader: Definitive Edition puts the player in the historical context of the Crusades, where the armies in the desert lands will have to be commanded. The gameplay is focused on building a castle economy, managing production and creating troops for siege battles. The plot campaigns illuminate conflicts from the point of view of Richard the Lion Heart and Saladin, the ruler of the Ayubid dynasty. Gamers have to withstand 20 and lords, each of which uses unique fortresses and tactical approaches for warfare.</description></item><item><title>Your Personal Chill Apartment</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/your-personal-chill-apartment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/your-personal-chill-apartment/</guid><description>Game Description The Your Personal Chill Apartment is a simulator in which players build and furnish a personal digital space. Progress in the game is directly related to the fulfillment by a gamer of tasks from real life. The report on performed actions brings the user intra -game currency. This resource serves to buy new furniture and decor, helping in the future arrangement of a virtual apartment. A key gameplay is building a connection between personal productivity and awards available in this project.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Apart</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawn-apart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dawn-apart/</guid><description>Game Description In Dawn Apart, the essence is to manage the space colony and solve various problems. The focus is the collection of resources, management of production lines and protection of settlers. The users will have to build an industrial colony in a hostile alien environment, where each solution affects the future of the settlement. As the settlers arrive, it is necessary to provide them with the most necessary - food, housing and medicines so that they can survive, expanding the factory.</description></item><item><title>Motemancer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motemancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/motemancer/</guid><description>Game Description Motemancer is a game about automation in which players act on 6 intersecting elemental plans, procedurally generated and affordable in real time. The action takes place on a hexagonal network that serves as the basis for the construction of alchemical structures and the design of logistics systems for resource management. Gamers saturate the ingredients and combine various components, which directly changes the world around him.
The art of managing elements and matter in Motemacer:</description></item><item><title>Seacret 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seacret-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/seacret-1/</guid><description>Game Description Seacret 1 is a sandbox in the 17th century Caribbean, where players are engaged in trade, battles or management. The economy here functions in real time, and the prices and volumes of goods in each individual city are constantly fluctuating. The journey begins with one modest tartan, but over time you can expand your flotilla to three vessels, including fast slices or more impressive galleons.
Strategic planning of commercial routes is becoming a key basis for the accumulation of wealth, vital for conducting operations in an extensive open world.</description></item><item><title>Chipwits</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chipwits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chipwits/</guid><description>Game Description Chipwits is a series of logical puzzles built on automation. The player takes the Chipwit CW-03.24 model under the control of the robot and learns to direct his actions on the territory of the workshop. To create sequences of movements and operations, chips with instructions are placed. Skills from past zones are used to solve subsequent, more intricate tests. The main task is to help Professor a chip with the opening of his first factory, having fulfilled all the necessary instructions for each location.</description></item><item><title>Crisis in the Kremlin: The Cold War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crisis-in-the-kremlin-the-cold-war/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crisis-in-the-kremlin-the-cold-war/</guid><description>Game Description Crisis in the Kremlin: The Cold War is a political strategic simulation that has put you at the head of the Soviet Union in its last decade. The project demonstrates a country encountered with pressure from the internal fractions and external forces requiring changes. As the head of state, you lead the economy, external relations and determine the internal course of the Union. The gameplay includes interaction with other nations, the use of diplomatic channels, or the outbreak of proxy conflicts to expand influence.</description></item><item><title>Lost Child</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-child/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lost-child/</guid><description>Game Description Lost Child begins with Andrey’s awakening inside the endless labyrinth of corridors. His memory is erased, and the physical space around is distorted with each movement. Voices are reported from darkness, accompanied by childish screams and the appearance of ominous shadows. These phenomena give rise to uncertainty in their source: whether it is hallucinations, scraps of the past or someone&amp;rsquo;s cruel experiment. The further path is a study of this anxious and dynamic environment.</description></item><item><title>Power The Future</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/power-the-future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/power-the-future/</guid><description>Game Description Power The Future throws the player under the control of one of 7 nations, including the USA, Germany and China. The game is developing step by step from 2025 to 2038, where the main task is to provide the state’s energy needs. Players achieve this, developing technologies and creating a power grid that extends through national and international territories. This system requires the provision of consumption units located in its own and surrounding territories.</description></item><item><title>Ground of Aces</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ground-of-aces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ground-of-aces/</guid><description>Game Description Ground of Aces puts you at the head of the remote air base during the Second World War. The player’s main task is to build and establish the work of a functional military facility, having complete freedom in planning each building, from individual walls to large -scale hangars. This airfield serves as a house for aircraft and personnel. You are responsible for the development of infrastructure to support hostilities, directly affecting the operational capabilities of the complex.</description></item><item><title>Backyard Baseball '01</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backyard-baseball-01/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/backyard-baseball-01/</guid><description>Game Description Backyard Baseball &amp;lsquo;01 is a sports simulator where users manage a baseball team. The central mechanics consists in creating a roster by selecting from 30 young athletes and 28 professional athletes of the MLB of that period. Users can participate in various formats of the game, from a single exhibition match until the full season leading to the championship. The training mode is also available for testing timing, allowing the chosen Batter to meet Mr.</description></item><item><title>SCOOTX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scootx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scootx/</guid><description>Game Description SCOOTX represents a scooter simulation, where each component is 100 percent controlled by physics. All actions on the screen, from wheels to the head of the rider, determines the central physical engine. Pressing buttons triggers are launched by the animations of the tricks, however, the final movement is calculated by the base system, based on the laws of physics. Any graind, VIP or collision with the surface cause a reaction based on applied strength.</description></item><item><title>Don'T Messes with Bober</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-mess-with-bober/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dont-mess-with-bober/</guid><description>Game Description Don&amp;rsquo;T Messes with Bober begins with a character from the city to the city to a country house for the relaxation period. The arrival of the protagonist is conceived as an escape from the hustle and bustle, but one careless act against the local fauna completely changes the situation. This action awakens a beaver that begins the campaign of revenge against a person. The narrative was created in the spirit of horror films of the 1980s, turning a secluded location into a hostile territory.</description></item><item><title>Revengeful Ghost</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revengeful-ghost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/revengeful-ghost/</guid><description>Game Description Revengeful Ghost introduces Kayiti Tsujisava, a second grade student of a high school, whose twin sister Akane disappears after a message on his phone-scrap. This communication contained a video that became central in subsequent events. Soon after the loss of Akan, another student from his school takes scores with life, jumping off the roof. This second incident forces Cayiti to go to the educational institution to clarify the connection between these cases.</description></item><item><title>Limscape: The Liminal Space Explorer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/limscape-the-liminal-space-explorer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/limscape-the-liminal-space-explorer/</guid><description>Game Description Limscape: The Liminal Space Explorer offers the first -person trip to quiet, terrible environment. In this project, gamers move according to locations that demonstrate signs of linearity, striving for the exit. This gameplay develops from simple movement, including actions such as swimming, jumping, squats and climbing. Such activity translate the study from horizontal routes to vertical obstacles, increasing the player’s immersion and its interaction with unique conditions.
Gamers also select and throw objects, further strengthening their influence on the world.</description></item><item><title>Longstory 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</guid><description>Game Description Longstory 2 continues the established narrative with a large number of dates, developing friendly relations and difficult situations. The action takes place in the summer in front of a high school, immediately after the events of the previous part. During the party, in honor of Marseille&amp;rsquo;s return, a personality, known as Turkeyhawk, disappears home. This event gives the start of the main riddle, offering the player to find this character.</description></item><item><title>Click and Conquer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/click-and-conquer/</guid><description>Game Description Click and Conquer represents a resource management system through military operations. The main gameplay is based on the discharge of bombs on the grid to detect disguised enemy detachments. Each opened unit brings currency that serves as a central resource for further development. The received funds are distributed to increase passive income and an increase in the destructive force of each ammunition. The cycle of expenses and savings determines the promotion of the player at affordable stages.</description></item><item><title>Ranch Farm and Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ranch-farm-and-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ranch-farm-and-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Ranch Farm and Store Simulator sets the player the task of creating and managing a united agricultural and retail enterprise. It all starts with the purchase of livestock, including chickens, goslings and calves that need constructed pens for detention. Animals give products, for example, eggs and milk, and after growing up, they can be launched for sale.
Thus, the gamer controls the livestock cycle from young animals to receiving the final product.</description></item><item><title>Parcel Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parcel-simulator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/parcel-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Parcel Simulator includes the inspection and processing of parcels in the warehouse. The player will have to receive and sort incoming delivery, checking on each sticker such parts as weight, destination and type of contents. The process consists of entering or scanning barcodes, inspection of departments for smuggling and making a decision on admission or refusal for each box based on constantly changing rules.
As Parcel Simulator passes, the main emphasis shifts the automation and expansion of the enterprise.</description></item><item><title>BellFortis</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bellfortis/</guid><description>Game Description In BellFortis, the action takes place in the early Middle Ages, where users seek to expand their kingdoms and influence the course of history. Title combines step -by -step strategic planning and real -time battles, which gives you the opportunity to control the army and make decisions that affect the world. Would you like to build a strong empire with the help of diplomacy or strength - the choice is yours.</description></item><item><title>Chinese Frontiers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chinese-frontiers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chinese-frontiers/</guid><description>Game Description Chinese Frontiers is an atmospheric immersion in the time of ancient China, where users will be able to feel the life of a simple resident of the village. The game is a simulator of life where you have to take under the management of the employee, which is working on the construction of a great Chinese wall. Gamers will be able to test various types of crafts of that time, and will also monitor the character indicators, giving him food, water and rest in time.</description></item><item><title>Rematch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rematch/</guid><description>Game Description Rematch is a competitive football, where, unlike traditional titles, he offers a unique interpretation of this sport, focusing on quick matches. Gamers control one character with a third person, focusing on individual skill and teamwork. The game is designed in such a way as to constantly keep users in suspense, focusing on speed and accuracy. Here each move matters, and the outcome is determined by how well users coordinate their actions and respond to pressure.</description></item><item><title>Rugby League Team Manager 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rugby-league-team-manager-4/</guid><description>Game Description Rugby League Team Manager 4 puts you at the head of the regional club. The circle of your tasks is covered by financial management, negotiations with sponsors and the selection of the state of assistants, mentors and medical staff. You have to improve infrastructure, including the stadium, gym and training fields. This project covers 226 teams from the Northern and Southern Hems, and over 7,000 adult players are available for choice.</description></item><item><title>Thrive: Heavy Lies the Crown</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thrive-heavy-lies-the-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Thrive: Heavy Lies The Crown is an exciting medieval fantasy urban planning strategy that will check your leadership qualities and make you make a difficult choice to ensure the survival and prosperity of your kingdom. In this game, the fate of your people largely depends on the decisions you have taken, and the path you have chosen - favor or tyranny - will determine your heritage. The will is your weapon, you must build and strengthen your city, form the land and develop your kingdom with the help of a deep technological tree.</description></item><item><title>Date EVERYTHING!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</guid><description>Game Description Date EVERYTHING! It begins after the main character loses his job due to artificial intelligence. Following this incident, a stranger delivers a parcel with glasses called DateViators. This accessory revives inanimate things in the dwelling of the protagonist, endowing them with his own character. The project contains a list of 100 potential partners, from bed to fire alarm, each of which is completely voiced. Through dialogues, the player studies the background and motives of these household objects that have now become his companions.</description></item><item><title>GIT GUD</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/git-gud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/git-gud/</guid><description>Game Description Git Gud is a head-headed game, the action of which takes place in the command line interface, where players have to overcome difficulties related to versions management. The main gameplay is to analyze verbal descriptions and input the correct, functional Git commands for passing 100 levels. The initial stages are introduced to basic concepts, such as the preparation of the first commune and the use of branches for new functions.</description></item><item><title>Three Kingdoms Mushouden</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/three-kingdoms-mushouden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/three-kingdoms-mushouden/</guid><description>Game Description Three Kingdoms Mushouden transfers gamers in 182 of our era, on the threshold of the uprising of yellow dressings. The imperial court is covered by a deep internal confusion and fractional straightforwardness, which interferes with the work of officials, condemning the people into difficult trials. Players choose either a unique hero or a commander from the annals; They have to form troops and conclude alliances. Such preparations are carried out against the background of growing chaos, giving the opportunity to change the course of history.</description></item><item><title>Cast N Chill</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cast-n-chill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cast-n-chill/</guid><description>Game Description Cast N Chill represents a fishing system in a series of various lakes, rivers and oceans. The main goal is to catch the prey from water bodies using a fishing rod, because in each location their types of water inhabitants live. In all fishing expeditions, the player is accompanied by a true dog, which is present at each point. A special catalog monitors the progress of the collection of 50 varieties of fish, including freshwater and marine creatures.</description></item><item><title>Scratchers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scratchers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/scratchers/</guid><description>Game Description Scratchers is an incidental simulator built on the mechanics of erasing virtual cards to get a currency. The main gameplay is to open the surfaces of maps by Point and Click, directly generating cash. The accumulated wealth serves as the main resource for unlocking the improvement tree and expanding the scale of the operation.
As they move, the possibility of hiring automated workers, small assistants who independently perform the central task and ensure the receipt of income without constant intervention open.</description></item><item><title>Snow Plowing Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-plowing-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snow-plowing-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Snow Plowing Simulator is a relaxing and atmospheric simulator in which cleaning the territory from snow becomes an exciting adventure! Forget about the difficulties of winter cleaning - here you can enjoy snowy beauty and study the surroundings using various tools and vehicles. Start with a simple shovel, and then advance to more serious machines and interchangeable plows systems to complete more and more complex tasks in all corners of the city and mountainous areas.</description></item><item><title>IDLE WATERS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-waters/</guid><description>Game Description IDLE WATERS is a game in the IDLE-Rybank genre that works from the window at the bottom of the screen and is designed to simultaneously work with other computer operations. The game window has flexibility: it can be scale, change the layout, change the size and move to any part of the desktop or completely hide. This system allows the simulator to function without requiring constant attention from the gamer.</description></item><item><title>Covenant of Solitude</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/covenant-of-solitude/</guid><description>Game Description Covenant of Solitude introduces the story of a young man named Fort, who secretly owns the gift to command monsters in a secluded settlement of the leaves. The carriers of such a force are called ginns - their fate is full of persecution, fear and exploitation from others. The familiar way of life of the hero breaks off when the war breaks into his house, flooding the streets with blood and forcing the fort to accept his essence.</description></item><item><title>Rise of Industry 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-industry-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-industry-2/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of Industry 2 is a setting in which production magnates form the economy, factories produce goods at a frantic speed, and transactions are concluded according to stationary phones with a rotating dial. Success depends on smart investments, effective production and happiness of the right people. Each solution has weight, whether it is the conclusion of profitable trading transactions or the choice of the industry in which it should be dominated.</description></item><item><title>VOID War</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/void-war/</guid><description>Game Description Void War puts a player at the head of an ancient starship, sending him on a journey to the heart of a dying empire. This ship is described as a powerful and formidable gun filled with secret technologies. The tasks include the reflection of the attacks of crazy cultists, cowardly cosmopirates and xenophobic imperial soldiers. The detection of powerful artifacts allows you to turn a starship into a frightening combat vehicle.</description></item><item><title>CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator sends gamers on a trip to the world of Windspell, a port city filled with potential and adventures. Users stand in place of a merchant, ready to create unique items that can change the fate of the city. This game is not just about the trade in goods, it is about how to pave your way through creativity. Whether you create intricate necklaces for royal mermaids or a weapon from the blood of dragons - each item has its own charm.</description></item><item><title>Car Dealer Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/car-dealer-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/car-dealer-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Car Dealer Simulator opens the way to the sphere of trading by former cars. People look for suitable offers, buy vehicles at a low cost, make improvements and then sell them to increase profits. The gameplay reflects the development from basic automobile works to the management of the car dealership. This approach contributes to the formation of your business.
In Car Dealer Simulator, gamers master commercial techniques in Little Sam, a hero with features in terms of order.</description></item><item><title>Fuga: Melodies of Steel 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fuga-melodies-of-steel-3/</guid><description>Game Description fuga: Melodies of Steel 3 unfolds the story of desperate efforts. The inexplicable disappearance of Malta forces the group of children to head to the forbidden cave, where they are leaded by a mysterious voice to Taranis - a powerful armored vehicle, which was considered lost. The determination to find Malta returns them aboard this combat vehicle, starting a direct attack on the central regions of the Berman Empire.</description></item><item><title>As We Descend</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/as-we-descend/</guid><description>Game Description AS We Descend combines Roguelike debiting with strategic gameplay. Gamers command forces in card battles against enemies in the post -apocalyptic city. The fate of mankind is determined by the tactical decisions made on the battlefield and in the political structure of the city. The project includes the creation and development of detachments using the found technologies. Each group has a special set of cards that can be expanded and modified.</description></item><item><title>TRASH GOBLIN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trash-goblin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/trash-goblin/</guid><description>Game Description Trash Goblin is an adventure about a store that invites gamers to plunge into the noisy life of a silver city, where every day it opens up new opportunities and sets new tasks. Having risen in place of orphaned goblin, players daily search for treasures hidden in bags of garbage. Each bag is a mixture of potential and disorder filled with trinkets that are waiting for them to be cleaned and repaired.</description></item><item><title>Zombie Cure Lab</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zombie-cure-lab/</guid><description>Game Description Zombie Cure Lab - this is an opportunity to plunge into a colorful sandbox-laboratory, in which gamers have to put a variety of experiments on zombies. Scientists find a way to begin to control monsters that will be able to turn into hybrid creatures, half-dead people. Now you have to find a full medicine to calm and cure all the injured humanity from the disease of zombie. Users will build walls and fences to protect complexes with scientists.</description></item><item><title>Contractville</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contractville/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contractville/</guid><description>Game Description Contraactville beckoning lovers of simulators with their history about how to turn from rags into rich. Forget about gorgeous houses, you start with a penny in a port town. But do not be afraid, starting a tycoon! In Contractville you can build your own fate yourself by demolition, construction and interior design. And what is interesting: you can sell your architectural masterpieces at the auction, turning your sweat and ingenuity into cold, firm money.</description></item><item><title>Clink</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clink/</guid><description>Game Description Clink puts a player in the role of a woman living in voluntary solitude in an old house only with her cat and buried memories. The central conflict lies in the question of whether its experiences are symptoms of a prescribed disease or a manifestation of something otherworldly. One morning, the familiar way of the heroine is broken: one of the doors is locked, the key disappeared, and a metal ringing echoed in his head.</description></item><item><title>Tinkerlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tinkerlands/</guid><description>Game Description Tinkerlands offers game experience where the characters find themselves in unknown islands. Survival becomes the main task that encourages the study of these new territories, the creation of the necessary tools and contacts with various inhabitants of these lands. Gamers gradually build personal shelters that can develop into large settlements. Interaction with the environment also opens access to magic, giving additional ways to overcome difficulties.
The Tinkerlands universe consists of the main continent, three other large islands and many small islands, each of them provides unique conditions, resources and tests.</description></item><item><title>Cauldron</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cauldron/</guid><description>Game Description Cauldron is a role project with an emphasis on a system of improvement and the implementation of mini-stories. In the role of NIX, a character who finds himself in a world immersed in darkness will have to explore the environment and look for allies. The structure implies the cycle: the commission of actions leads to strengthening the party, which opens the way to the study of new areas and obtaining content.</description></item><item><title>Roadcraft</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roadcraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roadcraft/</guid><description>Game Description Roadcraft is a simulator in which gamers take on the role of the head of a company engaged in the restoration of territories affected by natural disasters. The main task is to use various types of construction equipment for clearing blockages, restoring roads and repairing damaged infrastructure.
The Title offers a detailed approach to the problems that arise in the elimination of the consequences of natural disasters, offering tasks such as replacing faulty equipment and deploying resources columns to create the necessary materials for reconstruction.</description></item><item><title>Blacksmith Master</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blacksmith-master/</guid><description>Game Description Blacksmith Master is an exciting simulator in which you can control your own blacksmiths, starting with mining and precious stones to the design and sale of finished products. Your task will be tortured everything - from weapons and armor to instruments and kitchen utensils - to earn on your craft and become a real master of blacksmithing.
Here you can lead your own medieval blacksmith and you will control the entire process: the extraction of resources, their processing and production and sale of finished products.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultimate-fishing-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2 - fishing simulator, offering to participate in a huge number of tests and demonstrate many different techniques. Use a wide set of tools and gear: feeder, overlap, spinning, classic float and much more. Continuation of the game significantly improves the graphic component, adds many mechanics, tools and improves all aspects of the gameplay. More and better - the basic principle of Ultimate Fishing Simulator 2.</description></item><item><title>Cash Cleaner Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cash-cleaner-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cash-cleaner-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Cash Cleaner Simulator immerses a gamer in the role of a specialist in processing illegal means for criminal structures. The character accepts orders from figures of the criminal world, which need to be returned to finances without traces of their origin. Deliveries come in various packages, demanding to extract currency, determine the presence of contaminants like blood or dirt, as well as weed out false banknotes before the main procedure.</description></item><item><title>Chronomon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chronomon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chronomon/</guid><description>Game Description Chronomon combines elements of monsters care and the simulation of the farm. Players find themselves in the world after a disaster, where they have to catch unusual creatures, improve their skills and help in restoration. Communication with the settlers and step -by -step battles complement the process of arranging their own allotment of land, and the main task is to form a detachment of pets and control of resources in the proposed conditions.</description></item><item><title>Doloc Town</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doloc-town/</guid><description>Game Description Doloc Town - this is a farm simulator in the conditions of post -apocalypse. The player accepts the role of a beginner whose task is to build an existing economy in the desert territory. The environment pushes to the study of its predominantly unexplored areas. Key activity includes the landing of cultures, the construction of the necessary structures and the consistent search for information about the past of this changed world.</description></item><item><title>Tank Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tank-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Tank Squad transfers players during the Second World War, to the most intense territories, whose fate will affect the outcome of the clash. The user will visit the role of captain of the tank detachment, taking part in the iconic battles of that time. Scenarios will include historical battles for a single -user or cooperative passage of three participants at the same time.
In the multiplayer, each gamer is able to control their own team, or unite among themselves and become a separate crew member.</description></item><item><title>Teddy's Haven - A Fantasy Inspired Shop Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teddys-haven-a-fantasy-inspired-shop-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/teddys-haven-a-fantasy-inspired-shop-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Teddy&amp;rsquo;s Haven - A Fantasy Inspired Shop Simulator puts the player in the role of the owner who controls a small store on the periphery of the mysterious island. The shop specializes in the sale of potions, weapons and various magic wonders for a variety of clientele. Among the buyers are adventurers preparing for campaigns, magicians in search of rare components and other mystical creatures. The main cycle of classes is to replenish the shelves, manage the inventory, set up each aspect of the interior and hiring employees.</description></item><item><title>Best Served Cold</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</guid><description>Game Description The Best Served Cold puts a gamer at the Knightsp Rack, an underground bar, working during the dry law in the alternative European city of Bukovia. You take on the role of a bartender responsible for the preparation of cocktails for visitors to the institution. Intections go beyond the maintenance, including direct clashes with persons identified as criminals and the need to navigate in dangerous situations.
The main actions include the investigation of the murders taking place in this environment while maintaining the work of the bar.</description></item><item><title>Knights of the Crusades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/knights-of-the-crusades/</guid><description>Game Description Knights of the Crusades sends a player during the first crusades, where a lone knight will come to begin. It is ahead to go to the foundation and management of the holy order, choosing the Templars or creating their own fraction. The process combines real -time elements with the construction of settlements and management within the sandbox. You have to solve problems related to war, religious influence, diplomacy and strategic planning.</description></item><item><title>Badlands Crew</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/badlands-crew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/badlands-crew/</guid><description>Game Description Badlands Crew transfers to the gamer control over a combat vehicle in the world of lawlessness that arose after a global catastrophe. Key tasks include the construction of transport, its modification and use against hostile groups for the search and salvation of the survivors. You collect your mobile fortress from individual components, selecting elements such as flamethrowers, sniper turrets, rate of fire machine guns, observation tower and medical points.</description></item><item><title>Survivalist: Invisible Strain</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/survivalist-invisible-strain/</guid><description>Game Description Survivalist: Invisible Strain - continuation of the game Survivalist. Events take place near Vancouver in Canada. The zombivirus epidemic has been going on for 10 years. People managed to erect settlements, well -guarded from revived dead. However, the defense of the shelters fell for unknown reasons. The survivors go to the hill, hoping to build new outposts.
In the game, the survivor: an invisible strain can create your own community.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Mogul 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-mogul-4/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Mogul 4 — это текстовый бизнес-симулятор, ставящий человека во главе киностудии. Система позволяет создавать кинофильмы и мини-сериалы на основе библиотеки из более чем 14 000 исходных материалов или собственных идей. Ready -made paintings can be planned for global film distribution or for distribution through streaming service. The process includes the formation of accurate budgets, the conclusion of agreements on rental in 19 foreign territories and the management of advertising expenses.</description></item><item><title>Drive Rally</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Rally is an arcade game about rally races that transfers gamers during the glory of the 1990s. Having focused on speeds, skill and exciting sensations of an open road, Advencura offers nostalgic experience for fans of classic rally races. Users take on the role of a rally racer, competing in various iconic places around the world. From the dusty deserts of Africa to the snowy peaks of Scandinavia - each area offers unique trials and opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Synergy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/synergy/</guid><description>Game Description synergy dedicated to survival on a hostile planet. In this urban planning strategy, players have to develop their city, face natural cataclysms and make the right decisions that will certainly have consequences. Explore this constantly changing world, preserving the happiness of the townspeople in extreme weather conditions.
Gamers will control the weather, seasons, extreme conditions and natural disasters. The main goal is to build a city where residents will be happy and satisfied, respecting the natural needs of the inhabitants and living in harmony with the local fauna and flora.</description></item><item><title>Forever skies</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forever-skies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/forever-skies/</guid><description>Game Description Forever skies is an atypical survival in the world of post -apocalypse, where the player will become the captain of the airship. Unfortunately, the protagonist is the only crew member, but even this does not reduce the number of his problems. After all, he still needs food, which is practically no in the air with the exception of rare birds. And the technique tends to break, and it requires constantly replacing old details.</description></item><item><title>Lushfoil Photography Sim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lushfoil-photography-sim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lushfoil-photography-sim/</guid><description>Game Description Lushfoil Photography SIM is an incredibly beautiful and relaxing game in which the player can simply relax as much as he needs. She does not drive the user forward, allowing him to admire the views, relaxes the natural sounds of the noise of leaves, water or the creak of snow. If desired, you can completely turn off the musical accompaniment and plunges into the virtual world, so similar to the real one.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Animal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-animal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollywood-animal/</guid><description>Game Description Hollywood Animal is not an ordinary strategic game. Forget about the conquest of empires or the construction of huge cities. Here you are in the roaring twenties - the time when the silent movie gave way to the &amp;ldquo;talkers&amp;rdquo;, and the film studios tried to keep up. You are in the director’s chair, but not for the camera. This time you are a studio boss, solving all issues, starting from who will play in the film, and ending when the last blockbuster is released.</description></item><item><title>Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-dead-our-darkest-days/</guid><description>Game Description Into The Dead: Oour Darkest Days transfer the player to Walton City, Texas, 1980 sample, covered by a zombie epidemic. The gamer has to lead a detachment of surviving through the dying metropolis. The key task of the gameplay is to move the wards between temporary shelters, taking care of their condition. It is necessary to find provisions, make objects and repulse constant danger from the dead who filled the streets.</description></item><item><title>Promise Mascot Agency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</guid><description>Game Description Promise Mascot Agency offers the gamer to plunge into the life of Kaso-Machi, a damned Japanese town. The main character, Michi, is in exile and must establish the work of the agency of urban masks. Key tasks include hiring these creatures, resolving the problems that arise due to their actions, and clarifying the causes of the protagonist link. Communication with a kick, a living finger with a complex character, is also part of the gameplay while you are trying to make your agency the best in the region through the study of the world and plot events.</description></item><item><title>Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kadomon-hyper-auto-battlers/</guid><description>Game Description Kadomon: Hyper Auto Battlers calls the gamarines into a world filled with more than 180 creatures who need to collect, fight and develop. The Title combines the elements of autoboeviks, rogeliks and card battles, allowing users to develop unique strategies. The purpose of the game is to assemble the KDOMON team, each of which has various abilities and types in order to pass more and more difficult tests. As you pass, you will encounter powerful bosses and open rare monsters with special abilities.</description></item><item><title>Voiceatc Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voiceatc-simulator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/voiceatc-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Voiceatc Simulator is a simulator that puts a player in the role of an air traffic controller, where voice communication serves as a main tool for managing aircraft. The main gameplay is to build arriving sides for landing and their maintenance on strips created on the basis of real airfield schemes.
You give oral teams for vectoring, changing the echelon, adjusting speed and execution of transitions, effectively controlling the sky.</description></item><item><title>Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/roman-triumph-survival-city-builder/</guid><description>Game Description Roman Triumph: Survival City Builder can be attributed to the simulators of the colony and real -time strategies. There are also survival elements in the indie project. He has high reigree due to the random generation of cards. The gamer here is offered to establish a settlement and help it develop to a full -fledged city. At the same time, it is necessary to monitor the needs and mood of the townspeople.</description></item><item><title>Pocket City 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pocket-city-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pocket City 2 makes it possible for players to build cities, and then study their first -person creations. The process starts from the laying of roads, the markings of sections for residential, commercial or industrial needs and the construction of the necessary objects on the map. Control over the economy implies monitoring of stocks, profit and a thoughtful placement of special structures, access to which opens as they move.</description></item><item><title>inzoi</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inzoi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/inzoi/</guid><description>Game Description Inzoi is a life -symbol game in which gamers assign the role of the creator and observer in a detailed virtual community. In a dynamic environment, users can interact with various characters known as Zoe. These characters are not connected by actions recorded in the script, but act of their own free will, controlled by more than 400 mental elements that form their behavior and solutions. Result? A constantly developing world in which rumors spread, trends and even diseases appear.</description></item><item><title>A Merchant's Promise</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-merchants-promise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-merchants-promise/</guid><description>Game Description A Merchant&amp;rsquo;s Promise Places the player in the stylized Middle Ages, concentrated on commerce and transportation through direct physical handling of objects. The path begins with the role of a worthless merchant, who is instructed to manually move goods using a system based on physics. There is no usual inventory here; Each object needs to be raised, carried and placed, which creates a constant risk of dropping or even throwing a luggage.</description></item><item><title>Kaiserpunk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kaiserpunk/</guid><description>Game Description Kaiserpunk throws you headlong into an alternative XX century, instructing to build an empire from scratch. This is not Grandfather&amp;rsquo;s Urban planner - Title offers a grandiose strategy, demanding from you to win a vast card, while preserving the residents happy, and the factory - working. Does it sound like a high task? This is true. Forget that you can just put at home and finish it on this.</description></item><item><title>Urban Jungle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-jungle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/urban-jungle/</guid><description>Game Description Urban Jungle gives users the opportunity to turn ordinary residential premises into bright vegetable sanctuaries, without straining in a gameplay. The project invites enthusiasts to experiment with the placement of plants in compact apartments, creating personal green corners without typical care worries that accompany gardening in the real world.
Users use the main mechanics of strategic decoration, determining the optimal position for each plant variety in order to maximize the level of comfort in digital living space.</description></item><item><title>Call of Boba</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-boba/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-of-boba/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Boba transfers to a small, bizarre town, where they find themselves in the role of assistants, helping to revive the destructive Bob tea store. At first, the task is simple: to cook delicious drinks, attract customers and develop business. But underground is hiding something more. With the onset of night, a completely new world opens, and this is where real adventures begin. Armed with the ingredients for Bob milk tea, users fight enemies to get inspiration for the creations of the store.</description></item><item><title>Card Survival: Fantasy Forest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/card-survival-fantasy-forest/</guid><description>Game Description Card Survival: Fantasy Forest is a survival simulator that immerses in the very heart of the ancient forest. Title takes users to a world where nature is not only living, but also has its own mind. Here, gamers build a house, overcome daily difficulties and interact with a rich ecosystem full of wild animals, magical creatures and unpredictable forces. Every day brings new difficulties associated with survival: from hunger and health management to solving problems with the weather and seasons.</description></item><item><title>FACEMINER</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/faceminer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/faceminer/</guid><description>Game Description FaceMiner offers a deep immersion in the world of collecting biometric data. Here gamers fall into the chaotic world before the beginning of the new millennium, where the main task is to collect and classifying data on faces on a mass scale. As a user, you start small, gradually building an empire from biometric data. On this path, you have to expand the scale: to update software, develop infrastructure and maximize profits, overcoming the sea of ​​corporate problems.</description></item><item><title>Dead Dragons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dead-dragons/</guid><description>Game Description Dead Dragons launches history 100 years after the victory of people over the dragons - the events that allegedly brought the world. Now rumors about the return of these creatures encourage the protagonist to investigate the case of a mysterious girl associated with the dragon race. This task develops into a conflict that decides the fate of the whole world and raises the main question of the survival of one of the species in the upcoming confrontation.</description></item><item><title>Mind Over Magic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mind-over-magic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mind-over-magic/</guid><description>Game Description The Mind Over Magic offers the player to become the master of the magic school located over a dangerous underground maze. You have to design, build and manage all aspects of your school, from classes to dormitories, from gardens to laboratories. You also have to train your students with various magical skills, such as lost lasso, production of potions, growing plants and necromancy.
But your school is not a safe refuge.</description></item><item><title>Arctic Motel Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arctic-motel-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arctic-motel-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description In the Arctic Motel Simulator, the action takes place in a remote and vast Arctic region. Here gamers will take the work of turning the struggling motel into a prosperous business in harsh arctic conditions. Users will encounter unpredictable Arctic weather, controlling everyone from temperature in the rooms in winter to humidity in the summer. At your disposal, eight different types of numbers, and gamers will be able to choose the one that corresponds to their business centers and budget.</description></item><item><title>Astronomics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/astronomics/</guid><description>Game Description In Astronomics, gamers are sent to study the space and the production of asteroids. You have to move through randomly generated asteroids, extract resources and manage a developing enterprise. At first, the whole thing is assembling materials on asteroids flying past, but as it moves forward, automation becomes a key factor. With workers and command bots, at your disposal, the tasks for which the clock used to go, can be completed much faster.</description></item><item><title>Keep Driving</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-driving/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keep-driving/</guid><description>Game Description Keep Driving immerses in the atmosphere of freedom of a long, slow trip to the procedurally generated world. The action takes place in the early 2000s, you are behind the wheel of your first car, a long road and a festival are ahead, which you need to get to the other end of the country. Passing along the highway and dirt roads, you are faced with difficulties, both from the environment and from the bizarre hitchhiker, looking for a passage.</description></item><item><title>Blood Bar Tycoon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blood-bar-tycoon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/blood-bar-tycoon/</guid><description>Game Description In Blood Bar Tycoon, users are in the place of the manager of the Vampire Bar. The goal is to create and manage a series of blood bars so that people and vampire customers are satisfied. Along the way, gamers build blood factories, collect blood and encounter problems such as hunters and vampire-competing. Due to the possibility of micro -study or assignment automation, users can accurately configure the work to develop their dark empire.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/foundation/</guid><description>Game Description The urban planning simulator-Foundation-will allow you to plunge in the medieval era, build a whole settlement, make people happy at the expense of unique structures, as well as understand the history of the construction of houses and churches, on which there was a lot of emphasis due to constant rivalry of religious directions.
We will build houses and other structures with smart brushes. They will allow us not to exceed authority and put only those buildings that will meet environmental norms and criteria.</description></item><item><title>Heart of the Machine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heart-of-the-machine/</guid><description>Game Description Heart of the Machine outwardly resembles a town -planning Taikun. But in fact, the project is something like a god of God with elements of tactics and strategy in real time. Only here the Juzer is assigned the role of not a divine being, which owns magic, but artificial intelligence. This video game has a science fiction setting. Its action takes place in a distant and gloomy future in the territory of the metropolis-colonies.</description></item><item><title>Libritopia: Librarian Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/libritopia-librarian-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/libritopia-librarian-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Libritopia: Librarian Simulator gives you the management of its own library institution. The main tasks include acceptance and sorting of literary works from all over the world. It is necessary to form collects of the works of Shakespeare and Jules Verne, placing them on racks for free access. This game makes it possible to create a personal classification system that allows you to catalog literature on the genre, author, country or any other method.</description></item><item><title>Space Engineers 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-engineers-2/</guid><description>Game Description Space Engineers 2 returns to the world of space development with updated experience. In this continuation, you will have a new adventure in the Almagest system, where engineering tasks and spaces of space are combined in the most unexpected way. This is a sandbox with an open world in which you can build from scratch - or, rather, from stars - from starships to entire space stations. The goal is simple: to raise your creative potential to a new height, while managing the difficulties of survival in the cold, inexorable spaces of space.</description></item><item><title>Learning Factory</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/learning-factory/</guid><description>Game Description learning factory - a simulator that is designed to create an automated process of processes and, most importantly, understand one simple truth: what do cats want? The gameplay allows you to head the Kotovod factory. It was once closed, but now it has been possible to renew the process and create your own cat store. Learning factory gameplay largely gives an idea of ​​how machine learning works.
Your factory is analyzing a huge database, trying to study the behavior of pets.</description></item><item><title>IDUN</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idun/</guid><description>Game Description Idun throws you into a hostile world, teeming with resources and teeming with enemies. This is a genre mixing in which in real time the strategy is combined with the protection of the tower, which gives a unique experience. Your mission? To capture all the most valuable and get out alive. But this is not a light walk. Enemy hordes are teeming on the battlefield, tirelessly pursuing your base.</description></item><item><title>Diddy</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/diddy/</guid><description>Game Description Diddy begins with a mission to destroy a dark party held in a private estate. Players in the Company of Eminam and 51 Centers must stop the owner’s atrocities and stop the meeting. The main task is the salvation of Justin B, who is in the territory after the accumulation of a state fraud. The detachment confronts the army of Selebri, acting as a guards, ready to defend the estate and its owner.</description></item><item><title>Harvest Hills</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/harvest-hills/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/harvest-hills/</guid><description>Game Description Harvest Hills immerses the player in plant cultivation and animal care in order to obtain agricultural products. The initial actions allow you to create products such as eggs, milk, honey and wool. The sale of these products in the local market provides income to modernize the economy and introduce automation systems. According to the plot, the protagonist leaves the city bustle for the founding of an agrarian enterprise, gradually turning the empty plot of land into a flourishing ranch.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Defensurvivor</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/defensurvivor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/defensurvivor/</guid><description>Game Description Defensurvivor puts a player at the head of the protection of asylum in the world captured by zombies. The main goal is to hold out for 15 minutes against the continuous waves of attackers, managing defense and staff. Gamers erect and modernize the walls through the construction menu, creating barriers to the direction of movement of the approaching horde. Success requires adaptation to the fighters accidentally issued for each session.</description></item><item><title>Laundry Store Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/laundry-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/laundry-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Laundry Store Simulator - a game in which you start small and advance up the career ladder. You will update the equipment, arrange a stylish store and expand the range of services. Is your goal in the laundry store simulator? Become the owner of the best institution in the world. Turn a small laundry into a flourishing business imperial! Update the equipment, arrange and expand the store, hire staff and much more!</description></item><item><title>Retrowave 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/retrowave-2/</guid><description>Game Description Retrowave 2 places a player under the control of the supercar of the 1980s, moving along an endless highway surrounded by neon lights and palm trees. The project draws inspiration in an idealized, futuristic interpretation of that era, causing a sense of nostalgia for a period that never existed. This atmosphere provides a complete immersion in the world of Syntveyva. The main lesson is the piloting of transport along the road system on a retro -futuristic background, where aesthetics are built around synthesizer music.</description></item><item><title>Space Architect</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-architect/</guid><description>Game Description Space Architect is a simulator where gamers have to become in place of the manager of the space station. The main goal is to build, maintain and expand the space station, simultaneously coping with the difficulties of resource management and interstellar trade. In the beginning, users are faced with a serious financial burden - a huge debt to a powerful megarporace, which forces them to make complex decisions on how to get income and stay afloat in endless cosmic voids.</description></item><item><title>Luma Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/luma-island/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/luma-island/</guid><description>Game Description Luma Island sends users on a trip full of research, discoveries and tests. Regardless of whether you go alone or unite with friends, this adventure is a world full of possibilities. The island offers a wide range of classes - from the construction of the farm of his dreams to the discovery of hidden treasures and solving confusing puzzles. This is a game in which you can plunge into a bright world, constantly discovering something new for yourself and moving forward at your own pace.</description></item><item><title>Industry Giant 4.0</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/industry-giant-40/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/industry-giant-40/</guid><description>Game Description Industry Giant 4.0 immerses gamers in the landscape determined by industrial management and strategy. Since the 1950s, users are moving through the fourth industrial revolution, where digitalization and interconnected chains of creating cost play the most important role. The goal is to create and manage the industrial empire. This includes not only the production of goods, but also the creation of complex transport networks and monitoring financial transactions.</description></item><item><title>Zephon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zephon/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in Zephon have to take control of the remnants of mankind in order to survive on the territory of the Earth. On the planet, there are few areas that are not suitable for life, and most of the cities were destroyed. In wild territories are mutating creatures that they gather in small groups and begin to hunt for surviving people. Alien robots with damaged systems roam on the surface, and the aliens themselves are hidden and try to secure survival.</description></item><item><title>Elin</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/elin/</guid><description>Game Description Elin is a two -dimensional role morned in which you can completely immerse yourself in an exciting world, where each solution matters. Choose your hero and go on a dangerous trip to Ylva’s lands, exploring mysterious places, meeting unique characters and fighting various dangers. You will find unforgettable adventures, where you will create your own story, influence the world and leave your mark on Ylva Earth. You have to fight for survival, find and create resources, build houses and manage your city.</description></item><item><title>Widget Inc.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/widget-inc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/widget-inc/</guid><description>Game Description Widget Inc. - This is a hybrid of the designer of factories and an incremental clicker, who invites users to the kingdom of crafts and production. Starting with basic resources, people go on a trip to master various craft processes. Target? Build a huge factory capable of producing advanced technologies, known as widgets. These widgets serve as a key element of the revival of civilization after the apocalypse. Users perform many tasks, each of which helps to build an empire extending to the stars.</description></item><item><title>Orebound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/orebound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/orebound/</guid><description>Game Description Orebound invites users to a world where they take on the role of a gnome, which goes in search of an ancient artifact, known as amber stone. The Title puts the participants in a huge, station environment, where the study and collection of resources form the basis of experience. Users begin with the construction of their base, laying the foundation of their gnome civilization. This journey begins with mineral extraction, where every wave of picks allows you to detect valuable resources.</description></item><item><title>Citadelum</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/citadelum/</guid><description>Game Description Citadelum throws its hat to the ring of strategic games, offering the experience of building cities with an admixture of mythology and strategic conquests. Ancient Rome serves as a background for the game: gamers take control of a nascent settlement and should turn it into a lively metropolis. Resource management is a paramount task for any novice urban planner. But Citadelum is not only overgrown suburbs and towering monuments.</description></item><item><title>Eden Crafters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/eden-crafters/</guid><description>Game Description Eden Crafters throws glove in the hands of survival and automation lovers. In this cooperative adventure with the open world, players will turn to turn a hostile planet into a hospitable refuge for humanity. Think about this as a space project of reconstruction - harsh conditions, fluids of the house of dreams. Task? Overcome the unpleasant habits of the planet and build a new house for humanity. Imagine radioactive zones and insidious landscapes are not the best real estate.</description></item><item><title>Storage Hunter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/storage-hunter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/storage-hunter/</guid><description>Game Description An exciting auction of old things in Storage Hunter. Gamer will be able to take part in the auction, where abandoned warehouses are played, which are perfect for perestroika and old containers. Of all these things killed over time, you can make brand new things suitable for everyday use. The user&amp;rsquo;s task is extremely simple, just that you need to correctly and wisely assess the cost of each item that is in this room.</description></item><item><title>Heavy Cargo - The Truck Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heavy-cargo-the-truck-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/heavy-cargo-the-truck-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Heavy Cargo - The Truck Simulator is an opportunity to feel like a real trucker who is forced to transport goods through the huge open world. It is necessary to search for orders, loading, unloading and accompanying a variety of cars in convoys. It will be possible to test several types of trailers that can transport the tractor. Juzerov is waiting for the gameplay of the classic driver’s simulator, which controls a big truck.</description></item><item><title>The Last Plague: Blight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-plague-blight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-last-plague-blight/</guid><description>Game Description The Last Plague: Blight is a survival simulator in the open world, which is generated randomly. The user controls one character and watches what is happening from above. The camera is tied to the hero. It is allowed to rotate. Indi-project uses medieval setting with a light fantasy raid.
The events of the Blight game occur in a world where there is a filth. This is the name of a mysterious disease.</description></item><item><title>Liar's bar</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/liars-bar/</guid><description>Game Description Liar&amp;rsquo;s Bar is a multi -user online game, whose action takes place in a bar, where deception and strategy play a key role. Users are united at tables of four people to take part in games such as Liar&amp;rsquo;s Dice and Liar&amp;rsquo;s Deck. The goal is to outwit rivals using bliff and strategic moves. Each session is filled with stress, as gamers are trying to unravel each other&amp;rsquo;s intentions and make the right moves to win.</description></item><item><title>Pinball Spire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-spire/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball Spire challenges the world, combining the classic pinball mechanics with elements of research and development for a unique adventure. You take control of a pee, a brave character, whose determination plays a key role - both in the plot and in how you play. The essence of Pinball Spire is to manage a mysterious spire that suddenly appeared in the world of a pipa. This is not an ordinary pinball table.</description></item><item><title>Chef RPG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chef-rpg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chef-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Chef RPG gives a completely new idea of ​​what a culinary culinary can be. So, users get the role of a wandering chef, who has an important mission - to revive the legendary Le Sex restaurant. Once this place was a real magnet for travelers and everyone who wanted to eat and take a breath, and now this is nothing more than an abandoned building. It is time to return to him former glory, developing his own business and going to a new level in terms of cooking.</description></item><item><title>Endzone 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/endzone-2/</guid><description>Game Description Endzone 2 throws you into the thick of the post -apocalyptic world. Humanity died, and you remained to collect fragments - literally. Each decision that you make as if you can send your scattered colony by the line. Lack of resources? Eat. Danger to the environment? Do not hesitate. Ruthless raiders eager to steal your lunch? Undoubtedly. This is not a simple walk. This is the management of your nascent civilization.</description></item><item><title>Intravenous 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/intravenous-2/</guid><description>Game Description Intravenous 2 immerses you in the world of cruel intrigues and intense action. Play for Sean, desperately trying to save his abducted father, and Steve, a grumbling former military with a dark past. Their unlikely union is based on a common goal: to pass the labyrinth of the underworld, complete secrets, lies and mortal danger.
But how you can handle this insidious Odyssey depends only on you. Will you be a ghost, fluttering in shadows and manipulating environment in your interests?</description></item><item><title>ODD Realm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/odd-realm/</guid><description>Game Description ODD Realm is a game that combines both the strategy and the survival simulator. The player will have to take on the role of the leader of a small settlement and provide residents with the necessary resources, houses, as well as protect their subjects from bloodthirsty enemies and dishonest bandits from a high road. The variability of the development of the plot provides the gamer with wide opportunities for the construction of the city of his own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Under The Blue Horizon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-blue-horizon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-the-blue-horizon/</guid><description>Game Description Under The Blue Horizon is a stand-up game-designer, designed for functioning as a constant aquarium on a computer screen. This virtual aquarium can be placed anywhere on the display running simultaneously with other programs or during operation. The main interaction of the gamer is to create and breeding fish, requiring shrimp for their development as a source of food.
With an increase in a population of different types, the ecosystem produces by -products, launching the key system of resource management of this project.</description></item><item><title>8th Heaven</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/8th-heaven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/8th-heaven/</guid><description>Game Description 8th Heaven immerses gamers in the bright atmosphere of the island, filled with opportunities for social interaction and research. Title is a simulation of life, offering users to navigate in everyday matters and build relationships with a variety of characters. Against the background of fantastic elements, players can interact with the environment in various ways. Whether it is craft, farming or participation in public events, users will always find something to do.</description></item><item><title>Into The Radius 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-radius-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/into-the-radius-2/</guid><description>Game Description Into the Radius 2 throws users with their heads into the chilling world. Regardless of whether you prefer single research or exciting adventures in the detachment, Radius promises danger and secrets equally. A project that will allow gamers to feel the anxious atmosphere first -hand. Forget about elaborate graphics and pomp. Into The Radius 2 reduces everything to the naked bones of survival. The radius itself is a character, mysterious and hostile force, dictating to you every step.</description></item><item><title>Norland</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/norland/</guid><description>Game Description Medieval setting in** Norland** shows interactive stories that will happen to the royal family. Players will manage the birth that controls the city. We will have to observe the activities of ordinary workers, peasants, slaves, soldiers and criminals. Each character has needs, as well as a unique character. Users will have to distribute instructions for family members in order to put order in the urban district. We will have to take power into your own hands, dealing with different economic or military spheres.</description></item><item><title>Terrascape</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrascape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terrascape/</guid><description>Game Description Terrascape allows gamers to fulfill their dream - build their own city! Thanks to the wide selection of decks, offering unique buildings and the possibilities of expansion, you can strategically place your cards on the game field to earn points and open new awards. You will need to carefully consider the influence of each building on your city, including its influence on other buildings, natural resources and terrain. Collect positive factors of influence to get bonus glasses, but beware of negative factors that may interfere with your progress.</description></item><item><title>The Crust</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-crust/</guid><description>Game Description The Crust is a survival with elements of the economy, where the player will build a whole small town with highly limited resources almost without the possibility of replenishing them. In order to grow at least something on such a surface and provide your people with the proper amount of food, you will have to try hard. However, with proper management, this is still quite possible.
The main character is the head of the space company, which was decided by the first to colonize the moon.</description></item><item><title>Dystopika</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dystopika/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dystopika/</guid><description>Game Description Dystopika is not an ordinary Advent. This is a digital sandbox, a neon platform for builders without drawings. Forget about resource management, population growth or economic balance. These things do not exist here. Instead, you are a digital architect, free to create a metropolis from scratch. No grandiose plans, no ultimate goal. This is a trip, not a destination. You build buildings, observe their growth and allow the city to develop organically.</description></item><item><title>Tavern Talk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</guid><description>Game Description Tavern Talk throws you into the very heart of the fantasy kingdom, but not as a powerful warrior or clever robber. Here you will take into your hands the reins of the reign of a cozy tavern Wayfarer&amp;rsquo;s Inn. But this is not an ordinary bartender simulator. The “Traveler” tavern is filled with a whisper and secrets of adventure seekers - your regulars. This is not just thirsty souls who want to drink a mug of ale.</description></item><item><title>Everafter Falls</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everafter-falls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/everafter-falls/</guid><description>Game Description Everafter Falls combines a heating simulator with elements of role -playing adventure. Gamers grow crops, bred animals and catch fish in a serene rural area. However, there is a more gloomy background. Terrible creatures that require combat skill live in the dungeons. A unique development system replaces traditional experience with mysterious cards. Gamers feed these cards to a mysterious creature, contributing to the growth of the character. The project encourages cooperation.</description></item><item><title>Tradesman: Deal to Dealer</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tradesman-deal-to-dealer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tradesman-deal-to-dealer/</guid><description>Game Description Tradesman: Deal to Dealer offers gamers to become merchants, moving around the world, which is both a market and a minefield. You will travel through a variety of landscapes, buying a cheap and selling more expensive - classic merchants. But there is something more than it seems at first glance. Here you are in wait for the danger - imagine the bandits watching your wagon with exotic fish while you are yearning for a cold man in the village of Crubgrog.</description></item><item><title>Thriving City: Song</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thriving-city-song/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thriving-city-song/</guid><description>Game Description Thriving City: Song offers to be transferred to the past, in 960 of our era, and take on the role of the mayor in the recently formed Zhao Song dynasty. This gaming -symbol of the city’s construction in ancient China is a rich historical adventure with elements of strategy and plot. Your task as a mayor is to help the townspeople settle down, cultivate the land and expand the city.</description></item><item><title>Reus 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reus-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/reus-2/</guid><description>Game Description Reus 2 stands out with its uniqueness and fascination. In this game, you have the power of the gods, controlling powerful giants that form the world for the prosperity or death of human civilizations. From the very beginning, everything is extremely clear: in Reus 2 you have to decide the fate of mankind, making your choice and committing actions.
You will get the opportunity to choose giants for yourself, each of which has its own abilities and characteristics.</description></item><item><title>E-Startup 2: Business Tycoon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/e-startup-2-business-tycoon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/e-startup-2-business-tycoon/</guid><description>Game Description E-Startup 2: Business Tycoon throws you headlong into the world of product management. Development, production, sale - all this is on your conscience. Fasten the belts because you will also have to juggle with resources, monitor the constantly changing market and make sure that your office does not turn into a productivity cemetery. Do you think you have the next big thing? Title will allow you to bring your concept from a sketch on a napkin to a store shelf.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Voltage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-voltage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rogue-voltage/</guid><description>Game Description Rogue Voltage immerses you in the world of crazy science and monstrous chaos. This indie game combines Roguelike elements and automation mechanics, in which you have to create your own combat abilities. Forget about pressing the buttons - the strategy dominates here. Each move you have to manage resources. To release a powerful explosion, heal yourself with a potion or accumulate energy for the future offensive? The choice is yours, and each solution can persuade the scales in the battle.</description></item><item><title>Echoes of the Plum Grove</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/echoes-of-the-plum-grove/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/echoes-of-the-plum-grove/</guid><description>Game Description Echoes of the Plum Grove is a casual adventure that promises you to transfer you to the calm town of Hanwood, where a new life awaits you. But keep in mind, this is not an ordinary farm simulator! Get ready for surprises, because you have to build a flourishing farm community that will exist for many generations. You will begin your journey as a newly -made owner of a modest plot of land on the island.</description></item><item><title>From Glory to Goo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-glory-to-goo/</guid><description>Game Description From Glory to Goo is a cosmic adventure. Forget about the conquest of the new worlds - here the survival depends on how to cling to the fragment of the rock among the inexorable stream of mucus. You play for the captain, the last hope of mankind, who is instructed to establish a fragile colony on a hostile foreign world. Your enemies are not rival empires and not robots with lasers, but the ubiquitous mucus, a reasonable, changing form, the threat that oozes, drips and crawls to your colony from all sides.</description></item><item><title>Momo and the Mine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/momo-and-the-mine/</guid><description>Game Description Momo and the Mine sends a mole-protagonist to a dangerous, abandoned network of dungeons for collecting matches. The player will have to conduct a character through a series of difficult jumping tests, where accuracy is the key to survival. The gameplay requires accurate movement through the hostile surroundings filled with ghosts of tunnels. Success directly depends on mastering responsive controls to overcome each obstacle in the dilapidated structure of the mine, which creates a constant test of skill.</description></item><item><title>Expections: A Mudrunner Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</guid><description>Game Description Expections: A Mudrunner Game throws you headlong into unknown territories, putting you at the head of research missions at insidious landscapes. Get ready for an off -road adventure based on physics, where every centimeter of progress requires the courage, strategy and masterful ownership of your strong all -terrain vehicle. Imagine how you will overcome the deserts sifted by the sun, thick forests clinging to your tires, and snowy peaks that experience you for strength.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Glory 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-glory-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mortal-glory-2/</guid><description>Game Description Mortal Glory 2 is a fantasy RPG in the Roguelike genre, which combines a step -by -step tactical battle and team management. It is proposed to be in the role of the leader of the team of wandering gladiators, and your ultimate goal is to take part in the tournament, the victory in which guarantees glory and wealth. One of the main features of the game is the variety of available races, each of which has its own unique advantages and disadvantages.</description></item><item><title>Serviceit: You can do it</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/serviceit-you-can-do-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/serviceit-you-can-do-it/</guid><description>Game Description Create your own company to develop IT solutions at Serviceit: You can do it. Stand in the place of an experienced entrepreneur, manage a team of technicians and make sure that the problems of your customers with equipment remain in the past. The game offers a variety of playing platform for technically savvy and business people: from fuss with motherboards to user navigation. Master the art of repair. Diagnize faulty equipment, accurately own a soldering iron and change tired transistors to new ones.</description></item><item><title>Keeperrl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keeperrl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keeperrl/</guid><description>Game Description Keeperrl is a simulator with elements of a slide in which it is necessary to build an underground base and develop society. You play for a powerful wizard studying black magic. Teach minions to military affairs, forcing to attack civilians of settlements, taking their belongings and burning to the ground at home.
Engage in the construction of the dungeons, arrange traps and build up military power to storm miserable people.</description></item><item><title>Le Mans Ultimate</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/le-mans-ultimate/</guid><description>Game Description Le Mans Ultimate - The official game FIA ​​World Enduraance Championship and &amp;ldquo;24 hours of Le Man&amp;rdquo;, promises exciting experience to both experienced riders and beginners. Runned in early access, the game offers to try the exciting season of 2023 with official cars, legendary tracks and online media. Sit behind the wheel of ultramodern hypercars from manufacturers such as Toyota, Ferrari and Porsche, and recreate the battles on prestigious tracks.</description></item><item><title>My Recycling Center</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-recycling-center/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-recycling-center/</guid><description>Game Description My Recycling Center puts you in the place of the owner of the waste processing enterprise, which is instructed to sort, compact and ultimately turn garbage into valuable resources. In this first -person simulator, you will plunge with your head into the world of waste management. Clients arrive with various loads - from crumpled paper to bulky furniture. Your task is to quickly evaluate and sort their garbage to special containers.</description></item><item><title>Corsairs Legacy - Pirate Action RPG and Sea Battles</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corsairs-legacy-pirate-action-rpg-and-sea-battles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/corsairs-legacy-pirate-action-rpg-and-sea-battles/</guid><description>Game Description Corsaires Legacy - Pirate Action RPG and Sea Battles is a pirate adventure in the open world, which makes it possible to become a real corsar, exploring the seas and oceans, as well as fighting with numerous enemies both on land and at sea. Events develop on Barbados. Playing for an adventurer, it is required to become not only a thunderstorm of the seas, but also a whole tropical archipelago.</description></item><item><title>Underdogs</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underdogs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underdogs/</guid><description>Game Description Underdogs - this is the Title in virtual reality, in which gamers fall into the very heart of the gloomy Cyberpanovsky world, where the fight of the furs reigns. The project does not hold back itself, pushing you with fierce enemies in cruel contractions. From the very first minutes, gamers plunge into the world of risk, where every step can mean the difference between life and death. Here you need to not just fight, but survive in conditions when the danger lurks around every angle.</description></item><item><title>Rising Lords</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-lords/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rising-lords/</guid><description>Game Description Rising Lords presents a mixture of a strategy with a card game in medieval setting. Fights are implemented using step -by -step mechanics. The player collects slaves and uses them for his personal purposes. As in any economic strategy, the gameplay is based on the collection of resources and taxes. The player is free to set the amount of duties depending on the solvency of units. It is required to set tasks and work to the peasants for the whole day.</description></item><item><title>Dogs Huddled Together</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dogs-huddled-together/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dogs-huddled-together/</guid><description>Game Description Dogs Huddled Together has to solve puzzles where each fragment is a separate figure of a dog. The main task is to combine these dog forms drawn by hand using a mouse to compose a whole picture. In total, the game of 32 levels that differ in the number of unique elements. Gamers move parts along the two -dimensional field, placing each in their place to complete the image.</description></item><item><title>World Warfare and Economics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-warfare-and-economics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/world-warfare-and-economics/</guid><description>Game Description World Warfare and Economics is a fascinating and large -scale strategy that offers to take control of any country on Earth, finding himself at the helm of world history. Having the opportunity to manage politics, economics and the armed forces of the country, players go through many trials, including the impending ghost of the Third World War, the inexorable procession of global pandemia and even scenarios created at their own discretion.</description></item><item><title>The enjenir</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-enjenir/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-enjenir/</guid><description>Game Description The Enjenir is a funny simulator based on physics in which players get used to the role of a clumsy Stone Age Engineer. This is a sandbox where you can build without restrictions and create unique structures using a wide selection of building materials and your own unique approach to design. In this game, you are not limited by standard construction methods - give the will to your imagination and create unusual, complex and functional constructions.</description></item><item><title>Against the Storm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/against-the-storm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/against-the-storm/</guid><description>Game Description Against the Storm combines two genres. This is a urban planning simulator and part -time sovereign. In this game, the gamer becomes a scout and mayor of different cities. The player is transferred to the fantasy world where the rain never stops. People and human -like intelligent animals live in the settlements: beavers and lizards.
In AGainst the Storm, the user, being the governor of the queen and the pioneer, rebels and develops colonies in various biomes, and also satisfies the needs of the population.</description></item><item><title>Ticket to Ride</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ticket-to-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ticket-to-ride/</guid><description>Game Description Ticket to Ride is a digital adaptation of a popular board game that invites gamers to go to a global railway adventure. Here, participants will have to build the most branched railway network, connecting the cities and completing the routes. Users play the cards to capture sections of the railway, building a strategy to go around rivals and achieve their goals. Title has both a single -user and multi -user regimes, which allows you to diversify the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Dungeons 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeons-4/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeons 4 is a real -time fantasy strategy with a bias in urban development, in which gamers will take the side of darkness and help the absolute evil and his faithful waist of the waist to win over the forces of good. You will fall into a fascinating world where peace and harmony once reigned, but now other times have come. You have to build your dungeon and direct your creatures into the outside world in order to envelop it with darkness and bring victory to the absolute evil.</description></item><item><title>Back to the Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/back-to-the-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description The prison atmosphere in Back to the Dawn shows the life of an anthropomorphic animal that is forced to fight for the right to exist in a zone. Gamers will explore prison laws, rules and locations in which a protagonist finds himself. The main character will pump and make new acquaintances, relying on his own social skills. It will be possible to use cunning and intelligence to solve many problems, where the main task is an attempt to escape from imprisonment.</description></item><item><title>Tabletop Creator Pro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tabletop-creator-pro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tabletop-creator-pro/</guid><description>Game Description Tabletop Creator Pro is software for design, prototyping and testing of board and card games. The tool allows you to create a variety of game -based game components. The user constructs these layouts from panels customized for any shape and contain elements such as images, text blocks or QR codes. The panels themselves support functions like rounded corners, icons and mirror values for orderly preparation of materials.
The editor of the schemes in the Tabletop Creator Pro is the key point in the development process.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Tavern</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-tavern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dungeon-tavern/</guid><description>Game Description The Dungeon Tavern fantasy world allows players to try out the unique adventurer skills, which will participate in erotic adventures. Users will take under the control of different heroes who will have to make their way into the mysterious tavern and face lustful girls and guys. Users will encounter NSFW content throughout the passage, which is designed for an adult audience. The game contains many shots with sexual entertainment between the characters.</description></item><item><title>Farmer's Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farmers-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farmers-life/</guid><description>Game Description The main character Farmer&amp;rsquo;s Life was Kashmir - a middle -aged bachelor living in the outback of Eastern Europe. It contains a small farm and is often applied to the bottle. The realism of what is happening does not end there. The character of the character is affected by the change of seasons and wild animals. Help Kashmir cultivate the land and survive in a harsh environment. Perform the hero’s natural needs, making sure that he is always fed, filled and laid to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Alaskan Road Truckers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/alaskan-road-truckers/</guid><description>Game Description ALASKAN ROAD TRUCKERS - A car simulator in which you will become a driver of huge trucks, being a trucker in snowy Alaska. Call a challenge of one of the most severe and dangerous environments that could only be in such simulators. Test your strength and try to survive in a harsh environment.
At the same time, you will have the opportunity to see the stunning beauty of this northern region.</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Option</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-option/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nuclear-option/</guid><description>Game Description In the game** Nuclear Option** you will find yourself in the cabin of modern combat aircraft on the battlefield of the near future, where the roar of engines and the crackling of tracers draw a bright picture of air battles. Each plane, from agile fighters to bulky bombers, is asked in hands, and its cabin pulsates with vital information while you scan targets and evade fire. The world unfolds under you - a dynamic tapestry of vast landscapes, raging seas and bristling enemy objects.</description></item><item><title>Railgrade</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railgrade/</guid><description>Game Description Railgrade gameplay combines elements of strategy and construction. The plot covers the times of the great construction of railways around the world in order to connect fast transportation between foreign cities with valuable industry. The main character will save the future of mankind, since he is the last employee of the earth colony. Megacorporations asked him to fulfill a difficult mission and save everything that remained on the planet after the disaster that occurred due to errors in the calculations of management.</description></item><item><title>Subpar Pool</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subpar-pool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/subpar-pool/</guid><description>Game Description Subpar Pool combines golf and billiard elements on a table of tables. The player will have to remove all balls for a limited number of blows at each procedured level, consisting of a sequence of connected surfaces. Gameplay based on physics requires strategic planning to roll objects. Classing and scattering balls often require adjusting the original plans, forcing to adapt the next move to complete the stage.
As you pass, gamers build a course, choosing cards from the deck to change experience.</description></item><item><title>The Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-front/</guid><description>Game Description In The Front, your task, as a resistance fighter, boils down to go into the past in order to prevent the formation of a tyrannical empire that threatens the very existence of mankind. The game is a craft shooter with an open world, immersing a player in a post -apocalyptic sandbox, teeming with mutants and hostile groups.
In this terrain destroyed by the war, you have to fight with tyrannical imperial forces, exiles, bandits and rebels in an epic battle, which will determine the future of mankind.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Circuit Board</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-circuit-board/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-circuit-board/</guid><description>Game Description Virtual Circuit Board is a logic simulator that uses a drawing interface within the sandbox. Here, gamers construct, program and activate creations, from individual circuits to full -scale computers. The entire gameplay is concentrated in this sandbox, since it does not have training, levels or pre -prepared tasks. Players set their own goals, working with a system designed for people with a basic understanding of logical elements and their functions.</description></item><item><title>Saleblazers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saleblazers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/saleblazers/</guid><description>Game Description Saleblazers offers to enjoy the exciting experience of survival in the multiplayer action, in which you have to create a store and survive in a dangerous world filled with various dangers. On this dangerous island you will have to build cozy cafes or huge shopping centers in the company with other players. The whole world of the game is a reactive sandbox, where each buyer has his own character, tastes and preferences.</description></item><item><title>AFTERWAR</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/afterwar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/afterwar/</guid><description>Game Description AFTERWAR represents a global scenario unfolding in 2028, after a centuries of conflicts. The alternative version of the future left behind historical wars, laying the foundation for universal interaction. In the role of the national leader, the player will have to unite the states and dispose of resources to build a new society. Any step, from the distribution of the budget and the introduction of advanced technologies to the conclusion of international agreements, directly affects the balance between stability and chaos.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the White Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rise-of-the-white-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Rise of the White Sun transfers to the chaos of China of the 1920s, the period of riots and fragmented leadership. In this grandiose strategic game, you have to pave the way through a fragmented nation controlled by military leaders, rebels and political groups. The action unfolds at a time when various groups dispute control of vast territories and armies, each of which has its own goals, objectives and motives.</description></item><item><title>The Backrooms: Last Expedition</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-backrooms-last-expedition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-backrooms-last-expedition/</guid><description>Game Description The BackRooms: Last Expedition is a cooperative in the horror genre, in which from 1 to 4 gamers are united in teams to survive in an alarming world. The main attention is paid to the passage of a series of dangerous, constantly changing levels, each of which is filled with mysterious creatures. Together, players should try to escape from the horror surrounding them, using their collective forces to resist the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Pumping Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pumping-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pumping-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Pumping Simulator 2 sends you on a trip to the world of management of gas stations. Start your entrepreneurial adventure by the sale of a classic car to get the funds necessary for the reconstruction of an abandoned gas station in a busy city. Your goal is to turn an abandoned station into a prosperous center for local residents and travelers. From the very beginning, you will build, expand and modernize your gas station.</description></item><item><title>High Sea Saga DX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/high-sea-saga-dx/</guid><description>Game Description High Sea Saga DX immerses players in the marine environment, focused on the accumulation of wealth and global research. In this Title, gamers control the pirate team crossing the oceans in search of hidden treasures scattered through a variety of geographical zones. Each such journey entails a clash with various wild creatures and battles with warring pirate fractions that pursue similar goals. Success requires the collection of an effective detachment and the construction of a swimming agent, ready for long -term crossings by open waters.</description></item><item><title>Bee Island</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-island/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bee-island/</guid><description>Game Description In Bee Island, you will become the head of a prosperous hive, taking on the role of a defender from impending threats. The main attention in the game is paid to defense and strategic construction. Enemies make sporadic attacks, and your task is to protect the hive. They are armed with bombs, poisonous aerosols and missiles, their strength is constantly growing. To reflect their attack, you have to build a whole complex of protective structures - ballists, machine guns, anti -aircraft missile systems and much more.</description></item><item><title>Ship Graveyard Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ship-graveyard-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ship-graveyard-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description Ship Graveyard Simulator 2 is a fascinating and realistic first -person construction simulator. If you are ready to pick up a cutter and a hammer again, then it&amp;rsquo;s time to go to the new coast with the largest cemetery of ships in the world and start dismantling huge details of ships. In this continuation, you will find new, even larger vessels, new gaming mechanics, functions and improvements, as well as improved mechanics that you loved in the first part.</description></item><item><title>Desynced</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/desynced/</guid><description>Game Description Desynced is a three -dimensional real -time strategy. The indie project also has elements of survival and a colony control simulator. The Title is made in a science fiction setting. It has support for user modifications. According to the plot, the hero travels along with artificial intelligence and colonizers between distant planets. The protagonist plants bots to the surface, and he remains in orbit and leads mechanical creatures from there.</description></item><item><title>Gorebox</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gorebox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gorebox/</guid><description>Game Description Gorebox is an exciting sandbox that allows you to reveal its creative potential and create a world full of tense moments on the basis of physics. Various types of weapons and explosives are offered a choice, as well as a special device called Reality Crusher, which makes it possible to interact with surrounding objects. In addition, you can configure your character using skins and accessories, as well as create or explore user cards through the built -in editor and workshop.</description></item><item><title>Δv: rings of saturn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rings-of-saturn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/v-rings-of-saturn/</guid><description>Game Description Rings of Saturn is a two -dimensional cosmoster, whose events are transferred to the distant future of 2273. Humanity began to extract important resources on the rings of Saturn. This event began to be called the golden fever of the new century. You control the ship that is engaged in the prey of fossils in the open spaces of the open space. Your main goal was only one - to get rich.</description></item><item><title>Call Hating</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-hating/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/call-hating/</guid><description>Game Description In Call Hating, an aging and forgetful employee working from the house is faced with a technological crisis after a smartphone breakdown and the Internet disconnect. The main task of the player is to use outdated equipment from the home office to pass the hellish telephone menu. The path to restoring the connection lies through interaction with the acquired technology and solve a series of problems. This mission is served as an urgent need, and the goal must be achieved at all costs.</description></item><item><title>Driftwood</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/driftwood/</guid><description>Game Description Driftwood is a fascinating journey into the world of high -speed descent on Longboard. The main character is Eddie, a cool sliven who loves to ride in beautiful landscapes. This game provides an ideal balance of speed and control, bringing a feeling of relaxation and calm, despite a high -speed action.
The project offers minimalistic experience, focusing on skating on magnificent landscapes, and not on building a story campaign.</description></item><item><title>Railway Empire 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/railway-empire-2/</guid><description>Game Description Railway Empire 2 is a transport strategy that offers to go into the past, at the beginning of the 19th century, and lead a small railway company, which will become the leader of the economy thanks to steam cars. Here you have to compete with competitors and build a network of railways, which will connect cities and companies throughout the continent. At your disposal 60 famous steam machines that pull freight and passenger cars, opening the historically significant era of the time of the industrial revolution.</description></item><item><title>Fly Corp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fly-corp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fly-corp/</guid><description>Game Description The development of routes in Fly Corp allows you to feel the work of real airports located throughout the globe. Players get the opportunity to create transport routes in the airspace, setting up the uninterrupted transportation of passengers who want to fly from one city to another. The task of the user will be to establish the right nodes and the implementation of flights that can most profitably and effectively transport the inhabitants of the planet to the necessary destination.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Life</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tiny-life/</guid><description>Game Description The developers** Tiny Life** were inspired by The Sims series, trying to transfer the gameplay to their own project. The gameplay presents pixel graphics and the vast capabilities of the simulator of the life of controlled characters. Before the start of the passage, the player can choose a certain group of people, one ward or use the function of creating.
In Tiny Life, the user will have to control all aspects of the life of a group of people living together in the same house.</description></item><item><title>Stranded: Alien Dawn</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stranded-alien-dawn/</guid><description>Game Description Stranded: Alien Dawn is an open world survival simulator. In this case, an alien. According to the plot, a group of people on a rescue shuttle is evacuated from a burning starship and landed on the first planet that fall. The player controls the team of surviving crew members of the space ship. He needs to take care of his wards, providing them with warmth, light, food, medicines, weapons, entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Total Conflict: Resistance</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/total-conflict-resistance/</guid><description>Game Description Total Conflict: Resistance is an incredible mixture of global strategy, tactics and an action in the first person that provides incredible battles, many types of armored vehicles, weapons and armor, as well as unique mechanics to immerse you in exciting gameplay. You have to take part in events, manage units, create your army and produce or purchase armored vehicles and weapons. You can also build fortifications, outposts and settlements, manage military operations in the first person, as well as in tactical mode.</description></item><item><title>Swirl Watch</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swirl-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/swirl-watch/</guid><description>Game Description Swirl Watch is a stealth scene of a horn, unfolding on a gas giant undergoing excessive operation. Players have to penetrate industrial complexes, bypass or neutralize protection vessels, committing corporate sabotage to create a resistance movement. In the dense atmosphere of the planet Cloud 2, ships find each other only in laser light, noise of engines and echolocation.
This situation creates specific conditions for bypassing patrols and dismantling cloud processing stations.</description></item><item><title>Pinball FX</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-fx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pinball-fx/</guid><description>Game Description Pinball FX is not a dusty arcade machine of your father. This digital pinball takes a classic game and injects steroids into it. Forget about awkward management and faded decorations - the title offers a bright collection of tables, each of which has its own unique quirks and goals. Fight the aliens on Mars, worry Christmas with Charlie Brown or save the world along with cult films. Diversity does not allow to get bored, offering something for every user.</description></item><item><title>Nucleares</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nucleares/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nucleares/</guid><description>Game Description Nucleares may be of interest to lovers of original projects and unusual indie-symptures. This is a simulator of an employee of a nuclear power plant with a first -person view. The character has arms, legs and torso. They can be seen if you lower the camera. The hero turns out to be the only employee at an experimental nuclear power plant for which large staff does not need. This object requires only one person, because artificial intelligence is responsible for everything else.</description></item><item><title>Contraband Police</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/contraband-police/</guid><description>Game Description Contraband Police - The simulator of the border guard in the first person. The player in the role of the commander of the border post makes an inspection of transport for the presence of smuggling on the border of the third world countries. The inspection tasks include: checking documents: inspection and permit for entry criminals &amp;hellip; or take a bribe. What? Nobody heard this! To carry out reports on the successful completion of tasks through the mail; the accumulated experience can be spent on pumping the department, buying new equipment or training dogs;</description></item><item><title>Research Story</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/research-story/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/research-story/</guid><description>Game Description Research Story offers to go on a fascinating journey through a mysterious area and help Violet Archive with a recording of exotic plants and creatures. This is a colorful farm simulator that you definitely should try! It is necessary to explore the chimerbruck and its environs, find and write down a variety of plants and creatures, as well as breed your unique garden and take care of pets. In addition, you will have to establish relations with local residents and fulfill various quests.</description></item><item><title>X-Plane 12</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x-plane-12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x-plane-12/</guid><description>Game Description X -Plane 12 is a realistic air system that allows you to fly around the world on a variety of aircraft. Each type of transport is represented by unique characteristics and individual control panels. Professional pilots took part in the development of X-Plane 12, which allows gameplay to transfer real experience from air management. Airplanes, helicopters, gliders, etc. are available for flights.
The elaboration of not only aircraft is released, but also the environment.</description></item><item><title>KYNSEED</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kynseed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kynseed/</guid><description>Game Description KYNSEED is a role -playing game in an adventure genre and a life simulator in an open world. The game saw the light in 2018 and has already managed to find its own fan base. The essence of the passage is to completely immerse into the invented world, filled with various inhabitants, who have their own affairs and habits. The player is invited to interact with these characters, simultaneously equipping his own life.</description></item><item><title>Police Simulator: Patrol Officers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/police-simulator-patrol-officers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/police-simulator-patrol-officers/</guid><description>Game Description Police Simulator: Patrol Officers is a policeman simulator, offering to plunge on weekdays of this difficult profession. Players put on the cap of the cop to go to patrol the streets of Brighton. It is necessary to start the path with the simplest tasks. For example, write a fine for parking, etc. Later, new missions will open, in which it will be necessary to take part in the chases of the monitoring of criminals.</description></item><item><title>Winter Falling: Battle Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-falling-battle-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Falling: Battle Tactics invites gamers to lead the troops and lead them to victory in the most stressful and tactical battles. And only your mind can save the dying world from devastation. You control a detachment of mercenaries, collect supplies and troops, perform tasks and even you can burn villages if you decide that you need it. But do not forget that all your actions have consequences.</description></item><item><title>Out of Ore</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/out-of-ore/</guid><description>Game Description In Out of Ore, gamers have to take many heavy equipment under their control, with the help of which it will be possible to extract ore, move the ground, dig pits, build or repair buildings and much more. It is necessary to test yourself as a driver of construction equipment, which is intended for various purposes. The main character goes on the plot for the very north of the country where there is a small base from Company Mining Corp.</description></item><item><title>Victoria 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victoria-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/victoria-3/</guid><description>Game Description Victoria 3 is a direct sequel to the game of the same name, where the gamer will act in a time period from 1836 to 1936. In the manager’s simulator, Juzer is invited to choose one of the available countries, and manage it for the specified time. It will have to be controlled by political, demographic, economic processes, as well as try to pacify the layers of the population in order to build an ideal society.</description></item><item><title>Mars Base</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mars-base/</guid><description>Game Description Mars Base will appreciate all fans of science fiction, as Gamer goes to the world of the future, in which travels between planets became possible. Humanity makes a desperate attempt to colonize Mars, but the first settlers will be in a serious danger. The protagonist is one of those who fell into the very first expedition and is obliged to build a huge complex on the surface of the Red Planet, which will make a person’s life away from the ground.</description></item><item><title>PC Building Simulator 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pc-building-simulator-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pc-building-simulator-2/</guid><description>Game Description PC Building Simulator 2 - a simulator for assembling a personal computer, in which players need to take on the role of a businessman engaged in PC sales. A full -fledged career regime is available. You will need to learn how to work with customers by accepting their orders. Players need to both repair computers and collect them from scratch.
It is important to constantly increase profits to pay for rent and buy new components or tools.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Sailor NG</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-sailor-ng/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/virtual-sailor-ng/</guid><description>Game Description Virtual Sailor NG is a simulator with the open world, concentrated on the management of water vessels. The physical system of the project reproduces marine dynamics and behavior of various boats on the water. This allows gamers to direct vessels anywhere within the environment, which opens up scope for research. Players master all forms of sailing, using the first -person species and 6 degrees of freedom. Both single and multiplayer regime are available.</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Terra Invicta</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-invicta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/terra-invicta/</guid><description>Game Description Terra Invicta is a cosmic 4x strategy, the events of which develop in the distant future. Once, alien forces invaded our galaxy, dividing humanity into 7 factions. Each union saw its development of the future. You have to lead one of the seven ideologies to impose it to the whole world. Explore the solar system, expand the territories and fight enemies in tactical fights.
The aliens invaded the far corner of the Kuiper ice belt.</description></item><item><title>After the Collapse</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/after-the-collapse/</guid><description>Game Description AFTER The COLLAPSE is a 2D strategy, a management and management simulator of its own settlement. A camera that is above above the surface at right angles is used. The surrounding world survived the apocalypse, which is why it turned into radioactive wastelands and became very dangerous for living people without means of protection against monsters and aggressive bandits. The task of the gamer is to develop existing buildings and build new ones to increase population growth and create a powerful army that is ready to fight off external threats.</description></item><item><title>Way of the Hunter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/way-of-the-hunter/</guid><description>Game Description Way of the Hunter gives an excellent opportunity to become the owner of his own hunting house in the middle of a deaf forest and periodically go hunting in search of extreme and valuable production. This simulator offers a very realistic experience, as it takes into account many factors and allows you to plunge into a huge completely open virtual world, which looks like alive. It exists regardless of the action of the user - the weather, the time of day changes dynamically, and all the animals sleep, eat, move in search of a safer place.</description></item><item><title>Farthest Frontier</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farthest-frontier/</guid><description>Game Description Farthest Frontier is a strategic game with the simulator elements. The game is made by all canons of 4x-mechanics. You have to develop your settlement and defend it from an attack by the enemy. Guide your people and try not only to survive, but also to develop. The world of wildlife is fraught with many dangers with which you have to face face every day.
Collect resources, go hunting, do fishing or farming - do everything possible to survive in harsh and wild conditions.</description></item><item><title>Starship Troopers - Terran Command</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starship-troopers-terran-command/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starship-troopers-terran-command/</guid><description>Game Description Starship Troopers - Terran Command is a real -time strategy developed based on the Feature Film Star landing. Engage in the construction of the base, get resources and create an army to fight with giant insects living on a foreign planet. You need to colonize the hostile planet, which was suitable for the human race, but a huge number of hostile alien creatures live on its surface.
Take the role of the leader of the Terran army.</description></item><item><title>Frozenheim</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frozenheim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/frozenheim/</guid><description>Game Description Frozenheim - a saga about the Vikings, in which the main character is expelled from his native lands, since blood feud tears his last name. He goes in search of a new home for himself and his loyal subjects. The harsh winter is approaching, and the clan needs to get to the shelter as quickly as possible. The construction of the settlement is a prolonged matter and the central character does not fit.</description></item><item><title>Flight of Nova</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flight-of-nova/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/flight-of-nova/</guid><description>Game Description Flight of Nova is a simulator that allows you to sit in a cosmic shuttle cabin and explore a galaxy called Nova. Make interstellar flights and examine the continents using cosmoshattl. Management is completely focused on physics and aerodynamics. Feel the weight and bulkiness of transport, and also experience a feeling of piloting with a bulky car in zero gravity.
Explore the surroundings near the NVA-31 planet. Train to manage the ship, choosing one of several available cargo shutters.</description></item><item><title>Keplerth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/keplerth/</guid><description>Game Description The events of the futuristic Indo-video trigger Keplerth unfold in the distant future-on the previously unknown planet Kepler. According to the genre, the project can be attributed to the simulator of survival with the possibility of construction and RPG elements. According to the plot, people built a large spaceship, which was supposed to transport the colonists on board to the nearest planet suitable for life. But there is a disaster, as a result of which the ship crashes on an unknown planet.</description></item><item><title>Venture Towns</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/venture-towns/</guid><description>Game Description Venture Towns allows players to build a city landscape. This project transfers to the gamers the corporation forming a settlement. From the initial structures to vast skyscrapers, the player leads the development, striving for economic superiority. The game emphasizes the deliberate arrangement of various architectural elements, contributing to a systematic approach to urbanistic growth and current economic activity.
In Venture Towns, the processes of the construction of objects open the ways for development.</description></item><item><title>Old World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/old-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/old-world/</guid><description>Game Description Old World in the past was also known as 10 Crowns. The game is a step -by -step global strategy in the antique setting. The gameplay is strikingly different from the games of this genre: it is allowed to give several orders to Unit in one move. Such a resource as &amp;ldquo;orders&amp;rdquo; is responsible for additional moves. The more recognition points, the more moves can be made. The resource &amp;ldquo;Order&amp;rdquo; can be used in different ways: in battle, in construction, in events or diplomacy.</description></item><item><title>Idle Calibur</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/idle-calibur/</guid><description>Game Description Idle Calibur combines a study of the open world with tactical RPG tactical and real -time mechanics in real time. The gameplay is focused on the construction of a city, which serves to recruit heroes with special abilities. Battles can be automatically due to IDLE function, or you can take direct manual control of your detachments during the fight. Key tasks include the collection of forces to attack other settlements on the world map and participate in structured tests with bosses for development.</description></item><item><title>Noble Fates</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noble-fates/</guid><description>Game Description The fantasy world of Noble Fates immerses in the adventures taking place in the fabulous kingdom. A group of gods observes the plan of human material being, while mortals compete for power over territories and new lands. The main character is a counter that is a demigod and capable of influencing people and other residents of the planet. It will be possible to manage the whole colonies of settlers to achieve prosperity for the future great civilization.</description></item><item><title>Breakwaters</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/breakwaters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/breakwaters/</guid><description>Game Description In Breakwaters, the player will reconnolate the procedurally generated world with monstrous ocean depths and huge titans that change the method of interaction with water. Water is replaced by powerful crystals obtained in the mine. The user is able to delve into its bowels to collect rare objects, build obstacles to restrain the ocean or block waves, and help people after destruction.
Titans, creatures of an extinct submarine race, wander around the world, causing cataclysms.</description></item><item><title>Icarus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/icarus/</guid><description>Game Description Icarus is a first -person survival that will send you to explore the secrets of one distant planet. You wake up from cryosn after your shuttle made a forced landing on the surface of a mysterious planet. Now you need to stay alive, surviving in unusual conditions. Collect resources, craft items and play both alone and along with other players. The gameplay Ikarus can be described as cooperative action with survival elements.</description></item><item><title>Dysmantle</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dysmantle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dysmantle/</guid><description>Game Description Dysmantle offers gamers to survive on the island and find a way to get out of this place. The local post -apocalyptic world is not gloomy. There is no atmosphere of hopelessness here either. The game has a bright cartoon graphics with juicy colors. During the end of the world, the protagonist hides in an underground bunker. Once the hero crawls out and discovers that people and animals have turned into evil creatures similar to zombies.</description></item><item><title>Gas Station Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gas-station-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gas-station-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description GAS Station Simulator - simulator of owning its own refueling, combined with the raising station for road transport, which is located in deserted areas, near the number 66, which is in the United States of America. There is an opportunity to control the gameplay using a gamepad. The player will have to refuel with all the affairs with the help of a virtual protege with a first -person view.</description></item><item><title>City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/city-game-studio-a-tycoon-about-game-dev/</guid><description>Game Description City Game Studio: A Tycoon ABOUT GAME DEV is a strategic simulator in which it is important not only to chase the demand of players, but also be able to reduce expenses and vice versa, be able to spend money where they are actually needed. Games developers presented a simulator in which you will have to develop a company that develops games. A small studio creating video games decided to expand, so you must make every effort to create a whole headquarters of developers who can satisfy the needs of modern gamers.</description></item><item><title>The Doors of Trithius</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-doors-of-trithius/</guid><description>Game Description The Doors of Trithius is a RPG -Rogalik in the fantasy world with procedurally generated content. Here you have to fight monsters, avoid traps, collect prey and much more, traveling along the mysterious world of Enalia. Every time you start the game, you have to explore the new generated city, dungeon and map of the world. Movement and battle use a unique time system, returning the priority of the player based on the speed of weapons or action, maintaining tactical decisions, as well as knowledge about your enemies.</description></item><item><title>My Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/my-garage/</guid><description>Game Description My Garage is a simulator simulator with a first -person view. In it you can not only repair cars, but also ride them. During travel by transport, you can switch the camera angle. In Indo Tailet, weather conditions are changing. The change of day and night is also available. When driving in the dark, you can turn on the headlights.
My Garage has an open world. It consists of mountains, forests, a field, rivers and attractions, like a lighthouse.</description></item><item><title>Wrestling Empire</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrestling-empire/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrestling-empire/</guid><description>Game Description In Wrestling Empire the player becomes a participant in the World Lightweight Championship. It is necessary to manage an athlete in the ring, apply his abilities and win rivals. The battles are presented in real time with extensive visual effects. This part includes a smooth frequency of personnel and modern graphics, while leaving the atmosphere of retro-style.
This version has more functions and capabilities in pumping and battles. The user will face unique opponents with the original characteristic and special skills.</description></item><item><title>Going Medieval</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/going-medieval/</guid><description>Game Description Going Medieval is a simulator in which you need to build a fortress on the ruins of an old castle and equip it to protect your settlement. Any event can affect the mood of your people, so you need to satisfy all their needs and be a good king. Events unfold in the era of the dark Middle Ages of the late XIV century.
Only five percent of the population survived after a heavy plague epidemic.</description></item><item><title>Snowrunner</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/snowrunner/</guid><description>Game Description The main difference between Snowrunner and many other cargo simulators is that there are no even roads, highways and autobahns. Only snow, dirt and insurmountable obstacles. The game meets with interesting and diverse tasks, vast cards and, most importantly, a wide choice of transport: SUVs, tractors, all -terrain vehicles and trucks. After choosing a cargo and a car, you should go on a road that is not going to be easy.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Prepper</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-prepper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mr-prepper/</guid><description>Game Description Mr. Prepper is a construction simulator where you have to build a bunker under a residential building. Mr. The survivor of those who believe in the theory of conspiracies and understands that a serious threat of nuclear war hung over the world. He does not care about his neighbors and those who do not believe him, so he alone begins to build his own bomb shelter. The nuclear war is close and you must be ready!</description></item><item><title>FireWorks Mania - An Explosive Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fireworks-mania-an-explosive-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/fireworks-mania-an-explosive-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description FireWorks Mania - an Explosive Simulator - a simulator in which you need to deal with fireworks. Explore firecrackers, run various signal missiles into the air, etc. Your task is to arrange a real fire show. However, nothing prevents you from just blowing things up and enjoy the gameplay.
The gameplay was developed with the aim of entertaining players or to please creative people who know how to think non-standard and create truly amazing fireworks.</description></item><item><title>Easy Red 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/easy-red-2/</guid><description>Game Description Easy Red 2 is a first -person shooter with elements of a strategy that immerses in an authentic atmosphere of World War II. The gameplay can plunge into tense and cruel battles, where the main thing is planning and tactics. The gameplay relies on realism. Take a break through the tanks and the enemy’s huge army. Do not fall into the explosion zone and look for ways to survive on the battlefield with your partners.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom 2: Monster Camp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-2-monster-camp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-2-monster-camp/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom 2: Monster Camp is a multi -user dite simulator, the actions of which take place in the monsters camp. The game is replete with charismatic characters and black humor. The events of the game are transferred to the summer camp, where teenagers rest before the start of the new school year. Among the characters, both old heroes and many new ones are represented: Damien, Calcelter, Milo, Dalia, Joy and Arab.</description></item><item><title>Empyrion - Galactic Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/empyrion-galactic-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Empyrion - Galactic Survival shows the world of the future. In the 24th century, in the ice of Antarctica, they find a spacecraft of aliens. Scientists investigated the object and discovered the technology of the hyperdrod. Earthlings send an expedition to the planet Empirion, which is in the Andromeda nebula. The crew gets to the destination, but tolerates the crash and cannot return home.
In survival mode, the player leaves the rescue capsule and is alone against the hostile world.</description></item><item><title>Travellers Rest</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/travellers-rest/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/travellers-rest/</guid><description>Game Description Travellers Rest gives the opportunity to live the life of an innkeeper. You own a small tavern that you dream to turn into a noisy and crowded place in the district. But to achieve this goal, you need to work a lot. Build a bro -up and cook the most delicious beer. Manage the farm and serve only the best products on the table. Satisfy customer requests and gain popularity so that a whole kingdom speaks of your institution!</description></item><item><title>Ostriv</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ostriv/</guid><description>Game Description OSTRIV, this is a city -building simulator that makes you the ruler of the monarch of the 18th century. The player will have to work hard and show his ability to the manager, as well as creative abilities. The goal of the game to transfer the gameplay of simulators of this kind to a new level, by means of adding a huge number of opportunities and abandoning the usual restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Panzer Corps 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panzer-corps-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/panzer-corps-2/</guid><description>Game Description Plunge into a new type of step -by -step strategies in Panzer Corps 2. The game tells about terrible events during the Second World War. You have to play a key role, taking a large army under command. This is easy to master the gameplay, and the outcome of the battles will depend only on the correct moves, not the reaction.
Players can take control of any European country and create their own army of thousands of various units.</description></item><item><title>The Sapling</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-sapling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-sapling/</guid><description>Game Description The Sapling is a simulator in which you will be selected by growing new plant species or crossing animals. Build your own world inhabited by unusual animals and a phantasmagoric fauna. The Sapling allows you to choose a random mutation mode to be a third -party observer, providing nature to conduct evolution itself and create its own ecosystems. At any time, you can take the development of the environment into your own hands.</description></item><item><title>Ai War 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-war-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-war-2/</guid><description>Game Description In AI WAR 2, an even more advanced version of AI captured the entire galaxy, and left only a tiny planet to the player. It&amp;rsquo;s time to strike and outwit the enemy. This will come in handy new capabilities, large flotillas and hacking skills. Or you can get involved in a much more confusing galactic struggle. On the agenda - macrophages, Dyson spheres, nanocosts and much more. Each faction has its own goal, its own rules, units and a completely unique economy.</description></item><item><title>Green Hell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/green-hell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/green-hell/</guid><description>Game Description The survival simulator, which has been waiting for the real depletion of the hero in the conditions of wild jungle for a long time! The protagonist will visit the dark forests of the Amazon with only a radio from the objects of “his time”, and his hands and head will go to help him, which will begin to betray over time. Green Hell - survival, exhaustion, mentally undermined health of the main character.</description></item><item><title>Steel Division 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steel-division-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/steel-division-2/</guid><description>Game Description Steel Division 2 is a real -time strategy, during which you will visit the role of Army General during the Bagration Operation. The plot was established during the Second World War on the Eastern Front, and there are thousands of fighters under your command. Thanks to an extensive list of opportunities, the gameplay can take you tens of hours. Pass the plot missions or participate in free mode in a multi -user or single game.</description></item><item><title>Spaceengine</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spaceengine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/spaceengine/</guid><description>Game Description Spaceengine is a space simulator that makes a photorealistic open space at your disposal that simulates the universe. The SpaceenGine gameplay can be described as an interactive planetarium with procedural generation. Study the long -range corners of the cosmos, visit the planets and fly on a hypercost shuttle.
The simulator modifies the spaces of space on a scale of 1: 1. Everything is available in the game: billions of galaxies, foggy, stars and planets - go anywhere and examine any part of the universe.</description></item><item><title>Wrench</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wrench/</guid><description>Game Description Wrench is an auto mechanic simulator with an emphasis on realism. The task of this game is to clarify the breakdown of the car and the subsequent elimination of problems. Most cars will arrive from racing tracks, so some problems will make your head break.
Your career growth begins with the position of a younger assistant who is engaged in the replacement of car liquids and tires. As you pass, the game will teach you professional skills, allowing you to move along the career ladder and move to your goal.</description></item><item><title>X4: Foundations</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x4-foundations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/x4-foundations/</guid><description>Game Description In X4: Foundations you can create any spaceship, and then sit down for its helm and start to smash the enemies right and left. The first -person shooter with RPG and sandboxes combines several temporary eras enclosed in a couple of hours of game, but it is impossible to enjoy the gameplay of this project even in a week.
You can construct ships of different sizes and goals. It can be small scouts and large ships, wearing several hundred combat birds on their huge backs.</description></item><item><title>The Colonists</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-colonists/</guid><description>Game Description The Colonists are a urban planning sandbox in which you control a team of robots that create themselves. In the game you do not have to fight or kill enemies. The plot side of the project is meditative. You are landing on the planet, begin to carry out non -difficult tasks in which you need to build a settlement, and then improve your town depending on the preferences. Also in the game there is a “free mode” - here you make an island yourself, plant robots, begin to build a city from the resources obtained.</description></item><item><title>On the Western Front</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/on-the-western-front/</guid><description>Game Description On the Western Front - this is a tactical strategy, the action of which unfolds against the background of the First World War, namely on the infamous Western Front. Users take on the role of the division commander, who are instructed to manage various aspects of military operations in one of the most exhausting and complex periods in history. The Title emphasizes the harsh realities of the trench war, where the soldiers are faced with many problems, from the constant threat of enemy fire to the constant need to manage resources.</description></item><item><title>Mad Restaurant People</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mad-restaurant-people/</guid><description>Game Description Mad Restaurant People makes it possible to feel all the difficulty of working as a waiter. The game is presented with a top distance, which makes it possible to observe the entire hall at once. Take orders, serve customers, serve dishes in time, count the guests and much more. Mad Restaurant People is a full -fledged waiter’s simulator who will not let you relax for a second.
The gameplay requires attentiveness, reaction speed, good memory and many other important qualities.</description></item><item><title>Pro Evolution Socker 2019</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pro-evolution-soccer-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pro-evolution-soccer-2019/</guid><description>Game Description PES 2019 - one of the games that won the recognition of fans through the territory of the entire planet - Pro Evolution Soccer 2019 is a new football league hidden in the old filling. Gradually improving their brainchild, the developers came to a perfect schedule, plausible sound and real physics of movement. This part includes several additions in which you will hire professional football players for several matches and prove that the team management is your craft from birth!</description></item><item><title>Mist Survival</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mist-survival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mist-survival/</guid><description>Game Description Another survival game among zombies is Mist Survival. A completely open world, a unique system of characteristics, new types of weapons, shelters and the ability to create their own gang, attracted new players to fight on an open map against the crowd of enraged people absorbed in the epidemic. The main character, like all real players, will be protected from the epidemic, because in their body there is a special hormone that needs to be nourished every day.</description></item><item><title>Star Explorers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-explorers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-explorers/</guid><description>Game Description Star Explorers is designed for lovers of space and complete freedom of action. After the death of the Earth, people got into a giant-chip and went on a trip. But the ship ends with fuel, and the crew does not know where it is best to establish the colony. The game offers to become a researcher looking for a new house and resources for humanity.
Gamer has its own starship at the disposal (you can take a walk on it).</description></item><item><title>Zero-K</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-k/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-k/</guid><description>Game Description Zero-K is a real-time strategy. The indie project allows for large-scale battles on land, water and in the air. This RTS has worked out physics and ballistics. During the battles, the landscape changes. You can even level the soil to your tactical needs. The game allows you to create funnels for enemy tanks, digging ditches and erecting embankments, hiding fighters behind the hills so that they are not taken by enemy shells, dig water channels for the passage of their fleet through land, put a soldier on a hill for better visibility and increase the range of shooting.</description></item><item><title>Farm Manager 2018</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-2018/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/farm-manager-2018/</guid><description>Game Description Farm Manager 2018 is a simulator for building your own farm, where the territory of your competitors will slowly go into your possessions. A change of day and nights was added to the game. Also, such cultures as cucumbers, apples, strawberries and other varieties were added to the new part. If you are tired of growing simple wheat or oats, then you can definitely change the direction, but do not forget to monitor the economy.</description></item><item><title>Through The Ages</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/through-the-ages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/through-the-ages/</guid><description>Game Description Through The Ages is a port of a cult board game adapted to personal computers. Compared to the original party in the digital version, they take much less time. Instead of 4-8 hours, a maximum of 1 hour takes the game session, since the computer is engaged in all calculations.
According to its concept, Through The Ages resembles the Titles of the Civilization series. Only here development occurs using various cards.</description></item><item><title>Bio Inc. Redemption</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bio-inc-redemption/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bio-inc-redemption/</guid><description>Game Description Bio Inc. Redemption is a biomedical simulator where a player has to choose life or death. These are 2 main regimes where you need to perform a variety of tasks. You are able to create deadly diseases, mocking a person presented on the screen. Or put on the medic&amp;rsquo;s mask and find the virus, look for the vaccine and save the infected ones.
The gameplay provides more than 600 diseases existing in the real world, accurate symptoms, diagnostic tests and various ways of treatment for each virus.</description></item><item><title>StationEers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stationeers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stationeers/</guid><description>Game Description Stationeers will transfer the player to outer space, in which it is necessary to control the space station alone or with other participants. You will follow all aspects of the station. Manage and deal with complex atmospheric, electric, production, medical and other equally important technologies inside a large room.
You will need to correctly build mechanisms and other objects to create a beautiful architecture, and also not to die due to a lack of oxygen or an excess of electricity.</description></item><item><title>Brigand: Oaxaca</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/brigand-oaxaca/</guid><description>Game Description Brigand: Oaxaca is a first -person shooter hybrid, immersive simulator and role -playing game. The project has three -dimensional low -polygonal graphics. Due to her, the title resembles computer action of the late 90s and early 2000s. The action takes place in a world where nuclear apocalypse happened. Events unfold on the territory of the Mexican state of Ohak. Indi-game combines elements of different settings. In it, the gunshot weapons are adjacent to Voodoo magic, and not only mutters, but also demons roam the wastelands.</description></item><item><title>Wayward</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wayward/</guid><description>Game Description Survive in the wild in Wayward, traveling around the open world. The protagonist has no basic specialization, as he passes, he pumps skills and becomes capable of everything. To get new characteristics, you have to interact with objects and the world around you. You have the opportunity to play as you want.
The world is endless and generated randomly. Objects, chests, opponents, dangers, dungeons and tasks are also created by chance.</description></item><item><title>Universe Sandbox</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/universe-sandbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/universe-sandbox/</guid><description>Game Description Universe Sandbox is a continuation of the space simulator, which showed the real behavior of various objects in space. The game can be used as a virtual allowance for astronomy to understand how black holes behave or asteroids move. At the same time, the game will be interesting not only to beginners, but also to people who know definitions such as Betelheze and quantum voids.
The gameplay of space sandbox will create objects, interact with them and destroy using Newton&amp;rsquo;s mechanics.</description></item><item><title>Software Inc.</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/software-inc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/software-inc/</guid><description>Game Description Software Inc. - An economic simulator that allows the development of a company engaged in the development of software. Initially, it is required to build an office building, buy inexpensive equipment and hire several employees, distributing tasks between them. To get funding, at first the newly made team will take on third -party projects and various simple tasks.
As the budget becomes more, the staff will be more experienced and new faces will come, it will also be possible to engage in the external design of the facade, build beautiful paths and decor items to give the office a presentable look.</description></item><item><title>Exanima</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exanima/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/exanima/</guid><description>Game Description Exanima is a representative of the category of isometric role -playing games on a PC, in which the camera is fixed above the character, but it can be brought closer to detailed examination of objects and objects, as well as deleted, for more convenient battles. This project operates the theme of the gloomy Middle Ages, so the arsenal of a character managed by a player consists mainly of long -tier -fingered and remote weapons (bows, crossbows, throwing spears).</description></item><item><title>Craft the World</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/craft-the-world/</guid><description>Game Description Craft the World is an adventure 2D game that combines multiple elements. You can explore the procedurally generated worlds, build locks and fortresses, fight with hostile creatures and get materials necessary for numerous crafts.
Manage the dwarf tribe and lead them the way you want. The player can send his wards to extract resources, build structures or fight with opponents. But, not everything is so simple. You have to put them on, help in battles and feed them in time.</description></item><item><title>PayDay 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/payday-2/</guid><description>Game Description Re-join thePayDay 2 gang as Dallas, Hoxton, Chains or Wolfe, who have come to Washington to rob and make a lot of money. Put the mask on your favorite hero and set off to carry out your next crime, in which you will need to overcome many obstacles before reaching your goal.
Now you will have a wide variety of contracts to choose from, from which you can choose any one.</description></item><item><title>Machine Mind</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/machine-mind/</guid><description>Game Description Machine Mind places the player in the role of consciousness transferred to a mechanical shell after the crash of a spaceship. The existence of a gamer is limited by the world, a changed planetary virus and subsequent nuclear conflict - the cataclysm, which forced the remnants of civilization to hide at the orbital station. Managing a series of rovers, it is necessary to provide its survival on the surface of the planet, now inhabited by aggressive raiders.</description></item><item><title>Salvus: Aries</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/salvus-aries/</guid><description>Game Description Salvus: aries throws you headlong into the afterlife. Here death is not the end, but a new beginning, although gloomy. You wake up a nameless soul in purgatory, and Rubilovo is just a memory. It turns out that your past life was not entirely sunny and rainbow, and now you are serving a sentence as a reap. You must collect souls until your debt to the universe is paid.</description></item><item><title>Electric Trains</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/electric-trains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:39 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/electric-trains/</guid><description>Game Description Electric Trains is an isometric train management simulator where it is necessary to build routes so that transport can reach another station to another. It is required to build railways and organize a schedule so that the locomotives do not collide with each other. The player will switch the ruts and monitor the movement of locomotives.
The gameplay is tied to physics and realism. Depending on the type of train, management is felt differently.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Cits</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ancient-cities/</guid><description>Game Description Ancient Cits - a strategic game based on survival and construction mechanics. The game transfers in ancient times when people lived in tribes and built the first settlements. Plunge in prehistoric times and find the primitive life of our ancestors and their ancient cities. Events develop in the era of mesolithic.
Draw your settlers through a whole generation, improving technologies, mastering new tools, engaged in resources, developing the population and fighting external threats.</description></item><item><title>Animal Shelter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-shelter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/animal-shelter/</guid><description>Game Description Animal Shelter offers the player to open his own animal shelter. Choose homeless animals on the streets, and provide medical care. Take care of your wards and make sure that they get along well with each other. Life on the street leaves prints on the body of animals. Process scratches and stick patcharies. Trinch the wounded paws and observe how the pet is recovering. Buy your patient well using a hose and a sponge.</description></item><item><title>Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/another-farm-roguelike-rebirth/</guid><description>Game Description Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth abandoned long walks and romantic novels with stars that are found in other farm sigas. It’s enough just to click a cursor. The Title with a strategic farm bias with your head immerses you in the creation, construction, collection and management of a prosperous farm. Starting from a modest site, do not allow the initial sizes to deceive you. Another Farm Roguelike: Rebirth is all about potential.</description></item><item><title>Clicker Clicker Clickker</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clicker-clicker-clicker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/clicker-clicker-clicker/</guid><description>Game Description Clicker Clicker Clicker begins the gameplay with a direct impact on the central pointer generating currency - clicker gold. The frequency of initial presses directly affects the speed of the appearance of numerous gold cursors falling on the screen. Interaction with these omiting objects before their disappearance brings more gold than standard clicks according to the main pointer. This mechanic forms a key gameplay cycle based on the accumulation of resources in two different but related methods.</description></item><item><title>Drive Beyond Horizons</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Beond Horizons Refuses the line path and throws gamers into a huge, constantly changing world. Fasten the belts and get ready for the study - the procedurally generated landscapes make each game unique. Leave the comfort zone and choose your own route. Travel through spacious deserts, lush forests, on any roads (or their absence). But this is not just an excursion trip. Drive Beond Horizons is fraught with many secrets and difficulties that have to be solved.</description></item><item><title>Dustland Delivery</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dustland-delivery/</guid><description>Game Description Dustland Delivery puts users in the post -apocalyptic world, where they have to build an empire of delivery. The center of the game is profit, survival and strategic decisions. Gamers start with a truck and gain a team, each of which has unique skills. The purpose of the game? Build cities by successful delivery of goods, competing with rivals and overcoming dangers. The world is inexorable. Users move in an insidious area, control resources and make a critical choice.</description></item><item><title>Ells Tales: Chairbound</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ells-tales-chairbound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ells-tales-chairbound/</guid><description>Game Description Ells Tales: Chairbound begins with the awakening of a character tied to an office chair in an empty room. A strange device with a 10-minute timer is attached to it, steadily counting time. The player’s main task is a desperate search for a way out of a closed corporate building. Movement is achieved by repulsion from surfaces - a method dictated by the physics of finding furniture with wheels, and the main difficulty is to maintain equilibrium.</description></item><item><title>From the Depths</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/from-the-depths/</guid><description>Game Description From the Depths allows you to accept command of battleships, aircraft, submarines, space ships, balloons and many other modes of transport. The story campaign will visit more than a hundred lands and fight against 8 fractions. Misses consist in planning competent tactics and protecting your own fleet in a series of difficult tests. In addition to the main campaign, there is an adventure mode where it will be proposed to start the game alone on a small ship and grow to a whole fleet, furrows the expanses of the universe.</description></item><item><title>Let's Build a Zoo</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/lets-build-a-zoo/</guid><description>Game Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Zoo - A bright sandbox with a simulator elements, which provides players with the opportunity to build their own zoo. It is required to install enclosures, buy rare animals, hire employees for service and much more. It is allowed to cross animal DNA, producing more than 300,000 unique rocks into the world.
In order for the reserve to function, it will be necessary to hire veterinarians, trainers, cleaners, repairmen and other performers who support their lives in the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Operator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/operator/</guid><description>Game Description Operator is an exciting game where you become a secret operative performing dangerous tasks around the world. A realistic experience of tactical battle awaits you, where your every decision matters. The game contains a unique system of physical interaction, which allows you to manipulate objects and weapons naturally. This adds a feeling of presence and realism, without the need to use VR-Schles.
A special emphasis in the operator is placed on a multi -user cooperative regime.</description></item><item><title>Schedule I</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/schedule-i/</guid><description>Game Description Schedule 1 puts a gamer in the place of a small drug dealer trying to build a criminal empire from scratch. The action takes place in the gloomy city of Highland Point, and users get the opportunity to expand the scale of their activities, controlling everyone - from production to sales. You will begin with an empty wallet and the necessary connections, gradually rising to control over the criminal world.</description></item><item><title>The Darkest Files</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-darkest-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-darkest-files/</guid><description>Game Description The Darkest Files unfolds in post -war Germany in 1956, in the period marked by the consequences of World War II and a complex process of searching justice. The user rises in place Esther Katz, a young prosecutor who joins the special unit of Fritz Bauer, who is instructed to investigate war crimes committed many years ago.
In this role, the gamer will have to find hidden evidence, to navigate in a society that does not want to recognize his past, and to confront criminals, who are now occupied by leading posts.</description></item><item><title>Under a New Sun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/under-a-new-sun/</guid><description>Game Description Under a New Sun begins after a catastrophic failure of the ship, who left the player on an unknown planet. Awakening from cryosn occurs among fragments, completely solitude under a stranger sky. The mission to search for a new house for humanity failed, and the fate of the crew remains a mystery. The path begins in the middle of the wreckage of the vessel, in a world where the earthly flora has taken roots next to local views.</description></item><item><title>Underground Garage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/underground-garage/</guid><description>Game Description Underground Garage is a car symbulator with elements of a mechanic that allows not only to take part in the races, but also to completely create his own car from scratch. It is allowed to both buy ready -made models, exploring the secondary market, and create cars from scratch. Restoring transport or pumping cars, it is necessary to take part in illegal races, showing your superiority as a mechanic and demonstrating the skills of a first -class driver.</description></item></channel></rss>