<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>visual novels on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novels/</link><description>Recent content in visual novels on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Date EVERYTHING!</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/date-everything/</guid><description>Game Description Date EVERYTHING! It begins after the main character loses his job due to artificial intelligence. Following this incident, a stranger delivers a parcel with glasses called DateViators. This accessory revives inanimate things in the dwelling of the protagonist, endowing them with his own character. The project contains a list of 100 potential partners, from bed to fire alarm, each of which is completely voiced. Through dialogues, the player studies the background and motives of these household objects that have now become his companions.</description></item><item><title>Starvaders</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/starvaders/</guid><description>Game Description Starvaders a combination of a mechanic of collecting a deck and step -by -step battles on the field in the setting of an alien invasion. The gamer takes control of the combat vehicle to fight the aliens with the help of compiled cards. The process moves through roguelike style visits, which requires adaptation. The task is to defend the Earth through the thoughtful use of maps and the placement of detachments on the field.</description></item><item><title>Promise Mascot Agency</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/promise-mascot-agency/</guid><description>Game Description Promise Mascot Agency offers the gamer to plunge into the life of Kaso-Machi, a damned Japanese town. The main character, Michi, is in exile and must establish the work of the agency of urban masks. Key tasks include hiring these creatures, resolving the problems that arise due to their actions, and clarifying the causes of the protagonist link. Communication with a kick, a living finger with a complex character, is also part of the gameplay while you are trying to make your agency the best in the region through the study of the world and plot events.</description></item><item><title>Tavern Talk</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tavern-talk/</guid><description>Game Description Tavern Talk throws you into the very heart of the fantasy kingdom, but not as a powerful warrior or clever robber. Here you will take into your hands the reins of the reign of a cozy tavern Wayfarer&amp;rsquo;s Inn. But this is not an ordinary bartender simulator. The “Traveler” tavern is filled with a whisper and secrets of adventure seekers - your regulars. This is not just thirsty souls who want to drink a mug of ale.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/monster-prom-3-monster-roadtrip/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom 3: Monster Roadtrip - a continuation of the popular series of satirical adventure, the actions of which unfold in a fabulous universe. Instead of people, it is inhabited by various very cute monsters of all possible species and appearance. Unlike previous parts, here the developers do not focus on the simulation of dates, but on road travel and survival. Juzer needs to get to a certain epic place in order to end the campaign successfully.</description></item><item><title>WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs]</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wtc-relentless-protagonist-sxs/</guid><description>Game Description WTC: Relentless Protagonist [sxs] - this is a visual short story with two -dimensional graphics. She imitates anime drawing. The atmosphere combines drama, comedy and thriller. There are scenes with violence in the game. Title includes 102 scenes, and his script consists of 73,000 words. The plot has 3 endings and 2 epilogue. The video game is designed for about 6-8 hours of passage. The gameplay traditionally for the genre consists of considering pictures, reading the text and periodic decision -making.</description></item><item><title>Refind Self: The Personality Test Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/refind-self-the-personality-test-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/refind-self-the-personality-test-game/</guid><description>Game Description Refind Self: The Personality Test Game is a unique interactive science fiction in which the gameplay allows you to explore the depths of the user personality. In this 2D-visual short story, you fall in the place of the Android and find yourself on the grave of the doctor that created you. From this moment on, your journey unfolds as you are exploring different locations associated with the previous doctor, meeting along the way with various robots.</description></item></channel></rss>