<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Visual Novella on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novella/</link><description>Recent content in Visual Novella on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/visual-novella/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Demons Told Me to Make This Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-demons-told-me-to-make-this-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-demons-told-me-to-make-this-game/</guid><description>Game Description The Demons Told Me to Make This Game begins in the city of Red Havyvs at 5:00 a.m. on October 26, 2016. This moment marks the beginning of the last day of the world: the bloody ritual ends and a spirit named a dark light appears in the void. Being this incorporeal essence, the player cannot directly interact with the physical world. The main way of influence is the instilling in the inhabitants of the city and whipping them in the ear of instructions for sending their actions.</description></item><item><title>Return to ash</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/return-to-ash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/return-to-ash/</guid><description>Game Description Return To Ash begins with the awakening of the main character, Ashley, in a quiet and bright hospital ward. She discovers the disappearance of her physical ailments, and an absolute white void extends outside the window. This visual novel represents a narrative focused on the study of posthumry, with an emphasis on interpersonal ties and consequences of actions. The player’s elections directly affect the development of the plot, determining the path of Ashley in this unfamiliar dimension.</description></item><item><title>Near-Mage</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/near-mage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/near-mage/</guid><description>Game Description The magic universe in Near-Mage shows the adventures of the young girl Illy Vraj, who was invited to live in Transylvania for the summer. The girl will meet with her cousin Dominica, who wants to tell her about the secret witch&amp;rsquo;s kind. The heroine will receive the opportunity to enter the Transylvanian Institute of Magic, where he will master the art of witchcraft. The girl will go to the preparatory summer school to become a full -fledged caster.</description></item><item><title>Banebush</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banebush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/banebush/</guid><description>Game Description Banebush is a title whose action takes place in the mysterious Hukendary Mud, a place where few looked and where even fewer who returned. Users stand in place of the nameless protagonist, who finds himself in a distant and deserted area. The world is filled with puzzles, secrets and many trials that make users be on the alert. This is a game that requires research and strategy, because each choice has its own weight and affects the further path.</description></item><item><title>Grizzly Man</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grizzly-man/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grizzly-man/</guid><description>Game Description Grizzly Man represents a narrative, the action of which takes place in Alaska in 1983. The main character is Robert, suffering from amnesia after a forest incident of a 12-year ago and a guide. He leads a group of tourists up the river during salmon spawning, not knowing about his past of a government agent. Suddenly, the expedition is faced with a deadly pursuer, known as the Grisli man.</description></item><item><title>A night at the Watermill</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-night-at-the-watermill/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/a-night-at-the-watermill/</guid><description>Game Description A Night at the Watermill represents to gamers a narrative experience unfolding in an old water mill. Waking up, the players find themselves in an unfamiliar environment, fighting amnesia about their arrival. The task is to navigate in space, solve puzzles and collect a plot line that connects the protagonist with a water mill. Each interaction reveals more information about the circumstances of the character’s life and the secrets surrounding him.</description></item><item><title>Noctuary</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/noctuary/</guid><description>Game Description Noctuary - an alloy of visual novel and adventure action, which immerses abortor in the bright world, following the intertwined travels of Fanny and Alina. Being novice arbarars, the duet passes through the rich tapestry of characters, quests and enemies in this colorful kingdom. Distinguished by the inventive mechanics of the battle, the game allows you to smoothly switch the characters between fanchia and Alina, each of which is endowed with various skills and styles of battle.</description></item><item><title>Pygmalion</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pygmalion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/pygmalion/</guid><description>Game Description Pygmalion represents the levels-pungent levels built for manipulations with colored blocks. The main task is to clear the field, pushing these figures and thereby starting the synthesis or separation of colors based on their properties. Each stage has a strict limit on the number of available moves, which requires a gamer of foresight and strategic planning. Success is counted after the complete removal of all elements for the allotted amount of actions in the system that combines simple rules with complex, multi -stage solutions.</description></item><item><title>Concealed</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/concealed/</guid><description>Game Description Concealed begins with the fact that Maine Jiannan returns to the secondary school of Diinlin after the student exchange program. Her return to school life is interrupted when classmates begin to disappear without explanation. These events are correlated with old, unsolved matters and city legends circulating in the territory of the educational institution for years. Maine Jiannan has to face incidents and find a way to reveal the secrets hidden behind the facade of the school.</description></item><item><title>AI Roguelite</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-roguelite/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ai-roguelite/</guid><description>Game Description AI Roguelite is a text role -playing game where artificial intelligence generates all content and controls all game mechanics. The system determines each location, a non -game character, an enemy and an object that a player faces. In addition, recipes for creating things and fundamental rules of interaction also come from the neural network. As a result, the gamer has to explore the Universe, 100 percent consisting of elements created by a large language model, which provides a procedural adventure as a procedurally generated.</description></item><item><title>Ribby: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:45 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ribby-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Ribby: The Game - this is not a typical role -playing adventure. Forget about the extermination of dragons or collecting a million gold coins. Here is the hero - Ribbie, a kind girl, who has lost and seeking the house. Title combines elements of role -playing games and visual novels, creating a unique experience. Of course, the main goal is to return Ribbie home, but this is only the top of Lilia.</description></item><item><title>Sunrider Legends Tactics</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/sunrider-legends-tactics/</guid><description>Game Description Sunrider Legends Tactics will put a player at the head of the Navy leading his ships along the seas of the fantasy world in the era of sails. You have to command the courts in step -by -step battles, making tactical decisions on maneuvers, positioning and the use of weapons against enemy armades. The adventure will require solving strategic problems in the open sea and participation in special plot events.</description></item></channel></rss>