<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Shooter on Game Rift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooter/</link><description>Recent content in Shooter on Game Rift</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamerift.github.io/tags/shooter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Thing: Remastered</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-thing-remastered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-thing-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description The Thing: Remastered returns to Antarctica, continuing the story of the 1982 film. Nightdive Studios resurrects the 2002 horror third-person shooter with a sequel to Outpost 31. Players play as Captain J.F. Blake, commander of a US Special Forces rescue team sent to investigate the aftermath of a scientific expedition.
Gameplay centers on facing off against shape-shifting alien creatures in a challenging environment. Team management becomes one of the core mechanics in which players must navigate complex interpersonal dynamics and potential contagion among team members.</description></item><item><title>Battle Shapers</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-shapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battle-shapers/</guid><description>Game Description Battle Shapers is a thrilling sci-fi roguelite first-person shooter that puts you in the shoes of Ada, a determined warrior who must reclaim the future of New Elysium from the treacherous Overlords and their corrupt robot armies.
From the start of Battle Shapers, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself armed with a formidable array of futuristic weapons, special abilities, and even abilities stolen from the unforgiving Overlords themselves. Your task is to go through their treacherous towers, which are fraught with traps and dangers at every step.</description></item><item><title>RAM: Random Access Mayhem</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ram-random-access-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ram-random-access-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description RAM: Random Access Mayhem is a roguelike shooter that takes a familiar concept and turns it into something chaotic and strategic. In a world filled with bizarre robots, gamers take on the role of a disembodied AI programmed to wreak havoc. Unlike typical shooters, the adventure game features new mechanics: you control and switch between eight different types of enemies, each with their own unique abilities. This twist not only keeps the action fresh, but also requires quick thinking and strategy as you progress through increasingly difficult levels.</description></item><item><title>420BLAZEIT 2: GAME OF THE YEAR - Dank Dreams and Goated Memes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/420blazeit-2-game-of-the-year-dank-dreams-and-goated-memes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/420blazeit-2-game-of-the-year-dank-dreams-and-goated-memes/</guid><description>Game Description 420BLAZEIT 2: GAME OF THE YEAR - Dank Dreams and Goated Memes is a first-person shooter that stands out for its wild premise and unpredictable gameplay. The story follows a former Secret Service agent who leaves behind a life of danger and intrigue to pursue a quieter existence as an artist. However, peace does not last long. The agent is soon forced back into action to save memes from the clutches of the Illuminati, a shadowy organization that seems intent on controlling the internet&amp;rsquo;s most valuable content.</description></item><item><title>Space Trash Scavenger</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/space-trash-scavenger/</guid><description>Game Description Space Trash Scavenger takes place in a future where humanity has reached for the stars and survival means using what others have left behind. Here, gamers take on the role of scavengers operating in a galaxy littered with the rubble of an ancient conflict. The journey begins with a space drill - a multi-purpose node floating among the remains of abandoned ships, forgotten outposts and asteroid fields. This is not just a shelter, but a factory, equipped with critical systems for agriculture, defense and waste processing - all necessary to turn interstellar waste into something valuable.</description></item><item><title>Rusty's Day Off: Episode One - Janitor on Duty</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-day-off-episode-one-janitor-on-duty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/rustys-day-off-episode-one-janitor-on-duty/</guid><description>Game Description Rusty&amp;rsquo;s Day Off: Episode One - Janitor on Duty offers an original take on the first-person shooter (FPS) genre. The gamer will have to step into the shoes of Rusty, a janitor who is tasked with sorting out a situation at a workplace where a malfunction has occurred due to rogue robots. It&amp;rsquo;s not just running and gunning, there&amp;rsquo;s more to it than that. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to solve puzzles, interact with strange gadgets, and figure out how to stay alive while coping with mechanical chaos.</description></item><item><title>Red Dead Redemption</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption/</guid><description>Game Description The beginning of the 20th century was not easy in the Wild West in Red Dead Redemption. John Marston was previously a member of a gang of thugs, but decided to end his bloody occupation. The guy did not manage to start a quiet life - the hero was taken under the “guardianship” of government services, whose agents forced him to work for them. The character&amp;rsquo;s family was under their guns, and if they refused, John&amp;rsquo;s relatives would be killed.</description></item><item><title>Speedollama</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/speedollama/</guid><description>Game Description Speedollama is a fast-paced platform shooter that takes gamers into a world where llamas battle an army of alpacas. The unusual premise draws users into a chaotic world where humor and action collide in the most unexpected ways. The goal is simple: control a llama equipped with a mining machine and destroy waves of alpaca enemies. The title features a vibrant environment filled with quirky characters and varied challenges, making every moment exciting.</description></item><item><title>Shady Knight</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shady-knight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/shady-knight/</guid><description>Game Description Shady Knight is a first-person hand-to-hand combat game. The environment is interactive and contains a huge amount of dynamic combat. The gameplay combines elements of platforming. You will need to go through many towers and brutally tear apart your enemies. You use a sword with which you kill your enemies. You can also kick opponents onto spikes, shoot enemies with fire, and throw swords at their bodies to pin them to walls.</description></item><item><title>Aim Camp</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/aim-camp/</guid><description>Game Description Aim Camp is an adventure game that combines military simulator and interactive gameplay. It immerses gamers in a variety of training exercises aimed at honing their aiming and accuracy skills. Each exercise presents users with unique challenges, including scenarios such as close combat, sniping and drone operations. Gamers immerse themselves in these drills, where the goal is not only competition, but also a deeper understanding of accuracy.
The design of each scenario encourages a focused approach, requiring players to constantly adapt and improve their techniques.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Hanwell</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-hanwell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/beyond-hanwell/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond Hanwell takes players to a post-apocalyptic London. Westminster, once a bustling hub, now serves as the backdrop to a complex journey of survival. Anomalies, a growing threat, inhabit the ruins of Hanwell. Gamers fight them using collected weapons or gadgets from the environment. The title offers more than just survival. She is a mystery. The director, a shadow figure, holds the clues. Side missions and hidden areas enrich the narrative.</description></item><item><title>Iron Meat</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</guid><description>Game Description Iron Meat is a dynamic platformer made in the style of arcade shooters of the last century. The game takes place on Mars, when a group of scientists disappeared from radar without a trace. The case is entrusted to a member of an elite squad who goes in search of missing people. He must find out what really happened and who is behind this mysterious event.
The gameplay takes inspiration from classic action games such as Contra.</description></item><item><title>The Forever Winter</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forever-winter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-forever-winter/</guid><description>Game Description The Forever Winter is a tactical survival horror shooter set in a post-apocalyptic world. Gamers navigate a landscape dominated by massive war machines locked in a relentless conflict. Here, special attention is paid to strategic decision-making and cooperation: gamers extract resources and fight for survival. The dynamic collision system ensures that enemies have their own goals and react intelligently to user actions, creating an unpredictable battlefield.
In The Forever Winter, users form squads to plunder the dead and confront terrifying war machines.</description></item><item><title>Anomalous</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomalous/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/anomalous/</guid><description>Game Description Anomalous takes users to the fictional and totalitarian city-state of Kosolov. Local authorities were able to brainwash the population and forced residents to work until exhaustion in order to get rich at the expense of others. One day, the leaders of an industrial and closed country began to experiment on people. They decided to increase the military potential of the power and began to conduct experiments on dead workers in order to revive them and force them to perform their duties again.</description></item><item><title>Chains of Fury</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chains-of-fury/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/chains-of-fury/</guid><description>Game Description Crazy shooter Chains of Fury with completely destructible levels. Lost or lost in the corridors? Just destroy all the walls with a shotgun! Up to 80% of the entire location will be broken, which will give complete freedom of movement. But you can’t fight with concrete alone. Aliens robots, creepy monsters and huge bosses - all this will need to be turned into bloody stains on the concrete.</description></item><item><title>Hands of Necromancy 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hands-of-necromancy-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hands-of-necromancy-ii/</guid><description>Game Description Hands of Necromancy 2 is a dark fantasy first-person shooter that picks up where its predecessor left off. You can play as one of two characters, each with their own special abilities and spells. The game has reworked the necromancy system, so you can use new weapons and learn powerful spells. Transformations are important, allowing you to transform into various creatures to overcome obstacles and defeat enemies.
The game has many different environments: ancient castles, dry deserts, beautiful villages and creepy caves.</description></item><item><title>Hollowbody</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollowbody/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hollowbody/</guid><description>Game Description Hollowbody throws you headlong into the dark world of techno-noir. Imagine a short story, but you control the main character as he navigates a crumbling metropolis, a ghost town of a once bustling city. Forget the fancy graphics and pumping music, this is just an environmental story. Deserted streets and abandoned buildings speak volumes, whispering about a forgotten past. You wake up in this nightmare, ill-equipped and alone. Survival depends on your intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Stardiver</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stardiver/</guid><description>Game Description The underwater world of Stardiver amazes with its diversity. Under the water column lies an entire civilization that has adapted to this way of existence so that other forms of life do not bother them and do not start wars. Nevertheless, for humanity, a planet completely covered with water turned out to be more than a curious subject of research.
The main character is the head of a scientific group for the study of extraterrestrial forms of civilization.</description></item><item><title>Wild Bastards</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/wild-bastards/</guid><description>Game Description In Wild Bastards you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself in the captain&amp;rsquo;s chair of a ragtag spaceship filled with the galaxy&amp;rsquo;s most notorious criminals. Think space pirates with a penchant for trouble. This isn&amp;rsquo;t your grandpa&amp;rsquo;s space opera, but a roguelike shooter where every decision can mean the difference between exploding into stardom or becoming cosmic dust. The missions are spread across a series of tactical campaigns, each of which is an adventure.</description></item><item><title>I Am Your Beast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</guid><description>Game Description I Am Your Beast is not your average shooter. This narrative-driven game throws you headlong into a brutal conflict with the shadowy organization you once worked for. You play as Alphonse Harding, a former operative who has been lured back into the world of underground warfare. Survival and thinking quickly are key. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to navigate treacherous terrain, dodging and fighting enemies in a high-stakes chase.
Forget about going with guns at the ready.</description></item><item><title>Arcane Blast</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arcane-blast/</guid><description>Game Description In Arcane Blast you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself wearing the fur boots of Adrian, a cat mage on a mission. This roguelike adventure throws you into a chaotic world filled with spells, enemies, and the constant threat of a cat&amp;rsquo;s life. Do you think you can handle it? This isn&amp;rsquo;t your average walk in the park, unless that park is filled with evil goblins and fire-breathing lizards. It&amp;rsquo;s all about reflexes here.</description></item><item><title>Zero Hour</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/zero-hour/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Hour is a multiplayer tactical first-person shooter with realistic game mechanics that replicate the behavior of real special forces units in anti-terrorist operations. The setting for the action is criminal Bangladesh, where banditry is at a high level and is not going to give up ground to law enforcement officers. The locations where clashes between groups of terrorists and special forces occur are made using real scale, which greatly helps the atmosphere and involves gamers in the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Smells Like a Mushroom</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</guid><description>Game Description Smells Like a Mushroom is a sci-fi third-person shooter that takes gamers on a journey through the Milky Way. At the center is an invasion of creatures known as Magic Mushrooms. Users take on the role of Carrotado, a brave character tasked with preventing disaster. The gameplay includes platformer and shooter mechanics, and missions take place on various planets in the solar system.
Smells Like a Mushroom&amp;rsquo;s narrative is driven by an absurd story and features both single-player and co-op modes.</description></item><item><title>Hit of Chernobyl</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hit-of-chernobyl/</guid><description>Game Description Hit of Chernobyl immerses users in a post-apocalyptic environment where survival is of paramount importance. Finding themselves in an area contaminated by an unspecified disaster, gamers take on the role of an adventurer. He must navigate a landscape full of dangers, not only from the environment, but also from other characters. The world is populated by marauders, journalists and thrill seekers, each with their own motives. Finding unique artifacts becomes the main task, requiring users to overcome a landscape replete with difficulties.</description></item><item><title>The Moon 2044</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/the-moon-2044/</guid><description>Game Description The Moon 2044 takes place in a secret research facility on the Moon, where gamers take on the role of a genetically modified commando codenamed XV-11. The mission is to retrieve priceless samples from the depths of a lunar base that has fallen into darkness and is now overrun by hostile creatures. The facility, originally intended for experimental cancer research, hides many dark secrets that users will have to uncover.</description></item><item><title>Kamikaze Lasplanes</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</guid><description>Game Description Kamikaze Lassplanes is a visual novel that combines the plot of a novel with the action of a shoot-&amp;rsquo;em-up game. Set in a steampunk world, the dramatic storyline involves two powerful weapons, Lassplanes, and two girls who become them. Gamers navigate a war-torn kingdom and make choices that affect not only the fate of the kingdom, but also their own hearts.
The project introduces Alba Trosset and Hannah Brandenburg, two girls who transform into deadly warplanes.</description></item><item><title>Akimbot</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/akimbot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/akimbot/</guid><description>Game Description Akimbot throws you into a metal menagerie! Teaming up rogue robot Exe with unexpected partner Shipset, this game throws down the galactic gauntlet. Imagine: you are fighting your way through hordes of robotic enemies, spaceships at the ready, and all this in order to stop a universal catastrophe. Fasten your seat belts, because this is not an easy ride. Akimbot isn&amp;rsquo;t all button-mashing chaos. It&amp;rsquo;s a strategic dance with enemies to dodge and outwit in every level.</description></item><item><title>Squirrel with a Gun</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/squirrel-with-a-gun/</guid><description>Game Description Squirrel with a Gun offers a unique experience. Users control a squirrel armed with a gun. Target? Collect golden acorns in a secret underground vault. The squirrel that haunts the neighbors becomes a hero. Gamers move through a sandbox filled with puzzles and enemies. The facility serves as a playground for chaos. To survive, the squirrel uses weapons, claws and teeth. The gameplay combines shooting and platforming. Users collect golden acorns - a squirrel&amp;rsquo;s obsession.</description></item><item><title>PROTOCOL 11 - Episode 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/protocol-11-episode-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/protocol-11-episode-1/</guid><description>Game Description PROTOCOL 11 - Episode 1 is a journey through many worlds as Phil goes on a quest for justice. This is an exciting adventure in which gamers must return what was stolen by a strange race of invaders. The story touches on themes of friendship, love and the essence of humanity. Users mine resources, fight enemies and choose between direct combat and stealth. Gameplay involves jumping on platforms, shooting, and solving puzzles.</description></item><item><title>Nova Drift</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</guid><description>Game Description Nova Drift is a top-down action RPG adventure. The gamer has the opportunity to test his strength in piloting a space fighter, forced to fight enemies that are superior in numbers and firepower. The spaceship uses unusual technologies; it is created using biomechanics, which means that it seems to be alive and is constantly changing both in appearance and in terms of available weapons. Thanks to the addition of artificial intelligence trained in procedural random generation, the developers from a small indie formation were able to achieve almost endless replayability.</description></item><item><title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/outpost-infinity-siege/</guid><description>Game Description Outpost: Infinity Siege is a fun sci-fi first-person shooter with elements of base building and tower defense. You command the Mobile Outpost and go with the Protoslug Cannon to deeply explore the forbidden zone of Cygnet, where many dangers await you. Collect unique weapon units and strengthen the firepower of the outpost that is fighting with you. This game combines elements of TD, FPS and RTS at the same time, making the gameplay incredibly exciting.</description></item><item><title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midnight-ghost-hunt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/midnight-ghost-hunt/</guid><description>Game Description Midnight Ghost Hunt is a creepy version of hide and seek in which players will have to catch ghosts or, on the contrary, drive away people who disturbed the peace of the spirits. 4v4 confrontation takes place between friends or random users. The main task of the hunters is to catch all the evil spirits with the help of their equipment, and the ghosts are to kill all living things by any means.</description></item><item><title>STAR WARS: Battlefront Classic Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-battlefront-classic-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/star-wars-battlefront-classic-collection/</guid><description>Game Description STAR WARS: Battlefront Classic Collection brings back the beloved online shooters, remastered for modern consoles and PC. Players can now relive classic battles from the Star Wars galaxy, both online and offline, in this new collection. The collection includes the original game, as well as a bonus map: Jabba&amp;rsquo;s Palace. The second game, Battlefront 2, includes four bonus cards and two bonus heroes: Asajj Ventress and Kit Fisto.</description></item><item><title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suicide-squad-kill-the-justice-league/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/suicide-squad-kill-the-justice-league/</guid><description>Game Description Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is perfect for all fans of the DC universe who want to look at familiar heroes from a new angle. Now the roles have been changed, superheroes have become a danger to the local population, and a villainous squad led by the crazy Harley Quinn will have to save her. Loud explosions, massive destruction and mild madness reign in the city of Metropolis.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>Ready or Not</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ready-or-not/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ready-or-not/</guid><description>Game Description Ready or Not is a tactical shooter that positions itself as a special forces simulator. The project is designed for fans of SWAT 4. The creators tried to focus on realism and cruelty. The game has single player, co-op and PvP. The main gameplay consists of conducting a special operation within the campaign or individual missions. Before you begin, you need to listen to the briefing, study the map of the building, decide on points for the assault and select equipment.</description></item><item><title>Crab Champions</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Crab Champions is one of those projects where the gamer is given control of an extraordinary hero. As you can guess from the name, the characters of the game are crabs. The setting is tropical islands - the player will be surrounded by palm trees, sand, ocean, stones and exotic animals. And also other crabs, armed to the teeth. Crab Champions can be played in three different modes: Co-op.</description></item><item><title>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-darktide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/warhammer-40000-darktide/</guid><description>Game Description Warhammer 40,000: Darktide is a co-op first-person shooter. Events take place in the huge city of Tertium on the planet Atom Prime. The cult of insane heretics Admonition is trying to capture him. Four heroes, together with the forces of the Inquisition, must resist Chaos and stop the bloodthirsty horde of the living dead and save the inhabitants from extermination.
Since this is a classic co-op shooter, the gameplay is primarily focused on shooting and killing demonic enemies using melee weapons.</description></item><item><title>SIGNALIS</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/signalis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/signalis/</guid><description>Game Description The space horror film SIGNALIS is made in the style of anime. The indie project is a representative of the old-school survival horror genre. We play as a girl named Elster. She wakes up in a pressure chamber on a ship where something terrible happened. The main character is a Replica - a kind of android analogue. She periodically sees visions of others and picks up strange radio signals.</description></item><item><title>CULTIC</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cultic/</guid><description>Game Description Death in CULTIC is the beginning of a mysterious path, so you shouldn’t be afraid of it. The player will have to muster up the courage to fight through hordes of perverted cultists in order to gain the upper hand in this battle. As the character progresses, he encounters hundreds of NPCs with completely frozen minds, who are guided by blind faith in their ideals. The cultists are further corrupted by an immortal and invisible entity that seeks sole domination of the world.</description></item><item><title>Priest Simulator</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/priest-simulator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/priest-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Priest Simulator is a first-person action game where you take on the role of a priest. The peculiarity of the game is that you yourself choose what kind of priest to be: to forgive sins or to take the side of adultery? Forgive people? Or should I just get rid of them? The priest simulator gives you complete freedom of action.
Many people are familiar with the phrase: “with great power comes great responsibility,” but not all games provide the opportunity to experience this to the fullest.</description></item><item><title>Mirror 2: Project X</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror 2: Project X follows the adventures of Dinkudin Naoto, who collaborates with the FBI (Federal Bureau of Research and Conservation). The hero searches for mystical manifestations and otherworldly creatures that sometimes appear in the world. The plot begins with a story with a Demon that infects the body of one of the victims. During the proceedings and investigation of the case, the protagonist will find out the motivations and goals of the creatures in order to make a choice to support or destroy the monster.</description></item><item><title>Battlefield 2042</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-2042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-2042/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 2042 is a tactical action game, the main conflict of which is the confrontation between Russia and the United States in the world of the near future. Humanity has exhausted almost all of the Earth&amp;rsquo;s resources. Now the mighty superpowers have entered the race for the planet&amp;rsquo;s last fossils. Germany lost ground and the EU collapsed. The world is in the midst of a Second Great Depression. The gameplay is a first-person shooter.</description></item><item><title>MADNESS: Project Nexus</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/madness-project-nexus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/madness-project-nexus/</guid><description>Game Description MADNESS: Project Nexus is a three-dimensional dynamic shooter with a side view, as well as a huge number of opponents and violence that happens on the monitor screen. The arcade controls are easy to remember, allowing you to quickly start enjoying the gameplay. This project from indie developers is a driving mixture of beat&amp;rsquo;em&amp;rsquo;up and slasher using not only melee weapons, but also firearms with different damage.
The main feature of the gameplay is the ability to play cooperatively on one personal computer.</description></item><item><title>ULTRAKILL</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultrakill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/ultrakill/</guid><description>Game Description ULTRAKILL is a game inspired by classic and modern shooters. You will find yourself in a future where people have become extinct. Now the main thing on the planet has become machines whose fuel is blood. There was little valuable liquid left on the surface of the Earth, and so robots began to explore the underground world in search of living creatures. Game Features: Fight multiple enemies. Destroy the risen dead, demonic creatures and other profit seekers.</description></item><item><title>Risk of Rain 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/risk-of-rain-2/</guid><description>Game Description Risk of Rain 2 is a continuation of the classic online game, which has become better and more complex than the original. The player will challenge the cruel world alone or team up with friends to defeat hordes of monsters, collect the necessary relics and escape from the terrifying planet. With each new attempt, you will be able to better understand the behavior of your opponents and defeat them outright with your skills, even when they are outnumbered.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic is a co-op shooter with fast-paced gameplay in which you will fight with other users against alien monsters. The game is made in a sci-fi style and has procedurally generated levels in which you will fight. The mission can be completed by 1 to 4 players. Act as one. Dig, explore the area and shoot with enemies waiting for you in huge numbers around every corner.</description></item><item><title>GTA 4</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gta-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/gta-4/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 4 became a revolutionary, breakthrough game in the series of criminal action games with a conditionally open world and almost complete freedom of action. It is not only technically and plot-wise different from its predecessors, but also sets a new standard of quality for all representatives of this and other genres. It is worth noting that the concept of GTA has gone far beyond the scope of this franchise, and some mechanics from this series of games are used in projects from other studios.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life: Alyx</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-alyx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-alyx/</guid><description>Game Description Half-Life: Alyx became the first AAA quality game in history for virtual reality devices, the passage of which can be enjoyed on a PC only with the help of an appropriate device, namely a VR headset from Steam and related gadgets. The plot is a spin-off, the events of which unfold in the interval between the actions of the first and second parts. The Black Mesa Incident allowed Alliance forces to gain a foothold on the planet, leaving the remaining humans trapped in the cities.</description></item><item><title>DOOM Eternal</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-eternal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-eternal/</guid><description>Game Description DOOM Eternal, a first-person shooter, continues the campaign of DOOM (developed in 2016). Our hero is the Doom Slayer. He will kill mutants and monsters on the territory of Mars, the attached spaceship, its satellites and Earth. In many ways, the plot scenes are taken from the second part of the series. The main addition to the game was moving through the levels. If earlier we could move to the next level only after finishing it, then in the new part it will be possible to “climb” to another location where the events of the next level take place.</description></item><item><title>Black Mesa</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-mesa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/black-mesa/</guid><description>Game Description Black Mesa is a remake of the cult shooter Half-Life, which at one time turned out to be a breakthrough in the world of video games and made the name of Valve. They worked on this project for eight whole years, during which the creators tried to transfer the old game to the new Source engine with varying success. As a result, they managed to achieve the desired effect and in May 2015 the game was released.</description></item><item><title>Red Dead Redemption 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/red-dead-redemption-2/</guid><description>Game Description Red Dead Redemption 2 is a third-person shooter adventure game set in the Wild West in 1899. The action involves the Dutch Van Der Linde gang, which is being pursued by lawmen after a botched ferry robbery. The player will take control of Arthur Morgan, one of the gang members.
Some time after the unsuccessful prank, the gang decides that it is time to retire and live the rest of their lives like ordinary people, not bandits.</description></item><item><title>Halo: The Master Chief Collection</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halo-the-master-chief-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/halo-the-master-chief-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Halo: The Master Chief Collection is a complete collection of the cult shooter series about the Master Chief. The collection includes all numbered games in the series that were released before Halo: Infinite. At the same time, the developers have improved the visual component of the game, providing 4k resolution and HDR support for modern monitors.
The story tells of the confrontation between the United Nations Space Command and the religious alien alliance Covenant.</description></item><item><title>Insurgency: Sandstorm</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm/</guid><description>Game Description Insurgency: Sandstorm is a sequel to a multiplayer shooter built on deathmatches in confined spaces, with the ability to use light vehicles. The game has been significantly improved and expanded. The key to victory lies only through well-coordinated teamwork.
The action takes place in the Middle East, on the ruins of settlements and military bases. You need to carefully choose your weapon and explore the territory, because without caution and tactics you can quickly catch a bullet in the forehead.</description></item><item><title>DUSK</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dusk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/dusk/</guid><description>Game Description DUSK is a canonical first-person shooter created in a retro style. The plot is quite simple and clear - there is a small town called DUSK, in its vicinity ruins were discovered that have mystical properties. Many scientists and soldiers came here, studying strange objects and everyone gradually went crazy. They became possessed, and the government surrounded the entire area with a wall. A brave hero was found who entered the forbidden territory in search of these unique artifacts, but was captured by occultists and hung on hooks.</description></item><item><title>BATTLEFIELD 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-5/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 5 is a first-person shooter, the fifteenth game in the Battlefield series. Unlike previous games in the series, Battlefield 5 sacrifices historical accuracy for the sake of the player: weapon handling, for example, has been noticeably improved, making the game more like an arcade shooter. Most of the changes made to BFV are solid improvements over its predecessor.
War Stories is a series of single-player missions introduced in Battlefield V, where the player is invited to become an eyewitness to tragic events.</description></item><item><title>Mirror</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/mirror/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror is a visual novel that perfectly combines erotic content, an RPG component, an interactive plot and battles in which you take a direct part. The whole game is built on the “three in a row” principle. In the casual combination of characters, you will only take part in the battle on the Match 3 battlefield. That is, you will win if you can score more points. The game features three heroines who will oppose you throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-5/</guid><description>Game Description Finally, the plot of Far Cry 5 has reached America. Crazed fanatics unleashed their might on the state of Montana. A first-person shooter with action elements brings us to a reality in which even the movements of dogs will be more than real. The modernization of the shooter took several years, so the development studio warns us in advance that the game is based on religious motives. Age limit: 18+.</description></item><item><title>Stick Fight: The Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/stick-fight-the-game/</guid><description>Game Description Stick Fight: The Game is a multiplayer platformer with fighting game elements. Players control colorful people, overcoming obstacles and fighting each other. The main gameplay consists of moving, jumping and reacting quickly. On the path of the heroes there will be deadly obstacles that will take the lives of all those who hesitated even a little and did not react to the situation. Game features: from 2 to 4 players over a local or online network; physics-based combat system; about 100 well-developed and detailed locations; includes a level editor; various ranged and melee weapons; procedurally generated and contextual animations based on the system Totally Accurate Battle Simulator.</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Wildlands</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-wildlands/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the new part - Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands - truly inspires what the developers tried to convict all players of. It must be said, but there is no plot in a third-person shooter. You independently write the story of your team, which is initially aimed at destroying the cartel that trades and produces drugs. But more on that later.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s worth discussing the inner world of Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Recon Wildlands.</description></item><item><title>theHunter: Call of the Wild</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/thehunter-call-of-the-wild/</guid><description>Game Description The Hunter&amp;rsquo;s Open World is now available in theHunter: Call of the Wild. This is not a simple hunter simulator, where we will have to climb trees and hide in the grass to kill the next deer, but a full-fledged world with smells, changing wind and weather; with the individual behavior of each animal that must be killed to complete the task. This is not a simple hunt, but a real one!</description></item><item><title>Resident Evil 7: Biohazard</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/resident-evil-7-biohazard/</guid><description>Game Description Resident Evil 7: Biohazard is a survival horror game that continues the famous series of games, one of the founders of the genre. The release is timed to coincide with the twentieth anniversary of the universe. An option is available to play using a virtual reality helmet and control of special complete controllers from VR glasses.
The seventh part was a return to the roots of the first games in the series, because, unlike parts 5 and 6, which were focused on action, shooting and the plot taking place in different parts of the world, this project has the main location in the form of a small estate of the Baker family, which gives the atmosphere is claustrophobic and increases the degree of fear.</description></item><item><title>Killing Floor 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/killing-floor-2/</guid><description>Game Description A cooperative first-person shooter in which there are only two modes - survival and battle in the territory. Killing Floor 2 does not have a plot, but there is sharp FPS on several maps, where each player chooses the desired role for himself - a zombie or a department fighting an epidemic. In addition to the fact that the gameplay differs on both sides of the barricades, players can buy additional weapons, make skins and show who can stand up best on the map.</description></item><item><title>Titanfall 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/titanfall-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/titanfall-2/</guid><description>Game Description Titanfall 2 is a first-person shooter in a fantasy future setting. Continuation of the first game, released in 2014. In this part, in addition to online battles, there is a single-player campaign about Jack Cooper, a soldier who does not have his own titanium, but wants to get it. At the center of the story is the conflict between the militia, assembled from the common people, and the giant corporation IMC.</description></item><item><title>Battlefield 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/battlefield-1/</guid><description>Game Description Battlefield 1 is a first-person shooter in the setting of the First World War. The game is the 15th in the series of the same name. The plot is divided into five chapters and begins with a prologue. The story takes place in 1918 and is told from the perspective of tankman Daniel Edwards, who controls the Black Bass tank. Before the war, he was an ordinary driver, but now he has to break through the German line.</description></item><item><title>DOOM (2016)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/doom-2016/</guid><description>Game Description DOOM 2016, unlike DOOM Ethernal, has less dynamics, but is more related to the horror genre. We can say that it began the evolution of the series towards speed and platforming, and it is considered closer in spirit to the series than its brother released in 2020. It was the first step towards a global rethinking of the franchise.
The game takes place inside the corridors of a giant research complex.</description></item><item><title>Enter the Gungeon</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enter-the-gungeon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/enter-the-gungeon/</guid><description>Game Description In Enter the Gungeon you will remember such a genre as bullet hell or “hell of bullets”. The main characters explore the Gungeon and try to find a legendary artifact - a weapon that can kill the past. To do this, you need to fight your way through hordes of monsters and defeat formidable bosses. Loot, secrets, penny-pinching merchants and shopkeepers, new equipment and more loot - the recipe for a good game.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hot-dogs-horseshoes-and-hand-grenades/</guid><description>Game Description The game Hot Dogs, Horseshoes and Hand Grenades can be called a full-fledged weapons simulator. You need to go to the training ground, which contains a huge selection of different firearms: pistols, machine guns, shotguns, rocket launchers, grenades, etc. You can use any available ammunition, training on targets and taking the highest positions on the leaderboard. Afterwards you can go and set off fireworks.
Targets can be not only static within the walls of a gray pavilion, but also moving in open space.</description></item><item><title>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-siege/</guid><description>Game Description A new installment in the first-person shooter, Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s Rainbow Six Siege is a game of multiplayer destruction. We will not just destroy the map to which we and our friends were sent, but we will build traps, plant a bomb, and all this at a distance of a bow shot. The technical equipment of the new part is made specifically so that you can blow up everything in the open location of each level.</description></item><item><title>Just Cause 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/just-cause-3/</guid><description>Game Description Just Cause 3 is a continuation of the famous franchise about the adventures of a specially trained agent named Rico Rodriguez. This part of the series did not deviate from the style and genre of previous games in the universe where the mercenary nicknamed “Scorpio” lives. The end of the trilogy is made with the same driving action, open world, a large number of tricks and devices available in the protagonist’s arsenal, and an adventure plot in which the fate of an entire state will be at stake.</description></item><item><title>Metal Gear Solid 5: The Phantom Pain</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-5-the-phantom-pain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metal-gear-solid-5-the-phantom-pain/</guid><description>Game Description Metal Gear Solid 5: The Phantom Pain is a continuation of the famous series of stealth shooters from the recognized master of game design and production Hideo Kojima. The plot taking place in this game becomes a prequel to the very first game in the universe - Metal Gear. It forms a complete picture with the prologue released a little earlier - Metal Gear Solid V: Ground Zeroes.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 5 has received dozens of awards for its open world, and almost the most expensive multi-platform project in history is Grand Theft Auto V. The story opens before us in the same fictional state - San Andreas, made 1 to 1 as Southern California. We play as three robber friends who have spent their entire adult lives stealing cars, robbing small shops and people on the street. One day someone decides to get involved in organized crime, which they have been fighting for the last 5 years.</description></item><item><title>Metro 2033 Redux</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/metro-2033-redux/</guid><description>Game Description Metro 2033 Redux is a first-person shooter with a deep story and horror elements. The developers questioned not the simple existence of people underground, but the relationships between them. Has the main threat always been with us, in people? In the world of the post-apocalypse, we play as a character named Artem. He grew up underground, in the Moscow metro. In 2013, the world was hit by the terrible consequences of the latest epidemic.</description></item><item><title>Arma 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/arma-3/</guid><description>Game Description In Arma 3 we regain our independence by playing as a neutral side of this war. Inside the universe of the third Arma - 2030. Key opponents are still fighting for independence in economic and commodity terms. Among the enemies, a new structural organization CSAT appears, acting as a military-political alliance. While the crisis rages in Europe, the United States is at odds with China in the Pacific.</description></item><item><title>Tomb Raider</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/tomb-raider/</guid><description>Game Description Tomb Raider is a restart of the series telling about the adventures of Lara Croft. The ship on which the girl&amp;rsquo;s crew was sailing was wrecked. On the island she is captured and left tied in a cave. The adventurer frees herself from her bonds and goes to look for the crew members.
The player can choose the difficulty, which affects the course of battles. A vast world opens up before the gamer, divided into several locations.</description></item><item><title>Far Cry 3</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/far-cry-3/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter - Far Cry 3 - will teach you how to survive in the wild conditions of the open world, more or less value relationships with good people, and show you what real madness is. The series rewarded us with enough action, showing that a huge arsenal of weapons is just part of what can be given to players in return for their desire to enjoy a completely open world and a good story.</description></item><item><title>Hotline Miami</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotline-miami/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/hotline-miami/</guid><description>Game Description Hotline Miami is a 2D top-down action game created by two incredibly hardworking and talented young people under the auspices of the same computer game development studio - Dennaton Games. The international release of this project took place in October 2012. The developers admitted that they took their inspiration from the Hollywood crime action films of the 80s.
The game, as the name implies, takes place in the city of Miami, in the first half of the 80s.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-2/</guid><description>Game Description In Left 4 Dead 2 we have a choice between 4 characters. The coach is a massive African American; Nick is an avid gambler, a trickster and a master of theft; Rochelle is a black 29-year-old Depeche Mode fan and journalist; Ellis is a racing fan and car enthusiast. The cooperative first-person shooter captivated many players for several years, providing ample ground for exterminating zombies in 5 game campaigns, which take place in swamps, cities, caves and closed locations.</description></item><item><title>Left 4 Dead 1</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/left-4-dead-1/</guid><description>Game Description The first part of Left 4 Dead has 6 campaigns, several levels in each. The history and chronology of the chapters are interconnected, which will prevent the gamer from getting confused in the plot. At the beginning of each area, characters will appear at a checkpoint, where they can pick up weapons and ammunition and set off on their further journey.
The United States of America has been gripped by an unknown virus that turns people into terrible monsters with bouts of aggression and rage.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life 2: Episode Two</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2-episode-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2-episode-two/</guid><description>Game Description The open world of the newly released Half-Life 2: Episode Two at one time created a stir all over the world. Openly moving with one goal - to deliver information about the Alliance to the Resistance base - was a shocking task that players rushed into one after another. In the first-person shooter, we will continue to play as Gordon Freeman with Alixa Vance. Long journeys in the game are accompanied by frequent changes of scenes: now we are fighting against mutants, now we are solving puzzles, now we are watching an interactive film about the characters’ journey and their conversations.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-2/</guid><description>Game Description The first-person shooter, which instantly became the voice of the generation - Half-Life 2 - gave players hope for the third part. The game has received so many awards that there is no point in describing them in the context of the description. The plot reveals to us the continuation of the first part. Gordon Freeman takes up his mount again, but now the graphics have become more realistic, there are more locations, and the plot is even deeper.</description></item><item><title>POSTAL 2</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/postal-2/</guid><description>Game Description POSTAL 2 is a first-person shooter full of dark humor, references, blood and other hardcore stuff like desecrating graves or putting cats on a machine gun as a silencer. The plot develops in a strange town - Paradise. The main character of Postal 2 will be a character named Dude. He tries to live an ordinary life without doing anything illegal.
At the beginning of the story, he gets a job at the computer game development office Running with Scissors.</description></item><item><title>Counter-Strike</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/counter-strike/</guid><description>Game Description Counter-strike is a legendary multiplayer shooter, the founder of one of the most popular series in the history of the gaming industry.
The concept is simple but ingenious. Two teams - terrorists and special forces - are trying to destroy each other on the map. Terrorists have the ability to plant a bomb at one of the key points. and the counterterrorism department tries to predict which point the opponents will attack.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life (1998)</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-1998/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/half-life-1998/</guid><description>Game Description Half-Life (1998) - sci-fi shooter. One of the first games where the plot was completely presented using cutscenes in the engine. One of the main features of Half-Life was the artificial intelligence of enemies, which was striking in its elaboration. The story of Half-Life begins at the Black Mesa research facility in the mountains of New Mexico.
Control takes place for the young physicist Gordon Freeman, who is researching anomalous materials.</description></item><item><title>Neuro</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neuro/</guid><description>Game Description Neuro is a three-dimensional action game that gives the player the feeling of being inside a fictional world in the role of a psionicist who can use his abilities for combat purposes. The story told in this brainchild of the developers &amp;ldquo;Revolt Games&amp;rdquo; is a prequel to their other project called &amp;ldquo;Homeplanet&amp;rdquo;. The last missions of the single-player campaign develop in parallel with the start of their last game.</description></item><item><title>Bodycam</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/bodycam/</guid><description>Game Description Bodycam throws you headlong into a hyper-realistic multiplayer battlefield. Powered by Unreal Engine 5, this all-new shooter promises a next-gen experience that will redefine your expectations. Teamwork is key here. Every bullet counts, and the victory or defeat of your squad depends on your every decision.
Forget playing Rambo. Bodycam requires strategic thinking and coordinated attacks. Team up with your teammates, map out a plan of action, and use your arsenal to outmaneuver your opponents.</description></item><item><title>Cruelty Squad</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/cruelty-squad/</guid><description>Game Description Cruelty Squad is an immersive simulator that includes elements of stealth and first-person shooter. You will need to penetrate the depths of a high-tech corporation to stop its atrocities. A huge arsenal of weapons is available, including shotguns, darts, pistols, launchers and much more. The difficulty increases with each new stage. It is necessary to take part in intense firefights with a huge number of different enemies.
It is possible to emerge victorious from a fight without death.</description></item><item><title>Duck Game</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/duck-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/duck-game/</guid><description>Game Description Duck Game is an action game developed by Landon Podbielski and published by Adult Swim Games. You can play alone or with friends online. Duck Game gives us both options.
The game received extremely positive reviews from both professional critics and gamers, as well as from ordinary people. A simple 2D fighting game with multiplayer simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t get bad reviews. True, some are indignant about the name of the game because the name, according to some players, does not reflect anything.</description></item><item><title>Neon White</title><link>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamerift.github.io/posts/neon-white/</guid><description>Game Description Neon White is a first-person adventure platformer with card game elements. The gameplay stands out for its incredible dynamics and speed. It is necessary to quickly react to situations and the environment, because enemies, traps, obstacles and other dangers await you at every turn. Events develop behind the pearly gates of Paradise.
The task in the game is simple and trivial - you need to destroy all the demons in Heaven.</description></item></channel></rss>